<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/css" href="../../resources/stylesheets/wasmsgxml.css"?>
<TMSSource name="TivoliMessages" tmsVersion="1.0" xml:lang="en">
<!-- CMVC MSG File Name = UDDI/ws/code/uddi.jaxr/src/com/ibm/xml/registry/JAXRMessages.nlsprops, -->
<!-- DO NOT EDIT THIS FILE - This file was generated by the XML/Html & Property emitter -->
<!-- BEGIN MESSAGES -->
<Message ID="CWUDX0060W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="taxonomyConfig_file_invalid_property_value" varFormat="Java">
    taxonomyConfig_file_invalid_property_value=CWUDX0060W: taxonomyConfig.properties file contains an invalid property value: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A property value that was not valid was found in the taxonomyConfig.properties file while the connection is being initialized. The JAXR provider will ignore the property that is not valid, and therefore ignore the corresponding taxonomy.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that the taxonomyConfig.properties file is valid so that all taxonomies can be used. The correct format of each line is &lt;taxonomy ID&gt;=&lt;tModelKey&gt;,&lt;data filename&gt;,&lt;separator char&gt;.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWUDX0035E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="invalid_UDDI_XML_String" varFormat="Java">
    invalid_UDDI_XML_String=CWUDX0035E: Invalid UDDI XML String.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The String passed to the makeRegistrySpecificRequest method was not valid XML.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that the String passed to the makeRegistrySpecificRequest method is valid XML.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWUDX0039E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="object_type_invalid" varFormat="Java">
    object_type_invalid=CWUDX0039E: Invalid objectType: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The objectType that was passed is not valid.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Use a valid objectType.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWUDX0027E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="internal_Classification_change_value" varFormat="Java">
    internal_Classification_change_value=CWUDX0027E: Cannot change the value of an internal Classification.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The setValue method of an internal Classification interface was called.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Do not attempt to modify the value of an internal Classification interface directly. The value of an internal Classification interface is determined by the Classification&apos;s Concept interface and cannot be modified independently.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWUDX0011E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="Connection_is_closed" varFormat="Java">
    Connection_is_closed=CWUDX0011E: Connection is closed.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A method that required a connection to the registry was called after the connection was closed by a call to the Connection.close() method.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Do not call methods that require a connection to the registry after the connection has been closed.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWUDX0041E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="registryobject_classificationscheme_not_concept" varFormat="Java">
    registryobject_classificationscheme_not_concept=CWUDX0041E: RegistryObject is a ClassificationScheme not a Concept: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An objectType of LifeCycleManager.CONCEPT was passed, but the id or one of the objectKeys was that of a ClassificationScheme.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify the correct objectType that corresponds to the object keys.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWUDX0034E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="Invalid_maxrows" varFormat="Java">
    Invalid_maxrows=CWUDX0034E: The ConnectionFactory property javax.xml.registry.uddi.maxRows does not contain a parsable integer: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The createConnection method was called when the ConnectionFactory property javax.xml.registry.uddi.maxRows did not contain a valid integer.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that if the javax.xml.registry.uddi.maxRows ConnectionFactory property is set, it contains a valid integer.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWUDX0021E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="Exception_reading_taxonomyConfig_file" varFormat="Java">
    Exception_reading_taxonomyConfig_file=CWUDX0021E: An IOException occurred while attempting to read the taxonomyConfig.properties file.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The JAXR provider detected a java.io.IOException while attempting to read the taxonomyConfig.properties file.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the exception information to determine its cause.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWUDX0015E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="Could_not_serialize_XML_response" varFormat="Java">
    Could_not_serialize_XML_response=CWUDX0015E: Could not serialize XML response.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The JAXR provider caught a java.io.IOException while attempting to serialize the XML response.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the exception information to determine its cause.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWUDX0062E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="unexpected_object_exception_namePattern" varFormat="Java">
    unexpected_object_exception_namePattern=CWUDX0062E: Expecting object of type String or LocalizedString.  Got object of type: {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An object that was not a String or a LocalizedString was passed as a namePattern to a query method.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Use Strings or LocalizedStrings as namePattern objects.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWUDX0006E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="association_target_not_organization" varFormat="Java">
    association_target_not_organization=CWUDX0006E: Target object of an Association must be an Organization.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The object that was passed to the setTargetObject method was not an Organization.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Pass only Organization objects to the setTargetObject method.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWUDX0014E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="Could_not_parse_XML_input_stream" varFormat="Java">
    Could_not_parse_XML_input_stream=CWUDX0014E: Could not parse XML input stream.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The JAXR provider caught a java.io.IOException while attempting to parse the XML request.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the exception information to determine its cause.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWUDX0061E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="unexpected_object_exception" varFormat="Java">
    unexpected_object_exception=CWUDX0061E: Expecting object of type: {0}.  Got object of type: {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An object was passed to a method, where that method was not expecting an object of that type.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Pass objects of the appropriate type to JAXR methods.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWUDX0007E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="associationkey_format_incorrect" varFormat="Java">
    associationkey_format_incorrect=CWUDX0007E: Format of associationKey is incorrect. Correct format is &lt;sourceObjectKey&gt;:&lt;targetObjectKey&gt;:&lt;associationType&gt; : {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An associationKey object did not have the correct format.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that associationKey objects that are passed to the deleteAssociations method have the correct format.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWUDX0049E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="sortCode_Slot_must_have_only_1_value" varFormat="Java">
    sortCode_Slot_must_have_only_1_value=CWUDX0049E: A sortCode Slot must have only 1 value.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A Slot with name Slot.SORT_CODE_SLOT and multiple values was passed to the addSlot method.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    When adding a Slot with the name Slot.SORT_CODE_SLOT to a PostalAddress, ensure that it has only one value.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWUDX0036E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="Malformed_LifeCycleManagerURL" varFormat="Java">
    Malformed_LifeCycleManagerURL=CWUDX0036E: The ConnectionFactory property javax.xml.registry.lifeCycleManagerURL specifies a malformed URL.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The createConnection method was called when the ConnectionFactory property javax.xml.registry.lifeCycleManagerURL contained a Uniform Resource Identifier (URI) that does not use the correct URI syntax.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that the javax.xml.registry.lifeCycleManagerURL ConnectionFactory property contains a URL that uses the correct syntax.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWUDX0054E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SQL-92_LIKE_invalid_escape_sequence" varFormat="Java">
    SQL-92_LIKE_invalid_escape_sequence=CWUDX0054E: Invalid escape sequence found during SQL-92 LIKE processing: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A namePattern that contained an escape sequence that was not valid was passed to one of the indicated methods.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that the escape sequences in namePatterns are valid.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWUDX0064E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="Unsupported_auth_hint" varFormat="Java">
    Unsupported_auth_hint=CWUDX0064E: Unsupported value for the ConnectionFactory property javax.xml.registry.security.authenticationMethod: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    There was an attempt to create a connection with a value of the javax.xml.registry.security.authenticationMethod ConnectionFactory property that was not valid.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Use a valid value for this property.  Valid values are UDDI_GET_AUTHTOKEN and HTTP_BASIC.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWUDX0028E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="internal_Classification_missing_ClassificationScheme" varFormat="Java">
    internal_Classification_missing_ClassificationScheme=CWUDX0028E: The Concept of an internal Classification must have a parent ClassificationScheme.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A Concept without a parent ClassificationScheme (that is, it is not a taxonomy Concept) was passed to the setConcept method. When you set the Concept of a Classification interface, the Classification interface becomes internal, and must have a parent ClassificationScheme to be valid.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Pass only Concepts that represent taxonomy elements to the setConcept method.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWUDX0046E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="semantic_equivalence_pair_no_postal_key" varFormat="Java">
    semantic_equivalence_pair_no_postal_key=CWUDX0046E: Semantic equivalence pair does not contain a key in the postalAddressAttributes enumeration: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The javax.xml.registry.semanticEquivalences ConnectionFactory contains a keyPair that does not contain the path of a Concept in the PostalAddressAttributes enumeration. Semantic equivalences for UDDI JAXR providers are allowed only for Concepts in the PostalAddressAttributes enumeration.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Define semantic equivalences only for Concepts in the PostalAddressAttributes enumeration.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWUDX0025E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="internal_Classification_change_ClassificationScheme" varFormat="Java">
    internal_Classification_change_ClassificationScheme=CWUDX0025E: Cannot change the ClassificationScheme of an internal Classification.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The setClassificationScheme method of an internal Classification interface was called.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Do not attempt to modify the ClassificationScheme of an internal Classification interface directly. The ClassificationScheme of an internal Classification interface is determined by the Classification&apos;s Concept and cannot be modified independently.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWUDX0051E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SpecificationLink_has_only_1_UsageParameter" varFormat="Java">
    SpecificationLink_has_only_1_UsageParameter=CWUDX0051E: A SpecificationLink can have only one UsageParameter.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    There was an attempt to give the SpecificationLink more than one usage parameter.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Give a SpecificationLink a maximum of one usage parameter.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWUDX0005E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="association_source_or_target_not_set" varFormat="Java">
    association_source_or_target_not_set=CWUDX0005E: Source and target objects of an Association must be set in order to save.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    There was an attempt to save an Association that did not have both source and target objects set.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that  both source and target objects are set before you save Associations.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWUDX0020E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="Exception_reading_enumerationConfig_file" varFormat="Java">
    Exception_reading_enumerationConfig_file=CWUDX0020E: An IOException occurred while attempting to read the enumerationConfig.properties file.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The JAXR provider detected a java.io.IOException while attempting to read the enumerationConfig.properties file.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the exception information to determine its cause.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWUDX0013E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="Could_not_create_DocumentBuilder" varFormat="Java">
    Could_not_create_DocumentBuilder=CWUDX0013E: Could not create DocumentBuilder.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The JAXR provider caught a javax.xml.parsers.ParserConfigurationException while attempting to initialize the XML parser.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the exception information to determine its cause.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWUDX0024E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="interface_name_invalid" varFormat="Java">
    interface_name_invalid=CWUDX0024E: Invalid interface name: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An interface name that was passed to the createObject method is not valid.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Pass only valid interface names to the createObject method.  Valid interface names are public final static String fields of the LifeCycleManager class.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWUDX0038E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="Multiple_matches" varFormat="Java">
    Multiple_matches=CWUDX0038E: Multiple matches on find ClassificationScheme by name.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    More than one ClassificationScheme was found that matched the search criteria.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Narrow the search criteria to find only one ClassificationScheme.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWUDX0050E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SpecificationLink_has_only_1_ExternalLink" varFormat="Java">
    SpecificationLink_has_only_1_ExternalLink=CWUDX0050E: A SpecificationLink can have only one ExternalLink.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    There was an attempt to give a SpecificationLink more than one ExternalLink.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Give a SpecificationLink a maximum of one ExternalLink.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWUDX0030E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="internal_taxonomy_concept_invalid_parent" varFormat="Java">
    internal_taxonomy_concept_invalid_parent=CWUDX0030E: The parent RegistryObject of a taxonomy Concept must be either a Concept or a ClassificationScheme.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    There was an attempt to create a taxonomy Concept whose parent was not a Concept or a ClassificationScheme.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that the parent of a taxonomy Concept is another Concept or a ClassificationScheme.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWUDX0055E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SQL-92_LIKE_invalid_escape_sequence_terminating_pattern" varFormat="Java">
    SQL-92_LIKE_invalid_escape_sequence_terminating_pattern=CWUDX0055E: Invalid escape sequence found terminating pattern during SQL-92 LIKE processing: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A namePattern that ended with an escape sequence that was not valid was passed to one of the indicated methods.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that the escape sequences in namePatterns are valid.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWUDX0016E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="create_object_interface_name_unspecified" varFormat="Java">
    create_object_interface_name_unspecified=CWUDX0016E: Interface name of object to create not specifed.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A null interfaceName was passed to the createObject method.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that a valid interfaceName is passed to the createObject method.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWUDX0001E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="UDDIException" varFormat="Java">
    UDDIException=CWUDX0001E: Caught UDDIException on {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The JAXR provider caught a org.uddi4j.UDDIException while sending a request to the UDDI registry.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the exception information to determine its cause.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWUDX0026E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="internal_Classification_change_name" varFormat="Java">
    internal_Classification_change_name=CWUDX0026E: Cannot change the name of an internal Classification.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The setName method of an internal Classification interface was called.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Do not attempt to modify the name of an internal Classification interface directly. The name of an internal Classification interface is determined by the Classification&apos;s Concept interface and cannot be modified independently.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWUDX0048E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="Slot_values_not_unique" varFormat="Java">
    Slot_values_not_unique=CWUDX0048E: A Slot instance cannot have duplicate values.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A collection of values was passed to the setValues method that contained duplicate values.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Pass only a collection of unique values to setValues method.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWUDX0058W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="taxonomy_data_file_missing_parent_concept" varFormat="Java">
    taxonomy_data_file_missing_parent_concept=CWUDX0058W: Warning: Unable to locate parentConcept named {0} for concept named {1} in taxonomy datafile {2}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A taxonomy data file contains a line for a Concept whose parent cannot be located in that file.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that a parent exists for each Concept in the taxonomy data file.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWUDX0023E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="external_uri_not_accessible" varFormat="Java">
    external_uri_not_accessible=CWUDX0023E: External URI is not accessible: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An inaccessible Uniform Resource Identifier (URI) was passed to the setExternalURI method when URI validation was set to true by passing true to the ExternalLink.setValidateURI(boolean validate) method.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Either ensure that the URI is accessible, or set URI validation to false.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWUDX0010E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ClassificationScheme_from_taxonomy_Concept" varFormat="Java">
    ClassificationScheme_from_taxonomy_Concept=CWUDX0010E: Cannot create a ClassificationScheme from a taxonomy Concept.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A taxonomy Concept was passed to the createClassificationScheme method. This method allows Concepts that are returned by the BusinessQueryManager.findConcepts call to be converted to a ClassificationScheme.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that the Concept that is passed is semantically a ClassificationScheme.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWUDX0040E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="object_type_invalid_for_save" varFormat="Java">
    object_type_invalid_for_save=CWUDX0040E: Cannot save objects of type: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The type of object that was passed to the saveObjects method cannot be saved directly in the registry.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that objects passed to the saveObjects method are of a valid type. Valid types are Association, ClassificationScheme, Concept, Organization, Service, and ServiceBinding.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWUDX0012E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ConnectionFactory_properties_not_set" varFormat="Java">
    ConnectionFactory_properties_not_set=CWUDX0012E: ConnectionFactory properties are not set.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The createConnection() method was called before the properties had been set on the ConnectionFactory.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that the ConnectionFactory properties have been set before attempting to create a connection.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWUDX0052E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SpecificationObject_Concept_cannot_have_parent" varFormat="Java">
    SpecificationObject_Concept_cannot_have_parent=CWUDX0052E: SpecificationObject must be a Concept with no parent.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    There was an attempt to set a Concept with a parent (that is, a taxonomy Concept) as the specification object of the SpecificationLink.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Set a specification Concept as the specification object of a SpecificationLink.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWUDX0019W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="enumerationConfig_file_invalid_property_value" varFormat="Java">
    enumerationConfig_file_invalid_property_value=CWUDX0019W: enumerationConfig.properties file contains an invalid property value: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The JAXR provider has encountered a property value that is not valid in the enumerationConfig.properties file while the connection is being initialized. The JAXR provider will ignore the property that is not valid, and therefore ignore the corresponding enumeration.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that the enumerationConfig.properties file is valid so that all enumerations can be used. The correct format of each line is &lt;enumeration ID&gt;=&lt;enumeration name&gt;,&lt;data filename&gt;,&lt;separator char&gt;.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWUDX0003E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="AccessURI_and_TargetBinding_mutually_exclusive" varFormat="Java">
    AccessURI_and_TargetBinding_mutually_exclusive=CWUDX0003E: AccessURI and TargetBinding are mutually exclusive.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    There was an attempt to set both the AccessURI and the TargetBinding of a ServiceBinding interface.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Set either an AccessURI object or a TargetBinding object.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWUDX0066E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ServiceBinding_Classification_not_from_URLType_enumeration" varFormat="Java">
    ServiceBinding_Classification_not_from_URLType_enumeration=CWUDX0066E: Classification&apos;s Concept is not from the URLType enumeration. When using a JAXR Provider for UDDI, ServiceBinding can only be classified with a sub-concept of the URLType enumeration.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    There was an attempt to classify a ServiceBinding interface using an internal Classification interface that has a Concept that is not a sub-Concept of the internal URLType enumeration.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Classify a ServiceBinding interface using a sub-Concept of the URLType enumeration.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWUDX0042E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="registryobject_concept_not_classificationscheme" varFormat="Java">
    registryobject_concept_not_classificationscheme=CWUDX0042E: RegistryObject is a Concept not a ClassificationScheme: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An objectType of LifeCycleManager.CLASSIFICATIONSCHEME was passed, but the id or one of the objectKeys was that of a Concept.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify the correct objectType that corresponds to the object keys.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWUDX0017W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="enumeration_data_file_invalid_line" varFormat="Java">
    enumeration_data_file_invalid_line=CWUDX0017W: Enumeration data file {0} contains an invalid line: {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The JAXR provider has encountered a line in an enumeration data file that is not valid while the connection is being initialized. The JAXR provider will ignore the line that is not valid and will be unaffected.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that the enumeration data file is valid so that all members of the enumeration can be used. The correct format of each line is &lt;enumeration name&gt;&lt;separator char&gt;&lt;concept value&gt;.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWUDX0031E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="internal_taxonomy_concept_no_parent_no_path" varFormat="Java">
    internal_taxonomy_concept_no_parent_no_path=CWUDX0031E: Concept does not have a parent, therefore does not have a path.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The getPath() method was called on a Concept that was not a taxonomy Concept, but only taxonomy Concepts have parents and therefore paths.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Do not call the getPath() method on a Concept that is not a taxonomy Concept.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWUDX0004E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="association_source_not_organization" varFormat="Java">
    association_source_not_organization=CWUDX0004E: Source object of an Association must be an Organization.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The object passed to the setSourceObject method was not an Organization.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Pass only Organization objects to the setSourceObject method.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWUDX0059E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="taxonomy_data_file_read_exception" varFormat="Java">
    taxonomy_data_file_read_exception=CWUDX0059E: Could not read taxonomy data file: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The JAXR provider detected a java.io.IOException while attempting to read the taxonomy data file.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the exception information to determine its cause.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWUDX0029E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="internal_taxonomy_concept_cannot_save_as_tModel" varFormat="Java">
    internal_taxonomy_concept_cannot_save_as_tModel=CWUDX0029E: Taxonomy Concepts cannot be saved as UDDI tModels.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    There was an attempt to save a taxonomy Concept as a UDDI tModel in the registry. Taxonomy Concepts are used to classify objects saved in the registry, but they cannot be saved independently.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Do not  save taxonomy Concepts in the registry.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWUDX0008E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="AssociationType_concept_invalid_value" varFormat="Java">
    AssociationType_concept_invalid_value=CWUDX0008E: AssociationType Concept must come from the AssociationType enumeration, and have value either HasChild, HasParent, RelatedTo or EquivalentTo.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    When finding Associations, a Concept was passed in the associationTypes Collection that was from the AssociationType enumeration, but did not have a value that is valid for UDDI. When saving Associations, an Association was passed whose associationType Concept was from the AssociationType enumeration, but did not have a value that is valid for UDDI.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Use only Concepts for associationType objects that are from the AssociationType enumeration and have the value HasChild, HasParent, RelatedTo or EquivalentTo.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWUDX0043E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="RequestID_not_found" varFormat="Java">
    RequestID_not_found=CWUDX0043E: RequestID not found: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The requestId specified was not found.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Pass only valid requestIds to the getBulkResponse method. After the getBulkResponse method is called once for a particular requestId, that requestId is removed from the cache, and any subsequent calls to the getBulkResponse method for that requestId will result in an InvalidRequestException.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWUDX0002E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="TransportException" varFormat="Java">
    TransportException=CWUDX0002E: Caught TransportException sending request to registry.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The JAXR provider caught a TransportException while sending a request to the UDDI registry.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the exception information to determine its cause.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWUDX0053E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SpecificationObject_must_be_Concept" varFormat="Java">
    SpecificationObject_must_be_Concept=CWUDX0053E: SpecificationObject must be a Concept.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    There was an attempt to set a RegistryObject that was not a Concept as the specification object of a SpecificationLink.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Set a specification Concept as the specification object of a SpecificationLink.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWUDX0044E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="semantic_equivalence_invalid_concept_path" varFormat="Java">
    semantic_equivalence_invalid_concept_path=CWUDX0044E: {0} is not a valid path of a concept in a defined internal taxonomy.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A semantic equivalence is defined, in the  javax.xml.registry.semanticEquivalences property of a ConnectionFactory object, for a Concept in the PostalAddressAttributes enumeration, when there is no equivalent Concept defined in an internal taxonomy.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that the Concept paths used in the javax.xml.registry.semanticEquivalences ConnectionFactory property are defined in a internal taxonomy.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWUDX0022E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="external_uri_malformed" varFormat="Java">
    external_uri_malformed=CWUDX0022E: External URI is malformed: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A Uniform Resource Identifier (URI) that does not use the correct URI syntax was passed to the setExternalURI method when URI validation was set to true by passing true to the ExternalLink.setValidateURI(boolean validate) method.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Either ensure that the URI uses the correct syntax, or set URI validation to false.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWUDX0009E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="AssociationType_concept_not_from_enumeration" varFormat="Java">
    AssociationType_concept_not_from_enumeration=CWUDX0009E: AssociationType Concept must come from the AssociationType enumeration.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    When finding Associations, a Concept was passed that was not from the AssociationType enumeration in the associationTypes Collection. When saving Associations, an Association was passed whose associationType Concept was not from the AssociationType enumeration.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Use only Concepts from the AssociationType enumeration for associationType objects.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWUDX0045W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="semantic_equivalence_not_2_elements" varFormat="Java">
    semantic_equivalence_not_2_elements=CWUDX0045W: Semantic equivalence pair does not have exactly 2 elements: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The javax.xml.registry.semanticEquivalences ConnectionFactory contains a keyPair that contains more than two elements.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that the javax.xml.registry.semanticEquivalences ConnectionFactory property has the correct format, as defined in the JAXR specification.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWUDX0018E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="enumeration_data_file_read_exception" varFormat="Java">
    enumeration_data_file_read_exception=CWUDX0018E: Could not read enumeration data file: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The JAXR provider caught a java.io.IOException while attempting to read an enumeration data file.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the exception information to determine its cause.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWUDX0063E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="Unspecified_QueryManagerURL" varFormat="Java">
    Unspecified_QueryManagerURL=CWUDX0063E: The ConnectionFactory property javax.xml.registry.queryManagerURL is not specified.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    There was an attempt to create a connection without specifying the javax.xml.registry.queryManagerURL ConnectionFactory property.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify the javax.xml.registry.queryManagerURL ConnectionFactory property before attempting to create a Connection.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWUDX0032E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="internal_taxonomy_concept_no_value_no_path" varFormat="Java">
    internal_taxonomy_concept_no_value_no_path=CWUDX0032E: Concept does not have a value, therefore does not have a path.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The getPath() method was called on a Concept that did not have a value.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    A Concept must have a value to have a path, so do not attempt to call the getPath() method on Concepts that do not have a value.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWUDX0047E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="slot_name_invalid" varFormat="Java">
    slot_name_invalid=CWUDX0047E: Invalid Slot name: {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An slot name that was not valid was passed to one of the methods of the ExtensibleObject interface.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that the slot name is valid for the particular instance of ExtensibleObject.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWUDX0037E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="Malformed_QueryManagerURL" varFormat="Java">
    Malformed_QueryManagerURL=CWUDX0037E: The ConnectionFactory property javax.xml.registry.queryManagerURL specifies a malformed URL.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The createConnection method was called when the ConnectionFactory property javax.xml.registry.queryManagerURL contained a Uniform Resource Identifier (URI) that does not use the correct URI syntax.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that the javax.xml.registry.queryManagerURL ConnectionFactory property contains a URL that uses the correct syntax.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWUDX0033E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="internal_taxonomy_concept_parent_no_key_no_path" varFormat="Java">
    internal_taxonomy_concept_parent_no_key_no_path=CWUDX0033E: Concept&apos;s parent ClassificationScheme does not have an ID, therefore the Concept does not have a path.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The getPath() method was called on a Concept whose ClassificationScheme did not have an ID, therefore the Concept does not have a path.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Do not call the getPath() method on a Concept whose ClassificationScheme does not have an ID.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWUDX0056E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="System_property_http.proxyPort_not_parsable" varFormat="Java">
    System_property_http.proxyPort_not_parsable=CWUDX0056E: The System property http.proxyPort does not contain a parsable integer: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The createConnection() method was called when the System property http.proxyPort contained a String that was not a valid integer.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that if the System property http.proxyPort is set, it contains a valid integer.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWUDX0057W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="taxonomy_data_file_invalid_line" varFormat="Java">
    taxonomy_data_file_invalid_line=CWUDX0057W: Taxonomy data file {0} contains an invalid line: {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A taxonomy data file contains a line that is not valid.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that the line format is correct. The format of each line is &lt;taxonomy ID&gt;&lt;Concept name&gt;&lt;Concept value&gt;&lt;Concept parent&gt;.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWUDX0065E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ServiceBinding_Classification_has_no_Concept" varFormat="Java">
    ServiceBinding_Classification_has_no_Concept=CWUDX0065E: Classification does not have a Concept (Classification is external). When using a JAXR Provider for UDDI, ServiceBinding can only be classified with a sub-concept of the URLType enumeration.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    There was an attempt to classify a ServiceBinding interface using an external Classification, which therefore is not a Classification with a sub-Concept of the internal URLType enumeration.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Classify a ServiceBinding interface using a sub-Concept of the internal URLType enumeration.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<!-- END MESSAGES -->
</TMSSource>
