<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/css" href="../../resources/stylesheets/wasmsgxml.css"?>
<TMSSource name="TivoliMessages" tmsVersion="1.0" xml:lang="en">
<!-- CMVC MSG File Name = ws/code/runtime/src/com/ibm/ejs/resources/CONMMessages.nlsprops -->
<!-- DO NOT EDIT THIS FILE - This file was generated by the XML/Html & Property emitter -->
<!-- BEGIN MESSAGES -->
<Message ID="CONM6001W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MSG_CONM_6001W" varFormat="Java">
    MSG_CONM_6001W=CONM6001W: The system cannot expand the connection pool; waiting for a free connection instead.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A connection cannot be created.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the database can create as many connections as the connection pool.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CONM7013W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MSG_CONM_7013W" varFormat="Java">
    MSG_CONM_7013W=CONM7013W: Both the user ID and the password must be set for the test connection to work.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Either the user ID or password, but not both are set on a test connection request.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify both the user ID and password, or specify neither.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CONM1006E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MSG_CONM_1006E" varFormat="Java">
    MSG_CONM_1006E=CONM1006E: The DataSource class name &quot;{0}&quot; cannot be found for DataSource ({1}).
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The DataSource class name that is supplied cannot be found.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the Java archive (JAR) file with the specified class name is installed. If the DataSource is accessed by a direct Java Naming and Directory Interface (JNDI) lookup, rather than through a resource reference or a Container-Managed Persistent (CMP) enterprise bean, add the JAR file to the ws.ext.dirs Java virtual machine (JVM) system property on the Application Server.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CONM6017E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MSG_CONM_6017E" varFormat="Java">
    MSG_CONM_6017E=CONM6017E: In the enlist method, the connection is already associated with another transaction.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This connection cannot be enlisted in a transaction if it is already associated with a different transaction.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Avoid caching a connection for use by more than one thread in multiple concurrent transactions.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CONM6020W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MSG_CONM_6020W" varFormat="Java">
    MSG_CONM_6020W=CONM6020W: A connection is orphaned and returned to pool {0}.
{1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A connection that was in use by an application is held without being used or closed past the duration of the orphanTimeout value.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that all of the connections in the application are closed after each use.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CONM7009W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MSG_CONM_7009W" varFormat="Java">
    MSG_CONM_7009W=CONM7009W: A read only intent is used to update bean {0}.  An update intent is required to eliminate potential lost updates to bean {0} when used concurrently by multiple transactions.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A transaction is storing an update to a container-managed persistence (CMP) entity bean and the bean is deployed  using read only access intent.  If another transaction is storing the same CMP entity bean, the updates  of one transaction can overlay the updates of the other transaction.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    The application must ensure that concurrent transactions never update the same CMP entity bean.  If this action cannot be done, then the CMP entity bean must be redeployed using an update access intent  rather than a read-only access intent, to maintain data consistency.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CONM6000W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MSG_CONM_6000W" varFormat="Java">
    MSG_CONM_6000W=CONM6000W: A resource cannot process the two-phase commit &apos;prepare&apos; request because it supports the one-phase commit protocol only. The DataSource is: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The system is trying to call &apos;prepare&apos; on a one-phase resource.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CONM1005W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MSG_CONM_1005W" varFormat="Java">
    MSG_CONM_1005W=CONM1005W: The password for the supplied user ID &quot;{0}&quot;, is missing for DataSource ({1}).
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The DataSource user ID is supplied, but the password is not; the user ID is ignored.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Supply the password that corresponds to the user ID or remove the user ID.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CONM6016E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MSG_CONM_6016E" varFormat="Java">
    MSG_CONM_6016E=CONM6016E: The system is unable to enlist with the transaction.  Issuing new ({0}).
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The call to enlist with the transaction returned false or issued an exception.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the WebSphere Application Server logs and the database logs for messages that might indicate why the resource is unable to enlist.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CONM7008W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MSG_CONM_7008W" varFormat="Java">
    MSG_CONM_7008W=CONM7008W: A repeatable read isolation level or stronger is needed to eliminate potential lost updates to bean {0} if updated concurrently by multiple transactions.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A transaction is storing an update to a CMP entity bean. If another concurrently running  transaction is storing the same container-managed persistence (CMP) entity bean, the updates of one transaction might overlay  the updates of the other transaction.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify if the application can ensure that concurrent transactions never update the same container-managed persistence (CMP) entity bean.  If this action cannot be done, then the CMP entity bean must be redeployed using either the Java Database Connectivity (JDBC) repeatable read or  serializable isolation level.  Remember to redeploy all the other beans that are accessed by the transaction to use  the same isolation level.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CONM1004W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MSG_CONM_1004W" varFormat="Java">
    MSG_CONM_1004W=CONM1004W: The user ID for the supplied password is missing for DataSource ({0}).
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The DataSource password is supplied, but the user ID is not; the password is ignored.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Supply the user ID that corresponds to the password or remove the password.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CONM7012E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MSG_CONM_7012E" varFormat="Java">
    MSG_CONM_7012E=CONM7012E: The connection manager cannot find the Java archive (JAR) or the ZIP file for the DataSource class {0} in the provider library path for the DataSource {1} or in the class path.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The code needs to load the class for the Java Database Connectivity (JDBC) DataSource,  but the JAR or the ZIP file for the DataSource class is not found  on the provider library path for the DataSource or in the class path.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Either correct the installation of WebSphere Application Server so that the DataSource class can be found  on the provider library path or add the DataSource class JAR or ZIP file to the class path.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CONM7011W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MSG_CONM_7011W" varFormat="Java">
    MSG_CONM_7011W=CONM7011W: The connection manager cannot find the Java archive (JAR) file or the ZIP file for the DataSource class {0} in the provider library path for the DataSource {1}.  The code checks the class path for the JAR file.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The code needs to load the class for the JDBC DataSource,  but the JAR or ZIP file for the DataSource class is not found  on the provider library path for the DataSource.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Either correct the installation of WebSphere Application Server so that the DataSource class can be found  on the provider library path or add the DataSource class JAR or ZIP file to the class path.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CONM6015E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MSG_CONM_6015E" varFormat="Java">
    MSG_CONM_6015E=CONM6015E: The system cannot load XAResourceFactory in method ({0}) because the class ({1}) is not found. Issuing new ({2}).
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A required class is not found. The Java virtual machine (JVM) or the class loader cannot find the
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the class exists in the classpath and is accessible by the user.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CONM2000E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MSG_CONM_2000E" varFormat="Java">
    MSG_CONM_2000E=CONM2000E: The Connection Manager is unable to obtain a portability layer for DataSource ({0}).
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The system cannot map this driver to a portability layer, including the generic portability layer.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the cm.jar file is in the class path and is accessible.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CONM7007I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MSG_CONM_7007I" varFormat="Java">
    MSG_CONM_7007I=CONM7007I: Mapping the following SQLException, with ErrorCode {0} and SQLState {1}, to a StaleConnectionException: {2}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A mapping between the exceptions is occurring.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CONM6014I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MSG_CONM_6014I" varFormat="Java">
    MSG_CONM_6014I=CONM6014I: The system received exception ({0}) in method ({1}) and is issuing a new exception ({2}). The original exception stack trace is: {3}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This informational message indicates that one type of exception is received and another type is issued.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CONM7010W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MSG_CONM_7010W" varFormat="Java">
    MSG_CONM_7010W=CONM7010W: A deadlock can occur while storing container-managed persistence (CMP) entity bean {0} during multiclient same-key access processing.  A read-only method is followed by an update to the database.  You might need to change a read-only method from an access intent of read to an access intent of update, to avoid potential deadlock problems.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A transaction is storing an update to a CMP entity bean. The bean is deployed  using read-only access intent and either a Java Database Connectivity (JDBC) repeatable read or a JDBC serializable  isolation level. If another transaction is storing the same CMP entity bean, a database  deadlock can occur as a result of promotion of a read and share lock to a write exclusive lock.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    The application must ensure that concurrent transactions never update the same CMP entity bean.  If this action cannot be done, then the CMP entity bean must be redeployed using an update access intent  rather than a read-only access intent.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CONM1003E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MSG_CONM_1003E" varFormat="Java">
    MSG_CONM_1003E=CONM1003E: An error occurred when encrypting default password: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An exception occurred during the encryption of a password.  The password data is corrupt.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Replace the corrupted password with an uncorrupt password.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CONM7006E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MSG_CONM_7006E" varFormat="Java">
    MSG_CONM_7006E=CONM7006E: An exception occurred instantiating the class ({0}) for DataSource ({1}): {2}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An exception occurred instantiating the specified DataSource.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the underlying exception for more details.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CONM6013E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MSG_CONM_6013E" varFormat="Java">
    MSG_CONM_6013E=CONM6013E: The connection has outstanding work and cannot join a global transaction for DataSource ({0}).
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The connection has work that is either uncommitted or not rolled back.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Commit or roll back the work on the connection prior to using the connection in a global transaction.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CONM1002E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MSG_CONM_1002E" varFormat="Java">
    MSG_CONM_1002E=CONM1002E: An error occurred when decrypting default password: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An exception occurred during the decryption of a password.  Either the encrypted password data is corrupt or is encoded in an unsupported encryption.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Replace the encrypted password with uncorrupt data or make sure that it is encoded with a supported encryption algorithm.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CONM6009E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MSG_CONM_6009E" varFormat="Java">
    MSG_CONM_6009E=CONM6009E: The database is unable to get a connection to the database from DataSource ({0}).
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The database is unable to service a request for a new connection.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the SQL state code from the database to determine the exact cause of the problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CONM8002E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MSG_CONM_8002E" varFormat="Java">
    MSG_CONM_8002E=CONM8002E: The method that was invoked is not supported.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The method that was invoked is not supported on this JDBC 2.0 compliant connection manager.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Do not invoke this method.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CONM6008W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MSG_CONM_6008W" varFormat="Java">
    MSG_CONM_6008W=CONM6008W: The system timed out waiting for a connection from DataSsource ({2}). For information about the active connections, set the DataSource property &quot;{0}&quot; to {1} on DataSource &quot;{2}&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    All connections in the pool are in use for the duration of the connectionTimeout period.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    1) Increase the connectionTimeout Value. 2) Increase the maximum number of connections and verify that the database can handle the increased connection load.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CONM7005E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MSG_CONM_7005E" varFormat="Java">
    MSG_CONM_7005E=CONM7005E: The class ({0}) does not implement the javax.sql.ConnectionPoolDataSource or the javax.sql.XADataSource interface.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The DataSource class that is provided must implement the javax.sql.ConnectionPoolDataSource or the javax.sql.XADataSource interface.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Consult your database documentation and provide a class name that implements one of these interfaces.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CONM1001E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MSG_CONM_1001E" varFormat="Java">
    MSG_CONM_1001E=CONM1001E: The required property ({0}) is missing for DataSource ({1}).
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A required property is missing.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that all of the required properties are configured on the DataSource.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CONM6012E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MSG_CONM_6012E" varFormat="Java">
    MSG_CONM_6012E=CONM6012E: A database error occurred when setting the AutoCommit value for DataSource ({0}).
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The database is unable to service the request.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the SQL state code from the database to determine the exact cause of the problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CONM7004W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MSG_CONM_7004W" varFormat="Java">
    MSG_CONM_7004W=CONM7004W: An exception occurred setting the property {0} on class {1}: {2}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An exception occurred setting the specified property to the DataSource.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the underlying exception for more details
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CONM8001E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MSG_CONM_8001E" varFormat="Java">
    MSG_CONM_8001E=CONM8001E: Method {0} is not supported on a Java Database Connectivity (JDBC) V2.0 compliant DataSource.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The method that is invoked is a JDBC V4.0 compliant method, and is not supported on this JDBC 2.0 compliant connection manager.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Do not invoke this method, or use a JDBC 4.0 compliant connection pooling mechanism.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CONM6027W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MSG_CONM_6027W" varFormat="Java">
    MSG_CONM_6027W=CONM6027W: A connection is orphaned and returned to pool {2}.  For information about which code path is orphaning connections, set the DataSource property &quot;{0}&quot; to {1} on DataSource &quot;{2}&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This warning message describes how to turn on diagnostic information to detect orphaned connection code paths.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Set the diagnostic options to the value that is mentioned in the message.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CONM1000E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MSG_CONM_1000E" varFormat="Java">
    MSG_CONM_1000E=CONM1000E: Value &quot;{0}&quot; is not valid for property ({1}) for DataSource ({2}).
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    One of the DataSource properties is in an unexpected format.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that all of the properties for the DataSource are correct.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CONM6011E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MSG_CONM_6011E" varFormat="Java">
    MSG_CONM_6011E=CONM6011E: A connection pooling internal error occurred.  An illegal ConnectO state, &quot;{0}&quot;, on DataSource ({1}) is detected.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This exception is unexpected. The cause is not immediately known.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, see the problem determination on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page on http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CONM6007I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MSG_CONM_6007I" varFormat="Java">
    MSG_CONM_6007I=CONM6007I: The connection pool is destroyed for DataSource ({0}).
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is expected during the shut down of an Application Server.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CONM7003W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MSG_CONM_7003W" varFormat="Java">
    MSG_CONM_7003W=CONM7003W: The system cannot find the method to write property {0} on class {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A method to write the property to does not exist on the class.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    The property that is specified exists, but a write method does not; verify that the specified property can be written to the DataSource.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CONM8000E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MSG_CONM_8000E" varFormat="Java">
    MSG_CONM_8000E=CONM8000E: Method {0} is not supported on a Java Database Connectivity (JDBC) V2.0 compliant DataSource.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The method that is invoked is a JDBC V3.0 compliant method, and is not supported on this JDBC 2.0 compliant connection manager.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Do not invoke this method, or use a JDBC 3.0 compliant connection pooling mechanism.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CONM6010W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MSG_CONM_6010W" varFormat="Java">
    MSG_CONM_6010W=CONM6010W: A StaleConnectionException error occurred.  Purging the entire connection pool for DataSource ({0}).
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The system has issued a StaleConnectionException error.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the SQL state code from the database to determine the exact cause of the problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CONM6026W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MSG_CONM_6026W" varFormat="Java">
    MSG_CONM_6026W=CONM6026W: Timed out waiting for a connection from DataSource {0}.
{1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This warning message shows all the active connection tracers when a connection timeout occurs.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CONM7019E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MSG_CONM_7019E" varFormat="Java">
    MSG_CONM_7019E=CONM7019E: The Connection Manager attempted to use a V4.0 DataSource from a Version 2.3 or later servlet, which is not a valid configuration.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Only servlets with versions earlier than 2.3 can be used with a V4.0 DataSource.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Either reconfigure to use an earlier servlet version, or configure your servlet to use a V5.0 DataSource.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CONM7002W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MSG_CONM_7002W" varFormat="Java">
    MSG_CONM_7002W=CONM7002W: The system cannot find the property {0} on class {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The property to set does not exist on the class.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the specified property name is correct.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CONM6006E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MSG_CONM_6006E" varFormat="Java">
    MSG_CONM_6006E=CONM6006E: The required default password for the supplied default user ID, &quot;{0}&quot;, is missing for DataSource ({1}).
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The default password is missing.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Supply a valid password for the default user.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CONM7018E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MSG_CONM_7018E" varFormat="Java">
    MSG_CONM_7018E=CONM7018E: The Connection Manager attempted to use a V4.0 DataSource with an enterprise bean that is not valid. The current Enterprise JavaBeans (EJB) module is:  {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Only enterprise beans in V1.1 modules can be used with a V4.0 DataSource.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Either reconfigure the enterprise bean in a 1.1 module, or configure your enterprise bean to use a V5.0 DataSource.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CONM6025I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MSG_CONM_6025I" varFormat="Java">
    MSG_CONM_6025I=CONM6025I: The following connection manager diagnostic options are activated on DataSource {0}: {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This informational message indicates which connection manager diagnostic options are currently set.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CONM6024W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MSG_CONM_6024W" varFormat="Java">
    MSG_CONM_6024W=CONM6024W: An Exception, ({0}), was caught in createConnection method.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This warning message indicates that a non-SQL exception occurred while creating a connection.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CONM7001E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MSG_CONM_7001E" varFormat="Java">
    MSG_CONM_7001E=CONM7001E: The following exception occurred introspecting class {0}: {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An error occurred during introspection of the DataSource class.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the underlying exception for more details. If the problem persists, see the problem determination on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page on http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CONM7017E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MSG_CONM_7017E" varFormat="Java">
    MSG_CONM_7017E=CONM7017E: An exception occurred on the delistResource for local transaction: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The exception that is listed was received while delisting from the local transaction.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the exception to find the root cause of the problem. If the problem persists, see the problem determination on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page on http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CONM7020W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MSG_CONM_7020W" varFormat="Java">
    MSG_CONM_7020W=CONM7020W: The connection manager is unable to determine the backend database type.  DB2/390 semantics are not used.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The runtime is unable to determine if the DB2Connect backend is a DB2/390 database.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, see the problem determination on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page on http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CONM7000W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MSG_CONM_7000W" varFormat="Java">
    MSG_CONM_7000W=CONM7000W: An unrecognized database or driver {0} is found; using generic settings
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The database product ID or the driver class name is not found in the list of known databases.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the spelling is correct and that the database is supported.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CONM7016W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MSG_CONM_7016W" varFormat="Java">
    MSG_CONM_7016W=CONM7016W: The ConnectO.destroy method failed during the delist process from the local transaction : {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Delist is a Java Database Connectivity (JDBC) specified operation.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CONM6004E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MSG_CONM_6004E" varFormat="Java">
    MSG_CONM_6004E=CONM6004E: The required default user ID for the supplied default password is missing for DataSource ({0}).
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A password is supplied, but no user ID is supplied.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Supply a valid user ID and password, or remove the password.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CONM0000E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MSG_CONM_0000E" varFormat="Java">
    MSG_CONM_0000E=CONM0000E: The Connection Manager Application Programming Interfaces have been removed. Use the Connection Pooling Application Programming Interfaces.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The methods that are called are removed.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Use the new connection pooling API.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CONM6019W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MSG_CONM_6019W" varFormat="Java">
    MSG_CONM_6019W=CONM6019W: A SQLException occurred while validating the connection for DataSource {0}.  The exception is {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An SQLException was received while validating the connection.  The connection pool is purged and a new connection from the pool is returned.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CONM6002W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MSG_CONM_6002W" varFormat="Java">
    MSG_CONM_6002W=CONM6002W: The system cannot get an XA resource {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The system is unable to get an XA resource while destroying a connection.  Calling destroy means to close the connection and remove it from the free pool.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CONM7015E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MSG_CONM_7015E" varFormat="Java">
    MSG_CONM_7015E=CONM7015E: The was.install.library property is not set.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The was.install.library property is required and needs to be set.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Set the was.install.library property.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CONM7014W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MSG_CONM_7014W" varFormat="Java">
    MSG_CONM_7014W=CONM7014W: The test connection to the DataSource failed : {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A test connection was attempted from the administrative console.  This operation failed with the listed exception.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the exception for an explanation of the failed connection.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CONM6018E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MSG_CONM_6018E" varFormat="Java">
    MSG_CONM_6018E=CONM6018E: Calling unilateralCommit is not supported on a JTAEnabled connection in a global transaction.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    unilateralCommit was called on a JTAEnabled connection in a global transaction.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Do not use unilateralCommit on a JTAEnabled connection in application code. If the problem persists, see the problem determination on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page on http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CONM6021W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MSG_CONM_6021W" varFormat="Java">
    MSG_CONM_6021W=CONM6021W: A Java Database Connectivity (JDBC) provider property (TransactionBranchesLooselyCoupled) is set in Oracle. Oracle patch 2511780 must be applied before setting this property.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A custom property was set when creating the JDBC provider on an Oracle system. The property requires Oracle patch 2511780.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the patch is installed, no user action is required. Otherwise, contact Oracle support to obtain the patch.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<!-- END MESSAGES -->
</TMSSource>
