<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/css" href="../../resources/stylesheets/wasmsgxml.css"?>
<TMSSource name="TivoliMessages" tmsVersion="1.0" xml:lang="en">
<!-- CMVC MSG File Name = SERV1/ws/code/dpmanager/src/com/ibm/datapower/dmi/dataAPI/WCCMProvider/resources/messages.nlsprops -->
<!-- DO NOT EDIT THIS FILE - This file was generated by the XML/Html & Property emitter -->
<!-- BEGIN MESSAGES -->
<Message ID="CWPOW0510E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="RepositoryImpl.notADirectory" varFormat="Java">
    RepositoryImpl.notADirectory=CWPOW0510E: The {0} versions directory, which is specified in the configuration for the DataPower appliance manager, is not a directory.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The value, which is specified for the versions directory in the configuration for the DataPower appliance manager, is not a directory.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Change the value, which is specified for the versions directory in the configuration for the DataPower appliance manager, to a directory name.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPOW0516E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SettingsImpl.badDesiredVer" varFormat="Java">
    SettingsImpl.badDesiredVer=CWPOW0516E: The DPClonableDeviceSettings tag with the name={0} value within the DPManagedSet tag with the name={1} value has a desiredVersion={2} value.  The desiredVersion  which cannot be resolved in the configuration for the DataPower appliance manager.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Each DPClonableDeviceSettings tag within the DPManagedSet tag must have a valid desiredVersion value.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Change the desiredVersion value to reference a valid DPClonableDeviceSettingsVersion value in the configuration for the DataPower appliance manager.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPOW0514E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DomainImpl.dupDomain" varFormat="Java">
    DomainImpl.dupDomain=CWPOW0514E: In the configuration for the DataPower appliance manager, there are two DPDomain tags with the name={0} value within the DPManagedSet tag with the name={1} value.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Each DPDomain tag within the DPManagedSet tag must have a unique name value.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Remove the duplicate DPDomain tag from the configuration for the DataPower appliance manager..
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPOW0513E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ManagedSetImpl.errorObjectNameToRef" varFormat="Java">
    ManagedSetImpl.errorObjectNameToRef=CWPOW0513E: The DataPower appliance manager cannot resolve the {0} object name to an instance for the {1} class.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This exception is unexpected. The cause is not immediately known.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPOW0511E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DeviceImpl.dupDevice" varFormat="Java">
    DeviceImpl.dupDevice=CWPOW0511E: The DPDevice tag with the name={0} value and DPDevice tag with the name={1} value in the DataPower appliance manager configuration have the same {2} serialNumber value.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Each DPDevice tag in the configuration for the DataPower appliance manager must have a unique serialNumber value.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Remove the duplicate DPDevice tag from the configuration for the DataPower appliance manager.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPOW0519E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="FirmwareImpl.hasVer" varFormat="Java">
    FirmwareImpl.hasVer=CWPOW0519E: The DataPower appliance manager cannot delete the firmware with the {0} primary key because it has firmware versions.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This exception is unexpected. The cause is not immediately known.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPOW0515E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DomainImpl.badDesiredVer" varFormat="Java">
    DomainImpl.badDesiredVer=CWPOW0515E: The DPDomain tag with the name={0} value within the DPManagedSet tag with the name={1} value has a desiredVersion={2} value.  The desiredVersion value cannot be resolved in the configuration for the DataPower appliance manager.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Each DPDomain tag within the DPManagedSet tag must have a valid desiredVersion value.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Change the desiredVersion value to reference a valid DPDomainVersion value in the configuration for the DataPower appliance manager.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPOW0517E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DeployableConfiguration.hasVer" varFormat="Java">
    DeployableConfiguration.hasVer=CWPOW0517E: The DataPower appliance manager cannot delete the domain or settings with the {0} primary key because the domain or settings has versions.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This exception is unexpected. The cause is not immediately known.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPOW0518E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="FirmwareImpl.dupFirmware" varFormat="Java">
    FirmwareImpl.dupFirmware=CWPOW0518E: Two DPFirmware tags both have deviceType={0}, modelType={1}, strictFeatures={2} and  nonstrictFeatures={3} values in the configuration for the DataPower appliance manager.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Each DPFirmware tag in the configuration must have a unique combination of deviceType, modelType, strictFeatures and  nonstrictFeatures values.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Remove the duplicate DPFirmware tag and its related DPFirmwareVersion tags from the configuration for the DataPower appliance manager.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPOW0512E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ManagedSetImpl.dupManagedSet" varFormat="Java">
    ManagedSetImpl.dupManagedSet=CWPOW0512E: There are two DPManagedSet tags with the name={0} value in the configuration for the DataPower appliance manager.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Each DPManagedSet tag in the configuration  for the DataPower appliance manager must have a unique name value.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Remove the duplicate DPManagedSet tag from the configuration for the DataPower appliance manager.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<!-- END MESSAGES -->
</TMSSource>
