<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/css" href="../../resources/stylesheets/wasmsgxml.css"?>
<TMSSource name="TivoliMessages" tmsVersion="1.0" xml:lang="en">
<!-- CMVC MSG File Name = ws/code/sib.security/src/com/ibm/ws/sib/security/CWSIIMessages.nlsprops -->
<!-- DO NOT EDIT THIS FILE - This file was generated by the XML/Html & Property emitter -->
<!-- BEGIN MESSAGES -->
<Message ID="CWSII0218W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="USER_IDENTITY_ADOPT_DENIED_CWSII0218W" varFormat="Java">
    USER_IDENTITY_ADOPT_DENIED_CWSII0218W=CWSII0218W: The bus {0} denied the user {1} access to assume the identity of another user for the destination {2}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The user is not in the identityAdopter role for the destination.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If you want the user to assume the identity of other users when sending messages, add the user to the identityAdopter role for that destination.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSII0261E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="USER_REPOSITORY_GET_USER_INFO_FAILED_CWSII0261E" varFormat="Java">
    USER_REPOSITORY_GET_USER_INFO_FAILED_CWSII0261E=CWSII0261E: A failure occurred while querying information about the user {0} from the user repository for the bus {1}. The exception was {2}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    There has been an unsuccessful attempt to obtain information about a user from the user repository for the bus.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Retry the query.  If the retry is unsuccessful, the user repository may be unavailable and you should contact the user repository administrator.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSII0248W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SERVER_SEND_DEFAULT_TEMP_DEST_DENIED_CWSII0248W" varFormat="Java">
    SERVER_SEND_DEFAULT_TEMP_DEST_DENIED_CWSII0248W=CWSII0248W: The bus {0} denied access by the server identity to send messages to the temporary destination {1} because the user is not in the sender role for the default temporary destination prefix.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Server group is not in the sender role for the default temporary destination prefix.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If you want servers to send messages to the temporary destination, add the Server group to the sender role for the default temporary destination.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSII0262E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="USER_REPOSITORY_GET_GROUP_FAILED_CWSII0262E" varFormat="Java">
    USER_REPOSITORY_GET_GROUP_FAILED_CWSII0262E=CWSII0262E: A failure occurred while querying groups in the user repository for the bus {0} using query string {1}. The exception was {2}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    There has been an unsuccessful attempt to obtain a list of groups in the user repository for the bus.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Retry the query.  If the retry is unsuccessful, the user repository may be unavailable and you should contact the user repository administrator.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSII0201E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="UNABLE_TO_CREATE_ACCESS_CONTROL_FACTORY_CWSII0201E" varFormat="Java">
    UNABLE_TO_CREATE_ACCESS_CONTROL_FACTORY_CWSII0201E=CWSII0201E: An internal error has occurred. It is not possible to create an instance of {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This exception is unexpected. The cause is not immediately known.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSII0220W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="USER_SEND_TEMP_DEST_DENIED_CWSII0220W" varFormat="Java">
    USER_SEND_TEMP_DEST_DENIED_CWSII0220W=CWSII0220W: The bus {0} denied the user {1} access to send messages to the temporary destination {2} with the temporary destination prefix {3}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The user is not in the sender role for the relevant temporary destination prefix.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If you want the user to send messages to the temporary destination, add the user to the sender role for that temporary destination prefix.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSII0260E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="USER_REPOSITORY_GET_USER_FAILED_CWSII0260E" varFormat="Java">
    USER_REPOSITORY_GET_USER_FAILED_CWSII0260E=CWSII0260E: A failure occurred while querying users in the user repository for the bus {0} using query string {1}. The exception was {2}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    There has been an unsuccessful attempt to obtain a list of users in the user repository for the bus.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Retry the query.  If the retry is unsuccessful, the user repository may be unavailable and you should contact the user repository administrator.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSII0268E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="USER_REPOSITORY_LOOKUP_FAILURE_CWSII0268E" varFormat="Java">
    USER_REPOSITORY_LOOKUP_FAILURE_CWSII0268E=CWSII0268E: A failure occurred while looking up the user repository for the bus {0}. The exception was {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This exception is unexpected. The cause is not immediately known.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSII0233W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ANONYMOUS_DENIED_SEND_FOREIGN_BUS_CWSII0233W" varFormat="Java">
    ANONYMOUS_DENIED_SEND_FOREIGN_BUS_CWSII0233W=CWSII0233W: The bus {0} denied an anonymous user access to send a message to the foreign bus {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Everyone group is not in the sender role for the foreign destination.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If you want anonymous users to send messages to the foreign bus, add the Everyone group to the sender role for that foreign bus.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSII0203E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="UNABLE_TO_CREATE_SECURITY_CONTEXT_FACTORY_CWSII0203E" varFormat="Java">
    UNABLE_TO_CREATE_SECURITY_CONTEXT_FACTORY_CWSII0203E=CWSII0203E: An internal error has occurred. It is not possible to create an instance of {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This exception is unexpected. The cause is not immediately known.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSII0212W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ANONYMOUS_CONNECT_DENIED_CWSII0212W" varFormat="Java">
    ANONYMOUS_CONNECT_DENIED_CWSII0212W=CWSII0212W: The bus {0} denied an anonymous user access to the bus.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A client attempted to connect to the bus without supplying any credentials,and the Everyone group does not have the bus connector role for the bus.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that the client provides credentials, or that the Everyone group has access to connect to the bus.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSII0208W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="LTPA_AUTHENTICATION_FAILED_CWSII208W" varFormat="Java">
    LTPA_AUTHENTICATION_FAILED_CWSII208W=CWSII0208W: The bus {0} could not authenticate a user using an LTPA token.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An attempt was made to authenticate using an LTPA token, but the LTPA token was not valid.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that clients provide valid LTPA tokens for authentication.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSII0253E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SERVER_CREATE_DENIED_CWSII0253W" varFormat="Java">
    SERVER_CREATE_DENIED_CWSII0253W=CWSII0253E: The bus {0} denied access by the server identity to create temporary destinations from the destination prefix {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Server group is not in the creator role for the temporary destination prefix.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If you want servers to create temporary destinations using that prefix, add the Server group to the creator role for that temporary destination prefix.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSII9999E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="TEMPORARY_CWSII9999" varFormat="Java">
    TEMPORARY_CWSII9999=CWSII9999E: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    If the message does not give sufficient information, check any previous messages for further information.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If you are unable to resolve the problem ask your system administrator to help resolve the problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSII0206I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="AUTHENTICATION_SUCCEEDED_CWSII0206I" varFormat="Java">
    AUTHENTICATION_SUCCEEDED_CWSII0206I=CWSII0206I: The bus {0} authenticated the user {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A client successfully authenticated to the bus.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    None
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSII0204W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="BUS_SECURITY_ENABLED_ADMIN_DISABLED_CWSII0204W" varFormat="Java">
    BUS_SECURITY_ENABLED_ADMIN_DISABLED_CWSII0204W=CWSII0204W: The bus {0} has had security disabled because although the bus has been configured to be secure, administrative security has been disabled.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The system has been configured so that bus security is enabled, but administrative security has been disabled. This configuration is inconsistent and the bus is not secure.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Either enable administrative security or disable bus security.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSII0265E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="USER_REPOSITORY_DOES_GROUP_EXIST_FAILED_CWSII0265E" varFormat="Java">
    USER_REPOSITORY_DOES_GROUP_EXIST_FAILED_CWSII0265E=CWSII0265E: A failure occurred while querying the user repository for the bus {0} to see if the group {1} exists. The exception was {2}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    There has been an unsuccessful attempt to find out if a group exists in the user repository for the bus.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Retry the query. If the retry is unsuccessful, the user repository may be unavailable and you should contact the user repository administrator.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSII0224W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="USER_INQUIRE_DEFAULT_TEMP_DEST_DENIED_CWSII0224W" varFormat="Java">
    USER_INQUIRE_DEFAULT_TEMP_DEST_DENIED_CWSII0224W=CWSII0224W: The bus {0} denied the user {1} access to inquire the configuration of the temporary destination {2} with the default tempoaray destination prefix.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The user is not in the inquire role for the relevant temporary destination prefix. Users have the inquire role if they are in the sender, receiver or browser role for the temporary destination prefix.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the user should have inquire access add the user to the sender, receiver or browser role for the default destination prefix.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSII0217W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="USER_BROWSE_DENIED_CWSII0217W" varFormat="Java">
    USER_BROWSE_DENIED_CWSII0217W=CWSII0217W: The bus {0} denied the user {1} access to browse messages at the destination {2}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The user is not in the browser role for the destination.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If you want the user to send messages to the destination, add the user to the browser role for that destination.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSII0232W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ANONYMOUS_IDENTITY_ADOPT_DENIED_CWSII0232W" varFormat="Java">
    ANONYMOUS_IDENTITY_ADOPT_DENIED_CWSII0232W=CWSII0232W: The bus {0} denied an anonymous user access to assume the identity of another user for the destination {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Everyone group is not in the identityAdopter role for the destination.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If you want anonymous users to assume the identity of other users when sending messages, add the Everyone group to the identityAdopter role for that destination.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSII0234E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ANONYMOUS_CREATE_DEFAULT_DENIED_CWSII0234W" varFormat="Java">
    ANONYMOUS_CREATE_DEFAULT_DENIED_CWSII0234W=CWSII0234E: The bus {0} denied an anonymous user access to create temporary destinations using the default destination prefix.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Everyone group is not in the creator role for the default temporary destination prefix.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If you want anonymous users to create temporary destinations using the default temporary destination prefix then add the Everyone group to the creator role for the default temporary destination prefix.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSII0219W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="USER_DENIED_SEND_FOREIGN_BUS_CWSII0219W" varFormat="Java">
    USER_DENIED_SEND_FOREIGN_BUS_CWSII0219W=CWSII0219W: The bus {0} denied the user {1} access to send a message to the foreign bus {2}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The user is not in the sender role for the foreign destination.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If you want the user to send messages to the foreign bus, add the user to the sender role for that foreign bus.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSII0241E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_AUDIT_MODE_CWSII0241E" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_AUDIT_MODE_CWSII0241E=CWSII0241E: The bus {0} has been configured with an invalid audit mode of {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The bus has been configured with an audit mode which is not valid. The valid audit modes are all, none, or failure.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that you set a valid mode for the audit.bus.authentication custom property in the bus configuration.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSII0223W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="USER_SEND_DEFAULT_TEMP_DEST_DENIED_CWSII0223W" varFormat="Java">
    USER_SEND_DEFAULT_TEMP_DEST_DENIED_CWSII0223W=CWSII0223W: The bus {0} denied the user {1} access to send messages to the temporary destination {2} with the default temporary destination prefix.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The user is not in the sender role for the default temporary destination prefix.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If you want the user to send messages to the temporary destination, add the user to the sender role for the default temporary destination.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSII0252W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SERVER_INQUIRE_DEFAULT_TEMP_DEST_DENIED_CWSII0252W" varFormat="Java">
    SERVER_INQUIRE_DEFAULT_TEMP_DEST_DENIED_CWSII0252W=CWSII0252W: The bus {0} denied access by the server identity to inquire the configuration of the temporary destination {1} with the default temporary destination prefix.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Server group is not in the inquire role for the relevant temporary destination prefix. Users have the inquire role if they are in the sender, receiver or browser role for the temporary destination prefix.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If you want servers to have inquire access, add the Server group to the sender, receiver or browser role for the default destination prefix.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSII0222W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="USER_IDENTITY_ADOPT_TEMP_DEST_DENIED_CWSII0222W" varFormat="Java">
    USER_IDENTITY_ADOPT_TEMP_DEST_DENIED_CWSII0222W=CWSII0222W: The bus {0} denied the user {1} access to assume the identity of another user for the temporary destination {2} with the temporary destination prefix {3}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The user is not in the identityAdopter role for the relevant temporary destination prefix.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If you want the user to assume the identity of other users when sending messages, add the user to the identityAdopter role for that temporary destination prefix.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSII0258W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SERVER_BROWSE_DENIED_CWSII0258W" varFormat="Java">
    SERVER_BROWSE_DENIED_CWSII0258W=CWSII0258W: The bus {0} denied access by the server identity to browse messages at the destination {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Server group is not in the browser role for the destination.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If you want servers to send messages to the destination, add the Server group to the browser role for that destination.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSII0240W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ANONYMOUS_INQUIRE_DEFAULT_TEMP_DEST_DENIED_CWSII0240W" varFormat="Java">
    ANONYMOUS_INQUIRE_DEFAULT_TEMP_DEST_DENIED_CWSII0240W=CWSII0240W: The bus {0} denied an anonymous user access to inquire the configuration of the temporary destination {1} with the default temporary destination prefix.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Everyone group is not in the inquire role for the relevant temporary destination prefix. Users have the inquire role if they are in the sender, receiver or browser role for the temporary destination prefix.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If you want anonymous users to have inquire access, add the Everyone group to the sender, receiver or browser role for the default destination prefix.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSII0236W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ANONYMOUS_SEND_DEFAULT_TEMP_DEST_DENIED_CWSII0236W" varFormat="Java">
    ANONYMOUS_SEND_DEFAULT_TEMP_DEST_DENIED_CWSII0236W=CWSII0236W: The bus {0} denied an anonymous user access to send messages to the temporary destination {1} because the user is not in the sender role for the default temporary destination prefix.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Everyone group is not in the sender role for the default temporary destination prefix.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If you want anonymous users to send messages to the temporary destination, add the Everyone group to the sender role for the default temporary destination.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSII0247W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SERVER_SEND_TEMP_DEST_DENIED_CWSII0247W" varFormat="Java">
    SERVER_SEND_TEMP_DEST_DENIED_CWSII0247W=CWSII0247W: The bus {0} denied access by the server identity to send messages to the temporary destination {1} with the temporary destination prefix {2}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Server group is not in the sender role for the relevant temporary destination prefix.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If you want servers to send messages to the temporary destination, add the Server group to the sender role for that temporary destination prefix.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSII0210I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DYNAMIC_CONFIG_UPDATE_CWSII0210I" varFormat="Java">
    DYNAMIC_CONFIG_UPDATE_CWSII0210I=CWSII0210I: The authorization policy for the bus {0} has been updated as a result of an administrative update.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The administrator has updated the authorization policy for the bus.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    None
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSII0267E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="USER_REPOSITORY_CREATE_FAILURE_CWSII0267E" varFormat="Java">
    USER_REPOSITORY_CREATE_FAILURE_CWSII0267E=CWSII0267E: A failure occurred while creating the user repository for the bus {0}. The exception was {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This exception is unexpected. The cause is not immediately known.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSII0254W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SERVER_CONNECT_DENIED_CWSII0254W" varFormat="Java">
    SERVER_CONNECT_DENIED_CWSII0254W=CWSII0254W: The bus {0} denied the server identity access to the bus.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Server group is not in the bus connector role for the bus.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If you want servers to connect to the bus, add the Server group to the bus connector role.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSII0211W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="USER_CONNECT_DENIED_CWSII0211W" varFormat="Java">
    USER_CONNECT_DENIED_CWSII0211W=CWSII0211W: The bus {0} denied the user {1} access to the bus.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The user has not been granted the bus connector role for the bus.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If you want the user have access to the bus, add the user to the connector role for the bus.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSII0213W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="USER_SEND_DENIED_CWSII0213W" varFormat="Java">
    USER_SEND_DENIED_CWSII0213W=CWSII0213W: The bus {0} denied the user {1} access to send messages to the destination {2}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The user is not in the sender role for the destination.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If you want the user to send messages to the destination, add the user to the sender role for that destination.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSII0263E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="USER_REPOSITORY_GET_GROUP_INFO_FAILED_CWSII0263E" varFormat="Java">
    USER_REPOSITORY_GET_GROUP_INFO_FAILED_CWSII0263E=CWSII0263E: A failure occurred while querying information about the group {0} from the user repository for the bus {1}. The exception was {2}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    There has been an unsuccessful attempt to obtain information about a group from the user repository for the bus.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Retry the query.  If the retry is unsuccessful, the user repository may be unavailable and you should contact the user repository administrator.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSII0216W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="USER_INQUIRE_DENIED_CWSII0216W" varFormat="Java">
    USER_INQUIRE_DENIED_CWSII0216W=CWSII0216W: The bus {0} denied the user {1} access to inquire the configuration of the destination {2}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The user is not in the inquire role for the destination. A user has the inquire role if they are in the sender, receiver or browser role for the destination.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the user should have inquire access, add the user to the sender, receiver or browser role.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSII0209E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="GROUP_QUERY_FAILED_CWSII0209E" varFormat="Java">
    GROUP_QUERY_FAILED_CWSII0209E=CWSII0209E: The bus {0} is unable to access the user registry to find the groups of which the user {2} is a member. Exception {3}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This exception is unexpected. The cause is not immediately known.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSII0243W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ANONYMOUS_DENIED_IDENTITY_ADOPT_FOREIGN_BUS_CWSII0243W" varFormat="Java">
    ANONYMOUS_DENIED_IDENTITY_ADOPT_FOREIGN_BUS_CWSII0243W=CWSII0243W: The bus {0} denied an anonymous user access to adopt the identity of another user when sending a message to the foreign bus {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Everyone group is not in the identity adopter role for the foreign destination.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If you want anonymous users to adopt another user&apos;s identity when sending messages to the foreign bus, add the Everyone group to the identity adopter role for that foreign bus.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSII0239W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ANONYMOUS_INQUIRE_TEMP_DEST_DENIED_CWSII0239W" varFormat="Java">
    ANONYMOUS_INQUIRE_TEMP_DEST_DENIED_CWSII0239W=CWSII0239W: The bus {0} denied an anonymous user access to inquire the configuration of the temporary destination {1} with the temporary destination prefix {2}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Everyone group is not in the inquire role for the relevant temporary destination prefix. Users have the inquire role if they are in the sender, receiver or browser role for the temporary destination prefix.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If you want anonymous users to have inquire access, add the Everyone group to the sender, receiver or browser role for that temporary destination prefix.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSII0231W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ANONYMOUS_BROWSE_DENIED_CWSII0231W" varFormat="Java">
    ANONYMOUS_BROWSE_DENIED_CWSII0231W=CWSII0231W: The bus {0} denied an anonymous user access to browse messages at the destination {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Everyone group is not in the browser role for the destination.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If you want anonymous users to send messages to the destination, add the Everyone group to the browser role for that destination.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSII0202E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="UNABLE_TO_CREATE_LOGIN_FACTORY_CWSII0202E" varFormat="Java">
    UNABLE_TO_CREATE_LOGIN_FACTORY_CWSII0202E=CWSII0202E: An internal error has occurred. It is not possible to create an instance of {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This exception is unexpected. The cause is not immediately known.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSII0250W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SERVER_IDENTITY_ADOPT_DEFAULT_TEMP_DEST_DENIED_CWSII0250W" varFormat="Java">
    SERVER_IDENTITY_ADOPT_DEFAULT_TEMP_DEST_DENIED_CWSII0250W=CWSII0250W: The bus {0} denied access by the server identity to assume the identity of another user for the temporary destination {1} with the default temporary destination prefix.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Server group is not in the identityAdopter role for the default temporary destination prefix.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If you want servers to assume the identity of other users when sending messages, add the Server group to the identityAdopter role for the default temporary destination prefix.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSII0227W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ANONYMOUS_SEND_DENIED_CWSII0227W" varFormat="Java">
    ANONYMOUS_SEND_DENIED_CWSII0227W=CWSII0227W: The bus {0} denied an anonymous user access to send messages to the destination {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Everyone group is not in the sender role for the destination.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If you want anonymous users to send messages to the destination add the Everyone group to the sender role for that destination.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSII0225W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="USER_IDENTITY_ADOPT_DEFAULT_TEMP_DEST_DENIED_CWSII0225W" varFormat="Java">
    USER_IDENTITY_ADOPT_DEFAULT_TEMP_DEST_DENIED_CWSII0225W=CWSII0225W: The bus {0} denied the user {1} access to assume the identity of another user for the temporary destination {2} with the default temporary destination prefix.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The user is not in the identityAdopter role for the default temporary destination prefix.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If you want the user to assume the identity of other users when sending messages, add the user to the identityAdopter role for the default temporary destination prefix.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSII0255W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SERVER_SEND_DENIED_CWSII0255W" varFormat="Java">
    SERVER_SEND_DENIED_CWSII0255W=CWSII0255W: The bus {0} denied access by the server identity to send messages to the destination {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Server group is not in the sender role for the destination.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If you want servers  to send messages to the destination, add the Server group to the sender role for that destination.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSII0215E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="USER_CREATE_DENIED_CWSII0215W" varFormat="Java">
    USER_CREATE_DENIED_CWSII0215W=CWSII0215E: The bus {0} denied the user {1} the access to create temporary destinations from the destination prefix {2}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The user is not in the creator role for the temporary destination prefix.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If you want the user to create temporary destinations using the temporary destination prefix, add the user to the creator role for the temporary destination prefix.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSII0205W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="AUTHENTICATION_FAILED_CWSII205W" varFormat="Java">
    AUTHENTICATION_FAILED_CWSII205W=CWSII0205W: The bus {0} could not authenticate the user {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The supplied user name does not exist, or the password is not valid.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that the supplied user name is valid, and that the password is correct.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSII0251W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SERVER_INQUIRE_TEMP_DEST_DENIED_CWSII0251W" varFormat="Java">
    SERVER_INQUIRE_TEMP_DEST_DENIED_CWSII0251W=CWSII0251W: The bus {0} denied access by the server identity to inquire the configuration of the temporary destination {1} with the temporary destination prefix {2}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Server group is not in the inquire role for the relevant temporary destination prefix. Users have the inquire role if they are in the sender, receiver or browser role for the temporary destination prefix.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If you want servers to have inquire access, add the Server group to the sender, receiver or browser role for that temporary destination prefix.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSII0257W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SERVER_INQUIRE_DENIED_CWSII0257W" varFormat="Java">
    SERVER_INQUIRE_DENIED_CWSII0257W=CWSII0257W: The bus {0} denied access by the server identity to inquire the configuration of the destination {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Server group is not in the inquire role for the destination.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If you want servers to have inquire access, add the Server group to the sender, receiver or browser role.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSII0228W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ANONYMOUS_RECEIVE_DENIED_CWSII0228W" varFormat="Java">
    ANONYMOUS_RECEIVE_DENIED_CWSII0228W=CWSII0228W: The bus {0} denied an anonymous user access to receive messages from the destination {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Everyone group is not in the receiver role for the destination.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If you want anonymous users  to receive from the destination, add the Everyone group to the receiver role for that destination.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSII0245W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SERVER_DENIED_IDENTITY_ADOPTER_FOREIGN_BUS_CWSII0245W" varFormat="Java">
    SERVER_DENIED_IDENTITY_ADOPTER_FOREIGN_BUS_CWSII0245W=CWSII0245W: The bus {0} denied access by the server identity to adopt the identity of another user when sending a message to the foreign bus {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Server group is not in the identity adopter role for the foreign destination.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If you want servers to adopt the identity of another user when sending messages to the foreign bus, add the Server group to the identity adopter role for that foreign bus.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSII0238W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ANONYMOUS_IDENTITY_ADOPT_DEFAULT_TEMP_DEST_DENIED_CWSII0238W" varFormat="Java">
    ANONYMOUS_IDENTITY_ADOPT_DEFAULT_TEMP_DEST_DENIED_CWSII0238W=CWSII0238W: The bus {0} denied an anonymous user access to assume the identity of another user for the temporary destination {1} with the default temporary destination prefix.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Everyone group is not in the identityAdopter role for the default temporary destination prefix.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If you want anonymous users to assume the identity of other users when sending messages, add the Everyone group to the identityAdopter role for the default temporary destination prefix.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSII0237W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ANONYMOUS_IDENTITY_ADOPT_TEMP_DEST_DENIED_CWSII0237W" varFormat="Java">
    ANONYMOUS_IDENTITY_ADOPT_TEMP_DEST_DENIED_CWSII0237W=CWSII0237W: The bus {0} denied an anonymous user access to assume the identity of another user for the temporary destination {1} with the temporary destination prefix {2}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Everyone group is not in the identityAdopter role for the relevant temporary destination prefix.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If you want anonymous users to assume the identity of other users when sending messages, add the Everyone group to the identityAdopter role for that temporary destination prefix.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSII0230W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ANONYMOUS_INQUIRE_DENIED_CWSII0230W" varFormat="Java">
    ANONYMOUS_INQUIRE_DENIED_CWSII0230W=CWSII0230W: The bus {0} denied an anonymous user access to inquire the configuration of the destination {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Everyone group is not in the inquire role for the destination.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If anonymous users should have inquire access, add the Everyone group to the sender, receiver or browser role.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSII0242W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="USER_DENIED_IDENTITY_ADOPT_FOREIGN_BUS_CWSII0242W" varFormat="Java">
    USER_DENIED_IDENTITY_ADOPT_FOREIGN_BUS_CWSII0242W=CWSII0242W: The bus {0} denied the user {1} access to adopt the identity of another user when sending a message to the foreign bus {2}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The user is not in the identity adopter role for the foreign destination.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If you want the user to assume the identity of another user when sending messages to the foreign bus, add the user to the identity adopter role for that foreign bus.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSII0229E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ANONYMOUS_CREATE_DENIED_CWSII0229W" varFormat="Java">
    ANONYMOUS_CREATE_DENIED_CWSII0229W=CWSII0229E: The bus {0} denied an anonymous user access to create temporary destinations from the destination prefix {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Everyone group is not in the creator role for the temporary destination prefix.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If you want anonymous users to create temporary destinations using that prefix, add the Everyone group to the creator role for that temporary destination prefix.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSII0226E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="USER_CREATE_DEFAULT_DENIED_CWSII0226W" varFormat="Java">
    USER_CREATE_DEFAULT_DENIED_CWSII0226W=CWSII0226E: The bus {0} denied the user {1} access to create temporary destinations using the default destination prefix.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The user is not in the creator role for the default temporary destination prefix.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If you want the user to create temporary destinations using that prefix, add the user to the creator role for the default temporary destination prefix.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSII0246E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SERVER_CREATE_DEFAULT_DENIED_CWSII0246W" varFormat="Java">
    SERVER_CREATE_DEFAULT_DENIED_CWSII0246W=CWSII0246E: The bus {0} denied access by the server identity to create temporary destinations using the default destination prefix.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Server group is not in the creator role for the default temporary destination prefix.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If you want servers to create temporary destinations using the default temporary destination prefix, add the Server group to the creator role for the default temporary destination prefix.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSII0264E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="USER_REPOSITORY_DOES_USER_EXIST_FAILED_CWSII0264E" varFormat="Java">
    USER_REPOSITORY_DOES_USER_EXIST_FAILED_CWSII0264E=CWSII0264E: A failure occurred while querying the user repository for the bus {0} to see if the user {1} exists. The exception was {2}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    There has been an unsuccessful attempt to find out if a user exists in the user repository for the bus.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Retry the query.  If the retry is unsuccessful, the user repository may be unavailable and you should contact the user repository administrator.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSII0256W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SERVER_RECEIVE_DENIED_CWSII0256W" varFormat="Java">
    SERVER_RECEIVE_DENIED_CWSII0256W=CWSII0256W: The bus {0} denied access by the server identity to receive messages from the destination {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Server group is not in the receiver role for the destination.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If you want servers to receive messages from the destination, add the Server group to the receiver role for that destination.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSII0221W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="USER_INQUIRE_TEMP_DEST_DENIED_CWSII0221W" varFormat="Java">
    USER_INQUIRE_TEMP_DEST_DENIED_CWSII0221W=CWSII0221W: The bus {0} denied the user {1} access to inquire the configuration of the temporary destination {2} with the tempoaray destination prefix {3}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The user is not in the inquire role for the relevant temporary destination prefix. Users have the inquire role if they are in the sender, receiver or browser role for the temporary destination prefix.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If you want the user to have inquire access for the temporary destination prefix, add the user to the sender, receiver or browser role for that temporary destination prefix.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSII0259W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SERVER_IDENTITY_ADOPT_DENIED_CWSII0259W" varFormat="Java">
    SERVER_IDENTITY_ADOPT_DENIED_CWSII0259W=CWSII0259W: The bus {0} denied access by the server identity to assume the identity of another user for the destination {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Server group is not in the identityAdopter role for the destination.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If you want servers to assume the identity of other users when sending messages, add the Server group to the identityAdopter role for that destination.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSII0249W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SERVER_IDENTITY_ADOPT_TEMP_DEST_DENIED_CWSII0249W" varFormat="Java">
    SERVER_IDENTITY_ADOPT_TEMP_DEST_DENIED_CWSII0249W=CWSII0249W: The bus {0} denied access by the server identity to assume the identity of another user for the temporary destination {1} with the temporary destination prefix {2}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Server group is not in the identityAdopter role for the relevant temporary destination prefix.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If you want servers to assume the identity of other users when sending messages, add the Server group to the identityAdopter role for that temporary destination prefix.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSII0266E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="USER_REPOSITORY_GET_GROUPS_FOR_USER_CWSII0266E" varFormat="Java">
    USER_REPOSITORY_GET_GROUPS_FOR_USER_CWSII0266E=CWSII0266E: A failure occurred while querying the user repository for the bus {0} to obtain the groups the user {1} is in. The exception was {2}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    There has been an unsuccessful attempt to find out to which groups a user belongs. The attempt failed.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Retry the query.  If the retry is unsuccessful, the user repository may be unavailable and you should contact the user repository administrator.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSII0214W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="USER_RECEIVE_DENIED_CWSII0214W" varFormat="Java">
    USER_RECEIVE_DENIED_CWSII0214W=CWSII0214W: The bus {0} denied the user {1} access to receive messages from the destination {2}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The user is not in the receiver role for the destination.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If you want the user to receive messages from the destination, add the user to the receiver role for that destination.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSII0200E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="UNABLE_TO_CREATE_AUTH_UTILS_FACTORY_CWSII0200E" varFormat="Java">
    UNABLE_TO_CREATE_AUTH_UTILS_FACTORY_CWSII0200E=CWSII0200E: An internal error has occurred. It is not possible to create an instance of {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This exception is unexpected. The cause is not immediately known.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSII0207I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ANONYMOUS_AUTHENTICATION_SUCCEEDED_CWSII0207I" varFormat="Java">
    ANONYMOUS_AUTHENTICATION_SUCCEEDED_CWSII0207I=CWSII0207I: The bus {0} authenticated an anonymous client.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A client that has not provided credentials has successfully authenticated to the bus. This user can only connect to the bus if the Everyone group is in the bus connector role.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    None
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSII0269W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="AUTHZ_USER_REPOSITORY_LOOKUP_CWSII0269W" varFormat="Java">
    AUTHZ_USER_REPOSITORY_LOOKUP_CWSII0269W=CWSII0269W: The runtime accessed the user repository for bus {0} to populate missing unique name data when loading the authorization model for the bus.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    One or more entries in the authorization model for the bus do not have a unique name configured. If the unique name is not present then it is retrieved from the user repository whenever the authorization model is loaded. This places additional load on the user repository when starting servers or dynamically updating the bus configuration.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Run the populateUniqueNames wsadmin command. This will update the incomplete authorization entries with data from the user repository where possible. Any authorizations for users not present in the user repository should be updated to include a unique name using the relevant command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSII0244W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SERVER_DENIED_SEND_FOREIGN_BUS_CWSII0244W" varFormat="Java">
    SERVER_DENIED_SEND_FOREIGN_BUS_CWSII0244W=CWSII0244W: The bus {0} denied access by the server identity to send a message to the foreign bus {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Server group is not in the sender role for the foreign destination.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If you want the servers to send messages to the foreign bus, add the Server group to the sender role for that foreign bus.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSII0235W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ANONYMOUS_SEND_TEMP_DEST_DENIED_CWSII0235W" varFormat="Java">
    ANONYMOUS_SEND_TEMP_DEST_DENIED_CWSII0235W=CWSII0235W: The bus {0} denied an anonymous user access to send messages to the temporary destination {1} with the temporary destination prefix {2}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Everyone group is not in the sender role for the relevant temporary destination prefix.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If you want anonymous users to send messages to the temporary destination, add the Everyone group to the sender role for that temporary destination prefix.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<!-- END MESSAGES -->
</TMSSource>
