<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/css" href="../../resources/stylesheets/wasmsgxml.css"?>
<TMSSource name="TivoliMessages" tmsVersion="1.0" xml:lang="en">
<!-- CMVC MSG File Name = SIB/ws/code/sib.admin.commands/src/com/ibm/ws/management/commands/sib/CWSJAMessages.nlsprops -->
<!-- DO NOT EDIT THIS FILE - This file was generated by the XML/Html & Property emitter -->
<!-- BEGIN MESSAGES -->
<Message ID="CWSJA0028E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MULTIPLE_DESTS_FOUND_CWSJA0028" varFormat="Java">
    MULTIPLE_DESTS_FOUND_CWSJA0028=CWSJA0028E: Multiple destinations found.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Only one instance of a destination should exist within the scope specified, yet more than one instance has been located.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that destinations have unique configuration data within an administrative domain.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0129E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SERVER_NOT_CLUSTER_MEMBER_CWSJA0129" varFormat="Java">
    SERVER_NOT_CLUSTER_MEMBER_CWSJA0129=CWSJA0129E: The server &quot;{1}&quot; on node &quot;{0}&quot; is not a member of the cluster &quot;{2}&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The node and server supplied to the command do not correspond to a member of the cluster supplied.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that you used the correct spelling for the node, server and cluster name, and that the server is a member of the cluster.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0119E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="NO_FAILOVER_MEANS_NO_FAILBACK_CWSJA0119" varFormat="Java">
    NO_FAILOVER_MEANS_NO_FAILBACK_CWSJA0119=CWSJA0119E: If a messaging engine can not fail over, it can not fail back.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The failover parameter is set to false, but the failback parameter is set to true.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Either set the failback parameter to false, or set the failover parameter to true.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA1200E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="NO_COMMAND_RESULT_CWSJA1200" varFormat="Java">
    NO_COMMAND_RESULT_CWSJA1200=CWSJA1200E: The {0} command did not return a result.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Internal error. The specified command did not return a result.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Please contact your system administrator to resolve this problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0800E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CONFIG_ARCHIVE_CELL_NOT_FOUND_CWSJA0800" varFormat="Java">
    CONFIG_ARCHIVE_CELL_NOT_FOUND_CWSJA0800=CWSJA0800E: No cells found in configuration archive.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The configuration archive does not contain any cells.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that the configuration archive contains a cell.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0615E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="NODE_VERSION_NOT_VALID_FOR_WMQSERVER_CWSJA0615" varFormat="Java">
    NODE_VERSION_NOT_VALID_FOR_WMQSERVER_CWSJA0615=CWSJA0615E: node parameter specifies a pre version 6.1 node, which is not valid for a WebSphere MQ mediation execution point
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The node parameter specifies a WebSphere Application Server Version 6.0 node. This node cannot host a mediation execution point for a WebSphere MQ mediated destination.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Select a node that is of Version 6.1 or later.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0140E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SERVER_NOT_COMPATABLE_WITH_MEDIATION_SECURITY_CWSJA0140" varFormat="Java">
    SERVER_NOT_COMPATABLE_WITH_MEDIATION_SECURITY_CWSJA0140=CWSJA0140E: The server {0} on node {1} does not support the useServerIdForMediations option configured for bus {2}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The server could not be added to the bus because the bus has been configured to use the server identity for mediations, but the server resides on a pre-7.0 WebSphere Application Server Version node. The useServerIdForMediations is not compatible with pre-Version 7.0 nodes.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Change the bus to use an authentication alias for mediations instead of the server identity.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0051E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="NO_BUS_MEMBER_TARGET_CWSJA0051" varFormat="Java">
    NO_BUS_MEMBER_TARGET_CWSJA0051=CWSJA0051E: No bus member target found for WebSphere MQ server &quot;{0}&quot; on bus &quot;{1}&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    When added to a bus, a WebSphere MQ server should have one bus member target. None was found.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Report this problem to your system administrator.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0039E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="FAILED_TO_GET_RELIABILITY_VALUES_CWSJA0039" varFormat="Java">
    FAILED_TO_GET_RELIABILITY_VALUES_CWSJA0039=CWSJA0039E: Failed to determine values for &quot;reliability&quot; and &quot;maxReliability&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An internal error occurred while trying to determine values for the reliability and maxReliability parameters.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Report this problem to your system administrator.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA1615E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_SECURITY_EXIT_PARAMETERS_SUPPLIED_CWSJA1615" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_SECURITY_EXIT_PARAMETERS_SUPPLIED_CWSJA1615=CWSJA1615E: The &quot;securityExitInit&quot; parameter can only be supplied if the &quot;securityExit&quot; parameter is supplied.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The &quot;securityExitInit&quot; parameter can only be supplied if the &quot;securityExit&quot; parameter is supplied.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Supply the &quot;securityExit&quot; parameter or do not suplly the &quot;securityExitInit&quot; parameter.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0155E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_DESTINATION_PROPERTY_VALUE_CWSJA0155" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_DESTINATION_PROPERTY_VALUE_CWSJA0155=CWSJA0155E: The supplied mediationPoints are not valid for the specified target destination. Each mediation point must be a SIBMediationPoint belonging to the target queue.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Each mediation point must be a SIBMediationPoint belonging to the target queue.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Identify any non valid mediation point(s) and correct the list.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0151E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_DESTINATION_PROPERTY_VALUE_CWSJA0151" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_DESTINATION_PROPERTY_VALUE_CWSJA0151=CWSJA0151E: The supplied queuePoints are not valid for the specified target destination. Each queue point must be a SIBQueueLocalizationPoint belonging to the target queue.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Each queue point must be a SIBQueueLocalizationPoint belonging to the target queue.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Identify any non valid queue point(s) and correct the list.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0104E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ENGINE_NOT_FOUND_FOR_BUS_CWSJA0104" varFormat="Java">
    ENGINE_NOT_FOUND_FOR_BUS_CWSJA0104=CWSJA0104E: No messaging engines found at scope &quot;{0}&quot; for bus &quot;{1}&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The operation could not be invoked because no messaging engines exist at the specified scope for the given bus.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that there is a messaging engine at the specified scope for the given bus.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA2601E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_PARAM_COMBINATION_CWSJA2601" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_PARAM_COMBINATION_CWSJA2601=CWSJA2601E: Incorrect parameter combination supplied : node name = &quot;{0}&quot;, server name = &quot;{1}&quot;, cluster name = &quot;{2}&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The command should specify a specific server or a cluster. To specify a server a valid node name and server name must be provided. To specify a cluster just the cluster name should be provided.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Rerun the command specifying either a node and server name, or a cluster name.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA1400E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="NULL_TEMPLATE_ID_CWSJA1400" varFormat="Java">
    NULL_TEMPLATE_ID_CWSJA1400=CWSJA1400E: Application server template ID is null.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Internal error. The application server template ID is null.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Please contact your system administrator to resolve this problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0611E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MEDIATE_DESTINATION_PARAMETERS_INCORRECT_CWSJA0611" varFormat="Java">
    MEDIATE_DESTINATION_PARAMETERS_INCORRECT_CWSJA0611=CWSJA0611E: When supplying &quot;wmqServer&quot; parameter it must be supplied with either &quot;node&quot; and &quot;server&quot; parameters or &quot;cluster&quot; parameter.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Invalid parameters have been supplied to the command. When specifying the wmqServer parameter, you must specify execution point where the mediation will run.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that the wmqServer parameter is supplied with either the node and server parameters, or the  cluster parameter.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0024E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MULTIPLE_BUSMEMBERS_FOUND_CWSJA0024" varFormat="Java">
    MULTIPLE_BUSMEMBERS_FOUND_CWSJA0024=CWSJA0024E: Multiple bus members found.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Only one instance of a bus member should exist within the scope specified, yet more than one instance has been located.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that bus members have unique configuration data within an administrative domain.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0618E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DEST_NOT_IN_MQ_CWSJA0618" varFormat="Java">
    DEST_NOT_IN_MQ_CWSJA0618=CWSJA0618E: When specifying a value of true for parameter &quot;externallyMediated&quot; the destination being mediated must be assigned to WebSphere MQ.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Externally mediating destinations are only supported for destinations that are localized in WebSphere MQ.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Set the externallyMediated parameter to false, or mediate a destination that is assigned to WebSphere MQ.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0072E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="GLOBAL_SECURITY_DISABLED_CWSJA0072" varFormat="Java">
    GLOBAL_SECURITY_DISABLED_CWSJA0072=CWSJA0072E: Bus security has been specified to be enabled, but administrative security is disabled.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    You cannot set the busSecurity parameter to true unless you also enable administrative security.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Either use the administrative console to enable administrative security, or set the busSecurity parameter to false.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0605E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MEDIATE_DESTINATION_PARAMETERS_INCORRECT_CWSJA0605" varFormat="Java">
    MEDIATE_DESTINATION_PARAMETERS_INCORRECT_CWSJA0605=CWSJA0605E: Supply either &quot;node&quot; and &quot;server&quot; parameters or &quot;cluster&quot; parameter.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Null parameters have been supplied to the command.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that either the node and server parameters, or the cluster parameter, is supplied to the command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0208E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_CREATE_JMSQ_NAME_CWSJA0208" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_CREATE_JMSQ_NAME_CWSJA0208=CWSJA0208E: Not allowed to create a SIB JMS queue called &quot;{0}&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The name provided for the SIB JMS queue does not adhere to naming restrictions.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that the name does not begin with an underscore, and is not empty or null.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0406E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_CREATE_ACT_SPEC_NAME_CWSJA0406" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_CREATE_ACT_SPEC_NAME_CWSJA0406=CWSJA0406E: Not allowed to create a SIB JMS ActivationSpec called &quot;{0}&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The name provided for the SIB JMS ActivationSpec does not adhere to naming restrictions.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that the name does not begin with an underscore, and is not empty or null.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA1603E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MQ_SERVERPROXY_NOT_FOUND_CWSJA1603" varFormat="Java">
    MQ_SERVERPROXY_NOT_FOUND_CWSJA1603=CWSJA1603E: WebSphere MQ Server Proxy &quot;{0}&quot; not found on Bus {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified WebSphere MQ server proxy name could not be located within the bus administrative domain.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that the WebSphere MQ server proxy name specified is a valid name for an existing WebSphere MQ server proxy.  Check that the bus name specified is the correct bus for the WebSphere MQ server proxy.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0417E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_ACT_SPEC_FAILING_MSG_DELAY_VALUE_CWSJA0417" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_ACT_SPEC_FAILING_MSG_DELAY_VALUE_CWSJA0417=CWSJA0417E: The failingMessageDelay value, {0}, is not an valid long value greater than or equal to zero.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Valid values are zero or more, which indicate the period of time in milliseconds that passes before a failing message is retried before its maximum failed delivery limit is reached
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a value of zero or more.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0161E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_DATASOURCE_NAME_CWSJA0161" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_DATASOURCE_NAME_CWSJA0161=CWSJA0161E: The test connection to messaging engine datasource {0} cannot be validated.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Test Connection to given datasource cannot be validated.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that the datasource name is correct and server process at scope of datasource is running.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0604E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DESTINATION_ALREADY_MEDIATED_CWSJA0604" varFormat="Java">
    DESTINATION_ALREADY_MEDIATED_CWSJA0604=CWSJA0604E: Destination &quot;{0}&quot; is already mediated.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The destination specified is already mediated, and a destination cannot be mediated twice.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that the specified destination is not already mediated before trying to mediate it.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0034E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DEST_NOT_FOUND_ON_BUS_CWSJA0034" varFormat="Java">
    DEST_NOT_FOUND_ON_BUS_CWSJA0034=CWSJA0034E: Failed to find destination &quot;{1}&quot; on bus &quot;{0}&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The named destination could not be located on the named bus within the administrative domain.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that the named destination exists on the named bus.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0052E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="TOO_MANY_BUS_MEMBER_TARGETS_CWSJA0052" varFormat="Java">
    TOO_MANY_BUS_MEMBER_TARGETS_CWSJA0052=CWSJA0052E: Too many bus member targets found for WebSphere MQ server &quot;{0}&quot; on bus &quot;{1}&quot;. Number of bus member targets found was {2}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    When added to a bus, a WebSphere MQ server should have one bus member target. More than one was found.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Report this problem to your system administrator.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0126E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SERVER_NOT_FOUND_CWSJA0126" varFormat="Java">
    SERVER_NOT_FOUND_CWSJA0126=CWSJA0126E: The server &quot;{1}&quot; could not be found on node &quot;{0}&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The node and server names that were supplied to the command could not be used to resolve a Server object.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that you used the correct spelling for the node and server names, and that the Server exists in the configuration.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0058E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_MESSAGE_STORE_TYPE_COMBINATION_CWSJA0058" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_MESSAGE_STORE_TYPE_COMBINATION_CWSJA0058=CWSJA0058E: Can not specify both a file store AND a data store, or parameters implying such
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The message store type can be either a file store or a data store, but not both. Therefore parameters relating to both types are not allowed in the same command.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Either remove parameters relating to file store, or to data store.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0005E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="UNABLE_TO_CREATE_BUSMEMBER_CWSJA0005" varFormat="Java">
    UNABLE_TO_CREATE_BUSMEMBER_CWSJA0005=CWSJA0005E: Unable to create bus member &quot;{0}&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An exception was generated attempting to create a bus member with the configuration data provided.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that all configuration data for the bus member is valid.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0041E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="UNRECOGNIZED_PARAM_VALUE_CWSJA0041" varFormat="Java">
    UNRECOGNIZED_PARAM_VALUE_CWSJA0041=CWSJA0041E: Value for parameter &quot;{0}&quot; not recognised.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The value supplied for the specified parameter was not recognized.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Run the command again, supplying a valid value.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0038E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="NO_STEP_PARAM_VALUE_CWSJA0038" varFormat="Java">
    NO_STEP_PARAM_VALUE_CWSJA0038=CWSJA0038E: Required value not supplied for parameter &quot;{2}&quot; of step &quot;{1}&quot; of command &quot;{0}&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Either the specified parameter was not supplied for the specified step, or no value was supplied for it.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Run the command again, supplying the missing parameter value for the specified step.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0141E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CLUSTER_NOT_COMPATABLE_WITH_MEDIATION_SECURITY_CWSJA0141" varFormat="Java">
    CLUSTER_NOT_COMPATABLE_WITH_MEDIATION_SECURITY_CWSJA0141=CWSJA0141E: The cluster {0} does not support the useServerIdForMediations option configured for bus {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The cluster could not be added to the bus because the bus has been configured to use the server identity for mediations, but the cluster contains members that reside on pre-7.0 WebSphere Application Server Version node. The useServerIdForMediations is not compatible with pre-Version 7.0 nodes.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Change the bus to use an authentication alias for mediations instead of the server identity.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA2400E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SIB_LINK_EXCEPTION_CWSJA2400" varFormat="Java">
    SIB_LINK_EXCEPTION_CWSJA2400=CWSJA2400E: An internal error occured getting the &quot;name&quot; attribute of SIBLink &quot;{0}&quot; : &quot;{1}&quot;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An internal error has occurred. See the linked exception for details.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that a valid SIBLink name was specified to the command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0410E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_ACT_SPEC_DEST_TYPE_VALUE_CWSJA0410" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_ACT_SPEC_DEST_TYPE_VALUE_CWSJA0410=CWSJA0410E: {0} is not a valid value for destination type.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A value that is not valid has been entered for the destination type property.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check the documentation for a valid value for this property.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0134E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_MESSAGING_SERVER_CWSJA0134" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_MESSAGING_SERVER_CWSJA0134=CWSJA0134E: Server supplied does not have a SIB Service.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An exception occurred retrieving the SIB Services for the messaging server.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that a SIB Service exists for the messaging server.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0803E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="NO_CELLS_FOUND_CWSJA0803" varFormat="Java">
    NO_CELLS_FOUND_CWSJA0803=CWSJA0803E: Configuration contains no cells.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The configuration does not contain any cells.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that the configuration contains a cell.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0077E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CHAIN_ALREADY_EXISTS_CWSJA0077" varFormat="Java">
    CHAIN_ALREADY_EXISTS_CWSJA0077=CWSJA0077E: The transport chain name {0} already exists as a permitted transport for the bus {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An attempt was made to add a transport chain as a permitted transport to the bus.  This was unsuccessful because the transport chain is already a permitted transport for the bus.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Add a transport chain with a different name.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0106E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SERVER_NOT_COMPATIBLE_WITH_BUS_SECURITY_CWSJA0106" varFormat="Java">
    SERVER_NOT_COMPATIBLE_WITH_BUS_SECURITY_CWSJA0106=CWSJA0106E: Security settings for bus &quot;{0}&quot; are not compatible with server &quot;{1}&quot; because it resides on pre-6.1 node &quot;{2}&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The server could not be added to the bus because the server resides on a WebSphere Application Server Version 6.0 node, and bus security settings are not compatible with pre-Version 6.1 nodes. The permitted transport chains setting must not be LISTED or SSL_ENABLED. The Server group must not be in the bus connector role.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Disable security on the named bus, or modify the bus security settings so that bus security is compatible with pre-Version 6.1 nodes, or upgrade the named server so that it resides on a Version 6.1 node.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA1614E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_RECEIVE_EXIT_PARAMETERS_SUPPLIED_CWSJA1614" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_RECEIVE_EXIT_PARAMETERS_SUPPLIED_CWSJA1614=CWSJA1614E: The &quot;receiveExitInit&quot; parameter can only be supplied if the &quot;receiveExit&quot; parameter is supplied.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The &quot;receiveExitInit&quot; parameter can only be supplied if the &quot;receiveExit&quot; parameter is supplied.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Supply the &quot;receiveExit&quot; parameter or do not suplly the &quot;receiveExitInit&quot; parameter.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA1604E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MULTIPLE_SERVERPROXY_FOUND_CWSJA1604" varFormat="Java">
    MULTIPLE_SERVERPROXY_FOUND_CWSJA1604=CWSJA1604E: Multiple instances of WebSphere MQ Server Proxy &quot;{0}&quot; found on Bus {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Only one instance of a WebSphere MQ server proxy should exist with the name specified, yet more than one instance has been located.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that WebSphere MQ server proxy names are unique within the administrative domain.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA1600E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MQ_SERVER_NOT_FOUND_CWSJA1600" varFormat="Java">
    MQ_SERVER_NOT_FOUND_CWSJA1600=CWSJA1600E: WebSphere MQ Server &quot;{0}&quot; not found.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified WebSphere MQ server name could not be located within the administrative domain.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that the WebSphere MQ server name specified is a valid name for an existing WebSphere MQ server.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0045E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ERROR_VALIDATING_RELIABILITY_CWSJA0045" varFormat="Java">
    ERROR_VALIDATING_RELIABILITY_CWSJA0045=CWSJA0045E: An internal error occurred while validating reliability and maxReliability.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An internal error occurred while validating the reliability and maxReliability parameters.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Report this problem to your system administrator.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA2602E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CLUSTER_DOES_NOT_EXIST_CWSJA2602" varFormat="Java">
    CLUSTER_DOES_NOT_EXIST_CWSJA2602=CWSJA2602E: The cluster {0} does not exist.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified cluster does not exist.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Rerun the command specifying the name of a cluster that exists.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA2000E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="FOREIGN_BUS_NOT_FOUND_CWSJA2000" varFormat="Java">
    FOREIGN_BUS_NOT_FOUND_CWSJA2000=CWSJA2000E: The Foreign Bus &quot;{0}&quot; could not be found on Bus &quot;{1}&quot;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A foreign bus name was supplied to the command that could not be resolved on the specified bus.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that the foreign bus supplied to the command exists in the configuration.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0108E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="BAD_BUS_SECURITY_ATTRIBUTE_VALUE_CWSJA0108" varFormat="Java">
    BAD_BUS_SECURITY_ATTRIBUTE_VALUE_CWSJA0108=CWSJA0108E: The value &quot;{1}&quot; for the permitted transport chains bus security attribute is not valid for bus &quot;{0}&quot; because the bus contains at least one pre-6.1 bus member.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Enabling bus security, or changing the named bus security attribute to the indicated value when the bus contains one or more WebSphere Application Server Version 6.0 bus members, is not allowed because the value is not compatible with pre-Version 6.1 bus members. The permitted transport chains setting must not be LISTED or SSL_ENABLED.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Disable security on the named bus, or modify the named security setting to a value that does not conflict with pre-Version 6.1 bus members, or remove all pre-Version 6.1 bus members from the bus.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0030E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="FAILED_TO_FIND_BUS_BY_UUID_CWSJA0030" varFormat="Java">
    FAILED_TO_FIND_BUS_BY_UUID_CWSJA0030=CWSJA0030E: Failed to find Bus with UUID &quot;{0}&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The UUID specified does not belong to a bus in the administrative domain.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that the UUID specified belongs to a valid bus.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA1601E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MULTIPLE_MQ_SERVERS_FOUND_CWSJA1601" varFormat="Java">
    MULTIPLE_MQ_SERVERS_FOUND_CWSJA1601=CWSJA1601E: More than one WebSphere MQ Server named &quot;{0}&quot; found.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Only one instance of a WebSphere MQ server should exist with the name specified, yet more than one instance has been found.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that WebSphere MQ server names are unique within the administrative domain.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0200E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="NO_RESOURCE_ADAPTER_CWSJA0200" varFormat="Java">
    NO_RESOURCE_ADAPTER_CWSJA0200=CWSJA0200E: Failed to get SIB JMS resource adapter at specified scope.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An unsuccessful attempt was made to locate a JMS JCA resource adapter installed at the specified scope.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that a JMS JCA resource adapter exists within the specified scope.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0125E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="BUS_NOT_FOUND_CWSJA0125" varFormat="Java">
    BUS_NOT_FOUND_CWSJA0125=CWSJA0125E: The bus &quot;{0}&quot; could not be found.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The bus name that was supplied to the command could not be resolved to a Bus object.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that you used the correct spelling for the name, and that a Bus with that name exists in the configuration.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0020E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="UNABLE_TO_CREATE_DATASTORE_CWSJA0020" varFormat="Java">
    UNABLE_TO_CREATE_DATASTORE_CWSJA0020=CWSJA0020E: Unable to create data store.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An exception occurred creating a data store with the configuration data provided.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that the configuration data provided to create a data store is valid.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA1617E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ENDPOINT_PORT_NOT_SUPPLIED_CWSJA1617" varFormat="Java">
    ENDPOINT_PORT_NOT_SUPPLIED_CWSJA1617=CWSJA1617E: A port has not been supplied for the WebSphere MQ server endpoint
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A WebSphere MQ server endpoint must have a port.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Set the WebSphere MQ server endpoint port using the &quot;port&quot; parameter.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0166E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ME_RECOVERY_START_CWSJA0166" varFormat="Java">
    ME_RECOVERY_START_CWSJA0166=CWSJA0166E: The Messaging Engine configuration recovery has started for {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Messaging Engine configuration recovery has started.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    The Messaging Engine configuration recovery has started.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0012E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ENGINE_NOT_FOUND_CWSJA0012" varFormat="Java">
    ENGINE_NOT_FOUND_CWSJA0012=CWSJA0012E: The messaging engine &quot;{0}&quot; does not exist at scope &quot;{1}&quot; for bus &quot;{2}&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The operation could not be invoked because the given messaging engine does not exist for the given bus at the specified scope.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that a correct messaging engine name and scope are specified.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA1000E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="NO_DMGR_CELLS_FOUND_CWSJA1000" varFormat="Java">
    NO_DMGR_CELLS_FOUND_CWSJA1000=CWSJA1000E: Deployment manager configuration contains no cells.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    No cells were found in the deployment manager configuration.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that the deployment manager configuration contains a cell definition.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA2403E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SIB_LINK_NOT_FOUND_CWSJA2403" varFormat="Java">
    SIB_LINK_NOT_FOUND_CWSJA2403=CWSJA2403E: The SIBLink &quot;{0}&quot; could not be found on the messaging engine &quot;{1}&quot;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A SIBLink name was supplied to the command that could not be resolved on the messaging engine name supplied.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that both the messaging engine and SIBLink names supplied to the command exist in the configuration.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0062E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="UNEXPECTED_ERROR_CWSJA0062" varFormat="Java">
    UNEXPECTED_ERROR_CWSJA0062=CWSJA0062E: An unexpected error has occurred.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    There is an unexpected problem with the system.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check the log files for information about the problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0086E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_SERVER_CHARS_CWSJA0086" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_SERVER_CHARS_CWSJA0086=CWSJA0086E: The value {0} for the WebSphere MQ queue manager or queue sharing group contains invalid characters.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The WebSphere MQ queue manager or queue sharing group allowable characters range a-z, A-Z, 0-9, ., /, % and _.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Run the command again specifying a valid WebSphere MQ queue manager or queue sharing group value.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0107E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CLUSTER_NOT_COMPATIBLE_WITH_BUS_SECURITY_CWSJA0107" varFormat="Java">
    CLUSTER_NOT_COMPATIBLE_WITH_BUS_SECURITY_CWSJA0107=CWSJA0107E: Security settings for bus &quot;{0}&quot; are not compatible with cluster &quot;{1}&quot; because one or more of its member servers reside on a pre-6.1 node.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The cluster could not be added to the bus because at least one of its member servers resides on a WebSphere Application Server Version 6.0 node, and bus security settings are not compatible with pre-Version 6.1 nodes. The permitted transport chains setting must not be LISTED or SSL_ENABLED. The group Server must not be in the bus connector role.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Disable security on the named bus, or modify the bus security settings so that bus security is compatible with pre-Version 6.1 nodes, or upgrade the pre-Version 6.1 servers on the named cluster so that they reside on Version 6.1 nodes.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0136E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_PARAM_BOOTSTRAP_POLICY_CWSJA0136" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_PARAM_BOOTSTRAP_POLICY_CWSJA0136=CWSJA0136E: bootstrapPolicy setting {0} is not valid. Allowable values MEMBERS_ONLY, SIBSERVICE_ENABLED, MEMBERS_AND_NOMINATED.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The supplied parameter bootstrapPolicy has a value that is not valid, so the command was rejected.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Set the bootstrapPolicy to an allowable value of MEMBERS_ONLY, SIBSERVICE_ENABLED, MEMBERS_AND_NOMINATED.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0143E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="BAD_INITIAL_JVM_HEAP_SIZE_CWSJA0143" varFormat="Java">
    BAD_INITIAL_JVM_HEAP_SIZE_CWSJA0143=CWSJA0143E: The new initial JVM heap size value of {0} MB is not in the acceptible range of {1} MB to {2} MB.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The supplied initial JVM heap size value is not in the acceptable range.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Change the supplied initial JVM heap size value to one that is in the acceptable range.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0076E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="FILESTORE_NOT_VALID_FOR_VERSION_CWSJA0076" varFormat="Java">
    FILESTORE_NOT_VALID_FOR_VERSION_CWSJA0076=CWSJA0076E: filestore parameter is specified for a messaging engine on a pre version 6.1 node
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    You can only use a file store with a messaging engine on a WebSphere Application Server Version 6.1 or later node.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Select a data store, or choose a node that is of Version 6.1 or later.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA2001E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="NEXT_HOP_BUS_REQUIRED_CWSJA2001" varFormat="Java">
    NEXT_HOP_BUS_REQUIRED_CWSJA2001=CWSJA2001E: The parameter nextHopBus must be specified when routingType = Indirect
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    When the routingType parameter is set to Indirect, a valid nextHopBus parameter must be supplied.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that the nextHopBus parameter and value is supplied to the command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA2610E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SERVER_IS_BUS_MEMBER_CWSJA2610" varFormat="Java">
    SERVER_IS_BUS_MEMBER_CWSJA2610=CWSJA2610E: The server {0} on the node {1} is a bus member.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A server cannot be both a bus member and a bootstrap member.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA2203E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MQLINK_EXCEPTION_CWSJA2203" varFormat="Java">
    MQLINK_EXCEPTION_CWSJA2203=CWSJA2203E: An internal error occured getting the &quot;name&quot; attribute of MQLink &quot;{0}&quot; : &quot;{1}&quot;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An internal error has occurred. See linked exception for details.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that a valid MQLink name was specified to the command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA2208E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_MQLINK_TARGET_OBJECT_CWSJA2208" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_MQLINK_TARGET_OBJECT_CWSJA2208=CWSJA2208E: The target object is not a valid SIB MQLink object.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This command requires a valid SIB MQLink object to be passed in as the target object.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that the target object of the command is a SIB MQLink object.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0414E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_ACT_SPEC_FORWARDER_DOES_NOT_MODIFY_PAYLOAD_VALUE_CWSJA0414" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_ACT_SPEC_FORWARDER_DOES_NOT_MODIFY_PAYLOAD_VALUE_CWSJA0414=CWSJA0414E: {0} is not a valid value for the parameter: Forwarder does not modify payload after set.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A value that is not valid has been entered for this property. Valid values are true and false.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that a valid value is entered for the property.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0127E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ME_NOT_FOUND_CWSJA0127" varFormat="Java">
    ME_NOT_FOUND_CWSJA0127=CWSJA0127E: A messaging engine for bus &quot;{0}&quot; could not be found on server &quot;{1}&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The old bus and server names that were supplied to the command could not be used to resolve a messaging engine object.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that you used the correct spelling for the old bus and server names, and that the server is a member of the old bus.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0011E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MISSING_FOREIGN_PARAMETER_CWSJA0011" varFormat="Java">
    MISSING_FOREIGN_PARAMETER_CWSJA0011=CWSJA0011E: &quot;{0}&quot; must be set to create a foreign destination.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An attempt has been made to create an foreign destination without sufficient configuration detail.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that a foreign parameter is specified when creating the foreign destination.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0606E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="BUS_MEMBER_NOT_FOUND_CWSJA0606" varFormat="Java">
    BUS_MEMBER_NOT_FOUND_CWSJA0606=CWSJA0606E: Bus member &quot;{0}&quot; cannot be found.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The bus member specified could not be located in the administrative domain.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that the bus member specified exists before trying to use it.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0101E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="FILESTORE_NOT_VALID_PRE61_CWSJA0101" varFormat="Java">
    FILESTORE_NOT_VALID_PRE61_CWSJA0101=CWSJA0101E: A file store cannot be specified for a server which is not at version 6.1 or later.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The support for a file store is only available on WebSphere Application Server Version 6.1 or later. Either the -fileStore option was specified or another option was set that implied that a file store is to be used.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Run the command again, this time specifying a data store.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0135E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_SCOPE_SPECIFICATION_CWSJA0135" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_SCOPE_SPECIFICATION_CWSJA0135=CWSJA0135E: Scope specification is not valid.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The details specified do not represent a valid scope specification.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that valid node name, server name and cluster name details are used to represent the scope.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0019E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="UNABLE_TO_CREATE_ENGINE_CWSJA0019" varFormat="Java">
    UNABLE_TO_CREATE_ENGINE_CWSJA0019=CWSJA0019E: Unable to create messaging engine.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An exception occurred creating a messaging engine with the configuration data provided.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that the configuration data provided to create a messaging engine is valid.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA1608E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_SSLTYPE_NONE_PARAMETERS_CWSJA1608" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_SSLTYPE_NONE_PARAMETERS_CWSJA1608=CWSJA1608E: The parameters &quot;sslEndpoint&quot;, &quot;sslChain&quot;, &quot;sslCRL&quot;, &quot;sslReset&quot; and &quot;sslPeer&quot; are not valid when the &quot;sslType&quot; parameter is set to &quot;NONE&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The parameters &quot;sslEndpoint&quot;, &quot;sslChain&quot;, &quot;sslCRL&quot;, &quot;sslReset&quot; and &quot;sslPeer&quot; are not valid when the &quot;sslType&quot; parameter is set to &quot;NONE&quot;.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a different sslType or do not use the illegal parameters.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0047E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="REMOVING_REPLY_DESTINATION_CWSJA0047" varFormat="Java">
    REMOVING_REPLY_DESTINATION_CWSJA0047=CWSJA0047E: Can not have a reply destination bus with out a reply destination name.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A reply destination cannot be specified without a reply destination name. The reply destination object will be removed.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If a reply destination is required specify at least the reply destination name.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0160E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ONLY_ONE_SERVER_BUS_MEMBER_ALLOWED_CWSJA0160" varFormat="Java">
    ONLY_ONE_SERVER_BUS_MEMBER_ALLOWED_CWSJA0160=CWSJA0160E: Only one server bus member for each service integration bus can be added as part of the current profile.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Multiple server bus members for each service integration bus are not allowed for base profiles.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Review the proposed service integration bus configuration requirements and either adopt a single server bus member for each service integration bus deployment or use multiple server bus members for each service integration  bus in a non-base profile.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA1620E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ENDPOINT_HOST_NOR_PORT_NOT_SUPPLIED_CWSJA1620" varFormat="Java">
    ENDPOINT_HOST_NOR_PORT_NOT_SUPPLIED_CWSJA1620=CWSJA1620E: Neither a host or port has not been supplied for the WebSphere MQ server endpoint
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    At least one of the endpoint attributes must be modified
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Supply either a host, port or both parameters.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0112E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_ME_ASSISTANCE_PARM_COMBINATION_CWSJA0112" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_ME_ASSISTANCE_PARM_COMBINATION_CWSJA0112=CWSJA0112E: The assistanceEnabled or policyName parameter is missing, when both are required.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    To use messagine engine policy assistance, set the assistanceEnabled parameter to true and specify a policyName parameter.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Either set the assistanceEnabled parameter to true and specify a valid policyName parameter, or do not use messaging engine policy assistance (set the assistanceEnabled parameter to false).
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0159E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="BAD_PARAM_VALUE_CWSJA0159" varFormat="Java">
    BAD_PARAM_VALUE_CWSJA0159=CWSJA0159E: The useAllMediationPoints parameter can only be set false where mediationPoints contains some values
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    It is not valid to clear this option (setting it false) unless mediationPoints contains at least one mediation point
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Either set useAllQueuePoints true, or set mediationPoints to contain at least one mediation point
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0158E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="BAD_PARAM_VALUE_CWSJA0158" varFormat="Java">
    BAD_PARAM_VALUE_CWSJA0158=CWSJA0158E: The useAllQueuePoints parameter can only be set false where queuePoints contains some values
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    It is not valid to clear this option (setting it false) unless queuePoints contains at least one queue point
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Either set useAllQueuePoints true, or set queuePoints to contain at least one queue point
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA2207E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MQLINK_NOT_FOUND_CWSJA2207" varFormat="Java">
    MQLINK_NOT_FOUND_CWSJA2207=CWSJA2207E: The MQLink &quot;{0}&quot; could not be found on the messaging engine &quot;{1}&quot;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An MQLink with the name supplied could not be found on the messaging engine supplied.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that both the messaging engine and MQLink named on the command exist in the configuration.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0082E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_PARAM_COMB_CWSJA0082" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_PARAM_COMB_CWSJA0082=CWSJA0082E: busSecurity parameter specified with the secure parameter for the modifySIBus command.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    You cannot specify the busSecurity parameter with the secure parameter.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Remove either the busSecurity or the secure parameter from the modifySIBus command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0209E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_DELETE_JMSQ_NAME_CWSJA0209" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_DELETE_JMSQ_NAME_CWSJA0209=CWSJA0209E: Not allowed to delete a SIB JMS queue called &quot;{0}&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The name provided for the SIB JMS queue does not adhere to naming restrictions.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that the name does not begin with an underscore, and is not empty or null.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0025E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ENGINE_ALREADY_DEFINED_CWSJA0025" varFormat="Java">
    ENGINE_ALREADY_DEFINED_CWSJA0025=CWSJA0025E: Messaging engine already defined for this bus member.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A messaging engine already exists with the configuration data supplied.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that unique configuration data is specified for the messaging engine that is to be created.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0010E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MISSING_ALIAS_PARAMETER_CWSJA0010" varFormat="Java">
    MISSING_ALIAS_PARAMETER_CWSJA0010=CWSJA0010E: &quot;{0}&quot; must be set to create an alias destination.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An attempt has been made to create an alias destination without sufficient configuration detail.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that an alias parameter is specified when creating the alias destination.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0147E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="BAD_PARAM_VALUE_CWSJA0147" varFormat="Java">
    BAD_PARAM_VALUE_CWSJA0147=CWSJA0147E: The parameter &quot;auditAllowed&quot; is only valid for a destination type which is TopicSpace.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The auditAllowed parameter can only be used when the destination type is TopicSpace.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Remove the parameter specified, then reissue the command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0084E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_PORT_VALUE_CWSJA0084" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_PORT_VALUE_CWSJA0084=CWSJA0084E: The value {0} for parameter port is not a valid value.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Allowable values for the port parameter range between 0 and 65535.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Run the command again specifying a valid port value.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0075E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_PARAM_COMB_CWSJA0075" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_PARAM_COMB_CWSJA0075=CWSJA0075E: permittedChains parameter specified with the secure parameter for the modifySIBus command
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    You cannot specify the permittedChains parameter with the secure parameter.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Use the busSecurity parameter instead of the secure parameter.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0402E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MODIFY_FAILED_CWSJA0402" varFormat="Java">
    MODIFY_FAILED_CWSJA0402=CWSJA0402E: Unable to modify attributes of ActivationSpec {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    It is likely that incorrect or null parameters were passed to the modify command.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that all parameters passed to the modify command are valid.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0085E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_SERVER_LENGTH_CWSJA0085" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_SERVER_LENGTH_CWSJA0085=CWSJA0085E: The value {0} for the WebSphere MQ queue manager or queue sharing group is too long.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The maximum length for a WebSphere MQ queue manager or queue sharing group is 48 characters.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Run the command again specifying a valid WebSphere MQ queue manager or queue sharing group value.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0036E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="NO_PARAM_VALUE_CWSJA0036" varFormat="Java">
    NO_PARAM_VALUE_CWSJA0036=CWSJA0036E: Required value not supplied for parameter &quot;{1}&quot; of command &quot;{0}&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Either the specified parameter was not supplied, or no value was supplied for it.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Run the command again, supplying the missing parameter value.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0206E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_CREATE_JMSCF_NAME_CWSJA0206" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_CREATE_JMSCF_NAME_CWSJA0206=CWSJA0206E: Not allowed to create a SIB JMS connection factory called &quot;{0}&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The name provided for the SIB JMS connection factory does not adhere to naming restrictions.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that the name does not begin with an underscore, and is not empty or null.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA2603E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SERVER_DOES_NOT_EXIST_CWSJA2603" varFormat="Java">
    SERVER_DOES_NOT_EXIST_CWSJA2603=CWSJA2603E: The server {0} on node {1} does not exist.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified server does not exist.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Rerun the command specifying the name of a server and node that exists.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0071E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_PARAM_COMB_CWSJA0071" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_PARAM_COMB_CWSJA0071=CWSJA0071E: secure parameter specified with scriptCompatibility set to 6.1.  Set the scriptCompatibility to 6 when using the secure parameter
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The secure parameter is not compatible with WebSphere Application Server Version 6.1. The secure parameter is only valid for Version 6.0.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Either set the scriptCompatibility to 6, or use the busSecurity parameter with scriptCompatibility set to 6.1.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0070E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_PARAM_COMB_CWSJA0070" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_PARAM_COMB_CWSJA0070=CWSJA0070E: busSecurity parameter specified with scriptCompatibility set to 6.  Set the scriptCompatibility to 6.1 when using the busSecurity parameter
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The busSecurity parameter is not compatible with WebSphere Application Server Version 6.0. The busSecurity parameter is only valid for Version 6.1 and later.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Either set the scriptCompatibility to 6.1, or use the secure parameter with scriptCompatibility set to 6.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0021E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_CREATE_BUS_NAME_CWSJA0021" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_CREATE_BUS_NAME_CWSJA0021=CWSJA0021E: The bus with name &quot;{0}&quot; contains invalid characters
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Bus names cannot contain any of the following characters \/,#$@:;&quot;*?&lt;&gt;|=+&amp;%&apos; or start with _ or . or contain ]]&gt; .
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that a valid bus name is specified for the bus that is to be created.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0600E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MEDIATION_ALREADY_EXISTS_CWSJA0600" varFormat="Java">
    MEDIATION_ALREADY_EXISTS_CWSJA0600=CWSJA0600E: Mediation &quot;{0}&quot; already exists.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The mediation specified already exists within the administrative domain.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that all mediations are uniquely identified within an administrative domain.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0608E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DESTINATION_NOT_MEDIATED_CWSJA0608" varFormat="Java">
    DESTINATION_NOT_MEDIATED_CWSJA0608=CWSJA0608E: Destination &quot;{0}&quot; is not mediated.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    You cannot un-mediate a destination which is not already mediated.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that the destination is mediated before attempting to un-mediate it.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0124E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CANNOT_CORRECT_POLICY_CWSJA0124" varFormat="Java">
    CANNOT_CORRECT_POLICY_CWSJA0124=CWSJA0124E: The messaging engine is associated with a server cluster that does not have messaging engine policy assistance enabled, or that has messaging engine policy assistance enabled and the CUSTOM policy specified.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    To correct a core group policy for a messaging engine, the server cluster that the messaging engine is associated with must have messaging engine policy assistance enabled and the HA, SCALABILITY, or SCALABILITY_HA policy specified.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Either specify a messaging engine that is associated with a server cluster that has messaging engine policy assistance enabled and a valid policy type specified, or use modifySIBusMemberPolicy to modify the server cluster so that assistanceEnabled is true and policyName is set to a valid policy type.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA2005E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_VIRTUAL_LINK_TYPE_CWSJA2005" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_VIRTUAL_LINK_TYPE_CWSJA2005=CWSJA2005E: The foreign bus &quot;{0}&quot; does not contain a SIBVirtualMQLink child object.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The foreign bus specified contains a SIBVirtualGatewayLink, not the required SIBVirtualMQLink.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that the foreign bus specified has a SIBVirtualMQLink child object.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0122E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_ME_NAME_CWSJA0122" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_ME_NAME_CWSJA0122=CWSJA0122E: The messaging engine {0} is not valid.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    You attempted to create a core group policy for a messaging engine when the messaging engine is not associated with a server cluster that is a member of a bus.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that the name parameter is the name of a messaging engine that is associated with a server cluster that is a member of a bus.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0002E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MULTIPLE_BUSES_FOUND_CWSJA0002" varFormat="Java">
    MULTIPLE_BUSES_FOUND_CWSJA0002=CWSJA0002E: Multiple instances of bus &quot;{0}&quot; found.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Only one instance of a bus should exist with the name specified, yet more than one instance has been located.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that bus names are unique within the administrative domain.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0138E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SERVER_NOT_COMPATIBLE_WITH_BOOTSTRAP_POLICY_CWSJA0138" varFormat="Java">
    SERVER_NOT_COMPATIBLE_WITH_BOOTSTRAP_POLICY_CWSJA0138=CWSJA0138E: The bootstrap policy for bus &quot;{0}&quot; is not compatible with server &quot;{1}&quot; because it resides on pre-7.0 node &quot;{2}&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The server could not be added to the bus because the server resides on a pre-7.0 WebSphere Application Server Version node, and the bootstrap policy setting is not compatible with pre-Version 7.0 nodes. The bootstrap policy setting must not be MEMBERS_ONLY, or MEMBERS_AND_NOMINATED.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Change the bootstrap policy to be SIBSERVICE_ENABLED, or upgrade the named server so that it resides on a Version 7.0 node.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0029E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DUPLICATE_BUS_UUIDS_CWSJA0029" varFormat="Java">
    DUPLICATE_BUS_UUIDS_CWSJA0029=CWSJA0029E: Failed to find bus. More than one bus found with duplicate UUID.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An exception occurred due to multiple buses having identical UUIDs.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that each bus in an administrative domain has a unique UUID.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0026E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_DELETE_DEST_NAME_CWSJA0026" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_DELETE_DEST_NAME_CWSJA0026=CWSJA0026E: Not allowed to delete &quot;{0}&quot; because it is a system destination.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The destination with the name specified cannot be deleted.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that a valid destination name is specified for the destination that is to be deleted.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0105E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ENGINE_NOT_FOUND_WITH_UUID_CWSJA0105" varFormat="Java">
    ENGINE_NOT_FOUND_WITH_UUID_CWSJA0105=CWSJA0105E: The messaging engine with UUID &quot;{0}&quot; does not exist at scope &quot;{1}&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The operation could not be invoked because the messaging engine with the given UUID does not exist at the specified scope.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that there is a messaging engine at the specified scope.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0601E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MEDIATION_NOT_FOUND_CWSJA0601" varFormat="Java">
    MEDIATION_NOT_FOUND_CWSJA0601=CWSJA0601E: Mediation &quot;{0}&quot; cannot be found.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The mediation specified could not be found within the administrative domain.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that the mediation specified to the command exists.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0137E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="BAD_BUS_BOOTSTRAP_POLICY_VALUE_CWSJA0137" varFormat="Java">
    BAD_BUS_BOOTSTRAP_POLICY_VALUE_CWSJA0137=CWSJA0137E: The value &quot;{1}&quot; for the bootstrap member policy bus attribute is not valid for bus &quot;{0}&quot; because the bus contains at least one pre-7.0 bus member.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The bootstrap member policies of MEMBERS_ONLY and MEMBERS_AND_NOMINATED are not supported by pre-7.0 nodes, as a result they cannot be specified for a bus that contains pre-7.0 bus members.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a setting that is supported by a bus with pre-7.0 members, or remove all pre7.0 bus members from the bus.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0031E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="NO_ENGINE_NAMES_AVAILABLE_CWSJA0031" varFormat="Java">
    NO_ENGINE_NAMES_AVAILABLE_CWSJA0031=CWSJA0031E: No messaging engine names available for cluster.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A suitable messaging engine name could not be created.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Try specifying different configuration data when creating the messaging engine.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA2502E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="TARGET_OBJECT_OR_TARGET_PARMS_MISSING_CWSJA2502" varFormat="Java">
    TARGET_OBJECT_OR_TARGET_PARMS_MISSING_CWSJA2502=CWSJA2502E: A target object or target parameters &quot;{0}&quot; must be specified.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An AdminTask command is invoked without specifying either a target object or the parameters that are used to specify the target.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Reissue the command either specifying the target object directly, or specifying the target object using the target parameters.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0064E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MISSING_PARAM_FOR_CLUSTER_CWSJA0064" varFormat="Java">
    MISSING_PARAM_FOR_CLUSTER_CWSJA0064=CWSJA0064E: When creating a {0} on a cluster unable to use default values. The parameter {1} is required
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Certain default parameters do not apply with clusters, therefore valid values must be specified.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check that parameters are correct for this message store type on a cluster.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA2002E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_TYPE_PARAMETER_CWSJA2002" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_TYPE_PARAMETER_CWSJA2002=CWSJA2002E: The type parameter must be specified when routingType parameter = Direct
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    When the routingType parameter = Direct, a valid type parameter must be specified.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that the type parameter for the command is either SIBus or MQ.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0403E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="GET_RA_FAILED_CWSJA0403" varFormat="Java">
    GET_RA_FAILED_CWSJA0403=CWSJA0403E: Unable to find SIB JMS resource adapter in scope {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    It is likely that incorrect or null parameters were passed to the command.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that all parameters are valid, and that a JMS JCA resource adapter is installed at the specified scope.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0098E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_PARAM_COMBINATION_CWSJA0098" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_PARAM_COMBINATION_CWSJA0098=CWSJA0098E: The parameters &quot;aliasBus&quot; and &quot;foreignBus&quot; were supplied to the deleteSIBDestination command.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The deleteSIBDestination command takes either the aliasBus or the foreignBus parameter. The command had both parameters supplied.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If there are multiple destinations with the same name, then the aliasBus or foreignBus parameter can be used to identify either an Alias or a Foreign destination to delete.  Only one of the aliasBus or foreignBus parameters can be supplied.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0042E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="BAD_DESTINATION_NAME_CWSJA0042" varFormat="Java">
    BAD_DESTINATION_NAME_CWSJA0042=CWSJA0042E: Not allowed to create a SIBDestination called &quot;{0}&quot;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The destination name supplied to the createSIBDestination command is not valid.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Run the command again, supplying a valid destination name.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0116E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CANNOT_ENABLE_WITHOUT_POLICY_CWSJA0116" varFormat="Java">
    CANNOT_ENABLE_WITHOUT_POLICY_CWSJA0116=CWSJA0116E: The assistanceEnabled parameter is set to true but the policyName parameter is missing.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    To use messagine engine policy assistance, set the assistanceEnabled parameter to true and specify a valid policyName parameter. Valid policy names are HA, SCALABILITY, SCALABILITY_HA, or CUSTOM.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Either specify a valid policy name, or do not use messaging engine policy assistance (set the assistanceEnabled parameter to false).
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0130E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CLUSTER_ALREADY_BUS_MEMBER_CWSJA0130" varFormat="Java">
    CLUSTER_ALREADY_BUS_MEMBER_CWSJA0130=CWSJA0130E: The cluster &quot;{0}&quot; is already a member of bus &quot;{1}&quot;. Messaging engine migration is not supported in this scenario.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    To migrate a server messaging engine to a cluster, the cluster cannot be a member of the same bus already.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that the cluster is not a member of the same bus to which the server belongs.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0411E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_ACT_SPEC_TARGET_TYPE_VALUE_CWSJA0411" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_ACT_SPEC_TARGET_TYPE_VALUE_CWSJA0411=CWSJA0411E: {0} is not a valid value for target type.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A value that is not valid has been entered for the target type property.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check the documentation for a valid value for this property.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA1619E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ENDPOINT_NOT_SUPPLIED_CWSJA1619" varFormat="Java">
    ENDPOINT_NOT_SUPPLIED_CWSJA1619=CWSJA1619E: A WebSphere MQ server endpoint has not been supplied as the target object
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A WebSphere MQ server endpoint must be supplied as the target object
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Set a WebSphere MQ server endpoint as the target object.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0400E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ALREADY_EXISTS_CWSJA0400" varFormat="Java">
    ALREADY_EXISTS_CWSJA0400=CWSJA0400E: ActivationSpec with given name({0}) or jndiName({1}) already exists in given scope.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The named ActivationSpec already exists on the specified resource adapter.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that ActivationSpec objects are unique within a given scope.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0113E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_ME_POLICY_PARM_COMBINATION_CWSJA0113" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_ME_POLICY_PARM_COMBINATION_CWSJA0113=CWSJA0113E: The failover, failback, preferredServersOnly, or preferredServerList parameters are not valid.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The failover, failback, preferredServersOnly, and preferredServerList parameters are valid only when assistanceEnabled is true and policyName is CUSTOM.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Either set the assistanceEnabled parameter to true and the policyName parameter to CUSTOM, or or do not use these parameters.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0110E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_ME_ASSISTANCE_PARM_USE_CWSJA0110" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_ME_ASSISTANCE_PARM_USE_CWSJA0110=CWSJA0110E: The assistanceEnabled and policyName parameters are not valid when you add a server or WebSphere MQ Server as a bus member.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The assistanceEnabled and policyName parameters are valid only when you add a server cluster as a bus member.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Either do not use the assistanceEnabled and policyName parameters, or add a server cluster as a bus member.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0032E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DUPLICATE_DEST_UUID_CWSJA0032" varFormat="Java">
    DUPLICATE_DEST_UUID_CWSJA0032=CWSJA0032E: Failed to find destination. More than one destination with duplicate UUID.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    More than one destination within the administrative domain has the same UUID.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that each destination within the administrative domain has a unique UUID.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA2401E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="VIRTUAL_LINK_NOT_FOUND_CWSJA2401" varFormat="Java">
    VIRTUAL_LINK_NOT_FOUND_CWSJA2401=CWSJA2401E: A virtual link could not be found on foreign bus &quot;{0}&quot;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The foreign bus specified to the command does not have a  SIBVirtualGatewayLink child object.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that the foreign bus specified has a SIBVirtualGatewayLink child object.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0111E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_ME_ASSISTANCE_POLICY_NAME_CWSJA0111" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_ME_ASSISTANCE_POLICY_NAME_CWSJA0111=CWSJA0111E: The value of policyName {0} is not valid.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Valid policy names are HA, SCALABILITY, SCALABILITY_HA, or CUSTOM.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Either specify a valid policy name, or do not use messaging engine policy assistance (set the assistanceEnabled parameter to false).
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0063E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_PARAM_COMBINATION_CWSJA0063" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_PARAM_COMBINATION_CWSJA0063=CWSJA0063E: Can not specify parameter {0} for message store type {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A file store parameter has been specified for a data store, or a data store parameter has been specified for a file store.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check that the parameters are correct for this message store type.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0215E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="FAILED_TO_CREATE_JMSQUEUE_CWSJA0215" varFormat="Java">
    FAILED_TO_CREATE_JMSQUEUE_CWSJA0215=CWSJA0215E: Failed to create a SIB JMS queue with queue name : &quot;{0}&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An instance of a JMS Queue with the specified queue name could not be created.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that a valid queue name has been specified upon creation of the Queue object.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0415E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_ACT_SPEC_RETRYINTERVAL_VALUE_CWSJA0415" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_ACT_SPEC_RETRYINTERVAL_VALUE_CWSJA0415=CWSJA0415E: {0} is not a valid value for retry interval.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A value that is not valid has been entered for the retry interval property.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check the documentation for a valid value for this property.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0115E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_MODIFY_POLICY_PARMS_CWSJA0115" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_MODIFY_POLICY_PARMS_CWSJA0115=CWSJA0115E: The enableAssistance or policyName parameter is missing.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    To modify messagine engine policy assistance for a cluster, specify either the assistanceEnabled or the policyName parameter.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify the assistanceEnabled parameter, the policyName parameter, or both.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0407E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_DELETE_ACT_SPEC_NAME_CWSJA0407" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_DELETE_ACT_SPEC_NAME_CWSJA0407=CWSJA0407E: Not allowed to delete a SIB JMS ActivationSpec called &quot;{0}&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The name provided for the SIB JMS ActivationSpec does not adhere to naming restrictions.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that the name does not begin with an underscore, and is not empty or null.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0100E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DEST_NOT_FOUND_ON_BUS_CWSJA0100" varFormat="Java">
    DEST_NOT_FOUND_ON_BUS_CWSJA0100=CWSJA0100E: Failed to find destination &quot;{1}&quot; on bus &quot;{0}&quot; with a foreign bus &quot;{2}&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The named foreign destination could not be located on the named bus within the administrative domain.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that the named foreign destination exists on the named bus with the named foreign bus.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA2611E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SERVER_IS_BOOTSTRAP_MEMBER_CWSJA2611" varFormat="Java">
    SERVER_IS_BOOTSTRAP_MEMBER_CWSJA2611=CWSJA2611E: The server {0} on the node {1} is already a bootstrap member.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0162E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CANNOTSTART_MESSAGESTORE_DB_CWSJA0162" varFormat="Java">
    CANNOTSTART_MESSAGESTORE_DB_CWSJA0162=CWSJA0162E: The message store for datasource {0} cannot be started.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The message store cannot start due to some startup exception.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that the datasource value and scope is correct and valid to obtain connection.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA1004E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DMGR_DESTINATION_NOT_SPECIFIED_CWSJA1004" varFormat="Java">
    DMGR_DESTINATION_NOT_SPECIFIED_CWSJA1004=CWSJA1004E: No destination specified.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Internal error. Method invoked requires destination object.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Please contact your system administrator to resolve this problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0040E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="BAD_RELIABILITY_VALUE_CWSJA0040" varFormat="Java">
    BAD_RELIABILITY_VALUE_CWSJA0040=CWSJA0040E: The value supplied for &quot;reliability&quot; is greater than the value supplied for &quot;maxReliability&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The value supplied for the reliability parameter should be less than or equal to the value supplied for the maxReliability parameter.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Run the command again, supplying a value for the reliability parameter that is less than or equal to the value supplied for the maxReliability parameter.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA2202E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_PARAMETER_CWSJA2202" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_PARAMETER_CWSJA2202=CWSJA2202E: The value &quot;{0}&quot; is not valid for the parameter &quot;{1}&quot;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A value that is not valid was supplied for the parameter specified above.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See the command help for a list of valid parameter values.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0009E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DEST_ALREADY_EXISTS_CWSJA0009" varFormat="Java">
    DEST_ALREADY_EXISTS_CWSJA0009=CWSJA0009E: Destination &quot;{0}&quot; already exists.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The destination specified already exists on the bus.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that destinations on the bus have unique names.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0213E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_JMSTOPIC_PROPERTY_VALUE_CWSJA0213" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_JMSTOPIC_PROPERTY_VALUE_CWSJA0213=CWSJA0213E: Not allowed to configure a SIB JMS topic with &quot;{0}&quot; = &quot;{1}&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The value provided for the specified JMS Topic property is not valid.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that the value specified is allowed for the given property.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0081E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="UNABLE_TO_MEDIATE_DEST_CWSJA0081" varFormat="Java">
    UNABLE_TO_MEDIATE_DEST_CWSJA0081=CWSJA0081E: Unable to mediate destination {0} as the WebSphere MQ queue name {1} cannot be used as both the mediation and queue points.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    When mediating a destination that has a message point on WebSphere MQ, the pre-mediation point MQ queue name must not be the same as the message point MQ queue name.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Choose a different WebSphere MQ destination from which the mediation is to get messages.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0128E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CLUSTER_NOT_FOUND_CWSJA0128" varFormat="Java">
    CLUSTER_NOT_FOUND_CWSJA0128=CWSJA0128E: The cluster &quot;{0}&quot; could not be found.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The cluster name that were supplied to the command could not be used to resolve a Cluster object.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that you used the correct spelling for the cluster name, and that the Cluster exists in the configuration.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0016E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="UNABLE_TO_CREATE_DATASOURCE_CWSJA0016" varFormat="Java">
    UNABLE_TO_CREATE_DATASOURCE_CWSJA0016=CWSJA0016E: Unable to create data source.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An exception occurred creating a data source with the configuration data provided.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that the configuration data provided to create a data source is valid.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA1616E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ENDPOINT_HOST_NOT_SUPPLIED_CWSJA1616" varFormat="Java">
    ENDPOINT_HOST_NOT_SUPPLIED_CWSJA1616=CWSJA1616E: A host has not been supplied for the WebSphere MQ server endpoint
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A WebSphere MQ server endpoint must have a host.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Set the WebSphere MQ server endpoint host using the &quot;host&quot; parameter.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0217E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="FAILED_TO_CREATE_JMSCF_CWSJA0217" varFormat="Java">
    FAILED_TO_CREATE_JMSCF_CWSJA0217=CWSJA0217E: An internal error has occurred. Failed to create a SIB JMS connection factory.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This exception is unexpected. The cause is not immediately known.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA2606E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CLUSTER_NOT_SUPPORTING_BOOTSTRAP_MEMBERS_CWSJA2606" varFormat="Java">
    CLUSTER_NOT_SUPPORTING_BOOTSTRAP_MEMBERS_CWSJA2606=CWSJA2606E: The cluster {0} contains servers that do not support bootstrap members. The servers are on the nodes: {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    In order for clusters to be bootstrap members all the servers in the cluster must be on a node whose version is at least 7.0.0.0.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    This can be resolved either by upgrading all the nodes, or by choosing a different cluster.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0210E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_CREATE_JMST_NAME_CWSJA0210" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_CREATE_JMST_NAME_CWSJA0210=CWSJA0210E: Not allowed to create a SIB JMS topic called &quot;{0}&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The name provided for the SIB JMS Topic does not adhere to naming restrictions.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that the name does not begin with an underscore, and is not empty or null.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA2404E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DUPLICATE_NAMESPACE_ENTRY_CWSJA2404" varFormat="Java">
    DUPLICATE_NAMESPACE_ENTRY_CWSJA2404=CWSJA2404E: There is already a SIBLink or MQLink with the name &quot;{0}&quot;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    SIBLink and MQLink objects share a namespace within a messaging engine, and require unique names.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If you want to use the supplied name, ensure that neither an MQLink nor SIBLink already exists with that name. Otherwise, specify a different name.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0207E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_DELETE_JMSCF_NAME_CWSJA0207" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_DELETE_JMSCF_NAME_CWSJA0207=CWSJA0207E: Not allowed to delete a SIB JMS connection factory called &quot;{0}&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The name provided for the SIB JMS connection factory does not adhere to naming restrictions.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that the name does not begin with an underscore, and is not empty or null.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA1605E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="BUILT_IN_PROVIDER_CWSJA1605" varFormat="Java">
    BUILT_IN_PROVIDER_CWSJA1605=CWSJA1605E: The selected JMS provider is built-in and cannot be deleted.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Only custom JMS providers can be deleted.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Select a different JMS provider to delete.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA2407E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_NODE_ME_VERSION_FOR_PREFER_LOCAL_CWSJA2407" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_NODE_ME_VERSION_FOR_PREFER_LOCAL_CWSJA2407=CWSJA2407E: The messaging engine &quot;{0}&quot; is running in a v6.1 or earlier server. The preferLocal attribute can only be set to true when the server running the messaging engine is v7.0.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The preferLocal attribute can only be set to true when the server running the messaging engine is v7.0.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that the messaging engine hosting the link is running on a v7.0 server before setting the preferLocal attribute to true.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0418E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_ACT_SPEC_PARAM_VALUE_COMBINATION_CWSJA0418" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_ACT_SPEC_PARAM_VALUE_COMBINATION_CWSJA0418=CWSJA0418E: The failingMessageDelay value can only be greater than zero if autoStopSequentialMessageFailure is greater than zero.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The message delay is only used when sequential message failures are being monitored and the MDB endpoint can be automatically stopped.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a value of zero for the failingMessageDelay or a positive value for autoStopSequentialMessageFailure.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0017E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="UNABLE_TO_CREATE_RESOURCE_PROPERTYSET_CWSJA0017" varFormat="Java">
    UNABLE_TO_CREATE_RESOURCE_PROPERTYSET_CWSJA0017=CWSJA0017E: Unable to create resource property set.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An exception occurred creating a resource property set with the configuration data provided.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that the configuration data provided to create a resource property set is valid.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0000E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="BUS_ALREADY_EXISTS_CWSJA0000" varFormat="Java">
    BUS_ALREADY_EXISTS_CWSJA0000=CWSJA0000E: Bus &quot;{0}&quot; already exists.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Bus names must be unique within the administrative domain.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a name for this bus that is not already in use within the administrative domain.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA2010E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="FOREIGNBUS_NAME_SAME_AS_LOCAL_BUS_CWSJA2010" varFormat="Java">
    FOREIGNBUS_NAME_SAME_AS_LOCAL_BUS_CWSJA2010=CWSJA2010E: The name of the foreign bus cannot be the same as the local bus name &quot;{0}&quot; on which it is to be created.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    When creating a foreign bus, its name cannot be the same as the local bus on which it is being created. The name should be the unique name of the foreign bus to which you are connecting.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that the name parameter supplied is different to the bus parameter.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA2609E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="NODE_NOT_SUPPORTING_BOOTSTRAP_MEMBERS_CWSJA2609" varFormat="Java">
    NODE_NOT_SUPPORTING_BOOTSTRAP_MEMBERS_CWSJA2609=CWSJA2609E: The node {0} does not support bootstrap members.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    In order for a server to be a bootstrap member the node it is defined to needs to have a version that is at least 7.0.0.0.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    This can be resolved either by upgrading the nodes, or by choosing a server on a different node.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA2405E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_SCOPE_SPECIFICATION_CWSJA2405" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_SCOPE_SPECIFICATION_CWSJA2405=CWSJA2405E: Scope specification is not valid.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The details specified do not represent a valid scope specification.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that valid node name, server name and cluster name details are used to represent the scope.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0401E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CREATE_FAILED_CWSJA0401" varFormat="Java">
    CREATE_FAILED_CWSJA0401=CWSJA0401E: Unable to create SIB JMS ActivationSpec at scope {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The create command ran but no result object was returned.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that the correct configuration information has been passed to the create command being run.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0118E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="NO_FAILOVER_MEANS_PINNED_SERVER_CWSJA0118" varFormat="Java">
    NO_FAILOVER_MEANS_PINNED_SERVER_CWSJA0118=CWSJA0118E: If a messaging engine cannot fail over, it must run on one preferred server.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The failover parameter is set to false but either the preferredServersOnly parameter is set to false or the preferredServerList parameter does not specify one server.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Either ensure that the preferredServersOnly parameter is set to true and the preferredServerList parameter specifies one server, or set the failover parameter to true.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0170E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SUBSCRIPTIONID_MANDATORY_PARAMETER_CWSJA0170" varFormat="Java">
    SUBSCRIPTIONID_MANDATORY_PARAMETER_CWSJA0170=CWSJA0170E: The subscriptionId parameter is mandatory for republishing messages to a destination of type TopicSpace.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The subscriptionId parameter is mandatory for republishing messages to a destination of type TopicSpace.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Add the subscriptionId parameter to the command and rerun the command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0103E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCOPE_NOT_A_BUSMEMBER_CWSJA0103" varFormat="Java">
    SCOPE_NOT_A_BUSMEMBER_CWSJA0103=CWSJA0103E: The specified scope &quot;{0}&quot; is not a member of bus &quot;{1}&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The operation could not be invoked because the specified server or cluster is not a member of the given bus.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that a server or cluster is specified that is a member of the given bus.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0007E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_PARAM_COMBINATION_CWSJA0007" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_PARAM_COMBINATION_CWSJA0007=CWSJA0007E: Incorrect parameter combination supplied : node name = &quot;{0}&quot;, server name = &quot;{1}&quot;, cluster name = &quot;{2}&quot;, WebSphere MQ server name = &quot;{3}&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The parameters supplied do not provide a valid bus member configuration.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    To correctly identify a bus member, specify node name and server name, or cluster name, or WebSphere MQ server name.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA1612E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_SSLTYPE_TYPE_SUPPLIED_CWSJA1612" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_SSLTYPE_TYPE_SUPPLIED_CWSJA1612=CWSJA1612E: The sslType {0} is not valid (valid values are &quot;NONE&quot;, &quot;CENTRAL&quot;, &quot;SPECIFIC&quot; and &quot;CHAIN&quot;).
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Valid values for the sslType parameter are &quot;NONE&quot;, &quot;CENTRAL&quot;, &quot;SPECIFIC&quot; and &quot;CHAIN&quot;.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Set the sslType parameter to be either &quot;NONE&quot;, &quot;CENTRAL&quot;, &quot;SPECIFIC&quot; or &quot;CHAIN&quot;
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA1606E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WMQ_SERVER_NOT_SUPPLIED_CWSJA1606" varFormat="Java">
    WMQ_SERVER_NOT_SUPPLIED_CWSJA1606=CWSJA1606E: A WebSphere MQ server has not been supplied as the target object
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A WebSphere MQ server must be supplied as the target object
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Set a WebSphere MQ server as the target object.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0074E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_PARAM_TRANSPORT_CWSJA0074" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_PARAM_TRANSPORT_CWSJA0074=CWSJA0074E: Invalid permittedChains setting {0}.  Allowable values ALL|SSL_ENABLED|LISTED
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The supplied parameter permittedChains has a value that is not valid, so the command was rejected.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Set the permittedChains to an allowable value of ALL, SSL_ENABLED or LISTED.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0614E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="NO_BUS_MEMBER_CWSJA0614" varFormat="Java">
    NO_BUS_MEMBER_CWSJA0614=CWSJA0614E: No bus member found for WebSphere MQ server {0} on bus {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    When mediating a destination using a WebSphere MQ server it must have been added to the bus, but no bus member was found.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that the WebSphere MQ server has been added to the bus specified then retry the command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0607E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INCONSISTENT_CONFIG_DETECTED_CWSJA0607" varFormat="Java">
    INCONSISTENT_CONFIG_DETECTED_CWSJA0607=CWSJA0607E: Destination &quot;{0}&quot; cannot be mediated.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An inconsistent configuration has been detected.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Run cross document validation to check the destination configuration.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0212E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_JMSQUEUE_PROPERTY_VALUE_CWSJA0212" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_JMSQUEUE_PROPERTY_VALUE_CWSJA0212=CWSJA0212E: Not allowed to configure a SIB JMS queue with &quot;{0}&quot; = &quot;{1}&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The value provided for the specified JMS Queue property is not valid.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that the value specified is allowed for the given property.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0802W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="BUS_ALREADY_EXISTS_ON_DMGR_CWSJA0802" varFormat="Java">
    BUS_ALREADY_EXISTS_ON_DMGR_CWSJA0802=CWSJA0802W: WARNING: Bus &quot;{0}&quot; already exists in the deployment manager configuration. Bus &quot;{0}&quot; will NOT be replaced in the deployment manager configuration.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A bus of the same name already exists in the deployment manager configuration. As a result the bus on this node will not be added to the deployment manager configuration. However the node will still be federated.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that the named bus does not exist in the deployment manager configuration before running the addNode command. If there is a conflict in the names, the bus on the node being federated is not included. As a result the bus on the deployment manager must be configured to have the required resources needed. Either that, or the bus should be renamed or deleted.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0167E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ME_RECOVERY_COMPLETE_CWSJA0167" varFormat="Java">
    ME_RECOVERY_COMPLETE_CWSJA0167=CWSJA0167E: The Messaging Engine configuration recovery for {0} is complete.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Messaging Engine configuration recovery is complete.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    The Messaging Engine configuration recovery is complete.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA2500E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CONFIG_SERVICE_NOT_AVAILABLE_CWSJA2500" varFormat="Java">
    CONFIG_SERVICE_NOT_AVAILABLE_CWSJA2500=CWSJA2500E: The configuration service is not available.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An AdminTask command is trying to work with a process that is not connected to a server that has a running configuration service.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Reissue the command on a process that is connected to a server that has a running configuration service. For example a deployment manager, managed server or unmanaged server.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0057E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="BAD_PARAM_COMBINATION_CWSJA0057" varFormat="Java">
    BAD_PARAM_COMBINATION_CWSJA0057=CWSJA0057E: The WebSphere MQ queue name parameter must be specified for a destination on a WebSphere MQ Server
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    When creating a destination on a WebSphere MQ server the wmqQueueName parameter must be specified.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Change the destination type to be QUEUE then retry the command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0056E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="BAD_PARAM_COMBINATION_CWSJA0056" varFormat="Java">
    BAD_PARAM_COMBINATION_CWSJA0056=CWSJA0056E: The WebSphere MQ Server name parameter can only be specified with a destination type of QUEUE, the type specified was &quot;{0}&quot;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    When creating a destination the WebSphere MQ server name was specified with a destination type other than QUEUE.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Change the destination type to be QUEUE then retry the command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0055E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="BAD_PARAM_COMBINATION_CWSJA0055" varFormat="Java">
    BAD_PARAM_COMBINATION_CWSJA0055=CWSJA0055E: The parameter {0} with value {1} is not valid when specifying a WebSphere MQ Server name.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The supplied parameter is not valid when creating a destination. The parameter supplied is only valid when not specifying a WebSphere MQ server name.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Remove the parameter from the createSIBDestination command then retry the command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0054E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="BAD_PARAM_COMBINATION_CWSJA0054" varFormat="Java">
    BAD_PARAM_COMBINATION_CWSJA0054=CWSJA0054E: The parameter {0} with value {1} is only valid when specifying a WebSphere MQ Server name.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The supplied parameter is not valid when creating a destination.  The parameter supplied is only valid when specifying a WebSphere MQ server name.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Remove the parameter from the createSIBDestination command then retry the command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA1001E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="NO_DMGR_SESSION_SUPPLIED_CWSJA1001" varFormat="Java">
    NO_DMGR_SESSION_SUPPLIED_CWSJA1001=CWSJA1001E: No deployment manager configuration session supplied.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Internal error. Method invoked requires a deployment manager configuration session parameter.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Please contact your system administrator to resolve this problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0053E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="BAD_PARAM_COMBINATION_CWSJA0053" varFormat="Java">
    BAD_PARAM_COMBINATION_CWSJA0053=CWSJA0053E: The parameter {0} is only valid when specifying a WebSphere MQ Server name.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The supplied parameter is not valid when adding a server or a cluster to a bus.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Remove the parameter from the addSIBusMember command then retry the command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0096E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_REPLYTOQUEUE_LENGTH_CWSJA0096" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_REPLYTOQUEUE_LENGTH_CWSJA0096=CWSJA0096E: The value {0} for the WebSphere MQ reply to queue is too long.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The maximum length for a WebSphere MQ reply to queue is 48 characters.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Run the command again specifying an allowable WebSphere MQ reply to queue value.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0050E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="UNABLE_TO_CREATE_MQ_SERVER_PROXY_CWSJA0050" varFormat="Java">
    UNABLE_TO_CREATE_MQ_SERVER_PROXY_CWSJA0050=CWSJA0050E: Unable to create WebSphere MQ Server Bus Member.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An exception occurred creating a WebSphere MQ server bus member with the configuration data provided.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that the configuration data provided to create a WebSphere MQ server bus member is valid.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA1609E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_SSLTYPE_CENTRAL_PARAMETERS_CWSJA1609" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_SSLTYPE_CENTRAL_PARAMETERS_CWSJA1609=CWSJA1609E: The parameters &quot;sslEndpoint&quot; and &quot;sslChain&quot; are not valid when the &quot;sslType&quot; parameter is set to &quot;CENTRAL&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The parameters &quot;sslEndpoint&quot; and &quot;sslChain&quot; are not valid when the &quot;sslType&quot; parameter is set to &quot;CENTRAL&quot;.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a different sslType or do not use the illegal parameters.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0201E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="BAD_TYPE_CWSJA0201" varFormat="Java">
    BAD_TYPE_CWSJA0201=CWSJA0201E: Incorrect value for type parameter: {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An incorrect type has been found for the connection factory.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that the connection factory type is either Queue, Topic or All.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0018E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_BUS_MEMBER_CWSJA0018" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_BUS_MEMBER_CWSJA0018=CWSJA0018E: Bus member supplied is not a member of the specified bus.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified bus member is not a member of this bus.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that the specified bus member is a member of this bus.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0044E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="BAD_PARAM_COMBINATION_CWSJA0044" varFormat="Java">
    BAD_PARAM_COMBINATION_CWSJA0044=CWSJA0044E: Node, server, WebSphere MQ Server and/or cluster supplied when type is &quot;WebServices&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The node, server and cluster parameters should not be specified when the type is WebServices.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Run the command again, supplying a valid combination of parameters.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0114E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_CLUSTER_MEMBER_CWSJA0114" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_CLUSTER_MEMBER_CWSJA0114=CWSJA0114E: Server {1} on node {0} is not a member of cluster {2}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    You specified a server in the preferred servers list when that server is not a member of the current cluster.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that the servers specified for the preferredServerList parameter are members of the current cluster.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0088E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_CHANNEL_CHARS_CWSJA0088" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_CHANNEL_CHARS_CWSJA0088=CWSJA0088E: The value {0} for the WebSphere MQ channel contains invalid characters.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The WebSphere MQ queue channel allowable characters range a-z, A-Z, 0-9, ., /, % and _.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Run the command again specifying a valid WebSphere MQ channel value.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0003E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="BUS_MEMBER_ALREADY_EXISTS_CWSJA0003" varFormat="Java">
    BUS_MEMBER_ALREADY_EXISTS_CWSJA0003=CWSJA0003E: Bus member &quot;{0}&quot; already exists.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An attempt has been made to add a server to a bus of which it is already a member.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Do not attempt to add a bus member if the server in question is already a member.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0603E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DESTINATION_NOT_FOUND_CWSJA0603" varFormat="Java">
    DESTINATION_NOT_FOUND_CWSJA0603=CWSJA0603E: Destination &quot;{0}&quot; cannot be found.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The destination specified could not be found within the administrative domain.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that the specified destination exists.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA1613E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_SEND_EXIT_PARAMETERS_SUPPLIED_CWSJA1613" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_SEND_EXIT_PARAMETERS_SUPPLIED_CWSJA1613=CWSJA1613E: The &quot;sendExitInit&quot; parameter can only be supplied if the &quot;sendExit&quot; parameter is supplied.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The &quot;sendExitInit&quot; parameter can only be supplied if the &quot;sendExit&quot; parameter is supplied.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Supply the &quot;sendExit&quot; parameter or do not suplly the &quot;sendExitInit&quot; parameter.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0157E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_TARGET_DEST_LP_CWSJA0157" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_TARGET_DEST_LP_CWSJA0157=CWSJA0157E: The target destination for an Alias destination must not be localized on an MQ Server.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    It is not valid to supply a target destination for an Alias destination that is localized on an MQ Server.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Supply a target destination that is not localized on an MQ Server.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA2006E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_DEFAULT_PRIORITY_CWSJA2006" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_DEFAULT_PRIORITY_CWSJA2006=CWSJA2006E: The default priority specified &quot;{0}&quot; is not a valid value for this attribute.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The value of the default priority attribute must be between 0 and 9 inclusive.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that a valid value is specified for the default priority attribute.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0102E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MSG_ORDER_NOT_VALID_PRE61_CWSJA0102" varFormat="Java">
    MSG_ORDER_NOT_VALID_PRE61_CWSJA0102=CWSJA0102E: The maintainStrictMessageOrder option cannot be used for a destination that has all its message points on servers of a version less than 6.1.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The option to maintain strict message order is only available on WebSphere Application Server Version 6.1 or later.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Run the command again. Only specify strict message ordering if you also specify a server of Version 6.1 or later.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0117E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CANNOT_DISABLE_WITH_POLICY_CWSJA0117" varFormat="Java">
    CANNOT_DISABLE_WITH_POLICY_CWSJA0117=CWSJA0117E: A policyName parameter is specified when the assistanceEnabled parameter is set to false.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    To disable messaging engine policy assistance, set the assistanceEnabled parameter to false and do not specify a  policyName parameter.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Either set the assistanceEnabled parameter to false and do not specify a policyName parameter, or set the assistanceEnabled parameter to true and specify a valid policyName parameter.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0205E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="BAD_TARGET_CWSJA0205" varFormat="Java">
    BAD_TARGET_CWSJA0205=CWSJA0205E: Target object is not a SIB JMS topic.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The interface of the target object is not of type Topic.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that the target object is of type Topic.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0204E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="BAD_TARGET_CWSJA0204" varFormat="Java">
    BAD_TARGET_CWSJA0204=CWSJA0204E: Target object is not a SIB JMS queue.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The interface of the target object is not of type Queue.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that the target object is of type Queue.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0203E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="BAD_TARGET_CWSJA0203" varFormat="Java">
    BAD_TARGET_CWSJA0203=CWSJA0203E: Target object is not a SIB JMS connection factory.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The target object specified is not of type QueueConnectionFactory, TopicConnectionFactory or ConnectionFactory.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that a valid connection factory interface is specified to the target object.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0142E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="USE_SERVER_IDENTITY_FOR_MEDIATIONS_NOT_SUPPORTED_CWSJA0142" varFormat="Java">
    USE_SERVER_IDENTITY_FOR_MEDIATIONS_NOT_SUPPORTED_CWSJA0142=CWSJA0142E: The bus {0} could not be modified to use the server identity for mediations as it contains members that reside on pre-Version 7.0 nodes.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The bus contains servers or clusters that run on pre-Version 7.0 nodes. The userServerIdForMediations option does not support pre-Version 7.0 nodes so the command could not complete.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Upgrade the pre-Version 7.0 nodes.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA1602E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MQ_SERVER_NAME_NOT_UNIQUE_CWSJA1602" varFormat="Java">
    MQ_SERVER_NAME_NOT_UNIQUE_CWSJA1602=CWSJA1602E: A WebSphere MQ Server named &quot;{0}&quot; already exists.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A WebSphere MQ server name must be unique. A WebSphere MQ server with the supplied name already exists.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that WebSphere MQ server names are unique within the administrative domain.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0023E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="BUSMEMBER_NOT_FOUND_CWSJA0023" varFormat="Java">
    BUSMEMBER_NOT_FOUND_CWSJA0023=CWSJA0023E: Bus member not found.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The bus member specified could not be located within the administrative domain.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that a valid bus member is being located.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0033E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_MESSAGING_SERVER_CWSJA0033" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_MESSAGING_SERVER_CWSJA0033=CWSJA0033E: Server supplied does not have a SIB service.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    No SIB services were found for this messaging server.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that a SIB service exists for this messaging server.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0087E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_CHANNEL_LENGTH_CWSJA0087" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_CHANNEL_LENGTH_CWSJA0087=CWSJA0087E: The value {0} for the WebSphere MQ channel is too long.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The maximum length for a WebSphere MQ channel is 20 characters.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Run the command again specifying a valid WebSphere MQ channel value.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0405E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="NOT_SIB_JMS_ACT_SPEC_CWSJA0405" varFormat="Java">
    NOT_SIB_JMS_ACT_SPEC_CWSJA0405=CWSJA0405E: {0} is not a valid SIB JMS ActivationSpec.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The target object specified is not of the correct type.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that the target object is of type JMS ActivationSpec.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0090E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_SCOPE_SPECIFICATION_CWSJA0090" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_SCOPE_SPECIFICATION_CWSJA0090=CWSJA0090E: Scope specification is not valid, unable to locate cluster {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The details specified do not represent a valid scope specification.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that valid cluster name details are used to represent the scope.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0022E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_DELETE_BUS_NAME_CWSJA0022" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_DELETE_BUS_NAME_CWSJA0022=CWSJA0022E: Not allowed to delete a bus called &quot;{0}&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An exception has occurred attempting to delete a bus with the name specified.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that a valid bus name is specified for the bus that is to be deleted.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0078E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CHAIN_NOT_FOUND_CWSJA0078" varFormat="Java">
    CHAIN_NOT_FOUND_CWSJA0078=CWSJA0078E: The transport chain name {0} was not found as a permitted transport for the bus {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An attempt was made to remove a permitted transport from a bus. However the specified permitted transport chain is not a permitted transport for the specified bus.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the permitted transport exists on the bus, check and correct the name then reissue the command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0073E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CHAIN_NOT_FOUND_CWSJA0073" varFormat="Java">
    CHAIN_NOT_FOUND_CWSJA0073=CWSJA0073E: The permitted transport chain name {0} was not found
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The permitted transport chain with the specified name was not found on the bus.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Use the administrative console to check that the transport chain name exists and that the case of the name is correct, then reissue the command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA2200E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="BUS_NOT_FOUND_CWSJA2200" varFormat="Java">
    BUS_NOT_FOUND_CWSJA2200=CWSJA2200E: The bus name &quot;{0}&quot; could not be found.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The bus name that was supplied to the command could not be resolved to a Bus object.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that you used the correct spelling for the name, and that a Bus with that name exists in the configuration.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0006E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="UNSUPPORTED_TYPE_CWSJA0006" varFormat="Java">
    UNSUPPORTED_TYPE_CWSJA0006=CWSJA0006E: Destination type &quot;{0}&quot; is not supported by this command.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An incorrect destination type has been specified.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that the destination type specified is valid.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0609E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_CREATE_MEDIATION_NAME_CWSJA0609" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_CREATE_MEDIATION_NAME_CWSJA0609=CWSJA0609E: Not allowed to create a mediation called &quot;{0}&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The name provided for the mediation does not adhere to naming restrictions.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that the name does not begin with an underscore, and is not empty or null.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA1607E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SVRCONN_CHANNEL_NAME_NOT_SUPPLIED_CWSJA1607" varFormat="Java">
    SVRCONN_CHANNEL_NAME_NOT_SUPPLIED_CWSJA1607=CWSJA1607E: A name has not been supplied for the WebSphere MQ server SVRCONN channel
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A WebSphere MQ server SVRCONN channel must have a name.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Set the WebSphere MQ server SVRCONN channel name using the &quot;name&quot; parameter.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0089E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_SCOPE_SPECIFICATION_CWSJA0089" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_SCOPE_SPECIFICATION_CWSJA0089=CWSJA0089E: Scope specification is not valid, unable to locate node {0} and or server {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The details specified do not represent a valid scope specification.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that valid node and server name details are used to represent the scope.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0413E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_ACT_SPEC_CONSUMER_DOES_NOT_MODIFY_PAYLOAD_VALUE_CWSJA0413" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_ACT_SPEC_CONSUMER_DOES_NOT_MODIFY_PAYLOAD_VALUE_CWSJA0413=CWSJA0413E: {0} is not a valid value for the parameter: Consumer does not modify payload after get.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A value that is not valid has been entered for this property. Valid values are GuaranteedByUser and NotGuaranteedByUser.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that a valid value is entered for the property.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0146E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INITIAL_JVM_HEAP_SIZE_BIGGER_THAN_MAX_JVM_HEAP_SIZE_CWSJA0146" varFormat="Java">
    INITIAL_JVM_HEAP_SIZE_BIGGER_THAN_MAX_JVM_HEAP_SIZE_CWSJA0146=CWSJA0146E: The new initial JVM heap size value of {0} is bigger than the new maximum JVM heap size value of {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The supplied initial JVM heap size value is bigger than the supplied maximum JVM heap size value.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Change the supplied initial and maximum JVM heap size values so that the initial JVM heap size value is not be bigger than the maximum JVM heap size value.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0015E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SIB_JDBCPROVIDER_NOT_FOUND_CWSJA0015" varFormat="Java">
    SIB_JDBCPROVIDER_NOT_FOUND_CWSJA0015=CWSJA0015E: SIB JDBC provider not found.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An attempt has been made to locate a SIB JDBC provider within the scope provider, but none was found.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that there is a SIB JDBC provider available within the administrative domain.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA2408E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SIBLINK_FOREIGN_BUS_ALREADY_USED_CWSJA2408" varFormat="Java">
    SIBLINK_FOREIGN_BUS_ALREADY_USED_CWSJA2408=CWSJA2408E: The foreign bus &quot;{0}&quot; is already in use by another SIBLink.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The foreign bus specified already contains a reference to a SIBLink.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that a foreign bus is specified that doesn&apos;t reference a pre-existing SIBLink.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA1611E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_SSLTYPE_CHAIN_PARAMETERS_CWSJA1611" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_SSLTYPE_CHAIN_PARAMETERS_CWSJA1611=CWSJA1611E: The &quot;sslChain&quot; parameter is not valid when the &quot;sslType&quot; parameter is set to &quot;CHAIN&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The &quot;sslChain&quot; parameter is not valid when the &quot;sslType&quot; parameter is set to &quot;CHAIN&quot;.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a different sslType or do not use the illegal parameters.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0409E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_ACT_SPEC_READAHEAD_VALUE_CWSJA0409" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_ACT_SPEC_READAHEAD_VALUE_CWSJA0409=CWSJA0409E: {0} is not a valid value for read ahead.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A value that is not valid has been entered for the read ahead property.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check the documentation for a valid value for this property.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA2007E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="BAD_RELIABILITY_VALUE_CWSJA2007" varFormat="Java">
    BAD_RELIABILITY_VALUE_CWSJA2007=CWSJA2007E: The value supplied for &quot;reliability&quot; is greater than the value supplied for &quot;maxReliability&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The value supplied for the reliability parameter should be less than or equal to the value supplied for the maxReliability parameter.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Report this problem to your system administrator.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0004E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ENGINE_EXISTS_CWSJA0004" varFormat="Java">
    ENGINE_EXISTS_CWSJA0004=CWSJA0004E: Messaging engine &quot;{0}&quot; already exists.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The messaging engine specified already exists on the server.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that the messaging engine details are not identical to that of another messaging engine on the server.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0132E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="NO_ENGINE_NAMES_AVAILABLE_CWSJA0132" varFormat="Java">
    NO_ENGINE_NAMES_AVAILABLE_CWSJA0132=CWSJA0132E: No messaging engine names available for cluster.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A suitable messaging engine name could not be created.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Try specifying different configuration data when creating the messaging engine.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0169E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="GENERIC_EXCEPTION_OCCURED_CWSJA0169" varFormat="Java">
    GENERIC_EXCEPTION_OCCURED_CWSJA0169=CWSJA0169E: The JMS_IBM_ExceptionProblemDestination or JMS_IBM_ExceptionTimestamp parameters are not allowed in the selection criteria.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The JMS_IBM_ExceptionProblemDestination or JMS_IBM_ExceptionTimestamp parameters are reserved for internal use when running the command.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that you are not using the JMS_IBM_ExceptionProblemDestination or JMS_IBM_ExceptionTimestamp parameters in the selection criteria. Modify the selection criteria and rerun the command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0168E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="GENERIC_EXCEPTION_OCCURED_CWSJA0168" varFormat="Java">
    GENERIC_EXCEPTION_OCCURED_CWSJA0168=CWSJA0168E: A generic exception occurred while processing the command parameters.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Unable to query the MBeans objects.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check if the session is connected successfully using the specified connection parameters.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA2607E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CLUSTER_IS_BUS_MEMBER_CWSJA2607" varFormat="Java">
    CLUSTER_IS_BUS_MEMBER_CWSJA2607=CWSJA2607E: The cluster {0} is a bus member.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A cluster cannot be both a bus member and a bootstrap member.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA2009E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_PARAM_COMBINATION_CWSJA2009" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_PARAM_COMBINATION_CWSJA2009=CWSJA2009E: The routingType parameter is required if the type parameter is supplied.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The type parameter is only permitted if the routingType parameter is also supplied.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that the routingType parameter is supplied if the type parameter is supplied.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0013E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MULTIPLE_ENGINES_FOUND_CWSJA0013" varFormat="Java">
    MULTIPLE_ENGINES_FOUND_CWSJA0013=CWSJA0013E: Multiple messaging engines were found.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Multiple messaging engines have been found matching the configuration data provided.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that messaging engines are unique within the administrative domain.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA2501E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="TARGET_OBJECT_AND_TARGET_PARMS_SPECIFIED_CWSJA2501" varFormat="Java">
    TARGET_OBJECT_AND_TARGET_PARMS_SPECIFIED_CWSJA2501=CWSJA2501E: Target object and target parameters &quot;{0}&quot; can not be both specified.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An AdminTask command is specifying both a target object and one of the parameters that is used to specify the target.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Reissue the command either specifying the target object directly, or specifying the target object using the target parameters.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA1621E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SVRCONN_CHANNEL_NOT_SUPPLIED_CWSJA1621" varFormat="Java">
    SVRCONN_CHANNEL_NOT_SUPPLIED_CWSJA1621=CWSJA1621E: A WebSphere MQ server server connection channel has not been supplied as the target object
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A WebSphere MQ server server connection channel must be supplied as the target object
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Set a WebSphere MQ server server connection channel as the target object.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0120E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="FAILOVER_ON_PREF_SERVER_ONLY_ERROR_CWSJA0120" varFormat="Java">
    FAILOVER_ON_PREF_SERVER_ONLY_ERROR_CWSJA0120=CWSJA0120E: If a messaging engine can fail over to preferred servers only, there must be at least two servers in the preferred servers list.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The failover parameter is set to true and the preferredServersOnly parameter is set to true, but the the preferredServerList parameter does not specify at least two servers (one to run on, and one to fail over to).
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Either ensure that the preferredServerList parameter specifies at least two servers, or set the preferredServersOnly parameter to false.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA2608E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CLUSTER_IS_BOOTSTRAP_MEMBER_CWSJA2608" varFormat="Java">
    CLUSTER_IS_BOOTSTRAP_MEMBER_CWSJA2608=CWSJA2608E: The cluster {0} is already a bootstrap member.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0416E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_ACT_SPEC_AUTO_STOP_SEQ_MSG_FAILURE_VALUE_CWSJA0416" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_ACT_SPEC_AUTO_STOP_SEQ_MSG_FAILURE_VALUE_CWSJA0416=CWSJA0416E: The autoStopSequentialMessageFailure value, {0}, is not an valid integer value greater than or equal to zero.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Valid values are zero which indicates that MDB endpoints will not be automatically stopped. Or one or more, which indicates the number of failing sequential messages that will cause the MDB endpoint to be stopped.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a value of zero or more.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA2008E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_TYPE_VALUE_CWSJA2008" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_TYPE_VALUE_CWSJA2008=CWSJA2008E: An invalid type parameter was supplied to this command, allowable values are &quot;MQ&quot; or &quot;SIBus&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The type of either MQ or SIBus is required for this command.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that the type parameter for the command is either MQ or SIBus.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA2605E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SERVER_NOT_A_BOOTSTRAP_MEMBER_CWSJA2605" varFormat="Java">
    SERVER_NOT_A_BOOTSTRAP_MEMBER_CWSJA2605=CWSJA2605E: The server {0} on node {1} is not a bootstrap member.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified server is not a bootstrap member, so cannot be removed from the list of bootstrap members.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Rerun the command specifying the name of a server and node that is a bootstrap member.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0211E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_DELETE_JMST_NAME_CWSJA0211" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_DELETE_JMST_NAME_CWSJA0211=CWSJA0211E: Not allowed to delete a SIB JMS topic called &quot;{0}&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The name provided for the SIB JMS topic does not adhere to naming restrictions.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that the name does not begin with an underscore, and is not empty or null.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0602E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MEDIATION_IN_USE_CWSJA0602" varFormat="Java">
    MEDIATION_IN_USE_CWSJA0602=CWSJA0602E: Mediation &quot;{0}&quot; cannot be deleted. It is being used to mediate destination &quot;{1}&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A mediation cannot be deleted whilst it is being used to mediate a destination.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that a mediation is not being used before trying to delete it.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA2201E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ME_NOT_FOUND_CWSJA2201" varFormat="Java">
    ME_NOT_FOUND_CWSJA2201=CWSJA2201E: The messaging engine &quot;{0}&quot; could not be found on the bus supplied.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A messaging engine name was supplied to the command that could not be resolved on the bus name supplied.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that both the messaging engine and bus name supplied to the command exist in the configuration.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0001E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="BUS_NOT_FOUND_CWSJA0001" varFormat="Java">
    BUS_NOT_FOUND_CWSJA0001=CWSJA0001E: Bus &quot;{0}&quot; not found.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified bus name could not be located within the administrative domain.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that the bus name specified is a valid bus name for an existing bus.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0092E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_FILESTORE_SIZE_CWSJA0092" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_FILESTORE_SIZE_CWSJA0092=CWSJA0092E: Can not specify maximum temporary file store size if unlimited temporary store size is set to true.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    When the size of the temporary file store has been set to unlimited, a maximum temporary size cannot be set.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Remove the maximum temporary file store size parameter or change the unlimited temporary file store size to false then retry.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA1618E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ENDPOINT_PORT_NOT_VALID_CWSJA1618" varFormat="Java">
    ENDPOINT_PORT_NOT_VALID_CWSJA1618=CWSJA1618E: A valid value must be supplied for the endpoint port.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A valid value must be supplied for the endpoint port.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Set the WebSphere MQ server endpoint with a valid port number.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0145E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DEST_ALREADY_SPECIFIED_CWSJA0145" varFormat="Java">
    DEST_ALREADY_SPECIFIED_CWSJA0145=CWSJA0145E: Duplicate destination &quot;{0}&quot; in nameList.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The given destination is specified more than once in the nameList.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that the destinations specified in the nameList are unique.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA2604E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CLUSTER_NOT_A_BOOTSTRAP_MEMBER_CWSJA2604" varFormat="Java">
    CLUSTER_NOT_A_BOOTSTRAP_MEMBER_CWSJA2604=CWSJA2604E: The cluster {0} is not a bootstrap member.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified cluster is not a bootstrap member, so cannot be removed from the list of bootstrap members.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Rerun the command specifying the name of a cluster that is a bootstrap member.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0091E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="BAD_PARAM_VALUE_CWSJA0091" varFormat="Java">
    BAD_PARAM_VALUE_CWSJA0091=CWSJA0091E: The parameter &quot;topicAccessCheckRequired&quot; is only valid for a destination type which is TopicSpace.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The topicAccessCheckRequired parameter can only be used when the destination type is TopicSpace.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Remove the parameter specified, then reissue the command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA2402E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_VIRTUAL_LINK_TYPE_CWSJA2402" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_VIRTUAL_LINK_TYPE_CWSJA2402=CWSJA2402E: The foreign bus &quot;{0}&quot; does not contain a SIBVirtualGatewayLink child object.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The foreign bus specified contains a SIBVirtualMQLink, not the required SIBVirtualGatewayLink.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that the foreign bus specified has a SIBVirtualGatewayLink child object.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0171E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SUBSCRIPTIONID_NOT_FOUND_CWSJA0171" varFormat="Java">
    SUBSCRIPTIONID_NOT_FOUND_CWSJA0171=CWSJA0171E: The subscriptionId {0} provided in the command is currently not active on any of the publication points of the topic space {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    SubscriptionId is a mandatory parameter for republishing messages to a destination of type TopicSpace. The subscriptionId provided in the command is not found to be active on any of the publication points of the topic space.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that a valid subscription Id that is active is provided as an input to the command and rerun the command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0080E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DEST_NOT_FOUND_CWSJA0080" varFormat="Java">
    DEST_NOT_FOUND_CWSJA0080=CWSJA0080E: Destination {0} not found on bus {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified destination could not be found on the specified bus.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that the destination being located exists within the administrative domain.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0065E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MISSING_PARAM_CWSJA0065" varFormat="Java">
    MISSING_PARAM_CWSJA0065=CWSJA0065E: Can not create a {0} without a value for {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A value for the specified parameter is required to create a message store of this type.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check that the parameters are correct for this message store type.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0083E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="BAD_PARAM_VALUE_CWSJA0083" varFormat="Java">
    BAD_PARAM_VALUE_CWSJA0083=CWSJA0083E: The parameter {0} is only valid for a destination type which is either a Queue, Port or WebService
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The parameter supplied can only be used when the destination type is Queue, Port or WebService.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Run the command again without using the previously stated parameter.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0610E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_DELETE_MEDIATION_NAME_CWSJA0610" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_DELETE_MEDIATION_NAME_CWSJA0610=CWSJA0610E: Not allowed to delete a mediation called &quot;{0}&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The name provided for the mediation does not adhere to naming restrictions.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that the name does not begin with an underscore, and is not empty or null.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA2409E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SIBMQLINK_FOREIGN_BUS_ALREADY_USED_CWSJA2409" varFormat="Java">
    SIBMQLINK_FOREIGN_BUS_ALREADY_USED_CWSJA2409=CWSJA2409E: The foreign bus &quot;{0}&quot; is already in use by another MQLink.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The foreign bus specified already contains a reference to a MQLink.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that a foreign bus is specified that doesn&apos;t reference a pre-existing MQLink.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA1003E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DMGR_BUS_NOT_SPECIFIED_CWSJA1003" varFormat="Java">
    DMGR_BUS_NOT_SPECIFIED_CWSJA1003=CWSJA1003E: No bus specified.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Internal error. Method invoked requires a bus object.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Please contact your system administrator to resolve this problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0165E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MISMATCH_DATASOURCE_SCOPE_CWSJA0165" varFormat="Java">
    MISMATCH_DATASOURCE_SCOPE_CWSJA0165=CWSJA0165E: The scope of the data source  {0} does not match the scope of ME recovery.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The recovery of ME config cannot be done because scope of datasource does not match scope of given nodename or clustername
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that scope of given datasource matches scope of clustername or nodename
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0156E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_PARAM_COMBINATION_CWSJA0156" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_PARAM_COMBINATION_CWSJA0156=CWSJA0156E: The &quot;queuePoints&quot; and &quot;mediationPoints&quot; parameters can only be specified when the type of the destination is ALIAS.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    It is not valid to supply either queuePoints or mediationPoints when the destination type is not set to ALIAS.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Only supply &quot;queuePoints&quot; or &quot;mediationPoints&quot; when the destination type is set to ALIAS.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0154E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_PARAM_COMBINATION_CWSJA0154" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_PARAM_COMBINATION_CWSJA0154=CWSJA0154E: The &quot;mediationPoints&quot; parameter can only be used when the target destination is a queue destination with one or more mediation points.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Specifying mediation points is only permitted when the alias directly targets a Queue destination localized to a bus member with multiple messaging engines.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Do not supply the &quot;mediationPoints&quot; parameter, or supply it and target a Queue destination localized to a bus member with multiple messaging engines.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0153E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_PARAM_COMBINATION_CWSJA0153" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_PARAM_COMBINATION_CWSJA0153=CWSJA0153E: The &quot;mediationPoints&quot; parameter can only be used when the target destination is in the same bus as the alias destination definition.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Specifying mediation points is only permitted when the alias directly targets a Queue destination in the same bus as the alias definition (the &apos;bus&apos; parameter).
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Do not supply the &quot;mediationPoints&quot; parameter, or supplpy it and target a Queue destination in the same bus as the alias definition.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0079E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="BAD_PARAM_VALUE_CWSJA0079" varFormat="Java">
    BAD_PARAM_VALUE_CWSJA0079=CWSJA0079E: Incorrect value &quot;{0}&quot; for parameter &quot;scriptCompatibility&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The value supplied for the parameter scriptCompatibility is not valid.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Run the command again, supplying a value that is either 6 (for compatability with WebSphere Application Server Version 6.0) or 6.1 (for compatability with Version 6.1).
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA2204E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="FOREIGN_BUS_NOT_FOUND_CWSJA2204" varFormat="Java">
    FOREIGN_BUS_NOT_FOUND_CWSJA2204=CWSJA2204E: The foreign bus &quot;{0}&quot; could not be found on the bus &quot;{1}&quot;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The foreign bus name supplied to the command is not the name of a foreign bus configured on the bus.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that both the foreign bus and bus name supplied to the command exist in the configuration.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0152E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_PARAM_COMBINATION_CWSJA0152" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_PARAM_COMBINATION_CWSJA0152=CWSJA0152E: The &quot;mediationPoints&quot; parameter can only be used when the target destination is an existing queue destination.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Specifying mediation points is only permitted when the alias directly targets a Queue destination.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Do not supply the &quot;mediationPoints&quot; parameter, or supply it and target a Queue destination.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0150E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_PARAM_COMBINATION_CWSJA0150" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_PARAM_COMBINATION_CWSJA0150=CWSJA0150E: The &quot;queuePoints&quot; parameter can only be used when the target destination is a queue destination with one or more queue points.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Specifying queue points is only permitted when the alias directly targets a Queue destination localized to a bus member with multiple messaging engines.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Do not supply the &quot;queuePoints&quot; parameter, or supply it and target a Queue destination localized to a bus member with multiple messaging engines.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0060E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="UNABLE_TO_CREATE_FILESTORE_CWSJA0060" varFormat="Java">
    UNABLE_TO_CREATE_FILESTORE_CWSJA0060=CWSJA0060E: Unable to create file store.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A file store could not be created with the configuration data provided.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that the configuration data provided to create a file store is valid.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA2003E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_ROUTING_TYPE_PARAMETER_CWSJA2003" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_ROUTING_TYPE_PARAMETER_CWSJA2003=CWSJA2003E: An invalid routingType parameter was supplied to this command, allowable values are &quot;Direct&quot; or &quot;Indirect&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The routingType of either Direct or Indirect is required for this command.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that the routingType parameter for the command is either Direct or Indirect.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA2011E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INCORRECT_RELIABILITY_VALUE_CWSJA2011" varFormat="Java">
    INCORRECT_RELIABILITY_VALUE_CWSJA2011=CWSJA2011E: The value &quot;{0}&quot; is not a valid value for the attribute &quot;{1}&quot;. Valid values for &quot;{1}&quot; are BEST_EFFORT_NONPERSISTENT, EXPRESS_NONPERSISTENT, RELIABLE_NONPERSISTENT, RELIABLE_PERSISTENT or ASSURED_PERSISTENT.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An incorrect value has been supplied. Valid values are BEST_EFFORT_NONPERSISTENT, EXPRESS_NONPERSISTENT, RELIABLE_NONPERSISTENT, RELIABLE_PERSISTENT or ASSURED_PERSISTENT. These values are case sensitive.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure the a valid value is supplied to the command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0139E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CLUSTER_NOT_COMPATIBLE_WITH_BOOTSTRAP_POLICY_CWSJA0139" varFormat="Java">
    CLUSTER_NOT_COMPATIBLE_WITH_BOOTSTRAP_POLICY_CWSJA0139=CWSJA0139E: The bootstrap policy for bus &quot;{0}&quot; is not compatible with cluster &quot;{1}&quot; because it has members that reside on pre-7.0 nodes.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The cluster could not be added to the bus because the cluster has members that reside on a pre-7.0 WebSphere Application Server Version node, and the bootstrap policy setting is not compatible with pre-Version 7.0 nodes. The bootstrap policy setting must not be MEMBERS_ONLY, or MEMBERS_AND_NOMINATED.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Change the bootstrap policy to be SIBSERVICE_ENABLED, or upgrade the named cluster so that all servers in the cluster reside on a Version 7.0 node.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0412E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_ACT_SPEC_TARGET_SIGNIFICANCE_VALUE_CWSJA0412" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_ACT_SPEC_TARGET_SIGNIFICANCE_VALUE_CWSJA0412=CWSJA0412E: {0} is not a valid value for target significance.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A value that is not valid has been entered for the target significance property.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check the documentation for a valid value for this property.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0123E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ME_POLICY_ASSISTANCE_DISABLED_CWSJA0123" varFormat="Java">
    ME_POLICY_ASSISTANCE_DISABLED_CWSJA0123=CWSJA0123E: The messaging engine is associated with a server cluster that does not have messaging engine policy assistance enabled and the CUSTOM policy specified.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    To create a core group policy for a messaging engine, the server cluster that the messaging engine is associated with must have messaging engine policy assistance enabled and the CUSTOM policy specified.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Either specify a messaging engine that is associated with a server cluster that has messaging engine policy assistance enabled and the CUSTOM policy specified, or use modifySIBusMemberPolicy to modify the server cluster so that messaging engine policy assistance is enabled and the CUSTOM policy is specified.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0149E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_PARAM_COMBINATION_CWSJA0149" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_PARAM_COMBINATION_CWSJA0149=CWSJA0149E: The &quot;queuePoints&quot; parameter can only be used when the target destination is in the same bus as the alias destination definition.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Specifying queue points is only permitted when the alias directly targets a Queue destination in the same bus as the alias definition (the &apos;bus&apos; parameter).
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Do not supply the &quot;queuePoints&quot; parameter, or supply it and target a Queue destination in the same bus as the alias definition.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0148E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_PARAM_COMBINATION_CWSJA0148" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_PARAM_COMBINATION_CWSJA0148=CWSJA0148E: The &quot;queuePoints&quot; parameter can only be used when the target destination is an existing queue destination.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Specifying queue points is only permitted when the alias directly targets a Queue destination.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Do not supply the &quot;queuePoints&quot; parameter, or supply it and target a Queue destination.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0059E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_FILESTORE_SIZE_CWSJA0059" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_FILESTORE_SIZE_CWSJA0059=CWSJA0059E: Can not specify maximum permanent file store size if unlimited permanent store size is set to true
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    When the size of the permanent file store has been set to unlimited, a maximum permanent size cannot be set.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Remove the maximum permanent file store size parameter or change the unlimited permanent file store size to false then retry.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0404E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="LIST_FAILED_CWSJA0404" varFormat="Java">
    LIST_FAILED_CWSJA0404=CWSJA0404E: Failed to get list of existing SIB JMS ActivationSpecs from resource adapter {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The list command was unsuccessful either because null parameters were given, or no result was returned.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that all parameters passed to the command are valid, and not null.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA1610E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_SSLTYPE_SPECIFIC_PARAMETERS_CWSJA1610" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_SSLTYPE_SPECIFIC_PARAMETERS_CWSJA1610=CWSJA1610E: The &quot;sslChain&quot; parameter is not valid when the &quot;sslType&quot; parameter is set to &quot;SPECIFIC&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The &quot;sslChain&quot; parameter is not valid when the &quot;sslType&quot; parameter is set to &quot;SPECIFIC&quot;.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a different sslType or do not use the illegal parameters.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0097E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_REPLYTOQUEUE_CHARS_CWSJA0097" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_REPLYTOQUEUE_CHARS_CWSJA0097=CWSJA0097E: The value {0} for the WebSphere MQ reply to queue contains invalid characters.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The WebSphere MQ reply to queue allowable characters range a-z, A-Z, 0-9, ., /, % and _.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Run the command again specifying an allowable WebSphere MQ reply to queue value.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0095E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_FILE_SIZE_CWSJA0095" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_FILE_SIZE_CWSJA0095=CWSJA0095E: Maximum temporary store size can not be less than minimum temporary store size.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An attempt is being made to configure a maximum temporary store size with a value that is less than the minimum temporary store size.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Either lower the minimum temporary store size, increase the maximum temporary store size, or make the maximum temporary store size unlimited.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0094E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_FILE_SIZE_CWSJA0094" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_FILE_SIZE_CWSJA0094=CWSJA0094E: Maximum temporary store size must be greater than {0} megabytes.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The maximum temporary store size specified is lower than the maximum temporary store size minimum value.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Increase the size of the maximum temporary store size, or make it unlimited.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0093E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_FILE_SIZE_CWSJA0093" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_FILE_SIZE_CWSJA0093=CWSJA0093E: Minimum temporary store size can not be less than log size.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The temporary file store size must be greater than the temporary store log size.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Increase the temporary store size or decrease the log size.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0801E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DMGR_CELL_NOT_FOUND_CWSJA0801" varFormat="Java">
    DMGR_CELL_NOT_FOUND_CWSJA0801=CWSJA0801E: No cells found in the deployment manager configuration.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The deployment manager configuration does not contain any cells.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that the deployment manager configuration contains a cell.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0008E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_SCOPE_SPECIFICATION_CWSJA0008" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_SCOPE_SPECIFICATION_CWSJA0008=CWSJA0008E: Scope specification is not valid.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The details specified do not represent a valid scope specification.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that valid node name, server name and cluster name details are used to represent the scope.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0133E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_PARAM_COMBINATION_CWSJA0133" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_PARAM_COMBINATION_CWSJA0133=CWSJA0133E: Incorrect parameter combination supplied : node name = &quot;{0}&quot;, server name = &quot;{1}&quot;, cluster name = &quot;{2}&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The parameters supplied do not provide a valid bus member configuration.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    To correctly identify a bus member, specify node name and server name, or cluster name.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0144E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="BAD_MAX_JVM_HEAP_SIZE_CWSJA0144" varFormat="Java">
    BAD_MAX_JVM_HEAP_SIZE_CWSJA0144=CWSJA0144E: The new maximum JVM heap size value of {0} MB is not in the acceptible range of {1} MB to {2} MB.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The supplied maximum JVM heap size value is not in the acceptable range.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Change the supplied maximum JVM heap size value to one that is in the acceptable range.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA1002E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DMGR_CELL_NOT_SPECIFIED_CWSJA1002" varFormat="Java">
    DMGR_CELL_NOT_SPECIFIED_CWSJA1002=CWSJA1002E: No cell specified.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Internal error. Method invoked requires a cell object.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Please contact your system administrator to resolve this problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0202E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="COMMAND_FAILED_CWSJA0202" varFormat="Java">
    COMMAND_FAILED_CWSJA0202=CWSJA0202E: Failed to get J2C command result: {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The command was run but no result object was returned.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that the correct configuration information has been passed to the command being run.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0121E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="POLICY_CANNOT_CHANGE_WHEN_ASSIST_DISABLED_CWSJA0121" varFormat="Java">
    POLICY_CANNOT_CHANGE_WHEN_ASSIST_DISABLED_CWSJA0121=CWSJA0121E: You can not change the messaging engine policy when messaging engine policy assistance is disabled.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    You specified a new policyName parameter when the assistanceEnabled parameter is set to false.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that the assistanceEnabled parameter is set to true, then specify a valid policyName parameter.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0049E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MQ_SERVER_ALREADY_MEMBER_OF_BUS_CWSJA0049" varFormat="Java">
    MQ_SERVER_ALREADY_MEMBER_OF_BUS_CWSJA0049=CWSJA0049E: WebSphere MQ server &quot;{0}&quot; is already a member of bus &quot;{1}&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An attempt has been made to add an MQ server to a bus of which it is already a member.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Do not try to add an WebSphere MQ server to a bus of which it is already a member.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0163E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CANNOTSTART_MESSAGESTORE_FILE_CWSJA0163" varFormat="Java">
    CANNOTSTART_MESSAGESTORE_FILE_CWSJA0163=CWSJA0163E: The message store for file store {0} cannot be started.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The message store cannot start due to some startup exception.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that file store path is correct and reachable.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0099E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DEST_NOT_FOUND_ON_BUS_CWSJA0099" varFormat="Java">
    DEST_NOT_FOUND_ON_BUS_CWSJA0099=CWSJA0099E: Failed to find destination &quot;{1}&quot; on bus &quot;{0}&quot; with an alias bus &quot;{2}&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The named alias destination could not be located on the named bus within the administrative domain.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that the named alias destination exists on the named bus with the named alias bus.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0043E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="BAD_PARAM_VALUE_CWSJA0043" varFormat="Java">
    BAD_PARAM_VALUE_CWSJA0043=CWSJA0043E: The value of {2} is not valid for parameter {1} when destination type is {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The value supplied for the specified parameter is not valid.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Run the command again, supplying a valid value.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0131E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SERVER_NOT_BUS_MEMBER_CWSJA0131" varFormat="Java">
    SERVER_NOT_BUS_MEMBER_CWSJA0131=CWSJA0131E: The server &quot;{1}&quot; on node &quot;{0}&quot; is not a member of the bus &quot;{2}&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The node and server supplied to the command do not correspond to a member of the bus supplied.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that you used the correct spelling for the node, server and bus name, and that the server is a member of the bus.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA2406E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_CLUSTER_ME_VERSION_FOR_PREFER_LOCAL_CWSJA2406" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_CLUSTER_ME_VERSION_FOR_PREFER_LOCAL_CWSJA2406=CWSJA2406E: The messaging engine &quot;{0}&quot; is running in a cluster that contains one or more v6.1 or earlier servers. The preferLocal attribute can only be set to false when a cluster running the messaging engine contains only v7.0 servers.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The preferLocal attribute can only be set to false when a cluster running the messaging engine contains only v7.0 servers.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that the messaging engine hosting the link is running in a cluster containing only v7.0 servers before setting the preferLocal attribute to false.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0164E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_DATASOURCE_SCOPE_CWSJA0164" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_DATASOURCE_SCOPE_CWSJA0164=CWSJA0164E: The scope of the data source  {0} is invalid.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The message store cannot start due to some startup exception.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that scope of given datasource is valid
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0037E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="BAD_PARAM_VALUE_CWSJA0037" varFormat="Java">
    BAD_PARAM_VALUE_CWSJA0037=CWSJA0037E: Incorrect value &quot;{2}&quot; for parameter &quot;{1}&quot; of command &quot;{0}&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The value supplied for the specified parameter of the specified command is not valid.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Run the command again, supplying a valid value.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0069E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_FILE_SIZE_CWSJA0069" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_FILE_SIZE_CWSJA0069=CWSJA0069E: Maximum permanent store size can not be less than minimum permanent store size
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Maximum store size cannot be less than minimum store size.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Either lower the minimum store size, or increase the maximum store size, or make the maximum store size unlimited.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0068E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_FILE_SIZE_CWSJA0068" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_FILE_SIZE_CWSJA0068=CWSJA0068E: Maximum permanent store size must be greater than {0} megabytes
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The maximum permanent store size specified is lower than the maximum permanent store size minimum value.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Increase the size of the maximum permanent store size, or make it unlimited.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0067E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_FILE_SIZE_CWSJA0067" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_FILE_SIZE_CWSJA0067=CWSJA0067E: Log size must be greater than {0} megabytes
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The log size specified is lower than the minimum log size.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Increase the size of the log file.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0066E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_FILE_SIZE_CWSJA0066" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_FILE_SIZE_CWSJA0066=CWSJA0066E: Minimum permanent store size can not be less than log size
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The permanent file store size must be greater than the file store log size.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Increase the permanent store size or decrease the log size.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0027E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DEST_NOT_FOUND_CWSJA0027" varFormat="Java">
    DEST_NOT_FOUND_CWSJA0027=CWSJA0027E: Destination {0} not found on bus {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An exception occurred attempting to locate the specified destination.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that the destination being located exists within the administrative domain.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0216E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="FAILED_TO_CREATE_JMSTOPIC_CWSJA0216" varFormat="Java">
    FAILED_TO_CREATE_JMSTOPIC_CWSJA0216=CWSJA0216E: Failed to create a SIB JMS topic with topic name : &quot;{0}&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An instance of a JMS topic with the specified topic name could not be created.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that a valid topic name has been specified upon creation of the Topic object.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0109E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="BAD_GROUP_IN_BUS_CONNECTOR_ROLE_CWSJA0109" varFormat="Java">
    BAD_GROUP_IN_BUS_CONNECTOR_ROLE_CWSJA0109=CWSJA0109E: Found group &quot;Server&quot; in the bus connector role for bus &quot;{0}&quot;. This is not allowed because the bus contains at least one pre-6.1 bus member.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The named bus contains one or more WebSphere Application Server Version 6.0 bus members. Having the named group in the bus connector role is not compatible with pre-Version 6.1 bus members. The Server group must not be in the bus connector role.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Disable security on the named bus, or remove the named group from the bus connector role, or remove all pre-Version 6.1 bus members from the bus.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA2206E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="BUS_MEMBER_TARGET_NOT_FOUND_CWSJA2206" varFormat="Java">
    BUS_MEMBER_TARGET_NOT_FOUND_CWSJA2206=CWSJA2206E: A Bus Member Target with an Engine UUID of &quot;{0}&quot; could not be found
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The messaging engine UUID specified above could not be found on any of the existing bus member targets.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that the correct messaging engine was supplied to the command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0617E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="BAD_PARAM_COMBINATION_CWSJA0617" varFormat="Java">
    BAD_PARAM_COMBINATION_CWSJA0617=CWSJA0617E: When specifying a value of true for parameter &quot;externallyMediated&quot; and a WebSphere MQ server, the &quot;node&quot;, &quot;server&quot; or &quot;cluster&quot; parameters should not be specified.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Externally mediating destinations are only supported for destinations that are localized in WebSphere MQ.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Remove the node, server or cluster parameter that was specified.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0616E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="BAD_PARAM_COMBINATION_CWSJA0616" varFormat="Java">
    BAD_PARAM_COMBINATION_CWSJA0616=CWSJA0616E: When specifying a value of true for parameter &quot;externallyMediated&quot; a &quot;wmqServer&quot; parameter must be supplied.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    External mediation support is only valid for destinations localized to WebSphere MQ.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Either specify a false value for the externallyMediated parameter or add a wmqServer parameter.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA2004E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="VIRTUAL_LINK_NOT_FOUND_CWSJA2004" varFormat="Java">
    VIRTUAL_LINK_NOT_FOUND_CWSJA2004=CWSJA2004E: A virtual link could not be found on foreign bus &quot;{0}&quot;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The foreign bus specified to the command does not have a virtual link child object.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that the foreign bus specified has a virtual link child object.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0613E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="BAD_PARAM_COMBINATION_CWSJA0613" varFormat="Java">
    BAD_PARAM_COMBINATION_CWSJA0613=CWSJA0613E: When specifying a WebSphere MQ Server name using the &quot;wmqServer&quot; parameter the &quot;wmqQueueName&quot; parameter must be supplied.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    When specifying a WebSphere MQ server name a WebSphere MQ Queue name must be supplied.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Add the wmqQueueName parameter to the mediateSIBDestination command then retry.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJA0612E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="BAD_PARAM_COMBINATION_CWSJA0612" varFormat="Java">
    BAD_PARAM_COMBINATION_CWSJA0612=CWSJA0612E: The parameter {0} is only valid when specifying a WebSphere MQ Server name using the &quot;wmqServer&quot; parameter.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The supplied parameter is not valid when mediating a destination and a WebSphere MQ server name was not specified.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Remove the parameter from the mediateSIBDestination command then retry.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<!-- END MESSAGES -->
</TMSSource>
