<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/css" href="../../resources/stylesheets/wasmsgxml.css"?>
<TMSSource name="TivoliMessages" tmsVersion="1.0" xml:lang="en">
<!-- CMVC MSG File Name = ws/code/admin.jmx/src/com/ibm/ws/management/resources/fileservice.nlsprops -->
<!-- DO NOT EDIT THIS FILE - This file was generated by the XML/Html & Property emitter -->
<!-- BEGIN MESSAGES -->
<Message ID="ADFS0114W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADFS0114" varFormat="Java">
    ADFS0114=ADFS0114W: A port was not configured for the deployment manager&apos;&apos;s administrative functions.  File transfer will try to use the default port number &quot;{0}&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A problem exists in configured HTTP transports for the deployment manager.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the deployment manager transports are correct and match the ports defined in the admin_host virtualhost configuration by looking at serverindex.xml and virtualhosts.xml files.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADFS0113E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADFS0113" varFormat="Java">
    ADFS0113=ADFS0113E: A problem occurred trying to create a connection to the deployment manager. {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A connection could not be made to the dployment manager.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the deployment manager is running with no errors by looking at deployment manager server logs.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADFS0112E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADFS0112" varFormat="Java">
    ADFS0112=ADFS0112E: File transfer has failed with the following message: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    File download failed.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that file permissions are set properly and sufficient file system space exists.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADFS0111E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADFS0111" varFormat="Java">
    ADFS0111=ADFS0111E: Unable to find ObjectName for FileTransferServer: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The file transfer client was unable to resolve the MBean object name of the file transfer service.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the deployment manager is running with no errors by looking at deployment manager server logs.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADFS0109E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADFS0109" varFormat="Java">
    ADFS0109=ADFS0109E: FileTransferClient failed to get server configuration information: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Either a communication problem or other internal error occurred when the node agent tried to contact the deployment manager for file transfer configuration information.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify the deployment manager is running correctly with no errors by looking at deployment manager server logs.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADFS0108E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADFS0108" varFormat="Java">
    ADFS0108=ADFS0108E: An error occurred creating the transferred file &quot;{0}&quot;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The file being transferred could not be written to the file system.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that sufficient file system space exists to create the file.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADFS0107E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADFS0107" varFormat="Java">
    ADFS0107=ADFS0107E: The file to download &quot;{0}&quot; does not exist.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The file requested for download was not found at the deployment manager.  The path for the file being downloaded might not be correct, or a service could be experiencing a problem.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the path is correct for the file being downloaded.  Determine whether a service is having the problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADFS0106E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADFS0106" varFormat="Java">
    ADFS0106=ADFS0106E: An error occurred writing the transferred file &quot;{0}&quot;. {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    During a file upload from the node to the deployment manager a problem occurred either writing the file or communicating with the node.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check the logs files in the ${LOG_ROOT} directory for additional information regarding this error.  Verify that the remote host and remote port are correct for file transfer and there is disk space available.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADFS0105E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADFS0105" varFormat="Java">
    ADFS0105=ADFS0105E: The file transfer plug-in can not be loaded. {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    While initializing File Transfer, an exception occurred possibly due to problems loading a class.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the file transfer application installed correctly by checking ${LOG_ROOT}/installFiletransfer.log.  If necessary, reinstall the file transfer application.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADFS0104E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADFS0104" varFormat="Java">
    ADFS0104=ADFS0104E: An error occurred accessing the file system. {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The file service had problems getting properties of a requested property file.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that file permissions are set properly. See the first failure data capture (FFDC) log in the ${LOG_ROOT}/ffdc directory for additional information.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADFS0103E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADFS0103" varFormat="Java">
    ADFS0103=ADFS0103E: The directory &quot;{0}&quot; could not be created.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    During an administrative operation an attempt was made to create the directory named in the error message.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the access rights are set correctly for the directory in error.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADFS0102E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADFS0102" varFormat="Java">
    ADFS0102=ADFS0102E: An error occurred initializing the File Service component.  Exception: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    File services might be unavailable. Unavailability of file services could cause problems with file synchronization, file browsing, or other administrative functions.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADFS0101E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADFS0101" varFormat="Java">
    ADFS0101=ADFS0101E: An error occurred deactivating the &quot;{0}&quot; MBean.  Exception: {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    When the deployment manager or node agent was stopped, the file service MBean could not be deactivated.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADFS0100E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADFS0100" varFormat="Java">
    ADFS0100=ADFS0100E: An error occurred creating the &quot;{0}&quot; MBean.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The deployment manager or node agent could not initialize one of the file service MBeans.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADFS0161I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADFS0161" varFormat="Java">
    ADFS0161=ADFS0161I: A download was made from the non-standard path {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A file transfer download was made from an non-standard path.  Downloads are typically requested from the download or JobManager subdirectory of the configuration repository temporary directory.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    This message may be helpful when tracking unusual or unexpected file transfers.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADFS0160I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADFS0160" varFormat="Java">
    ADFS0160=ADFS0160I: An upload was made to the non-standard path {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A file transfer upload was made to a non-standard path.  Uploads are typically made to the upload or JobManager subdirectory of the configuration repository temporary directory.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    This message may be helpful when tracking unusual or unexpected file transfers.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADFS0143E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADFS0143" varFormat="Java">
    ADFS0143=ADFS0143E: The byte range for the download of the {0} file is not valid.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A request was made to download a portion of the file, but the byte range is not valid. The starting index cannot be less than 0, greater than the ending index, or greater than the length of the file.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a valid byte range, and retry the operation.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADFS0142E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADFS0142" varFormat="Java">
    ADFS0142=ADFS0142E: The {0} file path cannot be downloaded because it does not exist on the server, or the path that you specified is a directory.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The path that you specified does not exist on the server, or you specified a directory path rather than a file path.  This error also might result from inconsistent port definitions for the administrative host in the deployment manager virtualhosts.xml and serverindex.xml files.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a file that exists on the server, and try the operation again.  Ensure that the ports defined for admin_host in virtualhosts.xml match those for WC_adminhost and WC_adminhost_secure in the deployment manager serverindex.xml.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADFS0141E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADFS0141" varFormat="Java">
    ADFS0141=ADFS0141E: The {0} file path cannot be downloaded because it is a location or file type that is not allowed, or the path is not valid.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Downloading a file from this path is not allowed for one of the following reasons: downloading from this particular subdirectory is not allowed, files with this extension cannot be downloaded, the path contains a .. directory, or the path ends with an invalid character. The trace log on the target server might provide more information.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Retry the operation with a valid path.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADFS0140E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADFS0140" varFormat="Java">
    ADFS0140=ADFS0140E: The file transfer server cannot download the {0} file. The server returned HTTP error code {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An unanticipated HTTP error code was returned while attempting to download a file. More information might be available in your trace logs or in the trace logs of the server running the file transfer application.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Use the status code to determine and resolve the problem, and then retry the operation.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADFS0136W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADFS0136" varFormat="Java">
    ADFS0136=ADFS0136W: The server cannot locate a port configuration for the administrative functions.  Thus, the file transfer service will attempt to use the {0} default port number.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A problem exists in the configured HTTP transports for the server.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the server transports are correct and match the port numbers, which are defined in the admin_host virtual host configuration.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADFS0134I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADFS0134" varFormat="Java">
    ADFS0134=ADFS0134I: File transfer is configured with host=&quot;{0}&quot;, server=&quot;{3}&quot;, port=&quot;{1}&quot;, securityEnabled=&quot;{2}&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The information indicates how file transfer client is configured to communicate with the file transfer server.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADFS0133E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADFS0133" varFormat="Java">
    ADFS0133=ADFS0133E: An error occurred trying to connect to the file transfer server running in the deployment manager.  Exception: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The file transfer service running at the node agent cannot communicate with the file transfer service at the deployment manager.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the network connection is good.  Verify that the ports for deployment manager Web container are configured correctly in the deployment manager server configuration and in the virtual host configuration.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADFS0132W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADFS0132" varFormat="Java">
    ADFS0132=ADFS0132W: The host address of the deployment manager could not be determined. A default of &quot;localhost&quot; is being used. This is not valid for a configuration with more than one machine.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The TCP/IP configuration is not correct for the server since more then one machine exists for the configuration. If a node is configured at a machine different that the deployment manager, file transfer cannot occur between the node and the deployment manager.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the host address and domain name server (DNS) configurations are set correctly.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADFS0131W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADFS0131" varFormat="Java">
    ADFS0131=ADFS0131W: The host address of the deployment manager is 127.0.0.1.  This is not valid for a configuration with more than one machine.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The TCP/IP configuration is not correct for the server since more then one machine exists for the configuration. If a node is configured at a machine different from the deployment manager, file transfer cannot occur between the node and the deployment manager.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the host address and domain name server (DNS) configurations are set correctly.  For Linux configurations, configure the /etc/nsswitch.conf file to search the DNS before the /etc/hosts file.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADFS0130E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADFS0130" varFormat="Java">
    ADFS0130=ADFS0130E: Errors decrypting the password: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The password in the sas.client.props file could not be decoded.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the sas.client.props file is not corrupted and the contents for password is correct.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADFS0129E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADFS0129" varFormat="Java">
    ADFS0129=ADFS0129E: Errors occurred trying to read the SAS client configuration file. {0} {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The sas.client.props file cannot be opened.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the sas.client.props file is in the correct configured location based on the ${WAS_PROPS_DIR} variable. Verify that the file can be opened by checking the file permission.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADFS0128E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADFS0128" varFormat="Java">
    ADFS0128=ADFS0128E: The IBM JSSE package could not be loaded. It is needed to run file transfer in a secure environment. {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    File transfer could not be set up with security enabled.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that the ibmjsse.jar is in the class path. Verify that the SSL port is configured for deployment manager server.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADFS0126W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADFS0126" varFormat="Java">
    ADFS0126=ADFS0126W: A configured port for file transfer service was not found.  Default port {0} is being used.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The configured port information for the deployment manager Web container was not found in the configuration.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the deployment manager server configuration includes the proper HTTP transports looking at serverindex.xml and virtualhosts.xml files.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADFS0125E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADFS0125" varFormat="Java">
    ADFS0125=ADFS0125E: An exception occurred downloading a file {0}.  Exception: {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The deployment manager could not download a file to the nodeagent.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the exception information contains a Web address, verify that the IP address is correct for the deployment manager.  If the IP address is 127.0.0.1, the deployment manager domain name server (DNS) is not configured correctly.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADFS0124E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADFS0124" varFormat="Java">
    ADFS0124=ADFS0124E: An exception occurred uploading a file {0}.  Exception: {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A file could not be uploaded from the node to the deployment manager.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the exception information contains a Web address, verify that the IP address is correct for the deployment manager.  If the IP address is 127.0.0.1, the deployment manager domain name server (DNS) is not configured correctly.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADFS0123E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADFS0123" varFormat="Java">
    ADFS0123=ADFS0123E: An error occurred trying to contact the node agent &quot;{0}&quot;. Exception: {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The file transfer server could not contact the file transfer client at the node agent.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the node is running and that no errors initializing the nodeagent.  Look at nodeagent logs in the ${LOG_ROOT}/nodeagent directory.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADFS0122E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADFS0122" varFormat="Java">
    ADFS0122=ADFS0122E: The ObjectName &quot;{0}&quot; is not valid. Exception: {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The file transfer server had an internal error trying to resolve an object name.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADFS0121E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADFS0121" varFormat="Java">
    ADFS0121=ADFS0121E: An error occurred trying to resolve the MBean reference ObjectName for {0}. Exception: {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The file transfer server could not resolve the file transfer client&apos;s MBean at a specific node.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the node is running and there were no errors initializing the node agent.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADFS0120E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADFS0120" varFormat="Java">
    ADFS0120=ADFS0120E: Can not resolve the MBean reference ObjectName for {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The node agent is not running at the remote node.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the node agent is running looking at the nodeagent logs in ${LOG_ROOT}/nodeagent directory.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADFS0119E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADFS0119" varFormat="Java">
    ADFS0119=ADFS0119E: An unexpected exception occurred: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    File download/upload maybe fail.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that file permission are set properly and sufficient file system space exists. Verify that the deployment manager is running with no error by looking at deployment manager server logs.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<!-- END MESSAGES -->
</TMSSource>
