<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/css" href="../../resources/stylesheets/wasmsgxml.css"?>
<TMSSource name="TivoliMessages" tmsVersion="1.0" xml:lang="en">
<!-- CMVC MSG File Name = ws/code/admin.jmx/src/com/ibm/ws/management/resources/unnodeutils.nlsprops -->
<!-- DO NOT EDIT THIS FILE - This file was generated by the XML/Html & Property emitter -->
<!-- BEGIN MESSAGES -->
<Message ID="ADMK0203E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMK0203E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMK0203E=ADMK0203E:  Unmanaged node&apos;s platform type must be one of:
 os400, aix, hpux, linux, solaris, windows, os390
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The platform type specified is not a recognized type.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify one of the recognized platform types and resubmit the command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMK0206E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMK0206E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMK0206E=ADMK0206E:  Only one unmanaged node may be added to standalone systems.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Only one unmanaged node may be added to stand alone systems.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Do not add the unmanaged node to the system.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMK0204E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMK0204E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMK0204E=ADMK0204E:  The node you are attempting to create already exists in your workspace.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The node cannot be created because a node of the same name already exists.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Do one of the following actions: Create a node with a different name; or, to create the existing node again, first remove it, then create it.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMK0207E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMK0207E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMK0207E=ADMK0207E:  The command is not supported in job manager. You need to use queryManagedNodes command.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The command is not supported in job manager environment.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    You need to use queryManagedNodes command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMK0202E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMK0202E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMK0202E=ADMK0202E:  removeUnManagedNode should only be used to remove an unmanaged node.
 {0} is a managed node.  No changes were made.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An attempt was made to remove a managed node using the removeUnmanagedNode command. The removeUnmanagedNode command can be used to remove unmanaged nodes only. The specified managed node was not removed.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Use the administrative console or the removeNode command to remove a managed node.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMK0205E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMK0205E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMK0205E=ADMK0205E:  Base version of node must be of form:
  w.y.z.n 
where w, y, z, and n are integers.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The base version of the node must be of the form:
  w.y.z.n 
, where w, y, z, and n are integers.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a correct value and resubmit the command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<!-- END MESSAGES -->
</TMSSource>
