<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/css" href="../../resources/stylesheets/wasmsgxml.css"?>
<TMSSource name="TivoliMessages" tmsVersion="1.0" xml:lang="en">
<!-- CMVC MSG File Name = ws/code/appprofile.impl/src/com/ibm/ws/appprofile/accessintent/resources/accessintent.nlsprops -->
<!-- DO NOT EDIT THIS FILE - This file was generated by the XML/Html & Property emitter -->
<!-- BEGIN MESSAGES -->
<Message ID="ACIN0034E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ACIN_ERRO_PME_FILE_CREATION_FAILED" varFormat="Java">
    ACIN_ERRO_PME_FILE_CREATION_FAILED=ACIN0034E: The application {0} is configured for application profiling. The creation of ibm-application-ext-pme.xmi file failed.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified application is configured to require the Application Profiling service. The ibm-application-ext-pme.xmi file should be created for this application during installation. However, the file creation failed.  It could be because of configuration problems in Application profiling in the Enterprise Java Bean (EJB) modules.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check the Application profiling configuration in the EJB modules of this application.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ACIN0009I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ACIN_INFO_SERVICE_STOPPING" varFormat="Java">
    ACIN_INFO_SERVICE_STOPPING=ACIN0009I: The application profiling service is stopping.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The server is shutting down, and the application profiling service is stopping.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    There is no user action required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ACIN0015I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ACIN_INFO_SERVICE_STARTED_WITH_PROBLEMS" varFormat="Java">
    ACIN_INFO_SERVICE_STARTED_WITH_PROBLEMS=ACIN0015I: The application profiling service started; problems occurred during startup.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Problems were encountered starting the application profiling service.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Use previous messages to determine the problems encountered during startup. Verify that all the necessary classes and packages are in the correct locations, and verify that all the prerequisite services are enabled and started.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ACIN0005E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ACIN_WARN_CONFIG_REASON" varFormat="Java">
    ACIN_WARN_CONFIG_REASON=ACIN0005E: An access intent configuration for application {0} may be invalid because: {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An application was configured with attributes that could result in the application running in a mode that is not expected.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Use the error text that is provided to determine where the application might not be configured correctly. Reassemble the application with the appropriate attributes for access intent, and reinstall the application if it is necessary.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ACIN0004E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ACIN_WARN_CONFIG_KEY" varFormat="Java">
    ACIN_WARN_CONFIG_KEY=ACIN0004E: An access intent configuration for application {0} may be invalid: {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An application was configured with attributes that could result in the application running in an unexpected mode.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Use the key that is provided to determine where the application might not be configured correctly. The key is defined in the user documentation. Reassemble the application with the appropriate attributes for access intent if it is necessary.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ACIN0011W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ACIN_WARN_NO_SUCH_EJB" varFormat="Java">
    ACIN_WARN_NO_SUCH_EJB=ACIN0011W: The configuration element {0} is associated with a non-existent ejb.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A bean that was configured might have been removed from the module.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Remove the configuration element and reinstall the application.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ACIN0008E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ACIN_ERRO_NO_SERVICE" varFormat="Java">
    ACIN_ERRO_NO_SERVICE=ACIN0008E: The access intent or application profiling service could not resolve the following service: {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The access intent and the application profiling services require coordination with other services to function correctly. Without those services, the access intent and the application profiling service might not work correctly.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the other service that is necessary is installed and enabled.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ACIN0017W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ACIN_WARN_DUPLICATE_ACCESS_INTENT_CONFIG" varFormat="Java">
    ACIN_WARN_DUPLICATE_ACCESS_INTENT_CONFIG=ACIN0017W: The ejb element {0} has been configured with both the access intent {1} and {2}; {2} will be used.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A method or entity has been configured to run with two different access intents, forcing the Application Server to arbitrarily choose which one to use.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Reconfigure the application so that no method or entity is associated with more than one access intent policy, then reinstall the application.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ACIN0016I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ACIN_INFO_READ_AHEAD_HINTS_IGNORED" varFormat="Java">
    ACIN_INFO_READ_AHEAD_HINTS_IGNORED=ACIN0016I: Some read ahead hints in the module cannot be applied.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Read ahead hints are an optimization that cannot be applied to all of the container-managed relationships.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Determine the read ahead hints that cannot be applied, remove them from the application configuration, and then reinstall the application. The application will run correctly without removing the read ahead hints that are not applied; this message can be safely ignored.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ACIN0006I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ACIN_INFO_CANNOT_BE_DISABLED" varFormat="Java">
    ACIN_INFO_CANNOT_BE_DISABLED=ACIN0006I: The application profiling service cannot be disabled.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Even if the application profiling service is disabled using the administrative console, the application profiling service cannot actually be disabled.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Use the administrative console to enable the application profiling service.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ACIN0002E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ACIN_ERR_CONFIG_KEY" varFormat="Java">
    ACIN_ERR_CONFIG_KEY=ACIN0002E: An access intent configuration for application {0} is invalid: {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An application was configured with attributes that are not allowed or not formed well.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Use the key that is provided to determine where the application might not be configured properly. The key is defined in the user documentation. Reassemble the application with the appropriate attributes for access intent.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ACIN0021W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ACIN_WARN_CANNOT_ADMINISTER_FROM_CONSOLE" varFormat="Java">
    ACIN_WARN_CANNOT_ADMINISTER_FROM_CONSOLE=ACIN0021W: Application profiles in this application will not support administration from the console.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The configuration settings that are adminsitered through the console for application profiling could not be processed. The application will run according to the original deployment descriptors for the application.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Do not use the console tool to administer the configuration for application profiling. Uninstall and reinstall the application to correct the problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ACIN0026E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ACIN_ERRO_UNKNOWN_ACCESS_INTENT_POLICY" varFormat="Java">
    ACIN_ERRO_UNKNOWN_ACCESS_INTENT_POLICY=ACIN0026E: An unknown access intent policy {0} is specified that cannot be resolved; {1} will be used instead.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The definition of a referenced access intent policy cannot be found. If the policy was defined as an Enterprise-defined access intent policy, and the application is run on a non-Enterprise server, the defined policy will not be available.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the access intent policy that is referenced is properly defined for the version of the Application Server on which the application is running. Remove the access intent policy that is configured, and reconfigure the access intent using the Application Server assembly tools, then reinstall the application.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ACIN0031E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ACIN_ERRO_RESTART_SERVER_REQUIRED" varFormat="Java">
    ACIN_ERRO_RESTART_SERVER_REQUIRED=ACIN0031E: The J2EE 1.3 application {0} is configured for application profiling and is installed and starting on a running server that enables Application Profiling 5.x Compatibility Mode. You must re-start the server.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified application is configured to require the Application Profiling service, but it is installed and starting on a running server that enables Application Profiling 5.x Compatibility Mode.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Restart the server.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ACIN0028E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ACIN_ERRO_DISABLED_BUT_REQUIRED" varFormat="Java">
    ACIN_ERRO_DISABLED_BUT_REQUIRED=ACIN0028E: {0} is configured for application profiling, but the Application Profiling service is disabled. You must enable the Application Profiling service to start application {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified application is configured to require the Application Profiling service, but the Application Profiling service is not enabled.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Enable the Application Profiling service before starting the specified application that is configured for application profiling.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ACIN0029W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ACIN_WARN_COMPATIBILITY_MODE" varFormat="Java">
    ACIN_WARN_COMPATIBILITY_MODE=ACIN0029W: The J2EE 1.3 application {0} is configured for application profiling and is starting on a server that enables Application Profiling 5.x Compatibility Mode. Application Profiling 5.x Compatibility Mode is deprecated.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified application will run in V5.x Compatibility mode. The V5.x Compatibility Mode is deprecated.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that all the Java 2 Enterprise Edition (J2EE) V1.3 applications on this server that use application profiling can run properly with Application Profiling V5.x Compatibility Mode disabled, then configure the Application Profiling service to not use V5.x Compatibility Mode.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ACIN0022E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ACIN_ERRO_NULL_ATTRIBUTE" varFormat="Java">
    ACIN_ERRO_NULL_ATTRIBUTE=ACIN0022E: The following application profile attribute cannot be null: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Some configuration attributes are mandatory for the deployment descriptors for the application. The application cannot run as desired without completing the configuration properly.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that all the required attributes are specified properly.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ACIN0007I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ACIN_INFO_SERVICE_STARTED" varFormat="Java">
    ACIN_INFO_SERVICE_STARTED=ACIN0007I: The application profiling service started successfully.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The application profiling service started successfully as part of the normal server startup process.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    There is no user action required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ACIN0001E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ACIN_ERR_MISSING_KEY" varFormat="Java">
    ACIN_ERR_MISSING_KEY=ACIN0001E: Message key {0} was not found in any searched catalog.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A key was passed into the AccessIntentMessages class to resolve to a string, but a properties file for the locale could not be found, and the appropriate message could not be retrieved.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Refer to the message key to determine why the message catalog could not be found.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ACIN0010E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ACIN_ERRO_UNEXPECTED_EXCEPTION" varFormat="Java">
    ACIN_ERRO_UNEXPECTED_EXCEPTION=ACIN0010E: The access intent or application profiling service encountered an unexpected exception during the following: {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This exception is unexpected. The cause is not immediately known.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ACIN0025I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ACIN_INFO_NO_FINDER_FOR_UPDATE" varFormat="Java">
    ACIN_INFO_NO_FINDER_FOR_UPDATE=ACIN0025I: Some finders in the module do not support exclusive locks and will not successfully run under some pessimistic access intent policies.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Some user-defined queries do not support exclusive locking of the retrieved records. Execution of those queries under the access intent policies that require exclusive locks will result in an exception.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Refer to the documentation to determine the queries that do not support the access intent policies that require exclusive locks. Configure the application so that those queries will not run with access intent policies that require exclusive locks, or rewrite the query, redeploy and reinstall the application.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ACIN0003E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ACIN_ERR_CONFIG_REASON" varFormat="Java">
    ACIN_ERR_CONFIG_REASON=ACIN0003E: An access intent configuration for application {0} is invalid because: {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An application was configured with attributes that are not allowed or not formed well.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Use the error text that is provided to determine where the application might not be configured correctly. Reassemble the application with the appropriate attributes for access intent, and reinstall the application.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ACIN0018W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ACIN_WARN_DUPLICATE_TASK" varFormat="Java">
    ACIN_WARN_DUPLICATE_TASK=ACIN0018W: The j2ee element {0} has been configured with both the task name {1} and {2}; {2} will be used.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A method or component has been configured to run as two different task names, forcing the Application Server to arbitrarily choose which one to use.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Reconfigure the application so that no method or component is associated with more than one task, then reinstall the application.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ACIN0027W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ACIN_WARN_METHOD_LEVEL_DEPRECATION" varFormat="Java">
    ACIN_WARN_METHOD_LEVEL_DEPRECATION=ACIN0027W: {0} uses access intent configured on an entity method. Method-level access intent is deprecated.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Method-level access intent is configured within the specified application. Method-level access intent is deprecated.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Reconfigure the application using application profiling.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ACIN0033I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ACIN_INFO_PME_FILE_NOT_CREATED" varFormat="Java">
    ACIN_INFO_PME_FILE_NOT_CREATED=ACIN0033I: The application {0} is not configured for application profiling. The ibm-application-ext-pme.xmi file is not created for this application.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified application is not configured to require the Application Profiling service. The ibm-application-ext-pme.xmi file is not created for this application.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    There is no user action required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ACIN0032I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ACIN_INFO_PME_FILE_CREATED" varFormat="Java">
    ACIN_INFO_PME_FILE_CREATED=ACIN0032I: The application {0} is configured for application profiling. The ibm-application-ext-pme.xmi file is created for this application.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified application is configured to require the Application Profiling service. The ibm-application-ext-pme.xmi file is created for this application.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    There is no user action required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ACIN0013E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ACIN_ERRO_ACCESS_INTENT_UNAVAILABLE" varFormat="Java">
    ACIN_ERRO_ACCESS_INTENT_UNAVAILABLE=ACIN0013E: The access intent interface will be unavailable to BMP entities.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Bean Managed Persistent (BMP) entities that programatically use the access intent service will not be able to look up the interface in naming due to previous errors.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Use previous messages to determine the problems encountered during startup. Verify that all the necessary classes and packages are in the correct locations, and verify that all the prerequisite services are enabled and started.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ACIN0035W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="APPR_EJB_IN_WAR" varFormat="Java">
    APPR_EJB_IN_WAR=ACIN0035W: A task name could not be found. This can reflect a configuration error, or may be the result of using the application profiling extension in an EJB packaged in a War file.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Application Profiling support is intended for use with CMP beans which are not supported in EJBs in WARs. As a result applications are unable to access Task from EJBs in WARs.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Either remove usage of the application profile extension from the EJB (e.g. setTaskName), or do not attempt to package this EJB in a War file. If the application does not use an EJB packaged in a WAR please verify that the task name has been defined properly.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ACIN0023W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ACIN_WARN_DUPLICATE_TASK_PROFILE" varFormat="Java">
    ACIN_WARN_DUPLICATE_TASK_PROFILE=ACIN0023W: The task {0} has been configured with both the application profile {1} and {2}; {2} will be used.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    If a task is configured on two application profiles, then the server runtime must guess which mapping to use.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Remove the configuration for the task from one of the application profiles.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ACIN0024E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ACIN_ERRO_DEFAULTING_INTENT" varFormat="Java">
    ACIN_ERRO_DEFAULTING_INTENT=ACIN0024E: Could not determine the desired access intent for {0} and defaulted to {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Application Server could not determine the correct access intent for the bean. The Application Server loaded the bean with a default intent.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ACIN0030I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ACIN_INFO_NOT_ENABLED" varFormat="Java">
    ACIN_INFO_NOT_ENABLED=ACIN0030I: Application Profiling service is disabled.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Application Profiling service has been disabled in the configuration, and it will not be accessible on the server.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Disabling this service might cause other services on the server to fail. If you wish to enable the service, use the Administrative Console to configure services on this application server.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ACIN0019W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ACIN_WARN_DUPLICATE_TASK_REFERENCE" varFormat="Java">
    ACIN_WARN_DUPLICATE_TASK_REFERENCE=ACIN0019W: The j2ee component {0} has configured the logical task reference {1} to both the task named {1} and the task named {2}; {2} will be used.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A task reference has been configured to map to more than one task, forcing the Application Server to arbitrarily choose which one to use.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Reconfigure the application so that each task reference is associated with exactly one task, then reinstall the application.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ACIN0014I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ACIN_INFO_DEFAULT_WAS_DQ" varFormat="Java">
    ACIN_INFO_DEFAULT_WAS_DQ=ACIN0014I: The default access intent policy named {0} and assigned to the entity {1} was originally configured only for dynamic query.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An access intent policy was created in a previous version of the Application Server to act as the the default intent for dynamic queries. This configuration will be treated as the default access intent for all requests upon this entity, including dynamic queries.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Using the version of the assembly tool that was used to originally create the access intent policy for the dynamic query, rename the policy to DEFAULT, then reinstall the application.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ACIN0020W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ACIN_WARN_DUPLICATE_TASK_ACCESS_INTENT_CONFIG" varFormat="Java">
    ACIN_WARN_DUPLICATE_TASK_ACCESS_INTENT_CONFIG=ACIN0020W: The entity {0} has been configured for the task {1} with both the access intent policies {2} and {3}; {3} will be used.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An entity has been configured with two different access intent policies that are associated with the same task. The Application Server must arbitrarily choose which one to use.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Reconfigure the application so that each task is associated with only one application profile and every entity is configured with only one access intent within any application profile. Then reinstall the application.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<!-- END MESSAGES -->
</TMSSource>
