<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/css" href="../../resources/stylesheets/wasmsgxml.css"?>
<TMSSource name="TivoliMessages" tmsVersion="1.0" xml:lang="en">
<!-- CMVC MSG File Name = ws\code\ejbquery\src\OOSQLMessages.nlsprops -->
<!-- DO NOT EDIT THIS FILE - This file was generated by the XML/Html & Property emitter -->
<!-- BEGIN MESSAGES -->
<Message ID="WQRY1020E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="RTDSERR" varFormat="Java">
    RTDSERR=WQRY1020E: Runtime evaluation error - DataSource error [{0}] encountered.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An error was detected in attempting to access the data source.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Reset the data source. If the problem persists, refer to the IBM support Web site for information on problem determination.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0003E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="AEOWPTIQ" varFormat="Java">
    AEOWPTIQ=WQRY0003E: An error occurred while parsing input query: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An error occurred parsing the query for the enterprise Java bean (EJB), indicated in the message text.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify the query statement for the EJB. If the statement is valid, refer to the IBM support web site for information on problem determination.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0002E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="AEOWPTIO" varFormat="Java">
    AEOWPTIO=WQRY0002E: Internal error in mapping metadata. Invalid view: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A syntax error was detected in the mapping metadata generated by the WebSphere deployment tool. This error is in the view implementation or the inheritance typecode predicates.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    This indicates an internal error in the Application Server or the WSAD deployment tooling. Refer to the IBM support web site for information on problem determination.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0134E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="OBYGBDUDTCMP" varFormat="Java">
    OBYGBDUDTCMP=WQRY0134E: Cannot use order by, group by or distinct clause with CMP field [{0}] because it is mapped to a  user defined type.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Ordering, grouping, or DISTINCT is supported only for container-managed persistence (CMP) fields that are of types such as numbers, strings and date-time values.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the query statement for the enterprise Java bean (EJB).
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0004E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="AOODANDTC" varFormat="Java">
    AOODANDTC=WQRY0004E: An overflow occurred during a numeric data type conversion in function {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A mathematical error occurred executing a query scalar function for an enterprise Java bean (EJB). The message text indicates the name of the scalar function.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the query statement for the enterprise Java bean (EJB), or update the container-managed persistence (CMP) field values to avoid the overflow problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY1002E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="RTNSJT" varFormat="Java">
    RTNSJT=WQRY1002E: Runtime evaluation error - a non-supported JDBC SQL type {0} is encountered.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The following SQL types are allowed: INYINT, SMALLINT, INTEGER, BIGINT, FLOAT, REAL, DOUBLE, CHAR, VARCHAR, LOB, DECIMAL, DATE, TIME, and TIMESTAMP.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the application schema.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0093E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="TAD" varFormat="Java">
    TAD=WQRY0093E: internal error in metadata. Entry {0} is already defined
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    There was an internal error in mapping the metadata.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    This error indicates an internal error in the Application Server or the WSAD deployment tooling. Refer to the IBM support Web site for information on problem determination.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0020E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CIAPSICBCTAN" varFormat="Java">
    CIAPSICBCTAN=WQRY0020E: Invalid casting of field {0} to a non reference type
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The query statement for the enterprise Java bean (EJB) does not support casting a container-managed persistence (CMP) field or container-managed relationship (CMR) field to another type.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the query statement for the enterprise Java bean (EJB).
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0081E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="OBYRELN" varFormat="Java">
    OBYRELN=WQRY0081E: Invalid ORDER BY due to ordering by a CMR field {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Ordering is supported only for container-managed persistence (CMP) values that are orderable types, such as numbers, strings and date-time values.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the query statement for the enterprise Java bean (EJB).
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0037E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DNHAM" varFormat="Java">
    DNHAM=WQRY0037E: {0} {1} does not have a method {2}().
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The method with the given name was used in a query statement. The bean with the Abstract Schema Name (ASN) and the identification variable does not define this method. The use of methods in query statements is only supported in WebSphere Extended Edition.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the query statement for the enterprise Java bean (EJB).
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0151E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="TCSE" varFormat="Java">
    TCSE=WQRY0151E: The trim character &apos;&apos;{0}&apos;&apos; is not valid in a TRIM function.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A trim character can only be a single character on TRIM function.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the query statement for the enterprise Java bean (EJB).
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0036E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DNHAC" varFormat="Java">
    DNHAC=WQRY0036E: {0} {1} does not have a field {2}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A container-managed persistence (CMP) field or a container-managed relationship (CMR) field with the given name was used in a query statement. The bean with the Abstract Schema Name (ASN) and the identification variable does not define this field.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the query statement for the enterprise Java bean (EJB).
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0009E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ASNFCNU" varFormat="Java">
    ASNFCNU=WQRY0009E: The Abstract Schema Name {0} specified in the FROM clause of the query is not unique.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Abstract Schema Name (ASN) that is specified in the FROM clause of the query is defined in more than one installed applications.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Provide EJBHome or EJBLocalHome to uniquely identify the ASN name and resubmit the query. Follow the sample client code for the usage of EJBHome or EJBLocalHome.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0031E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CUDWLCOCCWLGT" varFormat="Java">
    CUDWLCOCCWLGT=WQRY0031E: Invalid use of DISTINCT. Cannot use DISTINCT if the select clause refers to fields that are mapped to columns greater than 254 bytes or to columns of type LOB.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Backend data store cannot compare columns which are greater than 254 bytes or binary data.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the query statement or the mapping for the enterprise Java bean (EJB).
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0040E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="EIAAASAOFMA" varFormat="Java">
    EIAAASAOFMA=WQRY0040E: EMPTY, EXISTS, IN, ALL, ANY and SOME are only for multivalued attributes.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The EMPTY, EXISTS, IN, ALL, ANY and SOME scalar functions can only be applied to container-managed relationship (CMR) fields and to subqueries.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the query statement for the enterprise Java bean (EJB).
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY1112E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ICCTS" varFormat="Java">
    ICCTS=WQRY1112E: Invalid comparison of Character {0} to String {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A character can only be compared to a character or a string of length 1.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the query statement for the enterprise Java bean (EJB).
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0008E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ASNFCND" varFormat="Java">
    ASNFCND=WQRY0008E: The Abstract Schema Name {0} specified in the FROM clause of the query is not defined
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Abstract Schema Name (ASN) that is specified in the FROM clause of the query is not defined in any of the installed applications.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that the ASN name is correct, or install the application that has the ASN name and submit the query again.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0110E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="UQV" varFormat="Java">
    UQV=WQRY0110E: Identification variable &apos;&apos;{0}&apos;&apos; is not defined.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The identification variable that was found with container-managed persistence (CMP) field or a container-managed relationship (CMR) field does not match the identification variable that is associated with any enterprise Java bean (EJB) that is being queried.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the query statement for the EJB.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY1047E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DISDNSP" varFormat="Java">
    DISDNSP=WQRY1047E: Distinct in the top level query is not supported.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A DISTINCT operation appears in the top level of the query. This is not supported by the query engine for the enterprise Java bean (EJB).
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the query statement for the EJB.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY1033E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ACHGSQLNULL" varFormat="Java">
    ACHGSQLNULL=WQRY1033E: Internal error: SQL statement for update/insert/delete is null.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This is an internal error in the Application Server.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Refer to the IBM support Web site for information on problem determination.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0043E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="GEOFST" varFormat="Java">
    GEOFST=WQRY0043E: Operator &gt;= cannot be used in the expression {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The &quot;greater than or equal&quot; operator can only be used with numeric, string, date-time or calendar types.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the query statement for the enterprise Java bean (EJB).
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0017E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CFTD" varFormat="Java">
    CFTD=WQRY0017E: Cannot define identification variable &apos;&apos;{0}&apos;&apos; over a single-valued path expression &apos;&apos;{1}&apos;&apos;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An identification variable must be defined as an Abstract Schema Name (ASN) or as a multivalued path expression. The identification variable that is indicated is defined with the path expression that is indicated in the message text, which ends in a single valued relationship name.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the query statement for the enterprise Java bean (EJB).
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY1040E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="RTEOWGSFMQO" varFormat="Java">
    RTEOWGSFMQO=WQRY1040E: Runtime evaluation error - Exception occurred while creating schema class from model query object [{0}].
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An error occurred trying to create an EClass defining the schema of the model query object.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the error in the model query object.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0023E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CINSITGBC" varFormat="Java">
    CINSITGBC=WQRY0023E: A path expression terminating in the CMP field {0} appears in a SELECT clause without an aggregate function but is not specified in the GROUP BY clause
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    When performing a grouping operation, elements of the SELECT clause must either be aggregation functions or grouping elements. The container-managed persistence (CMP) field indicated is used in the SELECT clause and does not appear in an aggregation function, but the CMP field is not a grouping element.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the query statement for the enterprise Java bean (EJB).
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY1010E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="RTSTVF" varFormat="Java">
    RTSTVF=WQRY1010E: Runtime evaluation error - failed to extract value of type {1} from the given string {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Application Server cannot convert the given string to its corresponding numeric value, because a format was encountered that is not able to be parsed.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the string representation of the number.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0000E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="AANSIVT" varFormat="Java">
    AANSIVT=WQRY0000E: Internal error in mapping metadata. Aggregates are not allowed
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An aggregation operation (for example SUM, AVG, and so on) appears in the mapping metadata. This is not currently supported by the query engine for the enterprise Java bean (EJB).
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    This indicates an internal error in the Application Server or the WSAD deployment tooling. Refer to the IBM support web site for information on problem determination.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0077E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="OBYBLOB" varFormat="Java">
    OBYBLOB=WQRY0077E: Invalid ORDER BY due to ordering by a field of type BLOB.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Ordering on java.sql.blob values is not supported.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the query statement for the enterprise Java bean (EJB).
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY1080E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DUPCMP" varFormat="Java">
    DUPCMP=WQRY1080E: Duplicate CMP field name [{0}] is specified in select expression.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Duplicate container-managed persistence (CMP) names, resulting in duplicate attributes, are present in the DataGraph. This is not allowed in queries that return Service Data Objects (SDOs).
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Rename one of the duplicates by using the AS syntax. For instance, &apos;select e.name, e.depSet.name as deptName from EmpBean e&apos;.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0065E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="NDFF" varFormat="Java">
    NDFF=WQRY0065E: Schema {0} is not defined for field {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified field does not denote a container-managed relationship (CMR) field or a container-managed persistence (CMP) field that is defined by the given schema.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check the query statement for the enterprise Java bean (EJB), or check the schema mapping of the application model.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0096E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="TNASTO" varFormat="Java">
    TNASTO=WQRY0096E: IS OF TYPE predicate constains invalid subtype. Type {0} is not a subclass of {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    When using the IS OF TYPE predicate to test the subtype of enterprise Java beans (EJBs), the subtype(s) that make the operand on the right side of the IS OF TYPE predicate must be defined subtypes of the EJB that is specified by the left side of the operand.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the query statement for the enterprise Java bean (EJB).
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0071E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="NOTRANS" varFormat="Java">
    NOTRANS=WQRY0071E: Query iterator is in an invalid state because it is being used outside the scope of the transaction that created it
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A query iterator is no longer valid, because the Java Database Connectivity (JDBC) cursor is not valid. This is probably due to an end-of-transaction operation. The query iterator cannot be used outside of the originating transaction scope.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the program that is running is user a valid programming model.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0130E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MDITONPF" varFormat="Java">
    MDITONPF=WQRY0130E: The {0} method in the query differs in type or number of parameters from any {1} method defined in the CMP Bean.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The method in the query statement for the enterprise Java bean (EJB) differs in the number or type of argument from all the methods with the same name in the EJB model.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the query statement for the enterprise Java bean (EJB).
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0083E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PTND" varFormat="Java">
    PTND=WQRY0083E: Parameter ?{0} is not defined or has an invalid datatype
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The program made an attempt to reference a parameter that is greater than the number of input parameters. The parameters are defined by the signature of the FINDER method or the SELECT method. For a dynamic query on an enterprise Java bean (EJB), the input parameters are passed on the exeucteQuery API. Attempting to use an input parameter whose data type is not supported by WebSphere may also result in this error.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the query statement for the EJB or the method signature.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0005E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="AQCBPITSOAP" varFormat="Java">
    AQCBPITSOAP=WQRY0005E: the SELECT clause of a subquery cannot contain a subquery
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A subquery that is used in a SELECT clause cannot contain a subquery in its own SELECT clause.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the query statement for the enterprise Java bean (EJB).
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY1037E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="RTTTCDWDOO" varFormat="Java">
    RTTTCDWDOO=WQRY1037E: Runtime evaluation error - Trying to create duplicate  sdo object for EClass [{0}] with primary key [{1}].
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    There was an error trying to create Service Data Objects (SDOs) with the same primary key.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the updates to the datagraph.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY1005E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="RTDTANS" varFormat="Java">
    RTDTANS=WQRY1005E: Runtime evaluation error - the specified Date/Time arithmetic is not currently supported.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Date/Time arithmetic is not currently supported.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the query statement for the enterprise Java bean (EJB) to avoid date/time arithmetics.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY1034E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="RTAEWIWDOQ" varFormat="Java">
    RTAEWIWDOQ=WQRY1034E: Runtime evaluation error - An exception occurred while initializing the ejb mediator query: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    There was an error in initializing the specified mediator query.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the mediator query.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY1013E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="RTINVRT" varFormat="Java">
    RTINVRT=WQRY1013E: Runtime evaluation error - an invalid result type from an arithmetic expression is detected.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Application Server cannot map the result type that is inferred from the expression.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the query statement for the enterprise Java bean (EJB).
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY1063E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ACHGRELFAIL" varFormat="Java">
    ACHGRELFAIL=WQRY1063E: Relationship [{0}] is not updatable.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The relationship is not able to be updated, because it is not specified in the EJBMediator query.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    The Application Server cannot update the relationship in the current DataGraph. To update the relationship, regenerate the DataGraph by specifying the relationship in the mediator query.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0094E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="TDTLOVOAII" varFormat="Java">
    TDTLOVOAII=WQRY0094E: Argument {0} for function {1} is invalid. The data type, length or value is incompatible with the function definition
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified argument cannot be used with the scalar function listed in the message text.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the query statement for the enterprise Java bean (EJB).
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY1032E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ACHGCMPCOLNP" varFormat="Java">
    ACHGCMPCOLNP=WQRY1032E: Internal error: CMPs and Columns are not paired. {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This is an internal error in the Application Server.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Refer to the IBM support Web site for information on problem determination.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY1031E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ACHGCMPNF" varFormat="Java">
    ACHGCMPNF=WQRY1031E: Internal error: This CMP field is not present in user&apos;&apos;s projection clause. {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This is an internal error in the Application Server.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Refer to the IBM support Web site for information on problem determination.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0055E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MIOFST" varFormat="Java">
    MIOFST=WQRY0055E: Operator - cannot be used in expression {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The MINUS operator is used with a data type that is not compatible. The message text contains the expression that is not correct.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the query statement for the enterprise Java bean (EJB).
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY1014E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="RTNSFEX" varFormat="Java">
    RTNSFEX=WQRY1014E: Runtime evaluation error - the specified field {0} is not retrievable from class {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An error was detected while attempting to retrieve a given field.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the class definition that is given, or correct the field name.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY1016E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="RTINVPT" varFormat="Java">
    RTINVPT=WQRY1016E: Runtime evaluation error - an invalid parameter type {0} is detected.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A value of NULL cannot be used as the type of a parameter.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Change the query method with a parameter type that is valid.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY1049E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PASSRMTOSDO" varFormat="Java">
    PASSRMTOSDO=WQRY1049E: Runtime evaluation error - DataGraph with static schema of pattern NO_DUMMY_ROOT returning more than one root sdo [{0}].
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A DataGraph that is based on the NO_DUMMY_ROOT pattern schema can have only one instance of a root Service Data Object (SDO).
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Create the mediator again with a query array for the enterprise Java bean (EJB) that returns a single root SDO.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY1018E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="RTINVPC" varFormat="Java">
    RTINVPC=WQRY1018E: Runtime evaluation error - an invalid plan cursor detected.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An internal error was found after the plan was evaluated.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Restart the system. If the problem persists, refer to the IBM support Web site for information on problem determination.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY1041E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="JOINFROM" varFormat="Java">
    JOINFROM=WQRY1041E: More than one join is detected in from clause.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Error occurred while trying to parse the FROM clause.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the query statement for the enterprise Java bean (EJB).
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0108E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="UC" varFormat="Java">
    UC=WQRY0108E: field {0} is not defined
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The field is not defined in the abstract schema as either a container-managed persistence (CMP) field or a container-managed relationship (CMR) field.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the query statement for the enterprise Java bean (EJB). Make sure that every path expression begins with an identification variable.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0022E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CINDFSSN" varFormat="Java">
    CINDFSSN=WQRY0022E: Internal error. Class {0} is not defined for SELECT STARN
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This is an internal error.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    This indicates an internal error either in the Application Server or the WSAD deployment tooling. Refer to the IBM support web site for information on problem determination.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY1084E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="XRELINVALID" varFormat="Java">
    XRELINVALID=WQRY1084E: Invalid Xrel [{0}] in mediator query, missing Data Object retrieval for [{1}].
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A Data Object must be retrieved for linking the relationships.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the query to include retrieval of the related Data Object.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY1000E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="RTICTBO" varFormat="Java">
    RTICTBO=WQRY1000E: Runtime evaluation error - operands {0} and {1} are incompatible types in the given binary arithmetic operation.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The program cannot issue a binary operation on two operands with types that are not compatible.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the query statement for the enterprise Java bean (EJB), or correct the application schema.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0138E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="BINTR" varFormat="Java">
    BINTR=WQRY0138E: The return type of {0} for method [{1}] is not allowed.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The return type specified cannot be used as the return type of a method.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the method with correct return type.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0137E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="BINTP" varFormat="Java">
    BINTP=WQRY0137E: The input argument type of {0} for method [{1}] is not allowed.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The input argument type specified cannot be used as the type of an input parameter of a method.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the method with correct parameter type.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY1012E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="RTILVFB" varFormat="Java">
    RTILVFB=WQRY1012E: Runtime evaluation error - an invalid value {0} is detected for the boolean field.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The supported boolean value are: false = 0 , true = 1.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the corresponding value that is stored in back-end database.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0109E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="UNOPEAUSS" varFormat="Java">
    UNOPEAUSS=WQRY0109E: There are an unequal number of select elements for a UNION operation
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    When performing a UNION operator, the SELECT statements that are operands to the UNION must contain an equal number of elements in the SELECT clauses.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the EJB query statement.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0078E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="OBYBOOL" varFormat="Java">
    OBYBOOL=WQRY0078E: Invalid ORDER BY due to ordering by a field of type boolean.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Ordering on boolean values is not supported.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the query statement for the enterprise Java bean (EJB).
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0152E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="UID" varFormat="Java">
    UID=WQRY0152E: The identifier {0} must be defined before it is used.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The identifier must be defined before it is referenced in a query statement for an enterprise Java bean (EJB).
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the query statement for the EJB.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0099E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="TOFST" varFormat="Java">
    TOFST=WQRY0099E: Operator * cannot be used in expression {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The multiply operator is used with an data type that is not compatible. The message text contains the expression that is not correct.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    : Correct the query statement for the enterprise Java bean (EJB).
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0092E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SE" varFormat="Java">
    SE=WQRY0092E: A syntax error was detected at character position {0} near token &lt;{1}&gt;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The query statement for the enterprise Java bean (EJB) does not satisfy the syntax diagram that is found in the documentation for EJB queries.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the query statement for the EJB.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY1030E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ACHGFLDEMP" varFormat="Java">
    ACHGFLDEMP=WQRY1030E: Internal error: A list of ChangedFieldRecords is empty.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This is an internal error in the Application Server.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Refer to the IBM support Web site for information on problem determination.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0039E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="EGPKFEODDE" varFormat="Java">
    EGPKFEODDE=WQRY0039E: internal error in query runtime. Error getting Primary Key for EJBObject {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An internal error occurred in the server at run time.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    This error indicates an internal error in the Application Server. Refer to the IBM support Web site for information on problem determination.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY1042E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DUPASN" varFormat="Java">
    DUPASN=WQRY1042E: Duplicate ASN name is detected in the graph.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An error occurred while trying to create an enterprise Java bean (EJB) mediator.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the query statement for the EJB.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0032E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DCIOBC" varFormat="Java">
    DCIOBC=WQRY0032E: Duplicate order by element {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A number or a path expression appears more than once in the ORDER BY clause.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the query statement for the enterprise Java bean (EJB).
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0059E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MTOIQ" varFormat="Java">
    MTOIQ=WQRY0059E: Query is too complex. It exceeds {0} select operations
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    There can be a maximum of 100 select statements in the final query generated by an query statement for the enterprise Java bean (EJB).
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Reduce the size and the number of SELECT operations in the query statement for the enterprise Java bean (EJB).
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY1009E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="RTLPCTD" varFormat="Java">
    RTLPCTD=WQRY1009E: Runtime evaluation error - a loss of precision was detected when converting {0} to DECIMAL.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An overflow or underflow condition was detected while converting a value to a decimal.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the query statement for the enterprise Java bean (EJB), or correct the application schema.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0075E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="OBCINAPE" varFormat="Java">
    OBCINAPE=WQRY0075E: The element {0}.{1} in the ORDER BY clause is invalid because it does not appear in the SELECT clause
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    If the ORDER BY clause is used, the element that is being ordered by must appear in the SELECT clause.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the query statement for the enterprise Java bean (EJB).
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0049E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="IOFST" varFormat="Java">
    IOFST=WQRY0049E: Inequality cannot be used in expression {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An inquality operator is used with a data type that is not compatible. The message text contains the expression that is not correct.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the query statement for the enterprise Java bean (EJB).
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0046E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="IHMDERR" varFormat="Java">
    IHMDERR=WQRY0046E: internal error in mapping metadata. Invalid typecode predicate: {0} for EJBHome {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A syntax error was detected in the mapping metadata that was generated by the WebSphere deployment tool. The given typecode predicates and the given Abstract Schema Name (ASN) for the EJBHome statement is failing.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    This error indicates an internal error in the Application Server or the WSAD deployment tooling. Refer to the IBM support Web site for information on problem determination.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0018E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CGMFC" varFormat="Java">
    CGMFC=WQRY0018E: Internal error in mapping metadata. Unable to access metadata for CMP/CMR field {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The mapping metadata for the field that is indicated by the message text cannot be accessed.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    This indicates an internal error in the Application Server or in the WSAD deployment tooling. Refer to the IBM support web site for information on problem determination.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0054E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MHPAAWGI" varFormat="Java">
    MHPAAWGI=WQRY0054E: Method signature mismatch. Method {0} has {1} parameters and {2} arguments were given in {3}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The method in the query statement for the enterprise Java bean (EJB) differs in number or the type of argument from all the methods with the same name that are in the programming model for the EJB.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the query statement for the enterprise Java bean (EJB).
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY1048E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="OCCNU" varFormat="Java">
    OCCNU=WQRY1048E: This OCC CMP field [{0}] has been changed by another user session and update to it is not allowed.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An OCC container-managed persistence (CMP) field has been changed by another user session, and an update to it is not allowed.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Regenerate the DataGraph, and run the operation again.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY1083E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SUBQRYINSDO" varFormat="Java">
    SUBQRYINSDO=WQRY1083E: Subquery in select clause is not allowed in mediator query.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A subquery in a SELECT clause is not allowed in a mediator query that returns Service Data Objects (SDOs).
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Remove the subquery from the SELECT clause.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0047E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ILNTMVPE" varFormat="Java">
    ILNTMVPE=WQRY0047E: Invalid path expression {0} attempts to dereference a collection valued CMR field.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A path expresssion cannot navigate through a multi-valued contianer-managed relationship (CMR) field.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the query statement for the enterprise Java bean (EJB).
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0026E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CNMBPI" varFormat="Java">
    CNMBPI=WQRY0026E: the ordinal numbers used in order by clause must be a positive integers
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Zero and negative numbers are not valid in the ORDER BY clause. Use the DESC keyword to sort in descending order.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the query statement for the enterprise Java bean (EJB).
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0155E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="OVMWSNOP" varFormat="Java">
    OVMWSNOP=WQRY0155E: You cannot use the overloaded methods &apos;&apos;{0}&apos;&apos; of bean &apos;&apos;{1}&apos;&apos; with the same number of input arguments.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Overloaded methods with the same number of input arguments are not supported.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the query statement for the EJB or the method definition.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY1039E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="RTWDOONU" varFormat="Java">
    RTWDOONU=WQRY1039E: Runtime evaluation error - SDO object [{0}] cannot be updated.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Service Data Object (SDO) cannot be updated because either its primary key is not specified in the projection clause of the EJBMediator query, or at least one OCC is defined but is not projected.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Generate the DataGraph again by specifying the primary keys in the mediator query. To update the SDO, include at least one of the OCC fields in your select clause.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0136E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="NS" varFormat="Java">
    NS=WQRY0136E: An invalid parameter type {0} is detected.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A specified type cannot be used as the type of a parameter.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the query statement for the enterprise Java bean (EJB) with a correct parameter type.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0070E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="NNEIA" varFormat="Java">
    NNEIA=WQRY0070E: A non numeric expression used with AVG
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An AVG function that requires a numeric expression was used incorrectly with an argument expression.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the query statement for the enterprise Java bean (EJB).
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY1004E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="RTIFBD" varFormat="Java">
    RTIFBD=WQRY1004E: Runtime evaluation error - {0} is not a valid representation of a BigDecimal.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The form of the decimal constant that is given in the query is not an acceptable format.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the decimal constant in the query statement for the enterprise Java bean (EJB).
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0063E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ND" varFormat="Java">
    ND=WQRY0063E: Parameter {0} is not defined
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The parameter that is indicated in the message text is not defined.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the query statement for the enterprise Java bean (EJB).
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY1113E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CMPAMSG45" varFormat="Java">
    CMPAMSG45=WQRY1113E: The following query may result in the generation of invalid SQL: [{0}]
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    If an EJBQL query contains a join in the FROM clause (for example, &quot;IN a.b.c.d dGroup&quot;) where a middle path element (b or c) utilizes class inheritance and there exists a predicate in the WHERE clause that navigates (b or c) to an entity that also utilizes inheritance, then the query processing engine can fail and produce invalid SQL for the query.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Redefine the query to avoid using a predicate that expresses the fault.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY1111E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CMPAMSG40" varFormat="Java">
    CMPAMSG40=WQRY1111E: The {0} Abstract Schema Name (ASN) is not mapped to CMP/A type bean.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The CMP/A FINDER method can only be used on a WebSphere Business Integration (WBI) platform for a query that is of the CMP/A type.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify the installation of WBI, and deploy the application again with a CMP/A deployment tool.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY1017E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="RTNPLTE" varFormat="Java">
    RTNPLTE=WQRY1017E: Runtime evaluation error - the number of parameters {0} passed in is less than expected {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The number of parameters that was passed in the query engine is less than what was expected.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the number of parameter that are passed in.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY1025E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="RTDTNV" varFormat="Java">
    RTDTNV=WQRY1025E: Runtime evaluation error - A datetime arithmetic operation or a datetime scalar function has a result that is not within the valid range of dates.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The result must fall between the dates January 1, 0001, and December 31, 9999, inclusively.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the expression.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0058E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MTMM" varFormat="Java">
    MTMM=WQRY0058E: Invalid MEMBER OF expression due to type mismatch.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Using the MEMBER OF predicate to compare an entity bean to a collection-valued container-managed relationship (CMR) field is not a valid operation, because the entity beans are not comparable or belong to different homes.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the query statement for the enterprise Java bean (EJB).
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY1110E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CMPAMSG35" varFormat="Java">
    CMPAMSG35=WQRY1110E: The null {0} Abstract Schema Name (ASN) is invalid.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Abstract Schema Name (ASN) cannot be null.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the query, and run the application again.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0052E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="LOFST" varFormat="Java">
    LOFST=WQRY0052E: Operator &lt; cannot be used in expression {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The &quot;less than or equal&quot; operator is used with a data type that is not compatible. The message text contains the expression that is not correct.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the query statement for the enterprise Java bean (EJB).
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY1015E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="RTILAEX" varFormat="Java">
    RTILAEX=WQRY1015E: Runtime evaluation error - a illegal access to a method {0} is detected.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The program cannot access or invoke the given method.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the application model.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY1038E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="RTFOWDOONU" varFormat="Java">
    RTFOWDOONU=WQRY1038E: Runtime evaluation error - Field [{0}] of sdo object [{1}] with primary key [{2}] is not updatable.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    There was an error trying to update a field that might be the primary key, part of primary key, output of a method, or output of a converter or an expression.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the updates to the datagraph.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0028E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CNT" varFormat="Java">
    CNT=WQRY0028E: Cannot navigate through a CMP field {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Application Server made an attempt to navigate past the container-managed persistence (CMP) or container-managed relationship (CMR) field. A path expression can only navigate through a single-valued CMR field.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the query statement for the enterprise Java bean (EJB).
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0074E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="NTF" varFormat="Java">
    NTF=WQRY0074E: Internal error: missing TYPE Field {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This error indicates an internal error in the Application Server or the WSAD deployment tooling.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Refer to the IBM support Web site for information on problem determination.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0027E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CNP" varFormat="Java">
    CNP=WQRY0027E: Path expression {0} is invalid. Cannot navigate past {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Application Server made an attempt to navigate past the container-managed persistence (CMP) or container-managed relationship (CMR) field. A path expression can only navigate through a single-valued CMR field.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the query statement for the enterprise Java bean (EJB).
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY1107E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CMPAMSG20" varFormat="Java">
    CMPAMSG20=WQRY1107E: Method {0} is not defined as CMP/A pushe-down method for {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Method does not exist in the CMP/A push-down methods list.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Define the method, and deploy the application again with a CMP/A deployment tool, or enter the correct method in the query, and run the application again.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0073E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="NTB" varFormat="Java">
    NTB=WQRY0073E: The number {0} is out of range.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The number that is specified is out of the legal range for its data type.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the query statement for the enterprise Java bean (EJB).
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0025E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CND" varFormat="Java">
    CND=WQRY0025E: The abstract schema name {0} is not defined
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Abstract Schema Name (ASN) that is indicated in the message text is not defined.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the query statement for the enterprise Java bean (EJB).
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0033E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DGBE" varFormat="Java">
    DGBE=WQRY0033E: Duplicate group by element {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A path expression appears more than once in the GROUP BY clause.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the query statement for the enterprise Java bean (EJB).
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY1106E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CMPAMSG17" varFormat="Java">
    CMPAMSG17=WQRY1106E: RemoteException while invoking {0} finder method on concrete bean object.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Application Server failed to invoke remote finder method.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the FINDER method, and deploy the application again with a CMP/A deployment tool.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY1105E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CMPAMSG16" varFormat="Java">
    CMPAMSG16=WQRY1105E: CSIException while invoking {0} finder method on concrete bean object.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Application Server failed to invoke the FINDER method on the concrete bean, because a back-end error occurred.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the FINDER method, and deploy the application again with a CMP/A deployment tool.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY1104E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CMPAMSG15" varFormat="Java">
    CMPAMSG15=WQRY1104E: The type of method argument {0} is not compatible with any of the method arguments defined in the CMP/A push-down methods list.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The method argument type is not compatible.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the method arguments, and deploy the application again with a CMP/A deployment tool, or enter correct method arguments in the query and run the application again.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY1103E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CMPAMSG14" varFormat="Java">
    CMPAMSG14=WQRY1103E: FinderException while invoking {0} finder method on concrete bean object.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Application Server failed to invoke the FINDER method on the concrete bean, because the wrong FINDER method name or argument was supplied.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the CMP/A push-down FINDER method, and deploy the application again with a CMP/A deployment tool.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY1102E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CMPAMSG13" varFormat="Java">
    CMPAMSG13=WQRY1102E: CSIException while getting the data cache entry object for the {0} Abstract Schema Name (ASN).
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The cache entry for this Abstract Schema Name (ASN) cannot be obtained.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the CMP/A push-down method that is in the user-defined implementation class for the push-down method, and deploy the application again with the CMP/A deployment tool.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY1101E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CMPAMSG12" varFormat="Java">
    CMPAMSG12=WQRY1101E: CSINoSuchObjectException while getting the data cache entry object for the {0} Abstract Schema Name (ASN).
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The cache entry for this Abstract Schema Name (ASN) cannot be obtained.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the CMP/A push-down method that is in the user-defined implementation class for the push-down method, and deploy the application again with the CMP/A deployment tool.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY1100E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CMPAMSG11" varFormat="Java">
    CMPAMSG11=WQRY1100E: CSIException while getting a collection of associated keys of target relationship for the {0} Abstract Schema Name (ASN).
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The associated keys for the target relationship cannot be obtained.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the Abstract Schema Name (ASN) is correct, or install the application that has the ASN name, and deploy the application again with CMP/A deploy tool.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY1099E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CMPAMSG10" varFormat="Java">
    CMPAMSG10=WQRY1099E: {0} is an invalid method argument for CMP/A.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The method arguments for CMP/A must be literal or ?.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the method arguments, and deploy the application again with the CMP/A deployment tool.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0121E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="RLIINVMDA" varFormat="Java">
    RLIINVMDA=WQRY0121E: There is no mapping for the cmr field.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    No mapping exist for the container-managed relationship (CMR) field to the relational database table.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Create a valid mapping for the CMR field.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY1003E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="RTIE" varFormat="Java">
    RTIE=WQRY1003E: Runtime evaluation error - internal error encountered.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An internal error was encountered.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Restart the system. If the problem persists, refer to the IBM support Web site for information on problem determination.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0111E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="UTCEOC" varFormat="Java">
    UTCEOC=WQRY0111E: Incompatible data types for element {0} of a UNION operation.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    When performing a UNION operator, the SELECT statements that are operands to the UNION must contain elements in the SELECT clauses that are of compatible type.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the query statement for the enterprise Java bean (EJB).
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0010E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ATEO" varFormat="Java">
    ATEO=WQRY0010E: An argument type error was found in {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The query expression indicated attempts to compare two expressions that are not compatible in type.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the query statement for the enterprise Java bean (EJB).
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0123E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="FEOWEICF" varFormat="Java">
    FEOWEICF=WQRY0123E: An error occurred while executing dataFrom method [{0}] of converter [{1}].
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The following error occurred while executing dataFrom method.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    The converter that is specified in the schema needs to extend from the root class of com.ibm.vap.converters.VapAbstractConverter. Correct the implementation of dataFrom method, or correct the query statement for the enterprise Java bean (EJB).
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY1008E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="RTINVDF" varFormat="Java">
    RTINVDF=WQRY1008E: Runtime evaluation error - {0} is in a unsupported date/time format.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A DATE value was supplied that is not valid. The valid format for the string representation of the DATE are: (yyyynnn), (yyyyMMdd),(yyyyMMddhhmmss),(yyyy-MM-dd-hh.mm.ss.nnnnnn),(dd.MM.yyyy).
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Use the correct date/time format for literals in the query statement for the enterprise Java bean (EJB). Refer to the documentation for supported date/time formats.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY1081E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="UNIONINSDO" varFormat="Java">
    UNIONINSDO=WQRY1081E: Union is not allowed in mediator query.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The UNION operation is not allowed in a mediator query that returns Service Data Objects (SDOs).
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Remove the UNION operation from the query.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0115E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="VHTMFC" varFormat="Java">
    VHTMFC=WQRY0115E: internal metadata mapping error. View {0} has a type mismatch for field {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    There was an internal error mapping the metadata.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    This error indicates an internal error in the Application Server or the WSAD deployment tooling. Refer to the IBM support Web site for information on problem determination.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY1011E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="RTILBTM" varFormat="Java">
    RTILBTM=WQRY1011E: Runtime evaluation error - a boolean typed field mapped to unsupported type is detected.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The supported mapping for boolean types are SMALLINT, INTEGER.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the application schema.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0125E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="IETRBTICF" varFormat="Java">
    IETRBTICF=WQRY0125E: Invalid object type returned by the dataFrom method of converter [{0}].
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The return type from the dataFrom method is not supported by the query engine.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the dataFrom method, or use another converter.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0112E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="UTFMMSFMWPC" varFormat="Java">
    UTFMMSFMWPC=WQRY0112E: Unable to find matching method signature for method {0} with parm count {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The correct method signature was not found in the remote or local interface that is being used for the enterprise Java bean (EJB).
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the programming model for the EJB.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0120E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="RLIINVMAP" varFormat="Java">
    RLIINVMAP=WQRY0120E: Invalid metadata cmr mapping.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    There was mapping of container-managed relationship (CMR) field to relational table for a database that was not valid.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the mapping of the CMR field to the relational table.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0053E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MAXOFST" varFormat="Java">
    MAXOFST=WQRY0053E: Function MAX cannot be used in expression {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The MAX function is used with a data type that is not compatible. The message text contains the expression that is not correct.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the query statement for the enterprise Java bean (EJB).
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY1019E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="RTPPERR" varFormat="Java">
    RTPPERR=WQRY1019E: Runtime plan parsing error.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An internal error was detected in the plan parser.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Restart the system. If the problem persists, refer to the IBM support Web site for information on problem determination.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0016E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CCCTAV" varFormat="Java">
    CCCTAV=WQRY0016E: Field {0} cannot be cast to another schema name
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The query statement for the enterprise Java bean (EJB) does not support casting a container-managed persistence (CMP) field or a container-managed relationship (CMR) field to another type.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the query statement for the enterprise Java bean (EJB).
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0091E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="RWOAOISC" varFormat="Java">
    RWOAOISC=WQRY0091E: invalid use of the keyword OBJECT. OBJECT is only used in select clause {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The keyword OBJECT is used in the select clause to project the object reference that is associated with an identification variable.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the query statement for the enterprise Java bean (EJB).
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0062E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="NCOBUWCT" varFormat="Java">
    NCOBUWCT=WQRY0062E: Internal metadata error related to NEST and expression: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The collection aggregate operation NEST is used with an incorrect type.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    This error indicates an internal error in the Application Server or the WSAD deployment tooling. Refer to the IBM support Web site for information on problem determination.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0021E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CINAPSICBCAAPTAT" varFormat="Java">
    CINAPSICBCAAPTAT=WQRY0021E: Invalid casting of field {0} to a reference type
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The query statement for the enterprise Java bean (EJB) does not support casting a container-managed persistence (CMP) field or container-managed relationship (CMR) field to another type.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the query statement for the enterprise Java bean (EJB).
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0019E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CIA" varFormat="Java">
    CIA=WQRY0019E: Usage of field &apos;&apos;{0}&apos;&apos; is ambiguous
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A field must always be used in the context of a path expression that begins with an identification variable.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the query statement for the enterprise Java bean (EJB).
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY1086E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SDOHXPINV" varFormat="Java">
    SDOHXPINV=WQRY1086E: Incompatible data types for element {0} of a mediator query.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    When the same Data Objects are retrieved in mediator queries, the container-managed persistence (CMP) fields in all of the SELECT clauses must match.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the mediator query statement.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0128E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVPCMV" varFormat="Java">
    INVPCMV=WQRY0128E: Invalid SELECT clause containing a multi valued CMR field.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The SELECT clause cannot contain any container-managed relationship (CMR) fields that are mutli-valued.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the query statement for the enterprise Java bean (EJB).
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0132E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PKCITIND" varFormat="Java">
    PKCITIND=WQRY0132E: Primary key column {0} in table {1} is not defined.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Primary key that is specified in the metadata at the table level and the key that is provided at implementation time do not match.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    This error indicates an internal error in the WSAD deployment tooling. Refer to the IBM support Web site for information on problem determination.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0150E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="FNS" varFormat="Java">
    FNS=WQRY0150E: The function [{0}] is not a supported built-in function.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified function is not supported in query statements for enterprise Java beans (EJBs).
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the query statement for the EJB.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0038E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DOFST" varFormat="Java">
    DOFST=WQRY0038E: Operator / cannot be used in expression {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The division operator can only be used on numeric types.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the query statement for the enterprise Java bean (EJB).
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0106E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="TTNCP" varFormat="Java">
    TTNCP=WQRY0106E: Invalid path expression attempts to dereference a non reference field {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    There is schema information for the given field that is not consistent.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the query statement for the EJB or check the application model.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0113E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="VDFINASS" varFormat="Java">
    VDFINASS=WQRY0113E: internal metadata mapping error. The view definition for {0} is not a SELECT statement
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    There was an internal error mapping the metadata.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    This error indicates an internal error in the Application Server or the WSAD deployment tooling. Refer to the IBM support Web site for information on problem determination.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY1046E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="AGGNSP" varFormat="Java">
    AGGNSP=WQRY1046E: Aggregation in the top level query is not supported.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An aggregation operation (for example SUM, AVG, and so on) appears in the top level of the query. This is not supported by the query engine for the enterprise Java bean (EJB).
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the query statement for the EJB.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0122E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="FEOWLCC" varFormat="Java">
    FEOWLCC=WQRY0122E: Following error occurred while loading converter class: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The converter class that is used in the application schema cannot be found or instantiated, or the converter class is not a valid.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Add the converter class in the class path or correct the application schema.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0089E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="RVUFS" varFormat="Java">
    RVUFS=WQRY0089E: EJB Query does not support the syntax select *.:
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Do not use the &apos;select *&apos; statement in query statements for enterprise Java beans (EJBs). For example, you cannot use &apos;select * from XyzBean&apos; to select all of the container-managed persistence (CMP) fields for XyzBean.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the query statement for the EJB.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY1082E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="GROUPBYINSDO" varFormat="Java">
    GROUPBYINSDO=WQRY1082E: group by or having clause is not allowed in mediator query.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The GROUP BY or HAVING clauses are not allowed in a mediator query that returns Service Data Objects (SDOs).
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Remove the GROUP BY or HAVING clauses from the query.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY1022E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="RTAEDBZ" varFormat="Java">
    RTAEDBZ=WQRY1022E: Runtime evaluation error - An ArithmeticException occurred while evaluating the arithmetic expression [{0}]
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An ArithmeticException occurred because of division by zero.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the arithmetic expression.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY1085E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SDOHXP" varFormat="Java">
    SDOHXP=WQRY1085E: There are an unequal number of CMP fields in the mediator queries that retrieve the same Data Object type.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The SELECT statements must contain an equal number of elements in the SELECT clauses for queries that retrieve the same type of Data Object.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the query statement for the enterprise Java bean (EJB).
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0044E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="GOFST" varFormat="Java">
    GOFST=WQRY0044E: Operator &gt; cannot be used in expression {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The &quot;greater than&quot; operator can only be used with numeric, string, date-time or calendar types.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the query statement for the enterprise Java bean (EJB).
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0117E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="VTIUFCO" varFormat="Java">
    VTIUFCO=WQRY0117E: internal metadata mapping error. View type {0} is undefined for field {1} on {2}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    There was an internal error mapping the metadata.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    This error indicates an internal error in the Application Server or the WSAD deployment tooling. Refer to the IBM support Web site for information on problem determination.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0001E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="AEOEASQ" varFormat="Java">
    AEOEASQ=WQRY0001E: An error occurred while executing a SQL query: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An error occurred executing an SQL statement. The message text indicates the SQL statement that failed. This message only applies to the WebSphere dynamic query service.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the SQL statement that is failing is valid for the target database. If the database schema is inconsistent with the schema used during deployment, or the database schema has changed, it might be necessary to redeploy the application. Otherwise, refer to the IBM support web site for information on problem determination.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY1051E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="EJBCOLMSG2" varFormat="Java">
    EJBCOLMSG2=WQRY1051E: Invalid/null collection parameter object provided for the {0} Abstract Schema Name (ASN).
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An error occurred trying to get a collection parameter object for the Abstract Schema Name (ASN).
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the collection parameter object that was passed to the query engine, and run the query again.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY1050E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="EJBCOLMSG1" varFormat="Java">
    EJBCOLMSG1=WQRY1050E: Error - unique inverse relationship cannot be determined for {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An error occurred trying to identify an inverse relationship.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Deploy the application again, and restart the application.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY1001E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="RTUSTUO" varFormat="Java">
    RTUSTUO=WQRY1001E: Runtime evaluation error - the type of operands {0} are not supported in the given unary operation.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An evaluation error occurred at run time. The program cannot issue a unary operation on a type that is not supported.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the query statement for the enterprise Java bean (EJB), or correct the application schema.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0124E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="FEOWCTIAFTIC" varFormat="Java">
    FEOWCTIAFTIC=WQRY0124E: An error occurred while creating the input argument for the dataFrom method [{0}] of converter [{1}].
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The following error occurred while creating the input argument for dataFrom method.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the input value according to the converter.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0098E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="TNOPEINETTNOCFV" varFormat="Java">
    TNOPEINETTNOCFV=WQRY0098E: internal error in mapping metadata. The number of projection elements is not equal to the number of columns for view {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    There was an internal error mapping the metadata.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    This error indicates an internal error in the Application Server or the WSAD deployment tooling. Refer to the IBM support Web site for information on problem determination.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0076E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="OBPENCWD" varFormat="Java">
    OBPENCWD=WQRY0076E: ORDER BY operation conflicts with usage of DISTINCT. Remove ORDER BY or DISTINCT
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Performing a DISTINCT operation in a query statement for an enterprise Java bean (EJB) that returns object references might produce an ORDER BY on the primary key fields of the EJB. If the query statement contains an ORDER BY clause that is specified by the user, the two ordering schemas might conflict.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Remove either the ORDER BY or the DISTINCT operation, and retry the query statement for the EJB.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0015E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CCBCTAT" varFormat="Java">
    CCBCTAT=WQRY0015E: Field {0} cannot be cast to another type
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The query statement for the enterprise Java bean (EJB) does not support casting a container-managed persistence (CMP) field or a container-managed relationship (CMR) field to another type.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the query statement for the enterprise Java bean (EJB).
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY1027E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ACHGPKNF" varFormat="Java">
    ACHGPKNF=WQRY1027E: Internal error: Primary keys are not present in user&apos;s projection clause.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This is an internal error in the Application Server.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Refer to the IBM support Web site for information on problem determination.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY1088E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ACHGWDONA" varFormat="Java">
    ACHGWDONA=WQRY1088E: Update a field which may be the primary key or part of primary key is not allowed.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    There was an error trying to update a field that might be the primary key or part of the primary key.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the updates to the DataGraph.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0051E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="LEOFST" varFormat="Java">
    LEOFST=WQRY0051E: Operator &lt;= cannot be used in expression {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The &quot;less than or equal&quot; operator is used with a data type that is not compatible. The message text contains the expression that is not correct.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the query statement for the enterprise Java bean (EJB).
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0107E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="TTOFVT" varFormat="Java">
    TTOFVT=WQRY0107E: Attempt to use a table or schema named _THIS with identification variable &apos;&apos;{0}&apos;&apos;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The _THIS keyword is a reserved word and cannot be used in an query statement for an enterprise Java bean (EJB).
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Change the schema name in the deployment descriptor or in the table name.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0013E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CAA" varFormat="Java">
    CAA=WQRY0013E: Math error occurred while computing aggregate function
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A mathematical error occurred computing the value of an AVG or SUM function.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the query statement for the enterprise Java bean (EJB) or the values for the container-manager persistence (CMP) field.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY1036E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="RTAEOWPCFCD" varFormat="Java">
    RTAEOWPCFCD=WQRY1036E: Runtime evaluation error - An error occurred while processing changes from the updated datagraph [{0}]
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An error occurred while trying to apply the DataGraph changes to the database. The changes have not been applied to the database. For the case of updating, one or more OCC fields might have been changed by another user session, and the update is not allowed.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Change the updates, or make the appropriate change to the database based on the error.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0095E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="TETAATOCOQDMCTQP" varFormat="Java">
    TETAATOCOQDMCTQP=WQRY0095E: A mismatch between the actual table schema and the schema used as deployment time. The mismatch is related to column _c{0} on quantifier _q{1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The table schema that is provided does not match the schema that is used to generate the mapping metadata at deployment time.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check the table schema and the schema that is used to generate the mapping metadata at deployment time.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY1007E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="RTNOBJ" varFormat="Java">
    RTNOBJ=WQRY1007E: Runtime evaluation error - invalid converter {0}. A null is return from converter.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A &apos;null&apos; return was received from the converter that was specified.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the converter.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0105E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="TSTITAITCARARAKBJ" varFormat="Java">
    TSTITAITCARARAKBJ=WQRY0105E: internal error in mapping metadata. The mapping for attribute {0} type {1} does not include a key based join
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    There was an internal error mapping the metadata.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    This error indicates an internal error in the Application Server or the WSAD deployment tooling. Refer to the IBM support Web site for information on problem determination.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0118E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="VTND" varFormat="Java">
    VTND=WQRY0118E: internal metadata mapping error. View type {0} is not defined.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    There was an internal error mapping the metadata.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    This error indicates an internal error in the Application Server or the WSAD deployment tooling. Refer to the IBM support Web site for information on problem determination.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0079E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="OBYCLOB" varFormat="Java">
    OBYCLOB=WQRY0079E: Invalid ORDER BY due to ordering by a field of type CLOB.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Ordering on java.sql.clob values is not supported.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the query statement for the enterprise Java bean (EJB).
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0102E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="TROTSOABPIMTOV" varFormat="Java">
    TROTSOABPIMTOV=WQRY0102E: The result of the subquery used with a basic predicate is more than one value
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A subquery that is used with a basic predicate must only return a single value. Mutliple values were returned at run time when the subquery was evaluated.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the query statement for the enterprise Java bean (EJB).
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0057E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MOVCCBUITFC" varFormat="Java">
    MOVCCBUITFC=WQRY0057E: Internal metadata error related to methods over home collections in the FROM clause: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This error indicates an internal error in the Application Server or the WSAD deployment tooling.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Refer to the IBM support Web site for information on problem determination.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0066E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="NDI" varFormat="Java">
    NDI=WQRY0066E: Internal metadata error. An abstract schema {0} is not defined but is referenced in path expression {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This is an internal metadata error.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    This error indicates an internal error in the Application Server or the WSAD deployment tooling. Refer to the IBM support Web site for information on problem determination.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0068E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="NMBAPIISSN" varFormat="Java">
    NMBAPIISSN=WQRY0068E: Internal error relating to SELECT q.STARN
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This is an internal error in the Application Server or the WSAD deployment tooling.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Refer to the IBM support Web site for information on problem determination.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0064E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="NDF" varFormat="Java">
    NDF=WQRY0064E: Field {0} is not defined in the EJB schema: {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The parameter that is indicated is a container-managed persistence (CMP) field or a container-managed relationship (CMR) field. The message text indicates the schema that is used in the query.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the query statement for the enterprise Java bean (EJB).
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0101E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="TQUAPEFCIVMUN" varFormat="Java">
    TQUAPEFCIVMUN=WQRY0101E: internal error in mapping metadata. Missing NEST function for column {0} in view {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    There was an internal error mapping the metadata.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    This error indicates an internal error in the Application Server or the WSAD deployment tooling. Refer to the IBM support Web site for information on problem determination.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0045E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ICIS" varFormat="Java">
    ICIS=WQRY0045E: Illegal character has been found in the input stream.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An illegal character was used in the query statement for an enterprise Java bean (EJB). The &quot;Syntax error&quot; message that follows the &quot;Illegal Character&quot; error message shows the location and the type of the illegal character.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check the query statment for the EJB for characters that are not valid.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0114E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="VDMF" varFormat="Java">
    VDMF=WQRY0114E: internal metadata mapping error. A view definition is missing for {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    There was an internal error mapping the metadata.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    This error indicates an internal error in the Application Server or the WSAD deployment tooling. Refer to the IBM support Web site for information on problem determination.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0119E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WNOAUIF" varFormat="Java">
    WNOAUIF=WQRY0119E: Incorrect number of arguments used in function: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The number of arguments that are used in the query statement is not consistent with the definition of the function that is indicated in the message text.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the query statement for the enterprise Java bean (EJB).
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0056E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MOFST" varFormat="Java">
    MOFST=WQRY0056E: Function MIN cannot be used in expression {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The MIN function is used with a data type that is not compatible. The message text contains the expression that is not correct.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the query statement for the enterprise Java bean (EJB).
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0116E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="VHTMFCO" varFormat="Java">
    VHTMFCO=WQRY0116E: internal metadata mapping error. View {0} has a type mismatch for field {1} on {2}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    There was an internal error mapping the metadata.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    This error indicates an internal error in the Application Server or the WSAD deployment tooling. Refer to the IBM support Web site for information on problem determination.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0072E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="NQLIOAROQ" varFormat="Java">
    NQLIOAROQ=WQRY0072E: Internal error. No correlations left after removing optional correlations in rewrite.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This error indicates an internal error in the Application Server or the WSAD deployment tooling.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Refer to the IBM support Web site for information on problem determination.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY1006E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="RTIVCTR" varFormat="Java">
    RTIVCTR=WQRY1006E: Runtime evaluation error - the specified converter, {0}, cannot be found, instantiated or invalid
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The converter class that is used in the application schema cannot be found or instantiated, or the converter class is not valid.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Add the converter class in the class path, or correct the application schema.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0034E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DISMTOIAF" varFormat="Java">
    DISMTOIAF=WQRY0034E: DISTINCT is specified more than once in aggregate functions.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Do not use DISTINCT more than once in aggregate functions in a query.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the query statement for the enterprise Java bean (EJB).
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY1045E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ACHGTXRBF" varFormat="Java">
    ACHGTXRBF=WQRY1045E: An exception has been raised during transaction service setRollbackOnly call {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Application Server cannot set &apos;roll back only&apos; for the transaction service, because the status of the transaction is: javax.transaction.Status.STATUS_NO_TRANSACTION or the setRollbackOnly call resulted in an exception.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    The application is responsible for rolling back the transaction. Modify the programming model appropriately.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY1026E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="RTAEWTBTIM" varFormat="Java">
    RTAEWTBTIM=WQRY1026E: Runtime evaluation error - An exception was thrown by the invoked method {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The method that was invoked threw an exception.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the invoked method in the application model.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0097E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="TND" varFormat="Java">
    TND=WQRY0097E: internal error in mapping metadata. Entry {0} is not defined
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    There was an internal error mapping the metadata.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    This error indicates an internal error in the Application Server or the WSAD deployment tooling. Refer to the IBM support Web site for information on problem determination.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY1087E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVCMP" varFormat="Java">
    INVCMP=WQRY1087E: Mediator query must specify CMP fields in the selection.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The SELECT clause in a mediator query must contain container-managed persistence (CMP) fields or expressions that reference CMP fields. A constant expression is not allowed.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the query statement.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0135E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CNOBGBD" varFormat="Java">
    CNOBGBD=WQRY0135E: Cannot use order by, group by or distinct clause with CMP field [{0}] because the length of the underlying data type is too long.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    You cannot use GROUP BY, ORDER BY, or DISTINCT with data types like clob, blob or other long binary or character data types.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the query statement for the EJB or the mapping.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0154E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PATHINJOIN" varFormat="Java">
    PATHINJOIN=WQRY0154E: There is a usage of path expression in &apos;&apos;{0}&apos;&apos; that is not valid.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    There is a path expression with an identification variable in a JOIN clause that is not correctly used.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Change the query to reference the identification variable where path expression is used.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0042E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="FMTOMMSFMWPC" varFormat="Java">
    FMTOMMSFMWPC=WQRY0042E: Found more than one matching method signature for method {0} with parm count {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The only method overloading that Query allows is for a method to have different numbers of parameters.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the programming model for the enterprise Java bean (EJB).
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY1023E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="RTUOOAE" varFormat="Java">
    RTUOOAE=WQRY1023E: Runtime evaluation error - Underflow or Overflow occurred  while evaluating the arithmetic expression [{0}]
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The result of the arithmetic operation is not within the range of the result type that was expected.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the arithmetic expression.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY1061E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ACHGOCCNMVANP" varFormat="Java">
    ACHGOCCNMVANP=WQRY1061E: Internal error: The OCC name and value are not paired. {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An internal error occurred.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Refer to the IBM support Web site for information on problem determination.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0061E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="NAF" varFormat="Java">
    NAF=WQRY0061E: Nested aggregate functions are not allowed
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An aggregate function such as SUM cannot contain another aggregate function in the argument expression.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the query statement for the enterprise Java bean (EJB).
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0104E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="TSTASFOR" varFormat="Java">
    TSTASFOR=WQRY0104E: The second or third argument of the SUBSTR function is out of range
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The sum of the second and third arguments is greater than the length of the first argument
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the query statement for the enterprise Java bean (EJB).
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0067E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="NMBAPIISQSN" varFormat="Java">
    NMBAPIISQSN=WQRY0067E: Internal error relating to SELECT q.STARN
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This is an internal error in the Application Server or the WSAD deployment tooling.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Refer to the IBM support Web site for information on problem determination.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0087E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="QIDUAQDIASSWAGBC" varFormat="Java">
    QIDUAQDIASSWAGBC=WQRY0087E: Identification variable &apos;&apos;{0}&apos;&apos; is dependent upon another identification variable &apos;&apos;{1}&apos;&apos; defined in a SELECT statement with a GROUP BY clause
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The identification variable that is indicated in the message text is used in a subquery and references another identification variable, which is indicated in the message text, in a manner that is not supported.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the query statement for the enterprise Java bean (EJB).
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0030E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="COCC" varFormat="Java">
    COCC=WQRY0030E: Counter overflow occurred computing COUNT.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An overflow occurred while computing the COUNT aggregate function.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the query statement for the enterprise Java bean (EJB) to avoid the overflow.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0029E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="COCA" varFormat="Java">
    COCA=WQRY0029E: Counter overflow occurred computing AVG.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An overflow occurred while computing the AVG aggregate function.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the query statement for the enterprise Java bean (EJB) to avoid the overflow.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0086E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="QCBUAAECFL" varFormat="Java">
    QCBUAAECFL=WQRY0086E: The double-quote character cannot be used as an escape character for LIKE
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    In a query with a &apos;LIKE&apos; predicate using the &apos;ESCAPE&apos; keyword, the double-quote character cannot be used as the escape character for &apos;%&apos; or &apos;_&apos;.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the query statement for the enterprise Java bean (EJB).
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY1035E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="RTFEOWEWDOQ" varFormat="Java">
    RTFEOWEWDOQ=WQRY1035E: Runtime evaluation error - Following error occurred while executing ejb mediator query [{0}]
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    There was an error in executing the specified mediator query. The input parameters for the query are included in the message text.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the mediator query or the schema for the enterprise Java bean (EJB).
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0082E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="POFST" varFormat="Java">
    POFST=WQRY0082E: Operator + cannot be used in expression {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The PLUS operator is used with an data type for which it is not compatible. The message text contains the expression that is incorrect.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the query statement for the enterprise Java bean (EJB).
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0129E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="GBYMETH" varFormat="Java">
    GBYMETH=WQRY0129E: Invalid group by clause. Cannot use method {0} in group by clause.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This method mapping to a back-end data store is not supported
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the query statement for the enterprise Java bean (EJB).
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0085E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="QADO" varFormat="Java">
    QADO=WQRY0085E: Identification variable &apos;&apos;{0}&apos;&apos; is already defined over &apos;&apos;{1}&apos;&apos;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    You cannot use the same correlation ID to refer to more than one instance of an enterprise Java bean (EJB in the same select clause.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the query statement for the enterprise Java bean (EJB).
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY1043E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ACHGMAERROR" varFormat="Java">
    ACHGMAERROR=WQRY1043E: A MediatorAdapter is provided and handles creation of data object {0}, but does not handle update of the same data object.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A mediator adapter is supplied, however the adapter only handles partial operations for a data object.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Modify the mediator adapter, and run the operation again.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0090E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="RVUFSP" varFormat="Java">
    RVUFSP=WQRY0090E: An identification variable {0} not defined in a subquery cannot be used as {1}.* in the select clause of the subquery.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    In order to use &apos;e.*&apos; in a subquery, the identification variable &apos;e&apos; must be defined in the subquery.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the query statement for the enterprise Java bean (EJB).
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0100E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="TQUAPEFCIVCHAGBOHC" varFormat="Java">
    TQUAPEFCIVCHAGBOHC=WQRY0100E: internal error in mapping metadata. The subquery used for column {0} in view {1} cannot have a GROUP BY or HAVING clause
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    There was an internal error mapping the metadata.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    This error indicates an internal error in the Application Server or the WSAD deployment tooling. Refer to the IBM support Web site for information on problem determination.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0007E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ASECRFL" varFormat="Java">
    ASECRFL=WQRY0007E: The escape charater {0} for LIKE must be a single character.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The LIKE predicate takes a single escape character. The string specified in the message text is greater than one character in length and is not valid.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the query statement for the enterprise Java bean (EJB).
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0048E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVPCF" varFormat="Java">
    INVPCF=WQRY0048E: Invalid SELECT clause containing an expression, input parameter or multiple elements.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    When a query for an enterprise Java bean (EJB) is used to define FINDER or SELECT methods, the SELECT clause must contain a single element that refers to an EJB or a single-path expression that specifies a container-managed persistence (CMP) field or a single-valued container-managed relationship (CMR) field.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the query statement for the enterprise Java bean (EJB).
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0088E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="QITPCCBN" varFormat="Java">
    QITPCCBN=WQRY0088E: Invalid nesting of subqueries in a SELECT clause
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A subquery that is used in a SELECT clause cannot contain a subquery in its own SELECT clause.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the query statement for the enterprise Java bean (EJB).
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY1098E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CMPAMSG9" varFormat="Java">
    CMPAMSG9=WQRY1098E: Exception while getting foreign key for the target of {0} role name in the cache.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The foreign key for the target relationship cannot be obtained.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the CMP/A push-down method in the user-defined implementation class for the push-down method, and deploy the application again with CMP/A deployment tool.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY1097E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CMPAMSG8" varFormat="Java">
    CMPAMSG8=WQRY1097E: CSIException while getting  a collection of local/remote EJB objects for the {0} Abstract Schema name  (ASN).
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Abstract Schema Name (ASN) that is specified in the FROM clause of the query is not defined in any of the installed applications.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the ASN name is correct, or install the application that has the ASN name, and submit the query again.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0035E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DIVTINS" varFormat="Java">
    DIVTINS=WQRY0035E: Internal error in mapping metadata. Distinct in metadata {0} is not supported.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A DISTINCT operation appears in the mapping metadata. This is not currently supported by the query engine for the enterprise Java bean (EJB).
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    This indicates an internal error in the Application Server or the WSAD deployment tooling. Refer to the IBM support Web site for information on problem determination.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY1096E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CMPAMSG7" varFormat="Java">
    CMPAMSG7=WQRY1096E: InconsistentAccessIntentException while getting EJB local/remote object for the {0} Abstract Schema name (ASN).
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The access intent that is defined for the ASN in not valid.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the access intent, re-install the application, and run the program again.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY1095E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CMPAMSG6" varFormat="Java">
    CMPAMSG6=WQRY1095E: CSIException while getting EJB local/remote object for the {0} Abstract Schema name (ASN).
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Abstract Schema Name (ASN) that is specified in the FROM clause of the query is not defined in any of the installed applications.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the ASN name is correct, or install the application that has the ASN name, and submit the query again.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY1094E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CMPAMSG5" varFormat="Java">
    CMPAMSG5=WQRY1094E: The number of method arguments for method {0} does not match with any of methods defined in the CMP/A push-down methods list for {1} Abstract Schema Name(ASN).
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The number of method arguments does not match those that are defined in the push-down methods list of the CMP/A deployment tool.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the query, or add the method to the CMP/A push-down list.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY1093E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CMPAMSG4" varFormat="Java">
    CMPAMSG4=WQRY1093E: CSINoSuchObjectException while getting EJB local/remote object for the {0} Abstract Schema Name (ASN).
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Abstract Schema Name (ASN) that is specified in the FROM clause of the query is not defined in any of the installed applications.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the ASN name is correct, or install the application that has the ASN name, and submit the query again.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0084E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PUCNFOBOU" varFormat="Java">
    PUCNFOBOU=WQRY0084E: Invalid use of path expression in ORDER BY. When using ORDER BY with a UNION operation the ORDER BY must use integer constants
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    When using ORDER BY clause with a UNION operation, the ORDER BY clause must use integer constants to indicate the container-managed persistence (CMP) attributes in the enterprise Java bean (EJB) that is being queried.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the query statement for the EJB.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY1092E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CMPAMSG3" varFormat="Java">
    CMPAMSG3=WQRY1092E: EJBContainerException while getting EJB home for the {0} Abstract Schema Name (ASN).
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Abstract Schema Name (ASN) that is specified in the FROM clause of the query is not defined in any of the installed applications.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the ASN name is correct, or install the application that has the ASN name, and submit the query again.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY1091E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CMPAMSG2" varFormat="Java">
    CMPAMSG2=WQRY1091E: CSIException while getting concrete bean class for the {0} J2EEName.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Abstract Schema Name (ASN) that is specified in the FROM clause of the query is not defined in any of the installed applications.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the ASN name is correct, or install the application that has the ASN name, and submit the query again.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY1090E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CMPAMSG1" varFormat="Java">
    CMPAMSG1=WQRY1090E: The {0} abstract schema name is not defined in the metadata.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    No such Abstract Schema Name (ASN) is defined in the metadata that was generated by a CMP/A deploy tool.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check your application, and deploy the application again with CMP/A deploy tool.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0127E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="TMAAICF" varFormat="Java">
    TMAAICF=WQRY0127E: Type Mismatch after applying dataFrom method of converter [{0}].
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The output type of the dataFrom method is not compatible in the given expression.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the query statement for the enterprise Java bean (EJB) or the converter.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY1044E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ACHGTXNF" varFormat="Java">
    ACHGTXNF=WQRY1044E: An exception has been raised during transaction service lookup {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Application Server cannot perform a lookup for the transaction service because the user application is a container-managed bean.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    The application is responsible for rolling back the transaction. Modify the programming model appropriately.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0133E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="UTOPLSTQ" varFormat="Java">
    UTOPLSTQ=WQRY0133E: Unable to obtain pessimistic lock since the query contains joins, subselects, order by, and group by.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The query statement for the enterprise Java bean (EJB) that contains JOINS, SUBSELECTS, ORDER BY, and GROUP BY cannot be run in pessimistic access intent.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Reconfigure the access intent, or change the query statement for the EJB.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY1028E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ACHGPKVNULL" varFormat="Java">
    ACHGPKVNULL=WQRY1028E: Primary key {0} value is null.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    There was an error trying to create a Service Data Object (SDO) without the primary key.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the updates to the datagraph.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0012E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="BTMM" varFormat="Java">
    BTMM=WQRY0012E: Invalid entity bean comparison due to types mismatch.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    You cannot use the &quot;equal or not equal&quot; predicate to compare two enterprise Java beans (EJBs) that cannot be compared. Only EJBs that are of compatible types and from the same home can be compared.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the query statement for the enterprise Java bean (EJB).
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY1062E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CDNHF" varFormat="Java">
    CDNHF=WQRY1062E: Class {0} does not have a feature named {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The static schema for the specified EClass does not have the named feature defined.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Redefine the static schema or the mediator query.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY1029E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ACHGPKVNP" varFormat="Java">
    ACHGPKVNP=WQRY1029E: Internal error in deletion: No Primary keys found or Primary keys name/value are not paired.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This is an internal error in the Application Server.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Refer to the IBM support Web site for information on problem determination.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0153E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="UIDJOIN" varFormat="Java">
    UIDJOIN=WQRY0153E: The identifier {0} is not defined within the scope of a JOIN clause.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The identifier must be defined within a JOIN clause.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the query statement for the enterprise Java bean (EJB).
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0103E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="TSCOASSMC" varFormat="Java">
    TSCOASSMC=WQRY0103E: The SELECT clause of a subquery is invalid because it specifies multiple columns
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A subselect statement can only return a single value.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the query statement for the enterprise Java bean (EJB).
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0069E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="NNEI" varFormat="Java">
    NNEI=WQRY0069E: A non numeric expression was used with {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A function that requires a numeric expression was used incorrectly with an argument expression. The message text shows the function.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the query statement for the enterprise Java bean (EJB).
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY1024E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="RTORBCDNMEOT" varFormat="Java">
    RTORBCDNMEOT=WQRY1024E: Runtime evaluation error - The object type [{2}] returned by the converter class [{0}] does not match the expected object type [{1}]
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The object that was returned by the objectFrom method of the converter is not the same as the object type that was expected.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Modify the converter class, or correct the application schema.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0080E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="OBYMETH" varFormat="Java">
    OBYMETH=WQRY0080E: Invalid order by clause. Cannot use method {0} in order by clause.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Method mapping to back-end data store is not currently supported.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the query statement for the enterprise Java bean (EJB).
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0006E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="AQIDUAQDIASSWAGBC" varFormat="Java">
    AQIDUAQDIASSWAGBC=WQRY0006E: An identification variable is dependent upon another identification variable ({0}) defined in a SELECT statement with a GROUP BY clause
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The identification variable is used in a subquery and references another identification variable, indicated in the message text, in a manner that is not supported.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the query statement for the enterprise Java bean (EJB).
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0011E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="AWCOASCCACF" varFormat="Java">
    AWCOASCCACF=WQRY0011E: The aggregate function {0} is used incorrectly or has an invalid argument
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The aggregate function (for example SUM, COUNT, and so on) indicated by the message text is not used correctly (such as being used in a WHERE clause), or the function contains an argument that is not valid (an expression that contains correlated and noncorrelated values).
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the query statement for the enterprise Java bean (EJB).
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0126E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ILGBCMRF" varFormat="Java">
    ILGBCMRF=WQRY0126E: Illegal to group by CMR field.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Container-managed relationship refers to an enterprise Java bean (EJB) object, and the object reference cannot be used in the GROUP BY clause.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the query statement for the enterprise Java bean (EJB).
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0041E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ERDQE" varFormat="Java">
    ERDQE=WQRY0041E: An exception has been raised during query evaluation.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An unknown exception occurred during the query evalution. If the query statement calls user-defined methods, verify that the method is not throwing an exception. Otherwise, this is an internal error.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If you are unable to resolve problem, refer to the IBM support Web site for information on problem determination.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0024E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CIOBLNE" varFormat="Java">
    CIOBLNE=WQRY0024E: Order by clause refers to an invalid element {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The ORDER BY clause of a query statement refers to a select element by an ordinal number that is indicated in the message text, but no such element exists.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the query statement for the enterprise Java bean (EJB).
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY1021E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="RTOBJFM" varFormat="Java">
    RTOBJFM=WQRY1021E: Runtime evaluation error - An error {0} occurred while executing objectFrom of class {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An exception occurred while executing the objectFrom method.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the class exists and that the arguments are correct.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0131E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="VIAIETFE" varFormat="Java">
    VIAIETFE=WQRY0131E: Void is an invalid  expression type for expression [{0}].
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Expressions with the type &apos;void&apos; should not be used in a query statement for an enterprise Java bean (EJB).
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the application schema, or correct the query statement for the EJB.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY1060E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MRTIE" varFormat="Java">
    MRTIE=WQRY1060E: Runtime evaluation error - The following internal error occurred for the mediator query [{0}].
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An internal error occurred.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Restart your system. If the problem persists, refer to the IBM support Web site for information on problem determination.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0050E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ISNNAWC" varFormat="Java">
    ISNNAWC=WQRY0050E: The field {0} cannot be used with the IS NULL predicate because it is a collection valued CMR field
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    IS NULL and IS NOT NULL must be used in path expresssions with container-managed persistence (CMP) fields or single-valued container-managed relationship (CMR) fields.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the query statement for the enterprise Java bean (EJB).
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0014E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CBAAF" varFormat="Java">
    CBAAF=WQRY0014E: Cannot define identification variable &apos;&apos;{0}&apos;&apos; over expression &apos;&apos;{1}&apos;&apos;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The identification variable specified is defined over an not valid association because the schema of the association contains no persistent fields.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check the query statement for the enterprise Java bean (EJB), or check the application model.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WQRY0060E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MTQAUITQ" varFormat="Java">
    MTQAUITQ=WQRY0060E: Query is too complex. More than {0} quantifiers are used in the query plan
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A maximum of 512 quantifiers can be used in the query plan that is generated by the query statement for the enterprise Java bean (EJB).
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Reduce the complexity of the query statement for the EJB.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<!-- END MESSAGES -->
</TMSSource>
