<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/css" href="../../resources/stylesheets/wasmsgxml.css"?>
<TMSSource name="TivoliMessages" tmsVersion="1.0" xml:lang="en">
<!-- CMVC MSG File Name = ws/code/adapter/src/resources/IBMDataStoreAdapterNLS.nlsprops -->
<!-- DO NOT EDIT THIS FILE - This file was generated by the XML/Html & Property emitter -->
<!-- BEGIN MESSAGES -->
<Message ID="DSRA7013E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DB2ZOS_CONFIG_ERROR" varFormat="Java">
    DB2ZOS_CONFIG_ERROR=DSRA7013E: Wrong configuration : JDBC driver does not support setDriverType
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The driverType custom property for the data source is not supported by the JDBC driver.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Remove the driverType from the custom properties for the data source.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA7605E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PROVIDER_NOT_FOUND" varFormat="Java">
    PROVIDER_NOT_FOUND=DSRA7605E: Internal error, providerType not found based on {0}, returning null
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The providerType was not found.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Visit the IBM support Web site for information on problem determination. Use the following data to help determine the possible causes of the error.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA7600E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CLOUDSCAPE_MIGRATION_FAILURE" varFormat="Java">
    CLOUDSCAPE_MIGRATION_FAILURE=DSRA7600E: Cloudscape migration of database instance {0} to new database instance {1} failed, reason: {2}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The migration of the Cloudscape instance failed, see the exception and the &lt;dbinstance&gt;_migration.log that is located in WAS_HOME/profiles/&lt;profileName&gt;/logs directory for details.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Fix the migration problem as described by the exception and the migration log. Delete the newly created database if it exists, and manually run the database migration tool again (WAS_HOME/derby/bin/embedded/db2jMigrate.bat/sh).
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA0080E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DSA_ERROR" varFormat="Java">
    DSA_ERROR=DSRA0080E: An exception was received by the Data Store Adapter. See original exception message: {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The database backend generated an exception that was caught by the Data Store Adapter.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Refer to the error text reported by the database software for possible sources of the error.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA0024E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DS_CREATE_ERROR" varFormat="Java">
    DS_CREATE_ERROR=DSRA0024E: The DataSource could not be created from implementation class &quot;{0}&quot;.  The exception is: {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An error occurred instantiating the data source.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify the data source class has a public constructor that is taking no parameters.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA0050W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DSA_INTERNAL_WARNING" varFormat="Java">
    DSA_INTERNAL_WARNING=DSRA0050W: Data Store Adapter internal warning occurred. Please contact WebSphere support with the following data: {0} {1} {2}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This exception is unexpected. The cause is not immediately known.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Visit the IBM support Web site for information on problem determination.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA9547W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SERVICE_ADDITION_FAILURE_DSRA9547W" varFormat="Java">
    SERVICE_ADDITION_FAILURE_DSRA9547W=DSRA9547W: The application server could not add the {0} service. The exception is: {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The application server could not add the service that was specified. Examine the exception for details.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the exception, and correct the problem. Restart the application server.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA8760W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="VENDOR_IMPL_NOT_FOUND" varFormat="Java">
    VENDOR_IMPL_NOT_FOUND=DSRA8760W: Unable to locate the implementation for vendor interface {0} after switching to another pooled connection. The unwrapped connection handle is no longer usable as that interface. The new connection implementation class is: {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The connection handle is now associated with a pooled connection that is different and that does not implement the interface that is requested for the wrapper.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Wrappers for the interface that is specified should not be used when the Wrapper.isWrapperFor method indicates that the connection is not a wrapper of the interface.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA0310E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="XID_MISMATCH" varFormat="Java">
    XID_MISMATCH=DSRA0310E: Xids do not match.
XAResource.start: {0}
XAResource.{1}: {2}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Application Server attempted to perform an XAResource operation with an Xid other than the Xid that is used for XAResource.start.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Obtain a new connection and attempt the transaction again.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA3608E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DSRA3608E" varFormat="Java">
    DSRA3608E=DSRA3608E: Invalid parameter value {0} for parameter {1} of type {2} for the {3} step of the {4} command.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The command step was not run because a parameter value that is not valid was specified for a resource property that is required.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    This problem usually occurs when the parameter value does not conform to the parameter type. Correct the problem, and try the operation again.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA7026W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="AUTHENTICATION_IMPLEMENTATION_WARNING" varFormat="Java">
    AUTHENTICATION_IMPLEMENTATION_WARNING=DSRA7026W: Connection Reauthentication cannot be enabled without overwriting the doConnectionSetupPerTransaction DataStoreHelper method to provide actual connection authentication implementation.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Reauthentication property is enabled, and the implementation code for the connection reauthentication in the DataStoreHelper class was not provided.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Overwrite the doConnectionSetupPerTransaction DataStoreHelper method and provide the connection reauthentication implementation code, or disable connection reauthentication by one of the following: 1) Clear the &quot;Enable database reauthentication&quot; option for the Datasource properties in the Application Server or 2) set the reauthentication custom property to false for the data source.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA7018I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="META_DATA_EXCEPTION" varFormat="Java">
    META_DATA_EXCEPTION=DSRA7018I: Database metadata access caused a non-stale connection exception.  Normal execution is resumed.  Exception is: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An exception occurred when the Application Server was trying to get or access the metadata object for the database.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the metadata is enabled on the backend database.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA8222E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="UNABLE_TO_CREATE_TRUSTED_CONNECTION" varFormat="Java">
    UNABLE_TO_CREATE_TRUSTED_CONNECTION=DSRA8222E: The application server was not able to create a trusted connection to the data source.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The application server could not create a trusted connection to the data source.  The JDBC driver did not return a valid connection, or returned an error that was not expected.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the exception, if available, and verify that the JDBC driver and database server support trusted context.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA3607E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DSRA3607E" varFormat="Java">
    DSRA3607E=DSRA3607E: The {0} step of the {1} command requires a value for the {2} resource property of type {3}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The command step was not run because a value was not specified for a resource property that is required.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    This is usually a problem with the command parameters. Correct the problem, and try the operation again.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA8209I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="JDBC_DRIVER_DEPRECATED" varFormat="Java">
    JDBC_DRIVER_DEPRECATED=DSRA8209I: WebSphere Application Server support for the {0} JDBC driver is deprecated. Consequently, it might not be officially certified with future WebSphere Application Server releases. If possible, consider using the {1} JDBC driver instead.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified JDBC driver might not be officially certified in future releases of the Application Server.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Continue using the JDBC driver or switch to a JDBC driver that is recommended.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA1000E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MESSAGE_INFLOW_NOT_SUPPORTED" varFormat="Java">
    MESSAGE_INFLOW_NOT_SUPPORTED=DSRA1000E: The WebSphere Relational Resource Adapter does not support message inflow.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The ResourceAdapter.endpointActivation method should not be used on the Relational Resource Adapter for the Application Server because it does not support message inflow.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Do not use the ResourceAdapter.endpointActivation method on the Relational Resource Adapter for the Application Server.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA3606E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DSRA3606E" varFormat="Java">
    DSRA3606E=DSRA3606E: Unable to update {0} resource property name of type {1} with value {2}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The command was not able to update the resource property that was specified with the value that was specified.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a value for the resource property that is valid, and try the operation again.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA0403W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="TBC_JCC_NOT_SUPPORTED" varFormat="Java">
    TBC_JCC_NOT_SUPPORTED=DSRA0403W: Datasource {0}: does not support tight branch coupling as the DB2 JCC driver is at an incorrect level
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The jdbc provider specified by datasource does not support the tight branch coupling option.  Tight branch coupling is only supported with minimum levels of DB2 Universal JCC driver version 3.51 or 3.6, as bundled with DB2 9.5 or 9 service levels, or the JCC4 driver version 4.1.  The default option of loose branch coupling will be used.  This may cause lock timeouts, deadlocks and/or transaction rollbacks if the application is designed for tight branch coupling since database locks will not be shared across transaction branches within the same global transaction.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    You must configure the datasource to use a supported level of JDBC driver and database, or configure your application to not require tight branch coupling.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA8160E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PARSE_ERROR" varFormat="Java">
    PARSE_ERROR=DSRA8160E: The application server is not able to parse data source custom property {0} near {1}. The full property value is {2}. Refer to the chained exception for more information.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The application server is not able to parse the value that is supplied for the data source custom property.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the data source custom property is specified correctly.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA0035W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DSA_INTERNAL_ERR_WARNING" varFormat="Java">
    DSA_INTERNAL_ERR_WARNING=DSRA0035W: DataStore Adapter internal error occurred. Please contact WebSphere support with the following information: {0} {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This exception is unexpected. The cause is not immediately known.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Visit the IBM support Web site for information on problem determination.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA9530E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="OBJECT_CANNOT_BE_CLONED" varFormat="Java">
    OBJECT_CANNOT_BE_CLONED=DSRA9530E: The object {0} is not cloneable.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The object cannot be cloned.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Do not call the clone() method.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA8010W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CANT_READ_SETTERS" varFormat="Java">
    CANT_READ_SETTERS=DSRA8010W: Unable to read setter methods from DataSource class.  Encountered {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An IntrospectionException occurred attempting to retrieve setter methods from the data source.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    The data source properties will not show up in the graphical user interface (GUI). You will need to enter them manually.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA7033E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="TRUSTED_WITH_AUTHENTICATION_IMPLEMENTATION_ERROR" varFormat="Java">
    TRUSTED_WITH_AUTHENTICATION_IMPLEMENTATION_ERROR=DSRA7033E: You cannot enable the useTrustedContextWithAuthentication custom property for the data source without overwriting the getPasswordForUseWithTrustedContextWithAuthentication DataStoreHelper.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The useTrustedContextWithAuthentication custom property is enabled, but the implementation code for the DataStoreHelper method that will return the password that the application server will use to switch the identity is not provided.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Overwrite the getPasswordForUseWithTrustedContextWithAuthentication DataStoreHelper method and provide the implementation code that will return the password, or set the useTrustedContextWithAuthentication custom property for the data source to false.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA3605E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DSRA3605E" varFormat="Java">
    DSRA3605E=DSRA3605E: The {0} step of the {1} command failed for the following reason: {2}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The command step did not complete successfully. This is usually a problem with the command parameters.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Evaluate the reason that is specified in the message to determine the problem. Correct the problem, and try the operation again.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA9130E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="OPERATION_NOT_PERMITTED" varFormat="Java">
    OPERATION_NOT_PERMITTED=DSRA9130E: Operation is not permitted by the application server: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Application Server does not permit the operation that was requested.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Do not use the operation that is specified.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA9510W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="NO_EMPTY_PRE_TEST_SQL_STRING" varFormat="Java">
    NO_EMPTY_PRE_TEST_SQL_STRING=DSRA9510W: Custom property preTestSQLString should not be empty if the pre-test connection option is selected.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The preTestSQLString custom property cannot be empty if the pretest connection option is selected. If you choose to leave the preTestSQLString property unspecified, performance might be affected.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Provide an SQL statement for preTestSQLString that is valid.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA7000W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="NO_EXCPT_MAP" varFormat="Java">
    NO_EXCPT_MAP=DSRA7000W: Mapped Exception could not be instantiated, reason: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Application Server could not map the exception. Refer to the exception that occurred during the mapping.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify the exception mapping in the error map table for the DataStoreHelper and in the exception constructor.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA9250E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="OP_NOT_SHAREABLE" varFormat="Java">
    OP_NOT_SHAREABLE=DSRA9250E: Operation {0} is not allowed during a global transaction for Shareable Connections.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Application Server does not allow calls to the setTypeMap, setReadOnly or setCatalog methods on Shareable Connections while a global transaction is active.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Do not call setTypeMap, setReadOnly or setCatalog on Shareable Connections in a global transaction, or switch to Unshareable Connections.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA3604E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DSRA3604E" varFormat="Java">
    DSRA3604E=DSRA3604E: Unable to locate a datasource template for provider name: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The command was not run because an JDBC provider was specified that is not valid.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a JDBC provider that is valid, and try the operation again.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA8216W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CR_JNDINAME_CONFIG_PROBLEM" varFormat="Java">
    CR_JNDINAME_CONFIG_PROBLEM=DSRA8216W: Unable to configure client reroute server list JNDI name on the data source class {0}.  Exception: {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Application Server received an exception when attempting to configure a data source with the client reroute method on the Java Naming and Directory Interface (JNDI) name.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the exception, correct the problem, and restart the Application Server.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA7028E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="IDENTITY_PROPAGATION_CONFLICT2_ERROR" varFormat="Java">
    IDENTITY_PROPAGATION_CONFLICT2_ERROR=DSRA7028E: You cannot use the TrustedConnectionMapping login configuration when the ThreadIdentity property is enabled.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The ThreadIdentity property cannot be enabled when you are using the TrustedConnectionMapping login configuration.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Disable the ThreadIdentity property for the data source, or do not use the TrustedConnectionMapping login configuration.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA3603E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DSRA3603E" varFormat="Java">
    DSRA3603E=DSRA3603E: Unable to locate a JDBC provider template for provider name: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The command was not run because a provider name was specified that is not valid.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a value for the provider name that is valid, and try the operation again.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA9410E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CANNOT_REASSOCIATE" varFormat="Java">
    CANNOT_REASSOCIATE=DSRA9410E: Handle reassociation is allowed only from the INACTIVE state. Current Connection state is {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Connection handles can only be reassociated from the INACTIVE state.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Close your current Connection handle, and obtain a new one.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA8660W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ERR_CLOSING_PARENT" varFormat="Java">
    ERR_CLOSING_PARENT=DSRA8660W: Error closing the ResultSet&apos;&apos;s parent Statement, {0}
{1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An error occurred closing the statement.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA7604I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CLOUDSCAPE_MIGRATION_DELETION_DONE" varFormat="Java">
    CLOUDSCAPE_MIGRATION_DELETION_DONE=DSRA7604I: Done deleting newly created Derby database {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Attempt to delete the newly created Derby database was successful.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required. This is an information message.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA8054W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HELPER_CTOR_ERR" varFormat="Java">
    HELPER_CTOR_ERR=DSRA8054W: DataStoreHelper, &apos;&apos;{0}&apos;&apos;, constructor issued following exception: {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The DataStoreHelper constructor issued an exception.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the properties that are passed to the constructor are correct, and verify that the DataStoreHelper constructor is implemented correctly.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA8150E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CLASS_LOAD_ERROR" varFormat="Java">
    CLASS_LOAD_ERROR=DSRA8150E: The data source custom property {0} contains an exception class that cannot be loaded: {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The application server is unable to load the specified class.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the data source custom property is specified correctly and is accessible to the application server.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA9602W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CMX_MONITORING_CHECKING_PROBLEM" varFormat="Java">
    CMX_MONITORING_CHECKING_PROBLEM=DSRA9602W: The application server received an exception when calling isMonitoringEnabled.  Disabling CMX End-to-End monitoring feature. The exception is: {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The application server received an exception when attempting to check if CMX monitoring is enabled.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the exception and the possible cause, fix the problem, and restart the application server.  Visit the WebSphere support website for troubleshooting help if you cannot resolve the issue after examining the exception.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA7029W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="IDENTITY_PROPAGATION_PROP_WARNING" varFormat="Java">
    IDENTITY_PROPAGATION_PROP_WARNING=DSRA7029W: The propagateClientIdentityUsingTrustedContext custom property for the data source is no longer used, value will be ignored.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The propagateClientIdentityUsingTrustedContext custom property for the data source is no longer used, application server runtime will enable Trusted Connection feature if TrustedConnectionMapping login configuration is used.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Delete the propagateClientIdentityUsingTrustedContext custom property for the data source.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA3602E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DSRA3602E" varFormat="Java">
    DSRA3602E=DSRA3602E: Invalid {0} parameter value specified: {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The command was not run because a value for a parameter was specified that is not valid.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a value for the specified parameter that is valid, and try the command again.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA7010E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DB2_FILE_OUTSTREAM_ERROR" varFormat="Java">
    DB2_FILE_OUTSTREAM_ERROR=DSRA7010E: trace file specified {0} does not exist, an exception will be thrown from the database if problem is not corrected.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The trace file that you specified on the data source does not exist.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Use an existing file for the trace file.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA0070E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="OBJECT_CLOSED_CANNOT_RUN" varFormat="Java">
    OBJECT_CLOSED_CANNOT_RUN=DSRA0070E: {0} is closed. Unable to perform: {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Application Server attempted to perform an operation on an object that is closed.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Retrieve a new instance of the object and attempt the operation again.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA8206I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="JDBC_DRIVER_VERSION" varFormat="Java">
    JDBC_DRIVER_VERSION=DSRA8206I: JDBC driver version  : {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The version of the Java Database Connectivity (JDBC) driver.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    The version that is listed above for the JDBC driver is now being used by applications.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA9121E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="NOT_A_JDBC_OBJECT" varFormat="Java">
    NOT_A_JDBC_OBJECT=DSRA9121E: Unable invoke method. Object is not a valid WebSphere JDBC Object.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    It is not allowed to use the &apos;jdbcCall&apos; method from the Application Server on objects that are not JDBC objects.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Use the &apos;jdbcCall&apos; method from the Application Server with JDBC objects only.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA7017I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ORACLE_TRACE_WARNING" varFormat="Java">
    ORACLE_TRACE_WARNING=DSRA7017I: Logging to file {0} cannot occur because of IOException {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An IOException occurred when the Application Server was trying to open the trace file that was specified.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the exception, fix the IO problem, and start the Application Server again.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA7032W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_EXTENDED_PROPERTY" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_EXTENDED_PROPERTY=DSRA7032W: The {0} datasource property can not be specified in the {1}. The {0} datasource property will be ignored.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The data source property is not valid in this context.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required. The Application Server will ignore the property at run time.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA7024I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="IDENTITY_PROPAGATION_CONFLICT1_INFO" varFormat="Java">
    IDENTITY_PROPAGATION_CONFLICT1_INFO=DSRA7024I: The reauthentication custom property for the data source cannot be enabled if TrustedConnectionMapping login configuration is used.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The reauthentication custom property for the data source cannot be enabled if TrustedConnectionMapping login configuration is used.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Disable the reauthentication custom property for the data source if TrustedConnectionMapping login configuration is used.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA3601E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DSRA3601E" varFormat="Java">
    DSRA3601E=DSRA3601E: {0} command failed for the following reason: {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The command did not complete successfully.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Evaluate the reason that is specified in the message to determine the problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA0022E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DSIMPLCLASS_NULL" varFormat="Java">
    DSIMPLCLASS_NULL=DSRA0022E: The DataSource implementation class is null.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A valid class name for a data source implementation is required when creating a JDBC provider.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Enter a valid class name for a data source implementation and attempt the operation again.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA9538W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="NON_TRANSACTIONAL_DATASOURCE_CONFLICT_WARNING_DSRA9538W" varFormat="Java">
    NON_TRANSACTIONAL_DATASOURCE_CONFLICT_WARNING_DSRA9538W=DSRA9538W: The jmsOnePhaseOptimization custom property for data sources takes precedence over the nonTransactionalDataSource custom property for data sources.  The Application Server will disable the nonTransactionalDataSource custom property on the data source at run time.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The nonTransactionalDataSource custom property cannot be enabled when the jmsOnePhaseOptimization custom property for data sources is enabled.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Disable the nonTransactionalDataSource or the jmsOnePhaseOptimization data source custom property.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA0095I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="IMPLICIT_TRANSACTION_FOUND" varFormat="Java">
    IMPLICIT_TRANSACTION_FOUND=DSRA0095I: A database transaction that is not tracked by WebSphere is found, attemping to rollback before cleaning connection. This message will be logged once for each DataSource. Subsequent implicit transactions will be resolved automatically.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The database has started a transaction on the connection. The Application Server will rollback the transaction before returning the connection to the pool.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Evaluate the application code to determine what might be causing the implicit transaction. The application code might be able to prevent further implicit transactions explicity, or you could configure an explicit action to take for the data source.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA9420E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CHILDREN_STILL_OPEN" varFormat="Java">
    CHILDREN_STILL_OPEN=DSRA9420E: Connection cannot be reassociated because child objects are still open.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Connection handles can only be reassociated if all the child objects are closed.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Close your current Connection handle, and obtain a new one.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA7027W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="KERBEROS_METHOD_NOT_SUPPORTED_WARNING" varFormat="Java">
    KERBEROS_METHOD_NOT_SUPPORTED_WARNING=DSRA7027W: A failure occurred during a getPooledConnection method that was using Kerberos credentials.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Application Server could not establish a connection to the database using Kerberos.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Resolve the problem that is described by referring to the exception that was created. Also, validate that the application is running with a version of the JDBC driver that supports getting connections using GSSCredentials.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA3600E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DSRA3600E" varFormat="Java">
    DSRA3600E=DSRA3600E: Validation for command {0} failed for the following reason: {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The command did not run because validation did not complete successfully.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Evaluate the reason that is specified in the message to determine the problem. This is usually a problem with the command parameters. Correct the problem, and try the operation again.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA9900I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="UNABLE_TO_CLEAN_UP" varFormat="Java">
    UNABLE_TO_CLEAN_UP=DSRA9900I: The application server cannot automatically clean up resource type {0} because the JDBC driver does not comply with JDBC {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The application server attempts to clean up some resources in case the application relies on closing the connection to free some resources. The application server&apos;s ability to release certain resources is limited by the JDBC specification compliance level of the JDBC driver.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    The application should ensure the resource is properly cleaned up instead of relying on closing the connection.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA9546W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SERVICE_LOOKUP_FAILURE_DSRA9546W" varFormat="Java">
    SERVICE_LOOKUP_FAILURE_DSRA9546W=DSRA9546W: The application server could not lookup the {0} service. The exception is: {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The application server could not lookup the service that was specified. Examine the exception for details.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the exception, and correct the problem. Restart the application server.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA8750W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="UNSUPPORTED_JDBC30_METHOD" varFormat="Java">
    UNSUPPORTED_JDBC30_METHOD=DSRA8750W: The JDBC 3.0 method {0} is not implemented on this JDBC Provider.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The method being invoked is part of the Java Database Connectivty (JDBC) specification V3.0, and the method does not exist on the provider.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that your JDBC provider supports the JDBC specification V3.0, or do not use this method.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA0304E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DISPLAY_XAEX_CONTENT" varFormat="Java">
    DISPLAY_XAEX_CONTENT=DSRA0304E:  XAException occurred. XAException contents and details are: {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A two-phase operation on the database resulted in an exception.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA0030E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DSA_INTERNAL_ERROR" varFormat="Java">
    DSA_INTERNAL_ERROR=DSRA0030E: Data Store Adapter internal error occurred. Please contact WebSphere support with the following data:  {0} {1} {2}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This exception is unexpected. The cause is not immediately known.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Visit the IBM support Web site for information on problem determination.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA8215W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CR_CONTEXT_CONFIG_PROBLEM" varFormat="Java">
    CR_CONTEXT_CONFIG_PROBLEM=DSRA8215W: Unable to configure client reroute server list JNDI context on the data source class {0}.  Exception: {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Application Server received an exception when attempting to configure a data source with the client reroute method. This could be caused by the use of an older level of a JCC driver.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check the level of the JCC driver, examine the exception, correct the problem, and restart the Application Server.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA9360E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_TRAN_STATE" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_TRAN_STATE=DSRA9360E: Unable to perform the requested operation from the following transaction state: {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    You cannot perform operations when the application is in the current transaction state.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Get a new Connection on which to perform the operation.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA7042W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ORACLE_DRIVER_UNSUPPORTED_WARNING" varFormat="Java">
    ORACLE_DRIVER_UNSUPPORTED_WARNING=DSRA7042W: Oracle does not support the use of version {0} of their JDBC driver with the version of the Java runtime environment that is used by the application server.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The application server uses a version of the Java runtime environment that Oracle does not support with this version of their JDBC driver.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    You must use Oracle JDBC driver version 11g or later, even if you are connecting to Oracle databases that are earlier than version 11g.  Refer to the Information Center for WebSphere Application Server for information on the version of the Oracle JDBC driver that you can use.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA0082E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DSA_ERROR_BATCH" varFormat="Java">
    DSA_ERROR_BATCH=DSRA0082E: The Batch update count is null.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The possible reasons are that the database returned a null value, or this is an internal error.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If you think the database might have returned a null value, do not use the batch update feature, switch to a database that supports batch update, or visit the support Web site for the database vendor. If you suspect the problem is related to an internal error, use the following trace settings (RRA=all=enabled and PMGR=all=enabled) and the FFDC files to determine the source of the error. Visit the IBM support Web site for information on problem determination.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA8026W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CR_PROP_WARNING" varFormat="Java">
    CR_PROP_WARNING=DSRA8026W: The {0} property of the data source class is incorrect.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This property contains a value that is not expected. The reroute function for the client might be disabled.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the value that is specified for the property is valid.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA7009I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DB2_TRACE_INFORMATION" varFormat="Java">
    DB2_TRACE_INFORMATION=DSRA7009I: DB2 JDBC logging is enabled, DB2 Universal driver is required to display any traces.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    DB2 requires the use of the DB2 Universal driver.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Use the DB2 Universal driver.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA8233W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SOCKET_KEEPALIVE_UNSUPPORTED_WARNING" varFormat="Java">
    SOCKET_KEEPALIVE_UNSUPPORTED_WARNING=DSRA8233W: Error occurred while accessing the class com.ibm.lang.ThreadProperties to setup the socket keep alive parameters.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The application server could not set the socket keep alive parameters because the Java version your system is using does not contain the class com.ibm.lang.ThreadProperties.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that the application server is running with a Java version that includes the class com.ibm.lang.ThreadProperties.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA8000E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="JAR_ZIP_NOT_FOUND" varFormat="Java">
    JAR_ZIP_NOT_FOUND=DSRA8000E: Java archive (JAR) or compressed files do not exist in the path or the required access is not allowed.  Path: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Application Server was not able to locate any Java archive (JAR) or compressed files in the class path that is specified for the JDBC provider.  Another case is that the files exist, but the file or directory permissions do not give the Application Server the required access.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the path that is specified is correct, and verify that the necessary Java archive (JAR) or compressed files are present.  Verify that the directories and files in the path have the required permissions.  On z/OS, check the MVS SYSLOG for permission errors.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA7021I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DB2_GETMSG_CONFIG_INFO_DSRA7021" varFormat="Java">
    DB2_GETMSG_CONFIG_INFO_DSRA7021=DSRA7021I: DB2 Universal XA datasource custom property, retrieveMessagesFromServerOnGetMessage value is changed from true to false.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The custom property for a DB2 Universal XA data source, retrieveMessagesFromServerOnGetMessage, was configured with a value of true. The Application Server has changed the value to false at run time to avoid problems during the processing of exceptions.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    To avoid this message, change the retrieveMessagesFromServerOnGetMessage value to false in the admininstrative console or in the configuration scripts, or remove the property completely. This only applies to DB2 Universal XA data sources.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA9603W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CMX_PROPERTY_CHANGE_FAILURE" varFormat="Java">
    CMX_PROPERTY_CHANGE_FAILURE=DSRA9603W: The application server received an exception while trying to change the value of the connection pool property {0}. The exception is: {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The application server received an exeception while trying to update the value of the specified connection pool property with a new value supplied to it by CMX.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required by the user.CMX should retry setting this property in case the initial attempt failed.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA0085E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DSA_BATCH_NO_UPDATE" varFormat="Java">
    DSA_BATCH_NO_UPDATE=DSRA0085E: The operation was successful, however, the number of rows updated was 0.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Some or all of the rows were not updated because of a collision that is usually caused by the use of the optimistic-concurrency-control AccessIntent.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Repeat the operation, or change the AccessIntent if the error persists.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA1212E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DELEGATE_JNDI_NAME_NOT_FOUND" varFormat="Java">
    DELEGATE_JNDI_NAME_NOT_FOUND=DSRA1212E: {0} is not configured as a delegate datasource for the Base Proxy DataSource {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The JNDI names for the delegate data source are configured in the custom property jndiNames using a syntax that is delimited by semicolons. The JNDI name is not in the jndiNames custom property.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the custom property jndiNames is set to a correct value. If so, set the JNDI name of the delegate data source to a valid value.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA8032W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CRSL_UNBIND_WARNING_X" varFormat="Java">
    CRSL_UNBIND_WARNING_X=DSRA8032W: The unbind method of JNDI name &apos;&apos;{0}&apos;&apos; failed:  Exception: {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The unbind method for the Java Naming and Directory Interface (JNDI) caused an exception.  The JNDI name might not be correct, or there might be a problem in the Naming service.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the JNDI name that was specified in the class properties for the data source is correct.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA0040E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WS_INTERNAL_ERROR" varFormat="Java">
    WS_INTERNAL_ERROR=DSRA0040E: WebSphere internal error occurred. Please contact WebSphere support with the following data: {0} {1} {2}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An error occurred in the WebSphere code.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Collect all trace and system logs, along with a description of the operation that you were attempting. Visit the IBM support Web site for information on problem determination.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA7025E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="IDENTITY_PROPAGATION_CONFLICT1_ERROR" varFormat="Java">
    IDENTITY_PROPAGATION_CONFLICT1_ERROR=DSRA7025E: The reauthentication custom property for the data source cannot be enabled when you are using the TrustedConnectionMapping login configuration.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The reauthentication custom property for the data source cannot be enabled when you are using the TrustedConnectionMapping login configuration.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Disable the reauthentication custom property for the data source, or do not use the TrustedConnectionMapping login configuration.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA0060W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WS_INTERNAL_WARNING" varFormat="Java">
    WS_INTERNAL_WARNING=DSRA0060W: WebSphere internal warning occurred. Please contact WebSphere support with the following data: {0} {1} {2}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This exception is unexpected. The cause is not immediately known.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Visit the IBM support Web site for information on problem determination.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA8208I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="JDBC_DRIVER_TYPE" varFormat="Java">
    JDBC_DRIVER_TYPE=DSRA8208I: JDBC driver type  : {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The type of the Java Database Connectivity (JDBC) driver.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    The type of JDBC driver that is listed above is now being used by applications.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA8020E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PROP_NOT_FOUND" varFormat="Java">
    PROP_NOT_FOUND=DSRA8020E: Warning: The property &apos;&apos;{1}&apos;&apos; does not exist on the DataSource class {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Application Server was not able to locate the data source property that was specified.  The possible reasons are: 1) The data source property is not spelled or capitalized correctly, 2) The property that is specified does not apply to the data source that is being configured, or 3) the Application Server contains the default configuration for a different version of the JDBC driver that was specified, and this caused a mismatch of data source properties.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the property that is specified is correct for the data source. Correct any errors with spellings or capitalization.  Delete the property if it does not apply (or no longer applies) to the JDBC driver that is used.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA8052W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HELPER_NEW_UP_ERR" varFormat="Java">
    HELPER_NEW_UP_ERR=DSRA8052W: Unable to find constructor for DataStoreHelper: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The DataStoreHelper class cannot be instantiated, because it does not have a public constructor that takes a properties object as the parameter.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Create a public constructor for your DataStoreHelper that will take a properties object as its parameter.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="TRAS9910W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="JDBC_TIMING_INFO" varFormat="Java">
    JDBC_TIMING_INFO=TRAS9910W: The {0} transaction on the {1} thread has been running for {2} ms, which exceeds the time set for emitting the trace on a running thread. The following stack trace shows what this thread is currently doing: {3} The following list gives the total run time of the transaction, all SQL statements that ran during the transaction, and the run time for each of the SQL statements:{4}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    You might be using the trace capability to address problems with a long running thread. In this situation,  possible reasons for the long running thread include, but are not limited to, network issues, database issues, or long running queries.  However, you might not be concerned with how long the thread is running if you are using this trace capability as, for instance, a debugging tool or a performance gauging tool. In this situation, no action is required.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If you are using the trace capability to address problems with long running threads, review the information provided. If necessary, check your network, databases, or other areas that could have issues that affect the run time of the thread. Make corrections based on your analysis. Otherwise, no action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA1100W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MC_CLEANUP_ERROR" varFormat="Java">
    MC_CLEANUP_ERROR=DSRA1100W: An error occurred while resetting a connection to its default state. The connection will be destroyed. {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The default connection manager received an error resetting a ManagedConnection to the default state.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If necessary, take action to return the database to a state in which it can be used.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA9110E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="OBJECT_CLOSED" varFormat="Java">
    OBJECT_CLOSED=DSRA9110E: {0} is closed.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Attempted to perform an operation on an object that is closed.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Retrieve a new instance of the object on which to perform the operation.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA8218I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DRIVER_SPEC_LEVEL" varFormat="Java">
    DRIVER_SPEC_LEVEL=DSRA8218I: JDBC driver specification level  : {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message displays the specification level of the Java Database Connectivity (JDBC) driver.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    The specification level of the JDBC driver listed above is now used by applications.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA0092I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="RESOLVING_DB_IMPLICIT_TRANSACTIONS" varFormat="Java">
    RESOLVING_DB_IMPLICIT_TRANSACTIONS=DSRA0092I: An implicit database transaction was detected. WebSphere will {0} the transaction. This message will be logged once for each DataSource. Subsequent implicit transactions will be resolved automatically.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Application Server has detected that the database started a transaction. The Application Server will attempt to resolve the transaction as configured in the custom properties for the data source.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    There is no user action required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA0023E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DS_CLASS_NOT_FOUND" varFormat="Java">
    DS_CLASS_NOT_FOUND=DSRA0023E: The DataSource implementation class &quot;{0}&quot; could not be found.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Application Server was not able to locate the class for the data source implementation that you specified.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the class name for the data source is correct and that it is in your class path.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA7004E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="OS_NOT_SUPPORTED" varFormat="Java">
    OS_NOT_SUPPORTED=DSRA7004E: showLockInfo method does not support {0} platform.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The showLockInfo method does not support the operating system that was specified.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Use the correct operating system, or configure the application to not use the showLockInfo method.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA8025I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="TEST_DS_SUCCESSFUL" varFormat="Java">
    TEST_DS_SUCCESSFUL=DSRA8025I: Successfully connected to DataSource.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The test of the data source connection was successful.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    The data source can now be used by applications.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA8035W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CRSL_CREATE_WARNING_X" varFormat="Java">
    CRSL_CREATE_WARNING_X=DSRA8035W: The creation of a DB2ClientRerouteServerList failed:  Exception: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The creation of a DB2ClientRerouteServerList caused an exception.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the exception. Verify that properties related to the reroute function for the client are specified correctly in the class properties for the data source.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA8221I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="KERBEROS_NOT_USED_BY_TC" varFormat="Java">
    KERBEROS_NOT_USED_BY_TC=DSRA8221I: Test connection cannot use Kerberos authentication, because some security information is only available to a resource at run time.  The application server will use the normal authentication to connect to the data source.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Test connection cannot be used to accurately test a connection that uses the Kerberos mapping alias.  Instead, test connection will use authentication information that is specified in the component-managed alias.  The result of the test might not accurately indicate whether a connection can be made within the context of an application if the connection is configured to use Kerberos authentication.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the connection to the data source can be made within the context of your application.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA0084E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DSA_BATCH_UNKNOWN" varFormat="Java">
    DSA_BATCH_UNKNOWN=DSRA0084E: The operation was successful, however, the number of rows updated is not known.  The database returned -2 in the batch update count.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The operation was successful, but the number of rows that were updated is not known. The database returned -2 in the batch update count. This exception is created to avoid any possible issues with data integrity.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Repeat the operation to determine if this error persists.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA0098I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DEPRECATED_PROPERTY_SPECIFIED" varFormat="Java">
    DEPRECATED_PROPERTY_SPECIFIED=DSRA0098I: A deprecated custom property has been specified on DataSource:{0}. The property {1} has been replaced by {2}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This typically indicates a typographical error when configuring the custom property for the data source. The error can be a remnant of an older configuration file or from an older wsadmin script. The new properties will take precedence over the deprecated names, however the old properties may be used at this time.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Update the validation properties for the new connection with the desired values, and remove the deprecated properties.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA1213E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DELEGATE_LOOKUP_FAILURE" varFormat="Java">
    DELEGATE_LOOKUP_FAILURE=DSRA1213E: Failed to look up datasource {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The data source lookup did not complete successfully. The data source might not be created, or it is created in the wrong scope.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the data source is created correctly.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA0302E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="THROW_XAEXCEPTION" varFormat="Java">
    THROW_XAEXCEPTION=DSRA0302E:  XAException occurred.  Error code is: {0}.  Exception is: {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A two phase operation on the database resulted in an exception.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA7019W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ORACLE_10G_DATASTORE_HELPER_WARNING" varFormat="Java">
    ORACLE_10G_DATASTORE_HELPER_WARNING=DSRA7019W: Oracle10gDataStoreHelper or a subclass of it must be used when configuring WebSphere DataSources to run using Oracle10g jdbc driver.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The data source for the Application Server is configured with the wrong DataStoreHelper.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Configure the data sources for the Application Server with the Oracle10gDataStoreHelper when you are using the JDBC driver for Oracle10g.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA7022W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DEPRECATED_API_WARNING" varFormat="Java">
    DEPRECATED_API_WARNING=DSRA7022W: {0} is a deprecated API.  Using the API will disable some WebSphere new features.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An API that is deprecated is being used.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Use a version of the API that is not deprecated. Refer to the Java documentation, or visit the IBM support site for information on problem determination.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA7038W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CAN_NOT_REMOVE_ORACLE_CONNECTION_CACHE_WARNING" varFormat="Java">
    CAN_NOT_REMOVE_ORACLE_CONNECTION_CACHE_WARNING=DSRA7038W: The application server was not able to remove existing Oracle connection cache with name: {0}.  Exception: {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The application server received an exception when attempting to remove the cache for an existing Oracle connection.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the exception, correct the problem, and restart the application server.  You could also manually remove the cache for the Oracle connection.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA9544E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HETEROGENOUS_USAGE_VIOLATION_ERROR" varFormat="Java">
    HETEROGENOUS_USAGE_VIOLATION_ERROR=DSRA9544E: You must use the get/use/close connection pattern if you are using the extending data source properties feature and the optimizeDB2ForGetUseClose data source custom property is enabled.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Connections cannot be shared if you are using the extending data source properties feature and the optimizeDB2ForGetUseClose data source custom property is enabled.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Disable the optimizeDB2ForGetUseClose data source custom property, or use the get/use/close connection pattern when you use unique extended data source properties within the same transaction.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA8030I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="TEST_DS_WARNINGS" varFormat="Java">
    TEST_DS_WARNINGS=DSRA8030I: Successfully connected to DataSource, with {0} warnings.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The test of data source connection was successful, but warnings were issued.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Review the data source configuration to fix the errors that are indicated by the warnings.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA9430E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HANDLE_IN_USE" varFormat="Java">
    HANDLE_IN_USE=DSRA9430E: Connection handle cannot be dissociated because it is currently in use.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An operation is currently being performed on the Connection handle. It cannot be dissociated during the operation.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Wait until all the operations on the handle have finished, then dissociate the handle.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA9010E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="METHOD_UNSUPPORTED" varFormat="Java">
    METHOD_UNSUPPORTED=DSRA9010E: &apos;&apos;{0}&apos;&apos; is not supported on the WebSphere {1} implementation.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The method that is specified is not supported by the implementation of the Application Server.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Do not use the method.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA0244E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="NOT_VALIDATED" varFormat="Java">
    NOT_VALIDATED=DSRA0244E: The connection did not validate within the designated interval.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The JDBC driver did not identify the connection as valid during the connection validation interval.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Wait for any retries of connection attempts that could be remaining, then attempt to determine the cause of the connection error.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA8203I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DB_PRODUCT_NAME" varFormat="Java">
    DB_PRODUCT_NAME=DSRA8203I: Database product name : {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message displays the product name for the Database.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    The Database name that is listed above is now being used by applications.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA8207I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ORA_READONLY" varFormat="Java">
    ORA_READONLY=DSRA8207I: Method setReadOnly(false) is ignored. No Oracle transaction will be started.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Oracle databases do not implement the setReadOnly method. A setReadOnly(true) method will not make the connection as readonly connection. The setReadOnly(false) is also not implemented, and a transaction is implicitly started by an Oracle database. The Application Server will not invoke the setReadOnly(false) method on an Oracle database to prevent an unnecessary transaction from being started.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Inspect your application to verify that your application does not depend on a transaction after the setReadOnly(false) method is called.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA8102E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="NOT_A_2_PHASE_DS" varFormat="Java">
    NOT_A_2_PHASE_DS=DSRA8102E: DataSource class cannot be used as two-phase: ClassCastException: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The &apos;enable2Phase&apos; property can only be set to true if the data source class implements XADatasource interface.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Set &apos;enable2Phase&apos; to true for XADataSource or false for ConnectionPoolDataSource.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA1110E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="TOO_MANY_CONNECTIONS" varFormat="Java">
    TOO_MANY_CONNECTIONS=DSRA1110E: Unable to establish a connection. The maximum number of connections for the connection pool, {0}, is already open.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The connection pool has reached its maximum limit for open connections. Additional connections cannot be established until some of the open connections are closed.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Adjust the application to require fewer connections to be open at the same time.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA0400W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="TBC_NOT_SUPPORTED" varFormat="Java">
    TBC_NOT_SUPPORTED=DSRA0400W: Datasource {0}: does not support tight branch coupling
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The database or the jdbc provider specified by datasource does not support the tight branch coupling option.  Tight branch coupling is only supported with a DB2 for z/OS database accessed by the DB2 Universal JCC driver.  The default option of loose branch coupling will be used.  This may cause lock timeouts, deadlocks and/or transaction rollbacks if the application is designed for tight branch coupling since database locks will not be shared across transaction branches within the same global transaction.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    You must configure the datasource to use a supported level of JDBC driver and database, or configure your application to not require tight branch coupling.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA1130E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CONN_ERROR_ON_CLEANUP" varFormat="Java">
    CONN_ERROR_ON_CLEANUP=DSRA1130E: A fatal connection error occurred on another connection while this connection was active. This connection cannot be reset to a usable state.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The connection cannot be reset for connection pooling because a connection error occurred while it was active.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If necessary, take action to return the database to a state in which it can be used.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA9545W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INFORMIX_JCC_CONFIG_WARNING" varFormat="Java">
    INFORMIX_JCC_CONFIG_WARNING=DSRA9545W: Informix data servers that us the Java Common Client (JCC) Driver only support a driverType data source custom property with a value of 4. The driverType value has been changed to 4 to continue the operation successfully.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The driverType custom property for the data source was set to the value of 2, and this value is not supported on Informix. The application server will change the value to 4 at run time.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    To avoid future warnings, change the driverType value to 4 in the administrative console or with JACL scripts, or omit setting the driverType value and it will default to the value of 4.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA8023W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="OPTION_NOT_VALID" varFormat="Java">
    OPTION_NOT_VALID=DSRA8023W: {0} is not a valid option for {1}. {1} will default to {2}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The value that is configured is not valid for the attribute that is specified.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the value that is specified or the attribute is valid.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA7012W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CLOUDSCAPE_CONFIG_WARNING" varFormat="Java">
    CLOUDSCAPE_CONFIG_WARNING=DSRA7012W: Cloudscape NetworkServer only supports a value of 4 for the driverType datasource custom property. The driverType value is changed to 4 to continue operation successfully
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The driverType custom property for the data source was set to the value of 2, and this value is not supported on Cloudscape. The Application Server will change the value to 4 at run time.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    To avoid future warnings, change the driverType value to 4 in the administrative console or with JACL scripts, or omit setting the driverType value and it will default to the value of 4.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA0087E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DSA_BATCH_PROBLEM" varFormat="Java">
    DSA_BATCH_PROBLEM=DSRA0087E: {0} operation was not successful because {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The batch operation that is specified above experienced an error.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the database log files, and visit the IBM support Web site for problem determination if no cause is readily apparent.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA7006I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DB2_LOCK_INFO" varFormat="Java">
    DB2_LOCK_INFO=DSRA7006I: Lock information should be available in file: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    DB2 wrote the lock information into the file name that is listed.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Open the specified file. It contains information on locks in your database. This information might be helpful in resolving deadlocks in the application.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA8200W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CONFIG_WARN" varFormat="Java">
    CONFIG_WARN=DSRA8200W: DataSource Configuration: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This is a warning message that is displayed during data source configuration.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Read the warning message and take appropriate action to fix the problem, if necessary.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA1102W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MC_VALIDATION_ERROR" varFormat="Java">
    MC_VALIDATION_ERROR=DSRA1102W: An error occurred while validating connections after detection of a fatal connection error. All connections will be destroyed. {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The default connection manager received an error requesting validation of pooled ManagedConnections.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If necessary, take action to return the database to a state in which it can be used.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA1301E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="APP_SPECIFIED_CONN_ERROR" varFormat="Java">
    APP_SPECIFIED_CONN_ERROR=DSRA1301E: The Relational Resource Adapter was notified of a connection error.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    There is an error with the connection that is specified. The connection will be purged according to the purge policy.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Create a new connection for future operations.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA9548I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SERVICE_NOT_FOUND_DSRA9548I" varFormat="Java">
    SERVICE_NOT_FOUND_DSRA9548I=DSRA9548I: The application server could not find the following service: {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The application server could not find the service that was specified.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Visit the support site for WebSphere Application Server for more information.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA1101W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MC_DESTROY_ERROR" varFormat="Java">
    MC_DESTROY_ERROR=DSRA1101W: An error occurred while destroying a connection. {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The default connection manager received an error destroying a ManagedConnection.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If necessary, take action to return the database to a state in which it can be used.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA7030I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CLOUDSCAPE_LOCK_INFO" varFormat="Java">
    CLOUDSCAPE_LOCK_INFO=DSRA7030I: Cloudscape Lock information for {0}
 The Locks.xid is :{1}
 The Locks.Type is:{2}
 The TableName is :{3}
 The Mode is      :{4}
 The  Lockname is :{5}
 The  State is    :{6}
 The  SQLString is:{7}
Lock number :{8}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This is the lock information that is reported by the Cloudscape database for your application.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    This is information on the locks in your database. You might want to use the information to resolve deadlocks in the application.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA9122E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="NO_WRAPPED_OBJECT" varFormat="Java">
    NO_WRAPPED_OBJECT=DSRA9122E: {0} does not wrap any objects of type {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The wrapper that is specified does not contain the wrapped object type that is specified.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the wrapper and the parameters for the wrapped object are specified correctly.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA8211I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="BACKEND_ID_CHECK_DISABLED" varFormat="Java">
    BACKEND_ID_CHECK_DISABLED=DSRA8211I: Backend id checking is disabled.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Backend ID checking is disabled. No validation of the backend ID will be performed.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Set the disableBackendIdChecking custom property for the data source to false, or remove the property to enable backend ID checking.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA9123E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="UNTRUSTED_METHOD" varFormat="Java">
    UNTRUSTED_METHOD=DSRA9123E: Invocation of the {0} method on the {1} class is not permitted via jdbcPass.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Application Server does not permit the specified method to be invoked through a jdbcPass.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the method does not alter the state of its native parameters of the Java Database Connectity (JDBC) object, visit the IBM support Web site to request that the method be added to the list of permitted methods for jdbcPass.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA8051W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HELPER_IMPL_ERR" varFormat="Java">
    HELPER_IMPL_ERR=DSRA8051W: Unable to instantiate DataStoreHelper: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The implementation class for the DataStoreHelper cannot be an interface or an abstract class.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Provide a class that fully implements the DataStoreHelper interface.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA0110E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="NOT_AVAILABLE_IN" varFormat="Java">
    NOT_AVAILABLE_IN=DSRA0110E: {0} is not available in {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The availability of certain features depends on the location where it is being used. For example, CMP 2 is not available in the Embeddable EJB Container.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Refer to the documentation to determine where the feature can be used.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA8053W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HELPER_ACCESS_ERR" varFormat="Java">
    HELPER_ACCESS_ERR=DSRA8053W: Unable to access the constructor for DataStoreHelper: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Application Server cannot access your DataStoreHelper constructor because it is not public.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that your DataStoreHelper constructor is a public method.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA8201W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CONFIG_WARN_WITH_X" varFormat="Java">
    CONFIG_WARN_WITH_X=DSRA8201W: DataSource Configuration: {0}
{1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This is a warning message that is displayed during data source configuration.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Read the warning message and take appropriate action to fix the problem, if necessary.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA1200E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="NO_MORE_ELEMENTS" varFormat="Java">
    NO_MORE_ELEMENTS=DSRA1200E: The iteration does not contain any more elements. Element {0} does not exist.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The &apos;next&apos; operation was invoked on an iterator that does not contain additional elements.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Invoke &apos;hasNext&apos; on the iteration before invoking the &apos;next&apos; operation to determine whether the iteration contains additional elements.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA8230W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="NONTRAN_DATASOURCE_WARNING" varFormat="Java">
    NONTRAN_DATASOURCE_WARNING=DSRA8230W: The application server is unable to determine if a transaction should be resolved because data source custom property {0} is configured but data source custom property {1} is not configured.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An attempt is made to pool a connection that has an AutoCommit value of False. The application server cannot determine if a transaction is active because the data source is configured as nontransactional. The application server will not attempt to resolve the transaction because the data source is not configured to automatically commit or roll back during connection cleanup.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Configure the data source to automatically commit or roll back on connection cleanup, or always reset the AutoCommit value to True.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA8028W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CR_PROP_WARNING_T2" varFormat="Java">
    CR_PROP_WARNING_T2=DSRA8028W: The Application Server was not able to configure DB2 client reroute persistence on the data source when the JDBC driver type 2 is used. The Application Server is ignoring the settings for persistence of DB2 client reroute information.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The DB2 JDBC driver type 2 has a built-in mechanism for updating and persisting the client reroute information.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Configure the data source to use the JDBC driver type 4, or remove the settings for persistence of client reroute information.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA7034I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="TRUSTED_WITH_AUTHENTICATION_IMPLEMENTATION_INFO" varFormat="Java">
    TRUSTED_WITH_AUTHENTICATION_IMPLEMENTATION_INFO=DSRA7034I: Enabling the useTrustedContextWithAuthentication custom property for the data source requires that you override the getPasswordForUseWithTrustedContextWithAuthentication DataStoreHelper method to provide the password that is required to switch trusted context identity.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The application server requires a password to switch trusted context identities if you enable trusted context with authentication. You must override the getPasswordForUseWithTrustedContextWithAuthentication DataStoreHelper method to get the password to the application server.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that you implement code that will override the getPasswordForUseWithTrustedContextWithAuthentication DataStoreHelper method.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA8043W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="TEST_CR_OCCURRED" varFormat="Java">
    TEST_CR_OCCURRED=DSRA8043W: The database connection has been rerouted.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The database connection has been rerouted to an alternate database server.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    This message is to notify you that a rerouting action has occurred. No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA9533E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_DS_CONFIGURATION" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_DS_CONFIGURATION=DSRA9533E: The jmsOnePhaseOptimization datasource checkbox cannot be checked when XA-capable datasource is used.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The jmsOnePhaseOptimization data source option can only be enabled on non XA-capable Datasources.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Use a data source that is not XA-capable, or clear the option for using jmsOnePhaseOptimization in the administrative console.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA7602I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CLOUDSCAPE_MIGRATION_DELETION_ATTEMPT" varFormat="Java">
    CLOUDSCAPE_MIGRATION_DELETION_ATTEMPT=DSRA7602I: Attempting to delete newly created Derby database {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An attempt is made to delete the new Derby database.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required. This is an informational message.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA8065W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HELPER_EXEC_ERR" varFormat="Java">
    HELPER_EXEC_ERR=DSRA8065W: An error occurred executing the DataStoreHelper method {0}: {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Application Server was not able to issue the DataStoreHelper method that is specified.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If you are using a custom DataStoreHelper, ensure that the code in the DataStoreHelper method that is specified is correct. Otherwise, check the configuration properties for the data source.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA0330E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ORACLE_RAC_RETRY" varFormat="Java">
    ORACLE_RAC_RETRY=DSRA0330E: The application server is delaying the {0} request, because the amount of time from the last stale connection, {1} milliseconds, is within the oracleRACXARecoveryDelay value, which is {2} milliseconds.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The data source custom property, oracleRACXARecoveryDelay, causes the application server to delay xa.commit and xa.rollback operations for the duration of the retry interval.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Wait for the transaction manager to retry the operation. You must configure heuristic retries on the transaction manager in order for oracleRACXARecoveryDelay to work properly.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA9500E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="NO_NEGATIVE_FETCH_SIZES" varFormat="Java">
    NO_NEGATIVE_FETCH_SIZES=DSRA9500E: Negative values are not allowed for fetch size.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The fetch size can only be set to a value that is not negative.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Choose a value for the fetch size that is not negative.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA9600W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CMX_DATA_POSTING_PROBLEM" varFormat="Java">
    CMX_DATA_POSTING_PROBLEM=DSRA9600W: The application server received an exception when posting data to CMX. The exception is: {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The application server received an exception when attempting to post data to CMX. This might mean that the data is not posted.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the exception and the possible cause.  Visit the WebSphere support website for troubleshooting help if you cannot resolve the issue after examining the exception.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA7037W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ORACLE_CONNECTION_POOLING_NOT_SUPPORTED_WARNING" varFormat="Java">
    ORACLE_CONNECTION_POOLING_NOT_SUPPORTED_WARNING=DSRA7037W: The JDBC Driver that is configured with the data source for the application server does not support Oracle connection pooling.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The caching feature for the Oracle connection is not supported on the JDBC driver that is being used. The feature will not be enabled.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Configure the application server to use an Oracle non-XA data source.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA9350E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="OP_NOT_VALID_IN_GT" varFormat="Java">
    OP_NOT_VALID_IN_GT=DSRA9350E: Operation {0} is not allowed during a global transaction.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Application Server does not allow calls to the commit, rollback, setSavepoint or releaseSavepoint methods on the Connection while a global transaction is active.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Do not call the commit, rollback, setSavepoint or releaseSavepoint methods on the connection when it is in a global transaction. If a non-transactional data source (for example, non-jta-data-source for Java Persistence API) is being used, then configure non-jta-data-source in persistence.xml and also configure the nonTransactionalDataSource custom property on the data source.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA8101E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="NOT_A_1_PHASE_DS" varFormat="Java">
    NOT_A_1_PHASE_DS=DSRA8101E: DataSource class cannot be used as one-phase: ClassCastException: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The &apos;enable2Phase&apos; property can only be set to false if the data source class implements the ConnectionPoolDatasource interface.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Set &apos;enable2Phase&apos; to true for XADataSource or false for ConnectionPoolDataSource.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA0250E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WS_ERROR" varFormat="Java">
    WS_ERROR=DSRA0250E: An exception was received by the Data Store Adapter. See original exception message: {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This exception is unexpected. The cause is not immediately known.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA0174W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DSH_GEN_USED" varFormat="Java">
    DSH_GEN_USED=DSRA0174W: Warning: GenericDataStoreHelper is being used.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The GenericDataStoreHelper has been initialized.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If this is expected, no user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA3610E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DSRA3610E" varFormat="Java">
    DSRA3610E=DSRA3610E: The target object submitted to command {0} is not a {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The command was not run because the target object references an element in the configuration that is not the type expected by the command.  For example, a data source was submitted as the target object to command deleteJDBCProvider,
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    This problem occurs when the configuration element referenced by the target object has an unexpected type.  Correct the problem and try the operation again.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA1120E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CONN_NEVER_CLOSED" varFormat="Java">
    CONN_NEVER_CLOSED=DSRA1120E: Application did not explicitly close all handles to this Connection. Connection cannot be pooled.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The connection will not be reset for connection pooling because the application failed to explicitly close all handles.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Modify the application to always close all connection handles.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA9542W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HETEROGENOUS_POOLING_NOT_SUPPORTED_WARNING_DSRA9542W" varFormat="Java">
    HETEROGENOUS_POOLING_NOT_SUPPORTED_WARNING_DSRA9542W=DSRA9542W: The JDBC Driver that is configured with the data source for the Application Server does not support the extending data source properties feature. The Application Server will not honor the extended data source properties.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The extending data source properties feature is not supported on the JDBC Driver that is being used. The extended data source properties are ignored.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Configure the Application Server to use the DB2 Universal JDBC Driver.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA0101W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="OBSOLETE_PROPERTY_SPECIFIED" varFormat="Java">
    OBSOLETE_PROPERTY_SPECIFIED=DSRA0101W: A removed custom property has been specified on DataSource:{0}. The property {1} has been replaced by {2}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Specified custom property has been made obsolete.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Use the new custom property in place of the old one.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA7041W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DATASTORE_HELPER_WARNING" varFormat="Java">
    DATASTORE_HELPER_WARNING=DSRA7041W: You must use the {0} class or a subclass of that data store helper when you configure a data source to use this JDBC driver: {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The data source for the application server is configured with the wrong DataStoreHelper class.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Configure the data source for the application server with the correct data store helper class that corresponds to the JDBC driver that you have configured.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA7036W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="METHOD_EXEC_FAILED_WARNING" varFormat="Java">
    METHOD_EXEC_FAILED_WARNING=DSRA7036W: The {0} method did not complete successfully. The reason is: {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The method that is invoked did not complete successfully.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the exception that was created to determine the reasons for the error.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA8055W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HELPER_CAST_ERR" varFormat="Java">
    HELPER_CAST_ERR=DSRA8055W: The class specified does not implement the DataStoreHelper interface: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The custom class for the DataStoreHelper does not implement the DataStoreHelper.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Update the custom class for the DataStoreHelper to implement the DataStoreHelper interface.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA7020E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="GENERIC_HELPER_NO_LOCK_INFO" varFormat="Java">
    GENERIC_HELPER_NO_LOCK_INFO=DSRA7020E: There is no locking information available from the GenericDataStoreHelper
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The GenericDataStoreHelper does not know how to collect the lock information.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Write or use a DataStoreHelper that is specific to the database.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA8001E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CANT_READ_JAR_ZIP" varFormat="Java">
    CANT_READ_JAR_ZIP=DSRA8001E: Unable to read JDBC provider jar or zip file: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    MalformedURLException occurred attempting to read a JDBC provider JAR or .zip file.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the path that is specified is correct, and verify that the necessary JAR files and .zip files are valid.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA8034W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CRSL_BIND_WARNING_X" varFormat="Java">
    CRSL_BIND_WARNING_X=DSRA8034W: The bind method of JNDI name &apos;&apos;{0}&apos;&apos; failed:  Exception: {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The bind method for the Java Naming and Directory Interface (JNDI) caused an exception. The JNDI name might be incorrect, or there might be a problem in the Naming service.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the JNDI name that was specified in the class properties for the data source is correct.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA8212I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DATA_STORE_HELPER_NAME" varFormat="Java">
    DATA_STORE_HELPER_NAME=DSRA8212I: DataStoreHelper name is: {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The name of the DataStoreHelper.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    This is an informational message. There is no user action required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA0091I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="UNSUPPORTED_METHOD" varFormat="Java">
    UNSUPPORTED_METHOD=DSRA0091I: Method {0} is not supported for this backend database
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An internal error has occurred.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Visit the IBM support Web site for information on problem determination.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA8213W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PROVIDER_NOT_SUPPORTED" varFormat="Java">
    PROVIDER_NOT_SUPPORTED=DSRA8213W: JDBC provider, {0}, is no longer supported by WebSphere Application Server.  Applications should use {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The application is using a JDBC provider that is no longer supported by the Application Server.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Use the JDBC provider that is provided in the error text.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA0180W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DSTRY_ERROR_EX" varFormat="Java">
    DSTRY_ERROR_EX=DSRA0180W: Exception detected during ManagedConnection.destroy().  The exception is:  {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An exception was detected cleaning up the ManagedConnection for a destroy operation.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Refer to the error reported by the database software to help determine the cause of the error.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA9541E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="TRUSTED_NOT_SUPPORTED_ERROR_DSRA9541E" varFormat="Java">
    TRUSTED_NOT_SUPPORTED_ERROR_DSRA9541E=DSRA9541E: The JDBC Driver that is configured with the data source for the Application Server does not support Trusted Connection.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Trusted Connection feature is not supported on the JDBC Driver that is being used.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Configure the Application Server to use the DB2 Universal JDBC Driver, or stop using TrustedConnectionMapping login configuration.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA7003E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MTHD_MIS_USE" varFormat="Java">
    MTHD_MIS_USE=DSRA7003E: A java.util.Properties object must be specified which includes all of the necessary connection information.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Some or all of the connection information that is required is missing.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See the Java documentation for the DataStoreHelper.showLockInfo() method for a description of the connection information which is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA8027W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CR_PROP_WARNING_X" varFormat="Java">
    CR_PROP_WARNING_X=DSRA8027W: The {0} property of the data source class is incorrect.  Exception: {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This property contains a value that is not expected. The reroute function for the client might be disabled.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the value that is specified for the property is valid.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA8225I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DATASOURCE_JNDI_NAME" varFormat="Java">
    DATASOURCE_JNDI_NAME=DSRA8225I: DataSource JNDI name : {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message displays the JNDI name of the DataSource.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA8220W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="REQUIRES_SPEC_LEVEL" varFormat="Java">
    REQUIRES_SPEC_LEVEL=DSRA8220W: Enablement of {0} requires a JDBC driver compliant with JDBC specification level {1} or higher.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Java Database Connectivity (JDBC) specification level that is specified in the error message is a prerequisite of the feature.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Disable the feature, or switch to a JDBC driver that is at the required level.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA7014I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DB2ZOS_CONFIG_INFO" varFormat="Java">
    DB2ZOS_CONFIG_INFO=DSRA7014I: The DB2 Universal JDBC driver runs in a RRS environment
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The DB2 Universal JDBC driver has been switched to run in an RRS environment on DB2 for z/OS.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    This is the informational message for the environment of the JDBC driver that is running.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA0015W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DISPLAY_SQLWARNING_DSRA0015W" varFormat="Java">
    DISPLAY_SQLWARNING_DSRA0015W=DSRA0015W: A warning was reported by a JDBC resource.  JDBC resource: {0}, SQLState: {1}, Error Code: {2}, Warning: {3}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A warning was reported by a JDBC resource.  There may be other warnings chained to this warning.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Review all warnings.  Note the SQLState and Error Code of each warning and refer to the documentation of the JDBC driver to resolve the issue.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA9001E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MAP_SQL_EXCEPTION" varFormat="Java">
    MAP_SQL_EXCEPTION=DSRA9001E: DataStoreAdapterException was created to map a SQLException.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A DataStoreAdapterException was created to map an SQLException.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    There is no user action required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA9531E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_OPERATION" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_OPERATION=DSRA9531E: Attempt to perform getConnection is not allowed because Passkey is not valid.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A passkey that is not valid was passed on the getConnection method.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Visit the IBM support Web site for problem determination information.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA9534E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_OPERATION2" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_OPERATION2=DSRA9534E: JMS failed to get an optimized connection.  The jmsOnePhaseOptimization datasource checkbox must be checked.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    JMS is attempting to get an optimized connection.  This action requires the jmsOnePhaseOptimization data source option to be enabled.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Enable the jmsOnePhaseOptimization option on the data source, or visit the IBM support Web site for information on problem determination.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA9532E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_OPERATION1" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_OPERATION1=DSRA9532E: Attempt to perform getConnection is not allowed for JDBC applications when the jmsOnePhaseOptimization datasource checkbox is checked.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The getConnection method on this data source can only be issued by JMS and CMP Applications.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Define another data source for the JDBC applications or set the jmsOnePhaseOptimization property to false.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA1210E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="NOTHING_TO_REMOVE" varFormat="Java">
    NOTHING_TO_REMOVE=DSRA1210E: The iterator is not positioned on any element. There is nothing to remove.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The &apos;remove&apos; operation was invoked when the iterator was not positioned on any element.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Position the iterator to a valid element before you invoke the &apos;remove&apos; operation.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA8210I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="BACKEND_ID_NOT_MATCH" varFormat="Java">
    BACKEND_ID_NOT_MATCH=DSRA8210I: The database product name {0} may not exactly match with the database represented by the backend ID {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The database which is represented by the backend ID might not match the data source that is connected.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Inspect the database version between the deployment and the runtime data source. If they are not the same, use a backend ID that matches the data source to deploy the enterprise Java bean (EJB), or change the data source to match the backend ID.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA0086E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DSA_GENERIC_MSG" varFormat="Java">
    DSA_GENERIC_MSG=DSRA0086E: An operation resulted in an Exception. Operation is: {0}. Exception is: {1}.  Possible cause {2}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The operation resulted in an exception.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the operation, the exception, and the database log files.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA9520E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="NO_NULL_STATEMENT" varFormat="Java">
    NO_NULL_STATEMENT=DSRA9520E: The passed-in Statement object cannot be set to null.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Statement object that was passed in cannot be set to null.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Set the Statement object to an object that is not null.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA8011E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="NO_SETTER_METHOD" varFormat="Java">
    NO_SETTER_METHOD=DSRA8011E: No setter method for property &apos;&apos;{0}&apos;&apos;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Application Server could not find a setter method on the data source to set the property that is requested.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the property name that is specified is correct.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA8033W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CRSL_LOOKUP_WARNING_X" varFormat="Java">
    CRSL_LOOKUP_WARNING_X=DSRA8033W: The lookup method of JNDI name &apos;&apos;{0}&apos;&apos; failed:  Exception: {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The lookup method for the Java Naming and Directory Interface (JNDI) caused an exception. The JNDI name might not be correct, or there might be a problem in the Naming service.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the JNDI name that was specified in the class properties for the data source is correct.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA7040I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WAS_CONNECTION_POOLING_DISABLED_INFO" varFormat="Java">
    WAS_CONNECTION_POOLING_DISABLED_INFO=DSRA7040I: The application server has disabled internal connection pooling.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The application server has detected the enablement of connection caching through the database. Connection pooling in the application server will be disabled.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If you do not want to disable connection pooling in the application server, disable connection pooling for the database server.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA0230E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_TX_STATE" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_TX_STATE=DSRA0230E: Attempt to perform operation {0} is not allowed because transaction state is {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The operation that was requested is not allowed during a transaction.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Perform the operation before starting the transaction or after completing the transaction.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA9115E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CONNECTION_INACTIVE" varFormat="Java">
    CONNECTION_INACTIVE=DSRA9115E: Operation cannot be performed. Connection handle is INACTIVE and implicit reactivation is disabled.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Attempted to perform an operation on a Connection handle that is not active.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Enable the InactiveConnectionSupport property for the resource adapter.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA8217W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CR_HOST_PORT_PROBLEM" varFormat="Java">
    CR_HOST_PORT_PROBLEM=DSRA8217W: Unable to configure client reroute on the data source class {0}. clientRerouteAlternateServerName and clientRerouteAlternatePortNumber data source custom property must be set and must have equal number of entries.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    To configure a data source with the client reroute method, clientRerouteAlternateServerName and clientRerouteAlternatePortNumber must be set to a value that is not null, and the number of alternate servers must match the number of alternate ports.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the problem, and restart the Application Server.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA7606I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CLOUDSCAPE_MIGRATED_NEW_DB_NAME" varFormat="Java">
    CLOUDSCAPE_MIGRATED_NEW_DB_NAME=DSRA7606I: The name of the new Derby database that will be created is {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The migration of the Cloudscape database instance will create a new Derby database instance with the specified name.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required. This is an informational message.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA0025E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CAST_EXCEPTION" varFormat="Java">
    CAST_EXCEPTION=DSRA0025E: Class {0} does not implement {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The object cannot be cast to the interface that is specified, because the object does not implement it.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that that the implementation class is correct and that it is provided.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA7031W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PROP_NOT_SUPPORTED" varFormat="Java">
    PROP_NOT_SUPPORTED=DSRA7031W: The {0} datasource custom property is not supported when using the {1} DataStoreHelper.  Disabling {0} datasource custom property.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The custom property for the data source cannot be enabled in the current environment.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Disable the custom property for the data source.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA8205I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="JDBC_DRIVER_NAME" varFormat="Java">
    JDBC_DRIVER_NAME=DSRA8205I: JDBC driver name  : {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message displays the name of the Java Database Connectivity (JDBC) driver.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    The name of the JDBC driver that is listed above is now being used by applications.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA7007W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ORACLE_MAYBE_BAD_ISOLATION" varFormat="Java">
    ORACLE_MAYBE_BAD_ISOLATION=DSRA7007W: Oracle does not support Serializable isolation level when using XA protocol, if XA is being used, an error will be thrown by Oracle.  To correct the problem, do not use PESSIMISTIC_UPDATE_LOCK_HINT_EXCLUSIVE since it cause a Serializable isolation level to be returned.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Oracle does not support the Serializable isolation level when using the XA protocol.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Do not use PESSIMISTIC_UPDATE_LOCK_HINT_EXCLUSIVE, because it causes the Serializable isolation level to be used.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA7011W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ORACLE_PATCH_WARNING" varFormat="Java">
    ORACLE_PATCH_WARNING=DSRA7011W: A Oracle JDBC provider property (TransactionBranchesLooselyCoupled) has been set.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A custom property was set when creating the JDBC provider from Oracle. The property requires the Oracle patch 2511780.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the patch is installed, no user action is required. Otherwise, visit the Oracle support Web site to obtain patch 2511780.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA8214W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CR_CONFIG_PROBLEM" varFormat="Java">
    CR_CONFIG_PROBLEM=DSRA8214W: Unable to configure client reroute on the data source class {0}. Exception: {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Application Server received an exception when attempting to configure a data source with the client reroute method.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the exception, correct the problem, and restart the Application Server.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA0097W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DUPLICATE_VALIDATION_PROPERTIES" varFormat="Java">
    DUPLICATE_VALIDATION_PROPERTIES=DSRA0097W: DataSource:{0} has specified custom properties {1} and {2}. {1} is deprecated and is replaced by {2}. The following values will be used {3}={4}  {5}={6}  {7}={8}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This typically indicates a typographical error when configuring the custom property for the data source.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Update the validation properties for the new connection with the desired values, and remove the deprecated properties.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA7001E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_METHOD_CALL" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_METHOD_CALL=DSRA7001E: This method must be called from DataDirect DataStoreHelper.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    MSSQLhelper methods can only be called from DataDirect helpers.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Use DataDirectDataStoreHelper.class in your setup.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA0020E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="OBJECT_NOT_FOUND" varFormat="Java">
    OBJECT_NOT_FOUND=DSRA0020E: {0} could not be found: {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This exception is unexpected. The cause is not immediately known.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA0402W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="TBC_DB_NOT_SUPPORTED" varFormat="Java">
    TBC_DB_NOT_SUPPORTED=DSRA0402W: Datasource {0}: the database version does not support tight branch coupling
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The database specified by the datasource does not support the tight branch coupling option.  Tight branch coupling is only supported with type 4 connections to DB2 for z/OS V8 (+ APAR PK47713) or DB2 for Linux, UNIX, Windows V8 and later versions.  The default option of loose branch coupling will be used.  This may cause lock timeouts, deadlocks and/or transaction rollbacks if the application is designed for tight branch coupling since database locks will not be shared across transaction branches within the same global transaction.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    You must configure the datasource to use a supported level of JDBC driver and database, or configure your application to not require tight branch coupling.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA8021W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PROP_SET_ERROR" varFormat="Java">
    PROP_SET_ERROR=DSRA8021W: Warning: error setting &apos;&apos;{0}&apos;&apos;{1}: {2}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An exception occurred setting the specified property on the data source.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the value that is specified is valid for the property.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA9543W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="KERBEROS_NOT_SUPPORTED_WARNING" varFormat="Java">
    KERBEROS_NOT_SUPPORTED_WARNING=DSRA9543W: The Application Server does not support Kerberos against the backend database that is being used.  No user name and password will be used to get a connection.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Application Server does not support Kerberos authentication on the database that is used. User name and password will not be used when getting a connection.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Disable Kerberos, or use a DB2 backend with the DB2 universal JDBC driver.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA0083E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DSA_BATCH_ERROR" varFormat="Java">
    DSA_BATCH_ERROR=DSRA0083E: one of the batched updates failed which caused the database to return -3 in the batch update count.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    One of the batched updates did not complete successfully and caused the database to return -3 in the batch update count. -3 is returned if the database continues to run the batched updates after one fails.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the database logs for possible sources of the error.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA8041I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="TEST_DS_FAIL_SQLX" varFormat="Java">
    TEST_DS_FAIL_SQLX=DSRA8041I: Failed to connect to the DataSource {0}.  Encountered SQLException with SQL State = {1}, Error Code = {2} : {3}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The test of data source connection failed.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Review the data source configuration to fix the error.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA7603E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CLOUDSCAPE_MIGRATION_DELETION_FAILURE" varFormat="Java">
    CLOUDSCAPE_MIGRATION_DELETION_FAILURE=DSRA7603E: Failed to delete newly created Derby database {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The attempt to delete the new Derby database has failed.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Manually delete the new Derby database.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA8100E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="JAVAX_CONN_ERR" varFormat="Java">
    JAVAX_CONN_ERR=DSRA8100E: Unable to get a {0} from the DataSource {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    See the linkedException for more information.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See the linkedException for more information.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA9020E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="NOT_A_JDBC_METHOD" varFormat="Java">
    NOT_A_JDBC_METHOD=DSRA9020E: The method invoked is not a JDBC method. WebSphere code must pass in a valid key to access this method.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This method is provided only for internal use by the Application Server.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Do not call this method.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA1300E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="FEATURE_NOT_IMPLEMENTED" varFormat="Java">
    FEATURE_NOT_IMPLEMENTED=DSRA1300E: Feature is not implemented: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The feature that was requested is not available.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Avoid using the feature, or switch to a driver version that supports the feature if possible.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA9400E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="REASSOCIATION_ERR" varFormat="Java">
    REASSOCIATION_ERR=DSRA9400E: Fatal error occurred during Connection reassociation: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The current Connection handle could not be reassociated.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Try obtaining a new Connection.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA1211E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="NULL_DELEGATE_JNDI_NAME" varFormat="Java">
    NULL_DELEGATE_JNDI_NAME=DSRA1211E: The JNDI name of the delegate datasource mapped from the Base Proxy DataSource JNDI name {0} is null or an empty string.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The JNDI name of the delegate data source cannot be null or an empty string.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Set the JNDI name of the delegate data source on the map for that specific proxy data source.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA8040I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="TEST_DS_FAIL" varFormat="Java">
    TEST_DS_FAIL=DSRA8040I: Failed to connect to the DataSource {0}.  Encountered {1}: {2}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The test of data source connection did not complete successfully.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Review the data source configuration to fix the error.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA8024W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="OPTION_NOT_COMPATIBLE" varFormat="Java">
    OPTION_NOT_COMPATIBLE=DSRA8024W: {0}={1} is not compatible with {2}={3}. The {2} attribute will default to {4}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The attributes that are specified are not compatible.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the attributes that are specified are compatible.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA9539W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="NON_TRANSACTIONAL_DATASOURCE_CONFLICT_INFO_DSRA9539W" varFormat="Java">
    NON_TRANSACTIONAL_DATASOURCE_CONFLICT_INFO_DSRA9539W=DSRA9539W: The nonTransactionalDataSource custom property for data sources cannot be enabled when connecting to IBM DB2 on z/OS using the DB2 Universal JDBC Driver Type 2.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Transaction problems will occur when you enable the nonTransactionalDataSource custom property for data sources and connect to IBM DB2 on z/OS with the DB2 Universal JDBC Driver Type 2.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Disable the nonTransactionalDataSource custom property for data sources or use the DB2 Universal JDBC Driver Type 4.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA8600W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ERR_CLOSING_OBJECT" varFormat="Java">
    ERR_CLOSING_OBJECT=DSRA8600W: Error closing {0}
{1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An error occurred closing the JDBC object that is specified.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA0099E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="UNKNOWN_WAS_CLASS" varFormat="Java">
    UNKNOWN_WAS_CLASS=DSRA0099E: An illegal attempt was made to load an unknown class {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An attempt was made to load a class that is not recognized by the Application Server.  Only classes that are recognized are allowed to be loaded by internal utilities.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Do not use internal utilities to load classes that are not able to be recognized by the Application Server.  If no such attempt was made, visit the IBM support Web site for information on problem determination.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA0010E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SQL_STATE_ERROR_CODE" varFormat="Java">
    SQL_STATE_ERROR_CODE=DSRA0010E: SQL State = {0}, Error Code = {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A database error occurred for which the SQL state and the Error code are listed.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Use the information associated with the error code to fix the problem in the database.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA7005E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DB2_CMD_ERROR" varFormat="Java">
    DB2_CMD_ERROR=DSRA7005E: showLockInfo(): could not execute db2 command {0}, reason: {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An exception occurred when an operation attempted collect lock information from the database.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA8650W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ERR_CLOSING_CHILD" varFormat="Java">
    ERR_CLOSING_CHILD=DSRA8650W: Error closing a JDBC child wrapper, {0}
{1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An error occurred closing the child object that is specified.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA7039W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CAN_NOT_CHECK_IF_ORA_CACHE_EXISTS_WARNING" varFormat="Java">
    CAN_NOT_CHECK_IF_ORA_CACHE_EXISTS_WARNING=DSRA7039W: The application server was not able to check for the existence of the Oracle connection cache with the name: {0}.  The exception is: {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The application server received an exception when attempting to check the existence of the Oracle connection cache.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the exception, correct the problem, and restart the application server. You could also manually remove the cache for the Oracle connection if it exists.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA0027W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="GET_ISOLATION_EXCEPTION" varFormat="Java">
    GET_ISOLATION_EXCEPTION=DSRA0027W: An exception occurred while the application server was determining the class loader isolation for the resource with JNDI name {1}. Exception: {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An exception occurred when the application server checked the resource to determine if it was configured for class loader isolation.  The code will proceed as if class loader isolation is not configured.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Refer to the exception message to help determine the cause of the problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA7035W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="METHOD_NOT_FOUND_WARNING" varFormat="Java">
    METHOD_NOT_FOUND_WARNING=DSRA7035W: The {0} method is not found on the {1} class.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The method that is invoked is not found on the specified class.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Use a version of the class that has the missing method, or reconfigure the application server to avoid calling the missing method.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA8204I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DB_PRODUCT_VERSION" varFormat="Java">
    DB_PRODUCT_VERSION=DSRA8204I: Database product version : {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message displays the product version for the Database.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    The Database version that is listed above is now being used by applications.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA0096I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_CLEANUP_OPERATION_SPECIFIED" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_CLEANUP_OPERATION_SPECIFIED=DSRA0096I: An unexpected value was specified on DataSource:{0} custom property:{1}. The value specified is {2}. Expected values are {3}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This typically indicates a typographical error when configuring the custom property for the data source.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that one of the expected values is specified for the custom property. If there is a typographical error, correct it and save the changes to the configuration.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA8770I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DEFAULT_MATCH_ORIGINAL" varFormat="Java">
    DEFAULT_MATCH_ORIGINAL=DSRA8770I: By default, the connection property, {0}, is matched for shareable connections based on the original connection request rather than the current state of the connection. You may use the data source custom property, {1}, to configure this behavior.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The data source custom property allows you to choose which connection sharing behavior you want.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the data source custom property is configured for the behavior you want.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA0401W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="TBC_START_FAILED" varFormat="Java">
    TBC_START_FAILED=DSRA0401W: Datasource {0}: does not support tight branch coupling xa_start option
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The database or the jdbc provider specified by datasource does not support the tight branch coupling option.  Either the DB2 for z/OS database or the DB2 Universal JCC driver has rejected the tight branch coupling xa_start option.  The default option of loose branch coupling will be used.  This may cause lock timeouts, deadlocks and/or transaction rollbacks if the application is designed for tight branch coupling since database locks will not be shared across transaction branches within the same global transaction.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Visit the IBM support Web site for information on problem determination.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA0240E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_CONNECTION" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_CONNECTION=DSRA0240E: Invalid Connection.  Connection Pool is being purged.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A request was initiated by the user to purge the pool. This request makes existing connections in the pool no longer valid.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Exit the transaction, and the method boundary, and attempt the logic again with a new connection.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA8720W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MULTITHREADED_ACCESS_DETECTED" varFormat="Java">
    MULTITHREADED_ACCESS_DETECTED=DSRA8720W: Detected multithreaded access on {0}.
Last used with thread id: {1}
Current thread id:        {2}
Stack trace of current thread:{3}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The application attempted to access a connection or the connection&apos;s corresponding Statements, ResultSets, or metadata from a different thread. This behavior is a violation of the programming model for the application server. Closing the objects that the application attempted to access in a finalize() method is also considered a programming model violation, because the finalize() method is run by the JVM in another thread.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Adjust the application to avoid multithreaded access.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA7015E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DB2ZOS_TYPE2_ERROR" varFormat="Java">
    DB2ZOS_TYPE2_ERROR=DSRA7015E: DB2 does not support driver type 2 with DB2XADataSource under DB2 for z/OS
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The driverType custom property for the data source was set to the value of 2 on the DB2XADatasource. This configuration is not supported by DB2 for z/OS.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Use the DB2ConnectionPoolDatasource or switch to the DB2 Universal JDBC driver type 4 if it is available for your configuration.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA9120E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CALL_NOT_ALLOWED" varFormat="Java">
    CALL_NOT_ALLOWED=DSRA9120E: WebSphere &apos;jdbcCall&apos; method should only be used for proprietary, non-JDBC methods. The &apos;jdbcCall&apos; method can be used to invoke the proprietary, non-standard extensions to JDBC. It should not be used to invoke the JDBC API methods.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The application attempted to use the &apos;jdbcCall&apos; method to invoke a Java Database Connectivity (JDBC) method instead of a proprietary extension, or the application attempted to use the &apos;jdbcCall&apos; method to invoke a proprietary method that is not supported by the application server.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the method is from the JDBC API, invoke the method directly on the JDBC resource, instead of using the &apos;jdbcCall&apos; method. If the method is a proprietary extension that is not supported by the application server, then do not use the method.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA7601W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PARTIAL_CLOUDSCAPE_MIGRATION" varFormat="Java">
    PARTIAL_CLOUDSCAPE_MIGRATION=DSRA7601W: Cloudscape migration of database instance {0} to new database instance {1} was partially completed.  Last step to complete successfully is: {2}.  Missing steps are {3}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The migration of the Cloudscape instance was partially completed. See the steps that are missing for more details on what needs to be finished manually.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Fix the migration problem as described by migration log, and create the missing parts. There is no need to run the migration tool again, because the missing parts can be created manually.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA9540E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="NO_NULL_CONNECTION" varFormat="Java">
    NO_NULL_CONNECTION=DSRA9540E: The Connection cannot be null.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Connection cannot be null.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Pass a connection object that is valid.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA8780I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DEFAULT_MATCH_CURRENT" varFormat="Java">
    DEFAULT_MATCH_CURRENT=DSRA8780I: By default, the connection property, {0}, is matched for shareable connections based on the current state of the connection rather than the original connection request. You may use the data source custom property, {1}, to configure this behavior.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The data source custom property allows you to choose which connection sharing behavior you want.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the data source custom property is configured for the behavior you want.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA0093I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ERROR_RESOLVING_DB_IMPLICIT_TRANSACTIONS" varFormat="Java">
    ERROR_RESOLVING_DB_IMPLICIT_TRANSACTIONS=DSRA0093I: An implicit database transaction was detected . WebSphere tried to {0} the transaction but an error occurred {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Application Server has detected that the database started a transaction. The Application Server will attempt to resolve the transaction as configured in the custom properties for the data source. An error occurred that prevented the transaction from being resolved.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Gather the FFDC log files and any server log files. If the error is not related to a database outage, visit the IBM support Web site for problem determination.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA8050W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HELPER_NOT_FOUND" varFormat="Java">
    HELPER_NOT_FOUND=DSRA8050W: Unable to find the DataStoreHelper class specified: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The possible causes are: 1) The DataStoreHelper class that was specified is not correct, 2) the name or the package name for the DataStoreHelper class that was specified is not correct,  3) the DataStoreHelper class is not included in the class path, or 4) the JDBC provider that is used might not be supported in this release of the Application Server.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Based on the corresponding cause, perform one of the following actions: 1) Switch to the DataStoreHelper class that is appropriate,  2) correct the name or package name for the DataStoreHelper class, 3) correct the class path, or 4) use a different JDBC provider or a different version of the Application Server.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DSRA9601W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CMX_REGISTRATION_PROBLEM" varFormat="Java">
    CMX_REGISTRATION_PROBLEM=DSRA9601W: The application server failed to register for CMX notification.  The exception is: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The application server received an exception when attempting to register for CMX notification.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the exception. Visit the WebSphere support website for troubleshooting help if you cannot resolve the issue after examining the exception.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<!-- END MESSAGES -->
</TMSSource>
