<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/css" href="../../resources/stylesheets/wasmsgxml.css"?>
<TMSSource name="TivoliMessages" tmsVersion="1.0" xml:lang="en">
<!-- CMVC MSG File Name = ws/code/ejbcontainer.impl/src/com/ibm/ejs/container/container.nlsprops -->
<!-- DO NOT EDIT THIS FILE - This file was generated by the XML/Html & Property emitter -->
<!-- BEGIN MESSAGES -->
<Message ID="CNTR0073E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_LOCAL_TRANSACTION_RESOLVER_CNTR0073E" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_LOCAL_TRANSACTION_RESOLVER_CNTR0073E=CNTR0073E: Bean &quot;{0}&quot; attempted to use an invalid Local Transactions Resolution control.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Local Transactions Resolution control must be ContainerAtBoundary for a container-managed transaction or a container-managed Activity Session.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Set the Local Transactions Resolution control to &quot;ContainerAtBoundary&quot;.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0018E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="NON_APPLICATION_EXCEPTION_CNTR0018E" varFormat="Java">
    NON_APPLICATION_EXCEPTION_CNTR0018E=CNTR0018E: EJB threw an unexpected (non-declared) exception. Exception data: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An exception, which is not declared on the EJB method signature, was created when the EJB container attempted to invoke an EJB method.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the stack trace to determine the origin of the exception.  If the exception originates from customer-written code, correct the cause of the exception. If not, visit the IBM support Web site for information on problem determination.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0173E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="NAME_ALREADY_BOUND_FOR_SAME_EJB_CNTR0173E" varFormat="Java">
    NAME_ALREADY_BOUND_FOR_SAME_EJB_CNTR0173E=CNTR0173E: The {0} interface of the {1} bean in the {2} module of the {3} application cannot be bound to the {4} name location. The {5} interface of the same bean has already been bound to the {4} name location.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Each enterprise bean interface must specify a unique binding location.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the binding file for one of these two bean interfaces so that each interface has a unique binding location.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0252W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="UNABLE_TO_PURGE_AUTOMATIC_TIMERS_CNTR0252W" varFormat="Java">
    UNABLE_TO_PURGE_AUTOMATIC_TIMERS_CNTR0252W=CNTR0252W: Unable to remove automatic Enterprise Java Bean timers from the scheduler for the {0} application and {1} module, running on the {2} server.  To remove the timers manually, use wsadmin to execute this command: $AdminTask removeAutomaticEJBTimers &quot;-appName {0} -moduleName {1} -serverName {2} -nodeName {3} &quot;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Any automatic Enterprise Java Bean timers associated with the application and module, on the server, were not removed from the scheduler.  Therefore, the scheduler may attempt to run these timers in the future.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Execute the &apos;removeAutomaticEJBTimers&apos; command from a connected wsadmin session to remove the timers associated with the application and module on this specific server.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0017W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SECURITY_COLLABORATOR_THREW_UNEXPECTED_EXCEPTION_CNTR0017W" varFormat="Java">
    SECURITY_COLLABORATOR_THREW_UNEXPECTED_EXCEPTION_CNTR0017W=CNTR0017W: Security collaborator threw unexpected exception. 
 Exception data: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This exception is unexpected. The cause is not immediately known.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0174I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DEFAULT_EJB_HOME_JNDI_NAME_CNTR0174I" varFormat="Java">
    DEFAULT_EJB_HOME_JNDI_NAME_CNTR0174I=CNTR0174I: The {0} bean in the {1} module is an Enterprise Java Beans (EJB) version prior to 3.0, and has no home binding name specified. The following binding name has been manufactured for this bean: {2}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The home interface will be bound at the specified naming location.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    There is no user action required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0024W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="IOEXCEPTION_READING_FILE_FOR_STATEFUL_SESSION_BEAN_CNTR0024W" varFormat="Java">
    IOEXCEPTION_READING_FILE_FOR_STATEFUL_SESSION_BEAN_CNTR0024W=CNTR0024W: Unable to open input stream: {0} {1} {2}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Enterprise Java Bean (EJB) container encountered an IOException while attempting to read a file for a stateful session bean.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See the message in the IOException to determine the action to take. Ensure that the proper file permissions are set for the file.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0327E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_SESSION_SYNCH_SIGNATURE_CNTR0327E" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_SESSION_SYNCH_SIGNATURE_CNTR0327E=CNTR0327E: The {0} method does not have the required method signature for a {1} session synchronization method.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Enterprise JavaBeans 3.1 specification requires that session synchronization methods of a stateful session bean class have the following signature: after-begin and before-completion : void &amp;lt;METHOD&amp;gt; (), after-completion : void &amp;lt;METHOD&amp;gt; (boolean)
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the session synchronization method signature for this bean class.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR9421E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CNTR9421E_INVALID_LTC_RESOLVER_PROPERTY" varFormat="Java">
    CNTR9421E_INVALID_LTC_RESOLVER_PROPERTY=CNTR9421E: The {0} property was assigned an incorrect value of {1}.  This property indicates the local transaction containment (LTC) resolver setting, and must be either Application (default) or ContainerAtBoundary.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The LTC resolver property was assigned an unsupported value.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    The LTC resolver property must be assigned a default value of Application or ContainerAtBoundary.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0107E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SFB_CONTROLLER_TOKENBYTES_CNTR0107E" varFormat="Java">
    SFB_CONTROLLER_TOKENBYTES_CNTR0107E=CNTR0107E: Method {0}  cannot convert token to byte array :  stoken = {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The method that is specified was not able to convert the servant token to a byte array.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    There is no user action required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0196E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SINGLETON_ACCESS_TIMEOUT_OVERFLOW_CNTR0196E" varFormat="Java">
    SINGLETON_ACCESS_TIMEOUT_OVERFLOW_CNTR0196E=CNTR0196E: The conversion of access timeout value {0} from {1} time unit to milli-seconds time unit resulted in an overflow.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The access timeout is specified either via annotations or by deployment descriptor. The resulting conversion to milli-seconds must be greater than zero and less than java.lang.Long.MAX_VALUE (9223372036854775807) to be valid.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the access timeout value for the method identified by the message. A method name of &quot;*&quot; is used in deployment descriptor to indicate all methods of the singleton class. If annotation is used and @AccessTimeout annotation is not found on the method, correct the @AccessTimeout annotation at class level.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0251W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="UNABLE_TO_PURGE_AUTOMATIC_TIMERS_CNTR0251W" varFormat="Java">
    UNABLE_TO_PURGE_AUTOMATIC_TIMERS_CNTR0251W=CNTR0251W: Unable to remove automatic Enterprise Java Bean timers from the scheduler for the {0} application, running on the {1} server.  To remove the timers manually, use wsadmin to execute this command: $AdminTask removeAutomaticEJBTimers &quot;-appName {0} -serverName {1} -nodeName {2} &quot;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Any automatic Enterprise Java Bean timers associated with the application, on the server, were not removed from the scheduler.  Therefore, the scheduler may attempt to run these timers in the future.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Execute the &apos;removeAutomaticEJBTimers&apos; command from a connected wsadmin session to remove the timers associated with the application on this specific server.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR5026E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="JIT_NO_EJBCREATE_METHOD_CNTR5026E" varFormat="Java">
    JIT_NO_EJBCREATE_METHOD_CNTR5026E=CNTR5026E: The {2} method of the {1} home interface for the {0} entity bean does not define a corresponding ejbCreate method for the {3} class.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    According to the Enterprise JavaBeans (EJB) specification, the entity bean class must implement an ejbCreate method for every create method for a home interface.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Change the bean class to provide an ejbCreate method that corresponds to the method.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0067W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="BMT_DEFINES_CMT_ATTRIBUTES_CNTR0067W" varFormat="Java">
    BMT_DEFINES_CMT_ATTRIBUTES_CNTR0067W=CNTR0067W: SessionBean &quot;{0}&quot; or its home attempted to use an invalid combination of Bean Managed Transactions and Container Managed method-level transaction attributes. The method-level transaction attributes will be ignored.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The enterprise Java bean (EJB) specification states that a session bean or the home of a session bean with &quot;Bean Managed Transactions&quot; must not declare transaction attributes for the method. The attributes for the Container Managed method-level transaction have no meaning, because the session bean will use Bean Managed Transactions.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Remove the transaction attributes for the methods of this bean or the bean home.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR9265E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INPUT_FILE_NOT_FOUND_CNTR9265E" varFormat="Java">
    INPUT_FILE_NOT_FOUND_CNTR9265E=CNTR9265E: The {0} input file was not found.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The file specified as the first parameter was not found.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check the spelling and the read permissions of the specified file.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0071E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_LOCAL_TRANSACTION_RESOLVER_CNTR0071E" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_LOCAL_TRANSACTION_RESOLVER_CNTR0071E=CNTR0071E: Bean &quot;{0}&quot; in an EJB 1.1 module attempted to use an invalid Local Transactions Resolution control of &quot;ContainerAtBoundary&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Local Transactions Resolution control, &quot;ContainerAtBoundary&quot;, is not supported for EJB V1.1 modules.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Select &quot;Application&quot; for the Local Transactions Resolution control.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR9410I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CNTR9410I_STOP" varFormat="Java">
    CNTR9410I_STOP=CNTR9410I: The embeddable Enterprise JavaBeans (EJB) container has closed.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Close method has been invoked and the embeddable Enterprise JavaBeans (EJB) container has completed its shutdown routine.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    There is no user action required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0056W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="FAILED_TO_GET_WRAPPER_CNTR0056W" varFormat="Java">
    FAILED_TO_GET_WRAPPER_CNTR0056W=CNTR0056W: Failed to get the wrapper for a bean. Bean: 
 {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This exception is unexpected. The cause is not immediately known.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0227E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PARTIAL_CLASS_INTERCEPTOR_ORDER_CNTR0227E" varFormat="Java">
    PARTIAL_CLASS_INTERCEPTOR_ORDER_CNTR0227E=CNTR0227E: The {0} enterprise bean has an interceptor-order element which specifies the following interceptor-order list: {1}.  This list is not a total ordering of the class-level interceptors for this bean.  It is missing the following interceptor names: {2}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    When the interceptor-order element is used, the specified ordering at the class-level must be a total order. The order must be over all of the interceptor classes that have been defined at that level and above.  The only exception to this rule is when interceptor classes have been explicitly excluded by means of an exclude-default-inteceptors element.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify additional interceptor names on the class-level interceptor-order element for this bean. Then, the bean will provide a total ordering of the interceptors.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0200E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SINGLETON_DEPENDS_ON_NON_SINGLETON_BEAN_CNTR0200E" varFormat="Java">
    SINGLETON_DEPENDS_ON_NON_SINGLETON_BEAN_CNTR0200E=CNTR0200E: The {0} singleton session bean in the {1} module depends on the {2} enterprise bean in the {3} module, but the target is not a singleton session bean.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The bean was configured to depend on another bean through the @DependsOn annotation or the depends-on element in the ejb-jar.xml file. However, the other bean is not a singleton.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Remove or change the dependency on the non-singleton bean, or adjust the type of the non-singleton bean.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR5023E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="JIT_INVALID_SF_HOME_METHOD_CNTR5023E" varFormat="Java">
    JIT_INVALID_SF_HOME_METHOD_CNTR5023E=CNTR5023E: The {1} home interface for the {0} bean has a method that does not start with the create string. The {2} method is not allowed.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    According to the Enterprise JavaBeans (EJB) specification, all methods that are defined on a home interface for a stateless session bean must start with the create string.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Change the name of the method on the home interface so that it starts with the create string, or remove the method.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR5031E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="JIT_INVALID_EJBFIND_RETURN_CNTR5031E" varFormat="Java">
    JIT_INVALID_EJBFIND_RETURN_CNTR5031E=CNTR5031E: The {2} method with the {3} return type on the {1} class for the {0} entity bean must return the {4} primary key class.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    According to the Enterprise JavaBeans (EJB) specification, the return type of the ejbFindByPrimaryKey method for an entity bean class must be the primary key type.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Change the return type of the method to the primary key class.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR5007E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="JIT_NO_DEFAULT_CTOR_CNTR5007E" varFormat="Java">
    JIT_NO_DEFAULT_CTOR_CNTR5007E=CNTR5007E: The {1} bean class for the {0} bean does not have a public constructor that does not take parameters.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    According to the Enterprise JavaBeans (EJB) specification, the bean class must have a public constructor that does not take parameters.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Change the bean class to have a public constructor that does not take parameters.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0254W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="UNABLE_TO_PURGE_TIMERS_BECAUSE_RUNNING_IN_LOCAL_MODE_CNTR0254W" varFormat="Java">
    UNABLE_TO_PURGE_TIMERS_BECAUSE_RUNNING_IN_LOCAL_MODE_CNTR0254W=CNTR0254W: The application or module that was updated or removed contained automatically created Enterprise Java Bean timers.  However, because processing ran in a local mode, the timers were not removed.  Use the removeAutomaticEJBTimers command to remove them manually.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Use the removeAutommaticEJBTimers command to manually remove any automatic Enterprise Java Bean timers that are no longer valid.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    The processing to remove automatic Enterprise Java Bean timers does not execute when you are running in a disconnected wsadmin session.  As a result, the automatic Enterprise Java Bean timers were not removed.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR5005E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="JIT_INVALID_ABSTRACT_CLASS_CNTR5005E" varFormat="Java">
    JIT_INVALID_ABSTRACT_CLASS_CNTR5005E=CNTR5005E: The {1} bean class for the {0} bean is defined as abstract.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    According to the Enterprise JavaBeans (EJB) specification, the bean class must not be defined as abstract.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Do not define the bean class as an abstract class.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0091W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MISSING_MSGDESTREF_BINDING_CNTR0091W" varFormat="Java">
    MISSING_MSGDESTREF_BINDING_CNTR0091W=CNTR0091W: A reference to a MessageDestinationRef could not be found in the deployment descriptor for the WebApp or EnterpriseBean with the display name {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Java Enterprise Edition (Java EE) component might have specified binding information that is not valid.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the binding information is correct in the deployment descriptor for the Java EE component.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR9416E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CNTR9416E_NO_DATASOURCECLASS_SPECIFIED" varFormat="Java">
    CNTR9416E_NO_DATASOURCECLASS_SPECIFIED=CNTR9416E: The embeddable Enterprise JavaBeans (EJB) container properties for the {0} data source do not contain the property, className.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The properties that the embeddable Enterprise JavaBeans (EJB) container uses contain a data source with no className specified.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Add a className property for this data source to the properties file.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR5024E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="JIT_INVALID_BMP_HOME_METHOD_CNTR5024E" varFormat="Java">
    JIT_INVALID_BMP_HOME_METHOD_CNTR5024E=CNTR5024E: The {1} home interface for the {0} bean has a method that starts with the remove string. The {2} method is not allowed.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    According to the Enterprise JavaBeans (EJB) specification, you cannot define methods on an entity bean home interface that start with the remove string.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Change the name of the method on the home interface so that it does not start with the remove string, or remove the method.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0158E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="TIMEOUT_METHOD_MISSING_REQUIRED_PARM_CNTR0158E" varFormat="Java">
    TIMEOUT_METHOD_MISSING_REQUIRED_PARM_CNTR0158E=CNTR0158E: The {0} session bean in the {1} module has the {2} method configured as a timeout method. This method must have a single parameter of the javax.ejb.Timer type, or take zero parameters.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Timer beans must implement a timeout method, which has either a single parameter of the javax.ejb.Timer type, or no parameters.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the bean implementation to include the required parameter, or include no parameters.   Then, reinstall the application.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0039E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CAUGHT_EXCEPTION_AND_RETHROWING_CNTR0039E" varFormat="Java">
    CAUGHT_EXCEPTION_AND_RETHROWING_CNTR0039E=CNTR0039E: EJB container caught {0} and is rethrowing the caught exception.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This exception is unexpected. The cause is not immediately known.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0105E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SFB_CONTROLLER_EXCEPTOKEN_CNTR0105E" varFormat="Java">
    SFB_CONTROLLER_EXCEPTOKEN_CNTR0105E=CNTR0105E: Method {0} caught exception: {1}   stoken = {2}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The method that is specified caught an exception when processing the servant token.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    There is no user action required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0090E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SERVICEREF_BINDING_EXCEPTION_CNTR0090E" varFormat="Java">
    SERVICEREF_BINDING_EXCEPTION_CNTR0090E=CNTR0090E: WebServiceRef binding failed for {0} : {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This exception is unexpected. The cause is not immediately known.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0324E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_SESSION_SYNCH_PARAM_CNTR0324E" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_SESSION_SYNCH_PARAM_CNTR0324E=CNTR0324E: The {0} method configured in the ejb-jar.xml file does not have the required method signature for a {1} session synchronization method for the {2} bean in the {3} module of the {4} application.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Enterprise JavaBeans 3.1 specification requires that session synchronization methods of a stateful session bean class have the following signature: after-begin and before-completion : void &amp;lt;METHOD&amp;gt; (), after-completion : void &amp;lt;METHOD&amp;gt; (boolean)
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the session synchronization method signature for this bean class.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0164E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="TIMEOUT_METHOD_THROWS_APP_EXCEPTION_CNTR0164E" varFormat="Java">
    TIMEOUT_METHOD_THROWS_APP_EXCEPTION_CNTR0164E=CNTR0164E: The {0} enterprise bean in the {1} module implements a {2} timeout method, which creates an application exception..
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Timeout methods must not create application exceptions.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the timeout method implementation to not create application exceptions.  Then, reinstall the application.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0003W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CANNOT_ACTIVATE_STATEFUL_BEAN_CNTR0003W" varFormat="Java">
    CANNOT_ACTIVATE_STATEFUL_BEAN_CNTR0003W=CNTR0003W: A Stateful SessionBean could not be activated: {0} {1} 
 {2}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The container failed to activate a stateful session bean from storage.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Take action based upon the exception message in message CNTR0003W.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0134E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_MDB_INTERFACE_SPECIFIED_CNTR0134E" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_MDB_INTERFACE_SPECIFIED_CNTR0134E=CNTR0134E: The {0} message-driven bean in the {1} module has an interface configured for a component, business, Web service endpoint, or home.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Message-driven beans cannot have any of these interface types configured.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the ejb-jar.xml file or source code annotation configuration settings for this bean.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR5016E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="JIT_MUST_EXTEND_EJBLOCALHOME_CNTR5016E" varFormat="Java">
    JIT_MUST_EXTEND_EJBLOCALHOME_CNTR5016E=CNTR5016E: The {1} interface, which has been configured as the local home interface for the {0} bean, must extend the javax.ejb.EJBLocalHome interface.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    According to the Enterprise JavaBeans (EJB) specification, the configured local home interface must extend the javax.ejb.EJBLocalHome interface.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Change the interface to extend the javax.ejb.EJBLocalHome interface or change the bean configuration to not specify the interface as a local home interface.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR5104E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="JIT_MISSING_REMOTE_EX_CNTR5104E" varFormat="Java">
    JIT_MISSING_REMOTE_EX_CNTR5104E=CNTR5104E: The {0} method on the {1} interface must be defined with the java.rmi.RemoteException exception on the throws clause.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    According to the Enterprise JavaBeans (EJB) specification, for remote business interface methods that implement the java.rmi.Remote interface, the throws clause must include the java.rmi.RemoteException exception.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Add the RemoteException exception to the throws clause of the method. Also, you can change the interface to not implement the java.rmi.Remote interface or change the application to not use the interface as an EJB remote interface.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0051E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CLIENT_INACTIVITY_TIMEOUT_CNTR0051E" varFormat="Java">
    CLIENT_INACTIVITY_TIMEOUT_CNTR0051E=CNTR0051E: Transaction has timed out due to no client activity for greater than {1} seconds. Transaction ID: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The client has been inactive longer than the inactivity timeout value.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    This can be a normal occurrence if client goes away and leaves a transaction active.  If client is still active, have an administrator determine whether to change the Client or the Transaction Inactivity Timeout value.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0052W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="LRU_THREAD_INTERRUPTED_CNTR0052W" varFormat="Java">
    LRU_THREAD_INTERRUPTED_CNTR0052W=CNTR0052W: LRU thread was interrupted. Terminating. {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This exception is unexpected. The cause is not immediately known.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0098I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="FBF_DISABLED_CNTR0098I" varFormat="Java">
    FBF_DISABLED_CNTR0098I=CNTR0098I: Container-managed pre-find persistent store synchronization disabled for bean: &quot;{0}&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The application is configured for this bean to not synchronize with persistent storage prior to the invocation of custom findBy methods. This behavior is not compliant with the enterprise Java bean (EJB) V2.0 and later specifications, but it can improve performance.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    There is no user action required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0036E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="FINDER_ON_BEAN_NOT_SUPPORTED_CNTR0036E" varFormat="Java">
    FINDER_ON_BEAN_NOT_SUPPORTED_CNTR0036E=CNTR0036E: EJB container does not support using the bean instance for finder methods on EJB 1.x container managed persistence and is throwing {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A bean that is configured for enterprise Java bean (EJB) V1.x container managed persistence has attempted to invoke methods on a bean instance for the processing of a finder method.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Redeploy the bean and attempt the operation again.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0153E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DUPLICATE_ROLES_SPECIFIED_IN_CLASS_ANNOTATION_CNTR0153E" varFormat="Java">
    DUPLICATE_ROLES_SPECIFIED_IN_CLASS_ANNOTATION_CNTR0153E=CNTR0153E: The {0} role is specified multiple times in the class level @RolesAllowed annotation on the {1} enterprise bean class.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A given role can be specified once in a @RolesAllowed annotation..
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Change the Java source code by removing the duplicate roles from this annotation. Then, reinstall the application.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0199E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SINGLETON_DEPENDS_ON_AMBIGUOUS_NAME_CNTR0199E" varFormat="Java">
    SINGLETON_DEPENDS_ON_AMBIGUOUS_NAME_CNTR0199E=CNTR0199E: The {0} singleton session bean in the {1} module depends on {2}, which does not uniquely specify an enterprise bean.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The bean was configured to depend on another bean with the specified name.  A bean with that name does not exist in the same module, and more than one module has a bean with that name.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Remove the dependency, or use a fully qualified bean name such as module.jar#BeanName
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0238E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INTERCEPTOR_METHOD_NOT_FOUND_CNTR0238E" varFormat="Java">
    INTERCEPTOR_METHOD_NOT_FOUND_CNTR0238E=CNTR0238E: The {2} interceptor class specifies the {1} method, which is not an {0} method of this class.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified method name is not a method of the interceptor class.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct either the method name or method signature to specify one of the methods of this interceptor class.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0063W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MISSING_EJBREF_BINDING_CNTR0063W" varFormat="Java">
    MISSING_EJBREF_BINDING_CNTR0063W=CNTR0063W: A reference to an EJB could not be found in the deployment descriptor for the WebApp or EnterpriseBean with the display name {0}. The EJB may have specified binding information that is not valid.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    There might be a deployment descriptor with syntax that is not valid.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the binding information in the deployment descriptor for the enterprise Java bean (EJB) is correct.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR9417E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CNTR9417E_MAXCONNECTIONS_VALUE_NOT_NUMERIC" varFormat="Java">
    CNTR9417E_MAXCONNECTIONS_VALUE_NOT_NUMERIC=CNTR9417E: The embeddable Enterprise JavaBeans (EJB) container properties for the {0} data source contain a {1} ConnectionPool.MaxConnections value that is not a positive numeric value or zero.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The properties that the embeddable Enterprise JavaBeans (EJB) container uses contain a data source with a ConnectionPool.MaxConnections value that is not a positive numeric value or zero.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Change the ConnectionPool.MaxConnections property value for this data source to be a positive numeric value or zero.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR9419E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CNTR9419E_JPA_CLOSE_FAIL" varFormat="Java">
    CNTR9419E_JPA_CLOSE_FAIL=CNTR9419E: The embeddable Enterprise JavaBeans (EJB) container failed to shutdown the JPA provider. Exception: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An error during shutdown processing prevented the JPA provider from closing correctly due to the exception. This is indicative of another problem that should have occurred earlier in the logs. Future attempts to use JPA may fail.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Resolve the failure by examining the exception, the logs, and the FFDC output to find and resolve the underlying problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0328W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MAXIMUM_UNCLAIMED_ASYNC_RESULTS_CNTR0328W" varFormat="Java">
    MAXIMUM_UNCLAIMED_ASYNC_RESULTS_CNTR0328W=CNTR0328W: There are {0} unclaimed results from remote asynchronous EJB method invocations.  The product will discard the oldest result when the number of unclaimed results exceeds {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The number of unretrieved results from remote asynchronous EJB method invocations is approaching or has exceeded the maximum.  When the number of unretrieved results exceeds the maximum, the product will discard the oldest result.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Monitor the AsyncFutureObjectCount PMI statistic to determine which EJB results have unclaimed results, and then update the corresponding client code to claim the results.  If results are being discarded faster than clients can claim them, then adjust the remote future object duration for EJB asynchronous methods, and set the com.ibm.websphere.ejbcontainer.maxUnclaimedAsyncResults system property to the desired maximum number of unclaimed results.  Alternatively, change the EJB to use a local interface rather than a remote interface since the results of an asynchronous method on a local interface do not need to be tracked by the EJB container and can be garbage collected normally.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR5001E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="JIT_MISSING_REMOTE_HOME_CNTR5001E" varFormat="Java">
    JIT_MISSING_REMOTE_HOME_CNTR5001E=CNTR5001E: The {0} bean is configured with the {1} remote component interface, but a remote home interface has not been provided.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    According to the Enterprise JavaBeans (EJB) specification, a remote home interface must be provided when a remote component interface is provided.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Change the application configuration to provide a remote home interface for the bean.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0131E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="REQUIRED_INTERFACE_MISSING_CNTR0131E" varFormat="Java">
    REQUIRED_INTERFACE_MISSING_CNTR0131E=CNTR0131E: The {0} bean in the {1} module does not have any configured productive interfaces.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Depending on the bean type, an enterprise bean must have at least one component, business, Web service endpoint, or message listener interface configured.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the ejb-jar.xml file or source code annotation configuration settings for this bean.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0326E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MULTIPLE_SESSION_SYNCH_METHODS_CNTR0326E" varFormat="Java">
    MULTIPLE_SESSION_SYNCH_METHODS_CNTR0326E=CNTR0326E: Multiple {0} session synchronization methods have been configured for the {1} bean. The configured session synchronization methods are : {2} and {3}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Enterprise JavaBeans 3.1 specification requires that only one of each type of session synchronization method be configured for a stateful session bean.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Configure only one of each type of session synchronization method for this bean.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR9261E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="UNABLE_TO_CREATE_TEMP_FILE_CNTR9261E" varFormat="Java">
    UNABLE_TO_CREATE_TEMP_FILE_CNTR9261E=CNTR9261E: Unable to create temporary file in the {0} directory.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A temporary file could not be created on the file system.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the file system permissions settings for the specified directory.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR9271E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="UNABLE_TO_DELETE_ROOT_DIRECTORY_FOR_STUBS_PROCESSING_CNTR9271E" varFormat="Java">
    UNABLE_TO_DELETE_ROOT_DIRECTORY_FOR_STUBS_PROCESSING_CNTR9271E=CNTR9271E: The {0} directory could not be deleted.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified directory can not be deleted.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Manually delete the directory.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0234E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_INIT_ANNOTATION_CNTR0234E" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_INIT_ANNOTATION_CNTR0234E=CNTR0234E: An initialization method for a stateful session bean can be an ejbCreate&amp;lt;METHOD&amp;gt; method only when the bean conforms to the Enterprise JavaBeans (EJB) 2.1 or earlier specification levels. Therefore, it cannot be applied to the {0} method of the {1} enterprise bean.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Enterprise JavaBeans 3.0 specification requires a matching ejbCreate&amp;lt;METHOD&amp;gt; to be the initialization method of a stateful session bean class. This requirement exists for stateful session beans that are written for the EJB 2.1 or earlier-level application programming interface (API).
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Remove the @Init annotation or the init-method element in ejb-jar.xml file from the specified method of this bean.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0148E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="NO_CONNECTION_FACTORY_FOR_CMP_BEAN_CNTR0148E" varFormat="Java">
    NO_CONNECTION_FACTORY_FOR_CMP_BEAN_CNTR0148E=CNTR0148E: The {0} Container Managed Persistence (CMP) entity bean is configured to use a CMP Connection Factory with a {1} Java Naming and Directory Interface (JNDI). This Connection Factory resource is not configured.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Connection Factory resource that is  required by this bean is not configured. The CMP entity bean will not function.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Create the required Connection Factory resource by ensuring that the proper data source is selected for CMP use in the administrative console.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0304W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="STATEFUL_TIMEOUT_ON_NON_SFSB_CNTR0304W" varFormat="Java">
    STATEFUL_TIMEOUT_ON_NON_SFSB_CNTR0304W=CNTR0304W: The {0} enterprise bean in the {1} module of the {2} application contains the @StatefulTimeout annotation.  The StatefulTimeout annotation is only valid on stateful session beans.  The Enterprise JavaBean (EJB) container will ignore the annotation on this bean.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The @StatefulTimeout annotation is only applicable to stateful session beans.  The Enterprise JavaBean (EJB) container will ignore the annotation on this bean.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Remove the @StatefulTimeout annotation from the specified bean, or make the bean a stateful session bean.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0320E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_SINGLETON_COMPONENT_INTERFACE_SPECIFIED_CNTR0320E" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_SINGLETON_COMPONENT_INTERFACE_SPECIFIED_CNTR0320E=CNTR0320E: The {0} singleton session bean in the {1} module has an interface configured for a component view.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    According to the Enterprise JavaBeans (EJB) specification, the EJB 2.1 remote and local client views are not supported for singleton session beans.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the ejb-jar.xml file or source code annotation configuration settings for this bean.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0080E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="TIMERSERVICE_NOT_AVAILABLE_CNTR0080E" varFormat="Java">
    TIMERSERVICE_NOT_AVAILABLE_CNTR0080E=CNTR0080E: EJB timer service is not available for EJB implementing the javax.ejb.TimedObject interface: {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The enterprise Java bean (EJB) implementation requires the EJB timer service, which has been disabled or did not start.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See the previous messages to determine why the EJB timer service did not start, and correct the problem or enable the EJB timer service.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR5003E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="JIT_NON_PUBLIC_CLASS_CNTR5003E" varFormat="Java">
    JIT_NON_PUBLIC_CLASS_CNTR5003E=CNTR5003E: The {1} bean class for the {0} bean is not defined as public.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    According to the Enterprise JavaBeans (EJB) specification, the bean class must be defined as public.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Define the bean class as public.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0162E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CONFIGURED_TIMEOUT_METHOD_NOT_FOUND_CNTR0162E" varFormat="Java">
    CONFIGURED_TIMEOUT_METHOD_NOT_FOUND_CNTR0162E=CNTR0162E: The {0} enterprise bean in the {1} module has specified the following timeout method: {2}  This method is not implemented by the bean.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Timer beans must provide an implementation for the configured timeout method.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the bean implementation to include the required timeout method.   Then, reinstall the application.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR5004E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="JIT_INVALID_FINAL_CLASS_CNTR5004E" varFormat="Java">
    JIT_INVALID_FINAL_CLASS_CNTR5004E=CNTR5004E: The {1} bean class for the {0} bean is defined as final.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    According to the Enterprise JavaBeans (EJB) specification, the bean class must not be defined as final.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Do not define the bean class as a final class.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR9241I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="NO_REMOTE_INTERFACES_CNTR9241I" varFormat="Java">
    NO_REMOTE_INTERFACES_CNTR9241I=CNTR9241I: The {0} Java archive (JAR) file has no level 3.0 enterprise beans with remote interfaces.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The listed jar file does not contain any level 3.0 enterprise beans with remote interfaces.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If this module should have contained level 3.0 enterprise beans with remote interfaces, check the module&apos;s annotations or ejb-jar.xml configuration data.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR5012E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="JIT_INVALID_EXTENDS_JAVAX_EJB_CNTR5012E" varFormat="Java">
    JIT_INVALID_EXTENDS_JAVAX_EJB_CNTR5012E=CNTR5012E: The {1} interface, which has been configured as a business interface for the {0} bean, must not extend the {2} interface.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    According to the Enterprise JavaBeans (EJB) specification, the configured business interfaces must not extend any interface in the javax.ejb package.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Change the business interface to not extend an interface in the javax.ejb package. Also, you can change the bean configuration to not specify the interface as a business interface.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0100E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SFB_CONTROLLER_EXCEPTION_CNTR0100E" varFormat="Java">
    SFB_CONTROLLER_EXCEPTION_CNTR0100E=CNTR0100E: Method {0} caught exception: {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An exception was caught in the specified method.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    There is no user action required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0021E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="NON_APPLICATION_EXCEPTION_ON_BEAN_CNTR0021E" varFormat="Java">
    NON_APPLICATION_EXCEPTION_ON_BEAN_CNTR0021E=CNTR0021E: EJB threw an unexpected (non-declared) exception while invoking a method on bean &quot;{1}&quot;. Exception data: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An exception, which is not declared on the EJB method signature, was created when the EJB container attempted to invoke this EJB method.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the stack trace to determine the origin of the exception.  If the exception originates from customer-written code, correct the cause of the exception. If not, visit the IBM support Web site for information on problem determination.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0078I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CUSTOMFINDER_SQLFORUPDATE_CNTR0078I" varFormat="Java">
    CUSTOMFINDER_SQLFORUPDATE_CNTR0078I=CNTR0078I: Custom Finder access intent support enabled for bean {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The user has specified that Custom Finders access intent must be honored. If the method has an Update access intent, the Access Intent will be honored.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    You can disable the processing of access intent for custom finders by using the Java Virtual Machine (JVM) and the properties at the bean level, or you can set the access intent of the method to Read-Only.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR9422E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CNTR9422E_INVALID_LTC_UNRESOLVED_ACTION_PROPERTY" varFormat="Java">
    CNTR9422E_INVALID_LTC_UNRESOLVED_ACTION_PROPERTY=CNTR9422E: The {0} property was assigned an incorrect value of {1}.  This property indicates the local transaction containment (LTC) unresolved action setting, and must be either Rollback (default) or Commit.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The LTC unresolved action property was assigned an unsupported value.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    The LTC unresolved action property must be assigned a default value of Rollback or Commit.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0115I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SFB_CONTROLLER_DRSEVENT_IS_CONGESTED_CNTR0115I" varFormat="Java">
    SFB_CONTROLLER_DRSEVENT_IS_CONGESTED_CNTR0115I=CNTR0115I: SfDRSControllerInstance {0} received event IS_CONGESTED.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The SfDRSControllerInstance that is specified received the event IS_CONGESTED.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    There is no user action required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0083E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CREATE_ENDPOINT_FAILED_CNTR0083E" varFormat="Java">
    CREATE_ENDPOINT_FAILED_CNTR0083E=CNTR0083E: Creation of a message endpoint failed: 
 {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This exception is unexpected. The cause is not immediately known.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0165E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="TIMEOUT_METHOD_MUST_RETURN_VOID_CNTR0165E" varFormat="Java">
    TIMEOUT_METHOD_MUST_RETURN_VOID_CNTR0165E=CNTR0165E: The {0} enterprise bean in the {1} module implements a {2} timeout method, which has a non-void return type.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Timeout methods must return void.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the timeout method implementation to return void.  Then, reinstall the application.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR5010E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="JIT_INVALID_MTHD_PREFIX_CNTR5010E" varFormat="Java">
    JIT_INVALID_MTHD_PREFIX_CNTR5010E=CNTR5010E: The name of the {2} business method of the {1} interface for the {0} bean must not start with ejb.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    According to the Enterprise JavaBeans (EJB) specification, the name of business methods must not start with ejb. Otherwise, conflicts might occur with the callback methods.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Change the name of the business method so that it does not start with ejb.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0221E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ML_DUPLICATES_CL_CNTR0221E" varFormat="Java">
    ML_DUPLICATES_CL_CNTR0221E=CNTR0221E: The {0} method-level interceptor for the {1} method of the {2} enterprise bean duplicates a name that is in the following class-level interceptor list: {3}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An interceptor class can be either a class-level or a method-level interceptor, but not both types.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Eliminate the interceptor class from either the class-level interceptor list or the method-level interceptor list.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0014W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="STATEFUL_BEAN_REAPER_THREAD_INTERRUPTED_CNTR0014W" varFormat="Java">
    STATEFUL_BEAN_REAPER_THREAD_INTERRUPTED_CNTR0014W=CNTR0014W: StatefulBeanReaper thread was interrupted; terminating. 
 {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This exception is unexpected. The cause is not immediately known.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0183E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="TIMERSERVICE_TIMERMANAGER_NOT_FOUND_CNTR0183E" varFormat="Java">
    TIMERSERVICE_TIMERMANAGER_NOT_FOUND_CNTR0183E=CNTR0183E: The timer manager used by the EJB timer service could not be obtained.
{0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An attempt was made to obtain the timer manager, because the option to create a separate thread pool for non-persistent timers was configured on the EJBTimer configuration object (uniqueTimerManagerForNP).
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    As an alternative, you may configure the timer service to use a scheduler for non-persistent timers.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0016W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="REMOVE_FROM_PASSIVATION_STORE_FAILED_CNTR0016W" varFormat="Java">
    REMOVE_FROM_PASSIVATION_STORE_FAILED_CNTR0016W=CNTR0016W: Passivated Stateful SessionBean &quot;{0}&quot; could not be removed due to exception: {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The container was unable to remove a passivated stateful session bean from the passivation store.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Take action based upon the exception message in message CNTR0016W.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0323E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="BOTH_SESSION_SYNCH_STYLES_CNTR0323E" varFormat="Java">
    BOTH_SESSION_SYNCH_STYLES_CNTR0323E=CNTR0323E: The {0} bean in the {1} module of the {2} application implements the javax.ejb.SessionSynchronization interface and also configures a session synchronization method in the ejb-jar.xml or with an annotation. The configured session synchronization method is {3}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Enterprise JavaBeans 3.1 specification requires that a stateful session bean must not both implement the javax.ejb.SessionSynchronization interface and also configure a session synchronization method in the ejb-jar.xml file or with an annotation.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Remove either the implementation of the javax.ejb.SessionSynchronization interface or the configuration of the session synchronization methods.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR9255E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MISSING_LOG_FILE_PARAM_CNTR9255E" varFormat="Java">
    MISSING_LOG_FILE_PARAM_CNTR9255E=CNTR9255E: The required log file name parameter is missing.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    For option -logfile, the log file name must be provided as the next parameter
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the usage statement and provide the required log file name parameter.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0244E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="BUSINESS_METHOD_NOT_FOUND_FOR_INTERCEPTOR_BINDING_CNTR0244E" varFormat="Java">
    BUSINESS_METHOD_NOT_FOUND_FOR_INTERCEPTOR_BINDING_CNTR0244E=CNTR0244E: The {0} method name is not found in one of the business interfaces of the {1} enterprise bean. A style {2} interceptor-binding element requires the method to be a business method of the enterprise bean.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    According to the Enterprise JavaBeans (EJB) specification, a style 3 or style 4 interceptor-binding must use a &amp;lt;method-name&amp;gt; tag to specify the name of a method that is found in one of the business interfaces of the enterprise bean.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Either specify one of the method names found in one of the business interfaces of the enterprise bean or add the method to one of the business interfaces of the enterprise bean.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR8992E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ENGLISH_ONLY_ERROR_MESSAGE_CNTR8992E" varFormat="Java">
    ENGLISH_ONLY_ERROR_MESSAGE_CNTR8992E=CNTR8992E: This message is an English-only Error message: {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This error message is not translated.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See message for details.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR9272E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="OUTPUT_FILE_NOT_FOUND_CNTR9272E" varFormat="Java">
    OUTPUT_FILE_NOT_FOUND_CNTR9272E=CNTR9272E: The {0} output file cannot be found.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified output file cannot be found.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check the spelling and the write permissions for the file.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0109E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SFB_CONTROLLER_EVENT_CNTR0109E" varFormat="Java">
    SFB_CONTROLLER_EVENT_CNTR0109E=CNTR0109E: Method {0}  event parameter is null.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The method that is specified was passed an event parameter that is null.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    There is no user action required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0140E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="JNDI_BINDING_HAS_NO_CORRESPONDING_BUSINESS_INTERFACE_CLASS_CNTR0140E" varFormat="Java">
    JNDI_BINDING_HAS_NO_CORRESPONDING_BUSINESS_INTERFACE_CLASS_CNTR0140E=CNTR0140E: The {0} bean in the {1} module has specified the {2} business interface, which does not exist for a business interface Java Naming and Directory Interface (JNDI) binding.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Each business interface JNDI binding must have a valid business interface class configured.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the ejb-jar.xml file or source code annotations to configure a valid business interface class.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0187E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_TX_ATTRIBUTE_FOR_ASYNCH_METHOD_CNTR0187E" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_TX_ATTRIBUTE_FOR_ASYNCH_METHOD_CNTR0187E=CNTR0187E: The {0} method on the {1} bean in the {2} module of the {3} application has a {4} transaction attributed configured.  Asynchronous methods only support transaction attributes of type TX_REQUIRED, TX_REQUIRES_NEW, or TX_NOT_SUPPORTED.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Asynchronous methods can have the following transaction attribute types configured: TX_REQUIRED, TX_REQUIRES_NEW, or TX_NOT_SUPPORTED.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Change the transaction attribute configuration on the method to one of the three supported types.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0322W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INCOMPATIBLE_RETURN_TYPES_CNTR0322W" varFormat="Java">
    INCOMPATIBLE_RETURN_TYPES_CNTR0322W=CNTR0322W: The {0} return type for the {1} method of the {2} enterprise bean is not compatible with the {3} return type for the corresponding method on the {4} interface.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    According to the Enterprise JavaBeans (EJB) specification, method return types for an enterprise bean must be compatible with the corresponding interface.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Change the return type of the method so that the enterprise bean and the interface return types are compatible.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0037E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PREPARED_STATEMENT_NOT_FOUND_CNTR0037E" varFormat="Java">
    PREPARED_STATEMENT_NOT_FOUND_CNTR0037E=CNTR0037E: Prepared statement does not map to connection.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This exception is unexpected. The cause is not immediately known.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR5013E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="JIT_INVALID_EXTENDS_REMOTE_CNTR5013E" varFormat="Java">
    JIT_INVALID_EXTENDS_REMOTE_CNTR5013E=CNTR5013E: The {1} interface, which has been configured as a local interface for the {0} bean, must not extend the javax.rmi.Remote interface.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    According to the Enterprise JavaBeans (EJB) specification, the configured local interfaces must not extend the javax.rmi.Remote interface.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Change the interface to not extend the javax.rmi.Remote interface. Also, you can change the bean configuration to not specify the interface as a local interface.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0004E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ATTEMPT_TO_ACQUIRE_LOCK_INTERRUPTED_CNTR0004E" varFormat="Java">
    ATTEMPT_TO_ACQUIRE_LOCK_INTERRUPTED_CNTR0004E=CNTR0004E: An attempt to acquire a lock was interrupted. 
 Lock : {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A thread attempting to acquire an exclusive lock within the container was interrupted while waiting for the lock.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0047E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="METHOD_NOT_ALLOWED_CNTR0047E" varFormat="Java">
    METHOD_NOT_ALLOWED_CNTR0047E=CNTR0047E: Bean is attempting to use interface or method &quot;{0}&quot; in a situation prohibited by the EJB specification.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Enterprise Java Bean (EJB) Specification does not allow the method for one of the following reasons: - The getRollbackOnly and setRollbackOnly methods of the MessageDriven-Context interface should be used only in the message-driven bean methods that run in the context of a transaction. # - Invoking the getCallerPrincipal and isCallerInRole methods is not allowed in the message-driven bean methods because the Container does not have a client security context. # - Invoking the getRollbackOnly and setRollbackOnly methods is not allowed in the message-driven bean methods for which the Container does not have a meaningful transaction context, and for all message-driven beans with bean-managed transaction demarcation. # - The UserTransaction interface is not available to message-driven beans with container- managed transaction demarcation. # - Invoking getEJBHome or getEJBLocalHome is not allowed in message-driven bean methods because there are no EJBHome or EJBLocalHome objects for message-driven beans. #
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Do not invoke the method in this environment.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0247E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DUPLICATE_STYLE_3_INTERCEPTOR_BINDING_CNTR0247E" varFormat="Java">
    DUPLICATE_STYLE_3_INTERCEPTOR_BINDING_CNTR0247E=CNTR0247E: More than one style 3 interceptor-binding element is provided in the deployment descriptor for the {0} method of the {1} enterprise bean.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    According to the Enterprise JavaBeans (EJB) specification, only one style 3 interceptor-binding can be used for each method of an enterprise bean.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct deployment descriptor so that only one style 3 interceptor-binding is used for the method of an enterprise bean.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0321E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INCOMPATIBLE_RETURN_TYPES_CNTR0321E" varFormat="Java">
    INCOMPATIBLE_RETURN_TYPES_CNTR0321E=CNTR0321E: The {0} return type for the {1} method of the {2} enterprise bean does not match the {3} return type for the corresponding method on the {4} interface.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    According to the Enterprise JavaBeans (EJB) specification, method return types for an enterprise bean must match the corresponding interface.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Change the return type of the method so that the enterprise bean and the interface return types are the same.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0008W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CANNOT_REMOVE_CNTR0008W" varFormat="Java">
    CANNOT_REMOVE_CNTR0008W=CNTR0008W: A passivated Stateful SessionBean could not be removed: {0} {1} {2}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The container was unable to remove a passivated stateful session bean from storage.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Take action based upon the exception message in message CNTR0008W.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0116I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SFB_CONTROLLER_DRSEVENT_NOT_CONGESTED_CNTR0116I" varFormat="Java">
    SFB_CONTROLLER_DRSEVENT_NOT_CONGESTED_CNTR0116I=CNTR0116I: SfDRSControllerInstance {0} received event NOT_CONGESTED.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The SfDRSControllerInstance that is specified received the event NOT_CONGESTED.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    There is no user action required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0002W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="FAILED_TO_GET_WRAPPER_FOR_HOME_CNTR0002W" varFormat="Java">
    FAILED_TO_GET_WRAPPER_FOR_HOME_CNTR0002W=CNTR0002W: Failed to get the wrapper for a home. 
 Home: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This exception is unexpected. The cause is not immediately known.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0139E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MULTIPLE_JNDI_BINDING_NAMES_CNTR0139E" varFormat="Java">
    MULTIPLE_JNDI_BINDING_NAMES_CNTR0139E=CNTR0139E: The {0} bean in the {1} module has multiple Java Naming and Directory Interface (JNDI) binding names specified for the {2} business interface.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Each business interface can have a single JNDI binding name configured.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the ejb-jar-bnd.xml bindings file to give this bean a single JNDI binding name.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR5015E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="JIT_MUST_EXTEND_EJBOBJECT_CNTR5015E" varFormat="Java">
    JIT_MUST_EXTEND_EJBOBJECT_CNTR5015E=CNTR5015E: The {1} interface, which has been configured as the remote component interface for the {0} bean, must extend the javax.ejb.EJBObject interface.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    According to the Enterprise JavaBeans (EJB) specification, the configured remote component interface must extend the javax.ejb.EJBObject interface.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Change the interface to extend the javax.ejb.EJBObject interface. Also, you can change the bean configuration to not specify the interface as a remote component interface.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0132E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_SESSION_BEAN_INTERFACE_SPECIFIED_CNTR0132E" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_SESSION_BEAN_INTERFACE_SPECIFIED_CNTR0132E=CNTR0132E: The {0} session bean in the {1} module has an interface configured for a message listener or Web service endpoint.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Stateless session beans cannot have message listener interfaces configured. Stateful session beans cannot have either of these interface types configured.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the ejb-jar.xml file or source code annotation configuration settings for this bean.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0188E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="UNEXPECTED_EXCEPTION_CNTR0188E" varFormat="Java">
    UNEXPECTED_EXCEPTION_CNTR0188E=CNTR0188E: An unexpected exception was caught.  The exception is: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This exception is unexpected. The cause is not immediately known.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0097W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MISSING_CONTAINER_DRSSETTINGS_CNTR0097W" varFormat="Java">
    MISSING_CONTAINER_DRSSETTINGS_CNTR0097W=CNTR0097W: Memory-to-memory replication settings for EJB container is missing.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Stateful session bean failover using memory-to-memory replication has been enabled, but the memory-to-memory replication settings are missing.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Disable stateful session bean failover, or provide the settings for memory-to-memory replication for the EJB container.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0154E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ATTEMPT_TO_REFERENCE_MISSING_INTERFACE_CNTR0154E" varFormat="Java">
    ATTEMPT_TO_REFERENCE_MISSING_INTERFACE_CNTR0154E=CNTR0154E: Another component is attempting to reference the {0} enterprise bean in the {1} module.  This bean does not support an implementation of the {2} interface, which the other component is attempting to reference.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The component that is attempting to reference this bean has a configuration error. The component has specified an unsupported interface for this bean.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Change the ejb-ref tag or @EJB annotation on the component that is attempting to reference this bean so that it specifies a supported interface. Check the log file for a related exception, which indicates the calling component that has the configuration error.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0201E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SINGLETON_DEPENDS_ON_SELF_CNTR0201E" varFormat="Java">
    SINGLETON_DEPENDS_ON_SELF_CNTR0201E=CNTR0201E: The {0} singleton session bean in the {1} module directly or indirectly depends on itself.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The bean was configured to depend on itself or another bean that indirectly depends on that bean through the @DependsOn annotation or the depends-on element in the ejb-jar.xml file.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Remove or change the dependency on the specified bean, or change one of its dependencies to not depend on it.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR9277I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="NO_REMOTE_INTERFACE_CLASSES_CNTR9277I" varFormat="Java">
    NO_REMOTE_INTERFACE_CLASSES_CNTR9277I=CNTR9277I: The {0} Java archive (JAR) or Web archive (WAR) file does not contain remote interface classes for a level 3.0 enterprise bean.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified JAR or WAR file does not contain any remote interface classes for a level 3.0 enterprise bean.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If this module should contain remote interface classes for a  level 3.0 enterprise bean, add these classes to the module.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0193E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SINGLETON_INVALID_CONCURRENCY_MANAGEMENT_CNTR0193E" varFormat="Java">
    SINGLETON_INVALID_CONCURRENCY_MANAGEMENT_CNTR0193E=CNTR0193E: The value, {0}, that is specified for the concurrency management type of the {1} enterprise bean class must be either Bean or Container.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The concurrency management type can be specified using either the @ConcurrencyManagement annotation or the concurrency-management-type tag in deployment descriptor for a Singleton session bean.  The value must be either BEAN or CONTAINER for Singleton session beans.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the @ConcurrencyManagement annotation or the concurrency-management-type tag so that the value is either Bean or Ccontainer.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0057W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_MIN_POOLSIZE_CNTR0057W" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_MIN_POOLSIZE_CNTR0057W=CNTR0057W: Minimum pool size specified for bean {0} not a valid integer: {1}. Default used instead.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Only a positive integer can be specified for the minimum pool size.  The default value will be used.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Change the value for the minimum pool size to a positive integer.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0013W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="UNABLE_TO_MAP_EXCEPTION_CNTR0013W" varFormat="Java">
    UNABLE_TO_MAP_EXCEPTION_CNTR0013W=CNTR0013W: Unable to map exception. 
 {0} 
 {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The container was unable to map exception to a valid CORBA exception.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0061I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="FBPK_READONLY_OVERRIDE_ALL_CNTR0061I" varFormat="Java">
    FBPK_READONLY_OVERRIDE_ALL_CNTR0061I=CNTR0061I: Read-only attribute on findByPrimaryKey method overridden to true for bean: &lt;All&gt;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The findByPrimaryKey read-only attribute has been specified to be overridden to true on all entity beans.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    There is no user action required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR5018E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="JIT_VOID_CREATE_RETURN_CNTR5018E" varFormat="Java">
    JIT_VOID_CREATE_RETURN_CNTR5018E=CNTR5018E: The {2} method of the {1} interface, which has been configured as a home interface for the {0} bean, does not return the component interface.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    According to the Enterprise JavaBeans (EJB) specification, all create methods on a home interface must return the component interface.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Change the create methods on the home interface to return the component interface.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR5034E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="JIT_INVALID_EJBHOME_RETURN_CNTR5034E" varFormat="Java">
    JIT_INVALID_EJBHOME_RETURN_CNTR5034E=CNTR5034E: The {2} method with the {3} return type on the {1} class for the {0} entity bean must return the {4} type. This type must be the same type as the corresponding home interface method.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    According to the Enterprise JavaBeans (EJB) specification, the return type of the ejbHome methods for an entity bean class must match the corresponding home interface method.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Change the return type of the method to the type that matches the corresponding home interface method.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0242E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_SFSB_CALLBACK_METHOD_CNTR0242E" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_SFSB_CALLBACK_METHOD_CNTR0242E=CNTR0242E: Because the {0} enterprise bean implements the javax.ejb.SessionBean interface, the {1} method must be a {2} method and not a {3} method.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    For a stateful session bean, the Enterprise JavaBeans 3.0 specification requires that the ejbRemove, ejbActivate, and ejbPassivate methods be treated as @PreDestroy, @PostActivate, and @PrePassivate life cycle callback interceptor methods, respectively. The ejbCreate method must be treated as an @Init method.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the deployment descriptor or annotation so that the method is the correct type of life cycle callback interceptor.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0184W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DUPLICATE_REF_STANZA_CNTR0184W" varFormat="Java">
    DUPLICATE_REF_STANZA_CNTR0184W=CNTR0184W: The ibm-ejb-jar-bnd.xml file contained in the {0} module has more than one {1} stanza with name attribute of {2} for the {3} interceptor class. Only the last {1} stanza is used. The interceptor class is using the java:comp namespace for the {4} enterprise bean.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An interceptor stanza contains more than one ejb-ref, resource-ref, resource-env-ref, or message-destination-ref stanza with the same value for its name attribute. Each ejb-ref, resource-ref, resource-env-ref, or message-destination-ref stanza is required to have a different name attribute value.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Either remove the extranous stanza or change the value of its name attribute in one or more ejb-ref, resource-ref, resource-env-ref, or message-destination-ref stanza so that the name is unique within the interceptor stanza and within the session or message-driven stanza for the enterprise bean.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR9275E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="OUTPUT_FILE_ALREADY_EXISTS_CNTR9275E" varFormat="Java">
    OUTPUT_FILE_ALREADY_EXISTS_CNTR9275E=CNTR9275E: The {0} output file already exists.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified output file must be a non-existing file.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a new output file name.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0144E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="NO_ACTIVATION_SPEC_BINDING_CNTR0144E" varFormat="Java">
    NO_ACTIVATION_SPEC_BINDING_CNTR0144E=CNTR0144E: The Enterprise JavaBeans (EJB) binding with the {0} Java Naming and Directory Interface (JNDI) name has a jca-adapter stanza that does not contain an activation-spec-binding-name value.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    All bindings for message driven beans require a jca-adapter stanza containing an activation-spec-binding-name value.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check the binding file and ensure that all message-driven bindings include a jca-adapter stanza with an activation-spec-binding-name value.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0006W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="FAILED_TO_CONNECT_TO_ORB_CNTR0006W" varFormat="Java">
    FAILED_TO_CONNECT_TO_ORB_CNTR0006W=CNTR0006W: EJBObject &quot;{0}&quot; could not be connected to the ORB.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The container failed to connect a deserialized stub (reference) object on an attempt to activate a stateful bean.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0121W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_CONTAINER_TRANSACTION_XML_CNTR0121W" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_CONTAINER_TRANSACTION_XML_CNTR0121W=CNTR0121W: XML configuration error in ejb-jar.xml for jar: &quot;{0}&quot;.  The container-transaction element in error has trans-attribute element: &quot;{1}&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    All ejb-name elements within the container-transaction element must match valid ejb-name elements within the enterprise-beans element.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the ejb-jar.xml file so that all ejb-name elements within the container-transaction element match valid ejb-name entries in the enterprise-beans element.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0143E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="NO_JCA_ADAPTER_BINDING_CNTR0143E" varFormat="Java">
    NO_JCA_ADAPTER_BINDING_CNTR0143E=CNTR0143E: The Enterprise JavaBeans (EJB) binding with the {0} Java Naming and Directory Interface (JNDI) name does not contain a jca-adapter stanza.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    All bindings for message driven beans require a jca-adapter stanza within the message-driven binding.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check the binding file and ensure that all message-driven bindings include a jca-adapter stanza.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0151E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DUPLICATE_ROLES_SPECIFIED_IN_METHOD_ANNOTATION_CNTR0151E" varFormat="Java">
    DUPLICATE_ROLES_SPECIFIED_IN_METHOD_ANNOTATION_CNTR0151E=CNTR0151E: The {0} role is specified multiple times in the @RolesAllowed annotation on the {1} method of the {2} enterprise bean class.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A specified role can be specified once in a @RolesAllowed annotation.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Change the Java source code by removing the duplicate roles from this annotation. Then, reinstall the application.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR9415E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CNTR9415E_NO_JNDINAME_SPECIFIED" varFormat="Java">
    CNTR9415E_NO_JNDINAME_SPECIFIED=CNTR9415E: The embeddable Enterprise JavaBeans (EJB) container properties for the {0} data source do not contain the property, name.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The properties that the embeddable Enterprise JavaBeans (EJB) container uses contain a data source with no Java Naming and Directory Interface (JNDI) name specified.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Add a name property for this data source to the properties file.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0009W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="BEAN_HAS_NOT_BEEN_INSTALLED_CNTR0009W" varFormat="Java">
    BEAN_HAS_NOT_BEEN_INSTALLED_CNTR0009W=CNTR0009W: An attempt to access bean &quot;{0}&quot; failed because it was not previously installed or problems occurred during its installation.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Application Server made an attempt to access an enterprise bean that has not been installed in the container.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Look for prior error messages that indicate that the bean installation has failed.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR5035W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="JIT_THROWS_CLAUSE_MISMATCH_CNTR5035W" varFormat="Java">
    JIT_THROWS_CLAUSE_MISMATCH_CNTR5035W=CNTR5035W: Multiple interfaces of the {0} bean define the same method signature, but with different exceptions on the throws clause. The following signature will be used for determining the application exceptions for the method : {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    According to the Enterprise JavaBeans (EJB) specification, the exceptions defined on the throws clause of a method are used by the container to determine which exceptions are application exceptions. If the exceptions on the throws clause of a method vary by interface, then unexpected exception behavior will occur for some of the interfaces.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Change the application so that all methods with the same signature define the same exceptions on the throws clause.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0152E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CONFLICTING_ANNOTATIONS_CONFIGURED_ON_CLASS_CNTR0152E" varFormat="Java">
    CONFLICTING_ANNOTATIONS_CONFIGURED_ON_CLASS_CNTR0152E=CNTR0152E: The class-level {0} and {1} annotations cannot be configured on the {2} enterprise bean class at the same time.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The annotations that are identified in this error message are in conflict with each other. Do not specify these annotations on the same class.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Change the Java source code by removing one, or both, of the annotations from the specified class. Then, reinstall the application.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0228E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PARTIAL_METHOD_INTERCEPTOR_ORDER_CNTR0228E" varFormat="Java">
    PARTIAL_METHOD_INTERCEPTOR_ORDER_CNTR0228E=CNTR0228E: The {0} enterprise bean specifies method-level interceptors for the {1} method with the following interceptor-order list: {2}.  This list is not a total ordering of the method-level interceptors for this bean.  The list is missing the following interceptor names: {3}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    When the interceptor-order element is used, the specified ordering at the method-level must be a total order. The order must be over all of the interceptor classes that have been defined at that level and above.  The only exception to this rule is when interceptor classes have been explicitly excluded by means of an exclude-class-interceptors or exclude-default-inteceptors element.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify additional interceptor names on the method-level interceptor-order element for this bean. Then, the bean will provide a total ordering of the interceptors.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0194E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SINGLETON_XML_OVERRIDE_CONCURRENCY_MANAGEMENT_CNTR0194E" varFormat="Java">
    SINGLETON_XML_OVERRIDE_CONCURRENCY_MANAGEMENT_CNTR0194E=CNTR0194E: The value {0} that is specified in the ejb-jar.xml file for concurrency management type is not the same as the @ConcurrencyManagement annotation value {1} on the {2} enterprise bean class.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The deployment descriptor cannot override the value that is provided by the @ConcurrencyManagement annotation on a Singleton session bean.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Remove or change the value in the ejb-jar.xml file so that it does not override the value in the @ConcurrencyManagement annotation.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR9270E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="EXISTING_FILE_PARAM_ERROR_CNTR9270E" varFormat="Java">
    EXISTING_FILE_PARAM_ERROR_CNTR9270E=CNTR9270E: The update file name parameter is not a Java archive (JAR), Web archive (WAR), or an enterprise archive (EAR) file type.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The update file name parameter must be a JAR, WAR, and EAR file type and include the file path.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Invoke the createEJBStubs command with the -help option to view the command syntax.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0086E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ERROR_DURING_TRAN_RECOVERY_SETUP_CNTR0086E" varFormat="Java">
    ERROR_DURING_TRAN_RECOVERY_SETUP_CNTR0086E=CNTR0086E: Transaction recovery setup error occurred for resource adapter {0}, MDB {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The createEndpoint method was called on the JCA MessageEndpointFactory object by the resource adapter, and the resource adapter passed an XAResource object as one of the parameters of createEndpoint method.  However, the resource adapter life cycle manager encountered an error which prevented it from setting up transaction recovery for this resource adapter. The endpoint cannot be created successfully.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the log for a prior error message indicating the setup failure for the message-driven bean (MDB) that was bound to the resource adapter. Correct the error to eliminate this error message.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0186E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DUPLICATE_REF_BINDING_CNTR0186E" varFormat="Java">
    DUPLICATE_REF_BINDING_CNTR0186E=CNTR0186E: The {0} bean in the {1} module of the {2} application has more than one {3} binding with the {4} name.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The ibm-ejb-jar.xmi or ibm-ejb-jar.xml file for the module has more than one binding for the same reference for the same EJB.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Remove all but one of the bindings for the reference in the bean.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0222E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ML_DUPLICATES_DEFAULT_CNTR0222E" varFormat="Java">
    ML_DUPLICATES_DEFAULT_CNTR0222E=CNTR0222E: The {0} method-level interceptor for the {1} method of the {2} enterprise bean duplicates a name that is in the following default interceptor list:  {3}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The interceptor class can be either a default interceptor or a method-level interceptor, but not both types.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Eliminate the interceptor class from either the default interceptor list or the method-level interceptor list.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0092W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HOME_NOT_FOUND_CNTR0092W" varFormat="Java">
    HOME_NOT_FOUND_CNTR0092W=CNTR0092W: Attempted to access EnterpriseBean {0}, that has not been started.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An application tried to access an enterprise bean of an application that has not been installed, has not been started, or did not start successfully.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the application has been installed and started. If the application has been installed and started, see the previous messages regarding the failure of the enterprise bean to start, and correct those problems.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0233E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_REMOVE_ANNOTATION_CNTR0233E" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_REMOVE_ANNOTATION_CNTR0233E=CNTR0233E: The {1} enterprise bean specifies an @Remove annotation on the {0} method.  This annotation is not valid because this method is not a business method of this bean.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Enterprise JavaBeans 3.0 specification requires that @Remove annotations be applied to business methods of a stateful session bean.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Either relocate the @Remove annotation to a business method of this bean, or change the specified method to be a business method.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR5106E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="JIT_INVALID_FINAL_METHOD_CNTR5106E" varFormat="Java">
    JIT_INVALID_FINAL_METHOD_CNTR5106E=CNTR5106E: The {0} method on the {1} class must not be declared as final for the {2} bean.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    According to the Enterprise JavaBeans (EJB) specification, all methods of the bean class and any superclass must not be declared as final when the bean class is exposed as a no-interface view. And, business methods must not be declared as final.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Change the application so the method is not declared as final.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR9251E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="UNABLE_TO_READ_FILE_CNTR9251E" varFormat="Java">
    UNABLE_TO_READ_FILE_CNTR9251E=CNTR9251E: Unable to read from the {0} file.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified file could not be opened for read operation.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the file system permissions setting for this file.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR5101W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="JIT_INVALID_THROW_REMOTE_CNTR5101W" varFormat="Java">
    JIT_INVALID_THROW_REMOTE_CNTR5101W=CNTR5101W: The {0} method on the {1} interface should not define the java.rmi.RemoteException exception on the throws clause.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    According to the Enterprise JavaBeans (EJB) specification, the throws clause of remote business interface methods should not include the java.rmi.RemoteException exception.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Remove the RemoteException exception from the throws clause of the method. Also, you can change the interface to implement the java.rmi.Remote interface or change the application to not use the interface as an EJB remote interface.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR5030E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="JIT_NO_EJBFIND_METHOD_CNTR5030E" varFormat="Java">
    JIT_NO_EJBFIND_METHOD_CNTR5030E=CNTR5030E: The {2} method of the {1} home interface for the {0} entity bean does not define a corresponding ejbFind method on the {3} class.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The method of the home interface for the entity bean does not define a corresponding ejbFind method on the class.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Change the bean class to provide an ejbFind method that corresponds to the method.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR5002E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="JIT_MISSING_LOCAL_HOME_CNTR5002E" varFormat="Java">
    JIT_MISSING_LOCAL_HOME_CNTR5002E=CNTR5002E: The {0} bean is configured with the {1} local component interface, but a local home interface has not been provided.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    According to the Enterprise JavaBeans (EJB) specification, a local home interface must be provided when a local component interface is provided.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Change the application configuration to provide a local home interface for the bean.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR9269W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="NO_BEANS_IN_MODULE_CNTR9269W" varFormat="Java">
    NO_BEANS_IN_MODULE_CNTR9269W=CNTR9269W: The {0} Enterprise JavaBeans (EJB) module does not have any enterprise beans configured.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    EJB modules must contain one or more enterprise beans.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that one or more enterprise beans are configured for this module. The enterprise beans must use either an ejb-jar.xml file , or source code annotations.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR9403E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CNTR9403E_DUPLICATE_MODULE_BASENAME" varFormat="Java">
    CNTR9403E_DUPLICATE_MODULE_BASENAME=CNTR9403E: The embeddable enterprise bean container cannot start multiple modules with the same file name: {0} and {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    User code has directed the embeddable container to start multiple modules with the same file name.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a list of modules that does not have duplicate file names, or rename one of the modules with a unique file name.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0312E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="NEGATIVE_STATEFUL_TIMEOUT_XML_CNTR0312E" varFormat="Java">
    NEGATIVE_STATEFUL_TIMEOUT_XML_CNTR0312E=CNTR0312E: The {0} Enterprise JavaBean (EJB) in the {1} module of the {2} application has a timeout value specified in the stateful-timeout deployment descriptor element which is negative: {3}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The stateful timeout must be postive, or 0 to indicate no timeout, or -1 to indicate infinite timeout.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Modify the stateful-timeout timeout element in the EJB deployment descriptor.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0248E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DUPLICATE_STYLE_4_INTERCEPTOR_BINDING_CNTR0248E" varFormat="Java">
    DUPLICATE_STYLE_4_INTERCEPTOR_BINDING_CNTR0248E=CNTR0248E: More than one style 4 interceptor-binding element is provided in the deployment descriptor for the {0} method with the {1} signature of the {2} enterprise bean.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    According to the Enterprise JavaBeans (EJB) specification, only one style 4 interceptor-binding can be used for each method of a given method signature of an enterprise bean.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct deployment descriptor so that only one style 4 interceptor-binding is used for the method of an enterprise bean.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0220E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DUPLICATE_CLASS_INTERCEPTOR_CNTR0220E" varFormat="Java">
    DUPLICATE_CLASS_INTERCEPTOR_CNTR0220E=CNTR0220E: CNTR0220E: The {0} interceptor class exists multiple times in the list of interceptors for the {1} enterprise bean. The following is the interceptor list for this bean: {2}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The @Interceptors annotation or the interceptor-class tag in the deployment descriptor was used to provide a list of interceptor class names.  A class must exist only once in the interceptor class list.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Eliminate the duplicate interceptor class from the interceptor class list.  Or, change the interceptor class name, if an incorrect name was specified.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR9260E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="USER_LOGFILE_PROBLEM_CNTR9260E" varFormat="Java">
    USER_LOGFILE_PROBLEM_CNTR9260E=CNTR9260E: The {0} exception occured while setting up the user log file.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The exception was not expected.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the file system permissions settings.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0072E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_ACTIVITY_SESSION_POLICY_CNTR0072E" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_ACTIVITY_SESSION_POLICY_CNTR0072E=CNTR0072E: Bean &quot;{0}&quot; attempted to use an invalid &quot;Activate at&quot; policy with a container managed Activity Session.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Beans that are configured to use an Activity Session that is container-managed must use an &quot;Activate at&quot; policy of &quot;Activity Session&quot; or must use a &quot;Load at&quot; policy of &quot;Interval&quot;, &quot;Daily&quot;, or &quot;Weekly&quot;.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that an &quot;Activate at&quot; policy of &quot;Activity Session&quot; or a &quot;Load at&quot; policy of &quot;Interval&quot;, &quot;Daily&quot;, or &quot;Weekly&quot; is used when using an Activity Session that is container-managed.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0077W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MISSING_RESENVREF_BINDING_CNTR0077W" varFormat="Java">
    MISSING_RESENVREF_BINDING_CNTR0077W=CNTR0077W: A reference to an ResourceEnvRef could not be found in the deployment descriptor for the WebApp or EnterpriseBean with the display name {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Java Enterprise Edition (Java EE) component might have specified binding information that is not valid.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the binding information in the deployment descriptor for the Java EE component is correct.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0137E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="IMPROPER_REMOTE_JNDI_BINDING_PREFIX_CNTR0137E" varFormat="Java">
    IMPROPER_REMOTE_JNDI_BINDING_PREFIX_CNTR0137E=CNTR0137E: The specific Java Naming and Directory Interface (JNDI) binding name that is provided for a remote home or bean begins with ejblocal:. The {2} remote binding name that is specified for the home or {0} bean in the {1} module cannot begin with ejblocal:.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The remote binding name for the given bean or home cannot begin with ejblocal:.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the remote binding name for the bean or home in the specified module.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR9408W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CNTR9408W_STOP_MODULE_FAILURE" varFormat="Java">
    CNTR9408W_STOP_MODULE_FAILURE=CNTR9408W: The Enterprise JavaBeans (EJB) module, {0} failed to stop. Exception: {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The embeddable Enterprise JavaBeans (EJB) container failed to shutdown the Enterprise JavaBeans (EJB) module due to the exception. The enterprise beans might still be bound into JNDI and are still accessible to clients. Future attempts to re-start that module might fail due to naming or other resource collisions.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Resolve the failure by examining the exception, the logs, and the FFDC output. If other modules stop cleanly,  examine the failing module.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0015W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="UNEXPECTED_EXCEPTION_DURING_STATEFUL_BEAN_CLEANUP_CNTR0015W" varFormat="Java">
    UNEXPECTED_EXCEPTION_DURING_STATEFUL_BEAN_CLEANUP_CNTR0015W=CNTR0015W: An unexpected exception occurred during stateful bean cleanup. 
 Exception data: 
 {0} 
 {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This exception is unexpected. The cause is not immediately known.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0027W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="FAILED_TO_COMMIT_CONNECTION_CNTR0027W" varFormat="Java">
    FAILED_TO_COMMIT_CONNECTION_CNTR0027W=CNTR0027W: Failed to commit connection: 
 {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An SQLException occurred when trying to commit a Datasource connection.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See the vendor-specific documentation for the database product you are using.  Typically a vendor-specific exception code will be displayed as part of the SQLException.  This exception code can be used, in combination with the vendor-specific documentation, to determine the cause of the exception.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0239E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="METHOD_NAME_INVALID_FOR_DEFAULT_CNTR0239E" varFormat="Java">
    METHOD_NAME_INVALID_FOR_DEFAULT_CNTR0239E=CNTR0239E: The method-name element is not valid for a style 1 interceptor-binding element.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The method-name element is not allowed in a style 1 interceptor-binding element.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the interceptor-binding to be a style 2 interceptor-binding element or remove the method-name element.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0060I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="POOLSIZE_VALUES_CNTR0060I" varFormat="Java">
    POOLSIZE_VALUES_CNTR0060I=CNTR0060I: (Min,Max) pool size is ({0},{1}) for bean {2}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    These are the minimum pool size and maximum pool size values that will be used for this bean type.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    There is no user action required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0070E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_ACTIVITY_SESSION_POLICY_CNTR0070E" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_ACTIVITY_SESSION_POLICY_CNTR0070E=CNTR0070E: Bean &quot;{0}&quot; in an EJB 1.1 module attempted to use an invalid Local Transactions Boundary of &quot;Activity Session&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Activity Sessions are not supported on EJB V1.1 modules.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Select &quot;Bean method&quot; for Local Transactions Boundary.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0316E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CONFLICTING_RESOURCE_REFERENCE_CNTR0316E" varFormat="Java">
    CONFLICTING_RESOURCE_REFERENCE_CNTR0316E=CNTR0316E: A resource reference conflict was detected.  {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A resource reference was defined in multiple places, with conflicting information.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Change the resource reference definitions so they no longer conflict, or use a single resource reference and remove the duplicate resource reference definitions.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR9252E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="OPTION_OVERSPECIFIED_CNTR9252E" varFormat="Java">
    OPTION_OVERSPECIFIED_CNTR9252E=CNTR9252E: The {0} option was specified multiple times.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An option may only be specified once per createEJBStubs command invocation.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Invoke the createEJBStubs command with -help option to view the command syntax.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0010W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="NUMBER_FORMAT_EXCEPTION_CNTR0010W" varFormat="Java">
    NUMBER_FORMAT_EXCEPTION_CNTR0010W=CNTR0010W: NumberFormatException occurred while converting &lt;env-entry-name&gt; {0} &lt;env-entry-value&gt; {1}: {2}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The container was unable to process an environment entry due to a NumberFormatException.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that the value for the environment entry is a valid string representation for the specified type.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0113I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SFB_CONTROLLER_DRSEVENT_REPLICATION_UP_CNTR0113I" varFormat="Java">
    SFB_CONTROLLER_DRSEVENT_REPLICATION_UP_CNTR0113I=CNTR0113I: SfDRSControllerInstance {0} received event REPLICATION_UP.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The SfDRSControllerInstance that is specified received the event REPLICATION_UP.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    There is no user action required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0102E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SFB_CONTROLLER_ENTRYKEY_CNTR0102E" varFormat="Java">
    SFB_CONTROLLER_ENTRYKEY_CNTR0102E=CNTR0102E: Method {0} entryKey is null.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified method was passed a entryKey parameter that is null.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    There is no user action required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0114I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SFB_CONTROLLER_DRSEVENT_REPLICATION_DOWN_CNTR0114I" varFormat="Java">
    SFB_CONTROLLER_DRSEVENT_REPLICATION_DOWN_CNTR0114I=CNTR0114I: SfDRSControllerInstance {0} received event REPLICATION_DOWN.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The SfDRSControllerInstance that is specified received the event REPLICATION_DOWN.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    There is no user action required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR5102E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="JIT_INVALID_SUBCLASS_REMOTE_EX_CNTR5102E" varFormat="Java">
    JIT_INVALID_SUBCLASS_REMOTE_EX_CNTR5102E=CNTR5102E: The {0} application exception that is defined on the {1} method of the {2} interface must not be defined as a subclass of the java.rmi.RemoteException exception.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    According to the Enterprise JavaBeans (EJB) specification, an application exception must not be defined as a subclass of the java.rmi.RemoteException exception.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Change the application so that there are no remote business interface methods that are defined with a java.rmi.RemoteException subclass on the throws clause.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0190E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="STARTUP_SINGLETON_SESSION_BEAN_INITIALIZATION_FAILED_CNTR0190E" varFormat="Java">
    STARTUP_SINGLETON_SESSION_BEAN_INITIALIZATION_FAILED_CNTR0190E=CNTR0190E: The {0} startup singleton session bean in the {1} module failed initialization with exception:
{2}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Startup Singleton Session bean instances are created as part of application start processing.  Any failure will result in the application failing to start.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Eliminate cause of the exception that is attached to this error message.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0087E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="RA_DOES_NOT_SUPPORT_XATRANSACTIONS_CNTR0087E" varFormat="Java">
    RA_DOES_NOT_SUPPORT_XATRANSACTIONS_CNTR0087E=CNTR0087E: Resource adapter {0} is not allowed to pass a non null XAResource to createEndpoint method for MDB {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The createEndpoint method was called on the JCA MessageEndpointFactory object by the resource adapter, and the resource adapter passed an XAResource object to the createEndpoint method. Transaction recovery for this resource adapter is not supported, because the resource adapter indicated that it does not support XA transactions. The resource adapter is not allowed to pass an XAResource object to the createEndpoint method.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Have the Resource Adaptor vendor correct the configuration or implementation of the resource adapter.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0205E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_ASYNC_METHOD_INTF_VALID_SPECIFIED_CNTR0205E" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_ASYNC_METHOD_INTF_VALID_SPECIFIED_CNTR0205E=CNTR0205E: The {0} bean in the ejb-jar.xml contains an async-method element with an invalid method-intf value. This value may only be &quot;Local&quot; or &quot;Remote&quot;. &quot;{1}&quot; was specified.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The only valid values for the method-intf element of an asynchronous method are &quot;Local&quot; and &quot;Remote&quot;.  Any other value is invalid and the EJB Container will not recognize the containing async-method element.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Modify the method-intf element&apos;s value to be either &quot;Local&quot; or &quot;Remote&quot;.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0066E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="LOCAL_TRAN_BOUNDARY_ACTIVITY_INVALID_CNTR0066E" varFormat="Java">
    LOCAL_TRAN_BOUNDARY_ACTIVITY_INVALID_CNTR0066E=CNTR0066E: Bean &quot;{0}&quot; attempted to use an invalid Local Transaction boundary value of &quot;activity session&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The local transaction boundary of &quot;activity session&quot; is not valid for message-driven beans.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Change the local transaction boundary from &quot;activity session&quot; to &quot;bean method&quot;, and restart the application server.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0043E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_ACTIVATION_POLICY_CNTR0043E" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_ACTIVATION_POLICY_CNTR0043E=CNTR0043E: Bean &quot;{0}&quot; is attempting to use an invalid combination of ActivationPolicy and LoadPolicy on a work load managed server.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The user has specified &apos;Commit Option A&apos; on an enterprise bean that is contained within a server that is work load managed.  This configuration combination is not supported.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Change the enterprise bean to use a different Commit Option, or change the server to not be work load managed.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0074E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="UNEXPECTED_METHOD_CALL_CNTR0074E" varFormat="Java">
    UNEXPECTED_METHOD_CALL_CNTR0074E=CNTR0074E: Unexpected method call occurred in {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This exception is unexpected. The cause is not immediately known.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0045W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="UNABLE_CONVERT_REMOTE_2_STUB_CNTR0045W" varFormat="Java">
    UNABLE_CONVERT_REMOTE_2_STUB_CNTR0045W=CNTR0045W: Unable to convert remote object to stub. Possible reason=&quot;{0}&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This exception is unexpected. The cause is not immediately known.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0163E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CONFLICTING_TIMEOUT_METHOD_NAMES_CNTR0163E" varFormat="Java">
    CONFLICTING_TIMEOUT_METHOD_NAMES_CNTR0163E=CNTR0163E: The {0} enterprise bean in the {1} module has specified the {2} timeout method on a timeout-method tag in XML. Also, the bean has specified the {3} timeout method on an @Timeout annotation in the Java source code.  This configuration conflicts.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Timer beans must configure only one timeout method.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the bean configuration to specify a single timeout method.  Then, reinstall the application.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0055W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="THROWABLE_WHILE_CONSTRUCTING_JAVA_COMP_ENV_CNTR0055W" varFormat="Java">
    THROWABLE_WHILE_CONSTRUCTING_JAVA_COMP_ENV_CNTR0055W=CNTR0055W: A Throwable exception was caught while attempting to construct &lt;env-entry-name&gt; {0} &lt;env-entry-value&gt; {1} 
 {2}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The container caught a Throwable when the container was trying to create a java:comp/env entry.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Take action based upon the exception message in message CNTR0055W.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0123W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_METHOD_PERMISSION_XML_CNTR0123W" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_METHOD_PERMISSION_XML_CNTR0123W=CNTR0123W: XML configuration error in ejb-jar.xml for jar: &quot;{0}&quot;.  The method-permission element in error for EJB: &quot;{1}&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    All ejb-name elements within the method-permission element must match valid ejb-name elements within the enterprise-beans element.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the ejb-jar.xml file so that all ejb-name elements within the method-permission element match valid ejb-name entries in the enterprise-beans element.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0146E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="BINDINGS_FILE_CONFIG_ERROR_CNTR0146E" varFormat="Java">
    BINDINGS_FILE_CONFIG_ERROR_CNTR0146E=CNTR0146E: The {0} bindings file contained in the {1} module has a configuration error at line number: {2}, column number: {3}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The bindings file contains either a simple syntax error, or a semantic violation.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the log file for additional &apos;caused by&apos; exceptions, which may provide specific parser message details.  Correct the bindings file error and reinstall the application.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0099I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SFB_CONTROLLER_INIT_CNTR0099I" varFormat="Java">
    SFB_CONTROLLER_INIT_CNTR0099I=CNTR0099I: {0} service has initialized successfully.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The z/OS Controller Service for Stateful SessionBean support in DRS has initialized successfully.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    There is no user action required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR9254E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="UNABLE_TO_WRITE_FILE_CNTR9254E" varFormat="Java">
    UNABLE_TO_WRITE_FILE_CNTR9254E=CNTR9254E: Unable to write to the {0} file.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified file could not be opened for write operation.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the file system permissions setting for this file.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0101E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SFB_CONTROLLER_NULLTOKEN_CNTR0101E" varFormat="Java">
    SFB_CONTROLLER_NULLTOKEN_CNTR0101E=CNTR0101E: Method {0} token is null.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified method was passed a servant token that is null.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    There is no user action required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0034I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INCOMPLETE_EXCEPTION_LIST_CNTR0034I" varFormat="Java">
    INCOMPLETE_EXCEPTION_LIST_CNTR0034I=CNTR0034I: ContainerEJBException.getExceptionChain is returning an incomplete list of exceptions.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This exception is unexpected. The cause is not immediately known.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0315E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PERSISTENCE_REF_DEPENDENCY_NOT_DECLARED_CNTR0315E" varFormat="Java">
    PERSISTENCE_REF_DEPENDENCY_NOT_DECLARED_CNTR0315E=CNTR0315E: The {0} stateful session bean in the {1} module in the {2} application did not declare a dependency on the {3} persistence reference.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    When a stateful session bean is located in a WAR, it must declare dependencies on all persistence context references and persistence unit references that it intends to access.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Add the appropriate @PersistenceContext or @PersistenceUnit source code annotation to the stateful session bean, or add the appropriate persistence-context-ref or persistence-unit-ref element to the appropriate session element in the XML deployment descriptor.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0108E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SFB_CONTROLLER_EXCEPTPROXY_CNTR0108E" varFormat="Java">
    SFB_CONTROLLER_EXCEPTPROXY_CNTR0108E=CNTR0108E: Method {0}  caught exception {1} while acquiring proxy for token =  {2}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The method that is specified caught an exception acquiring a proxy for processing the servant token.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    There is no user action required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR9274E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="UNABLE_TO_CREATE_FILE_CNTR9274E" varFormat="Java">
    UNABLE_TO_CREATE_FILE_CNTR9274E=CNTR9274E: The createEJBStubs command cannot create the {0} file.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified file cannot be created on the file system.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the file system permissions settings for the specified directory.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0206E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ASYNC_METHOD_MUST_RETURN_VOID_OR_FUTURE_CNTR0206E" varFormat="Java">
    ASYNC_METHOD_MUST_RETURN_VOID_OR_FUTURE_CNTR0206E=CNTR0206E: The {0} asynchronous method on the {1} bean has a return type of {2}.  A return type of void or future&lt;V&gt; is required for asynchronous methods.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Asynchronous methods must return void or future&lt;V&gt;.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the asynchronous method implementation to return void or future&lt;V&gt;.  Then, reinstall the application.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR9407W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CNTR9407W_NO_MODULES" varFormat="Java">
    CNTR9407W_NO_MODULES=CNTR9407W: There are no valid Enterprise JavaBeans (EJB) modules to start.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The embeddable Enterprise JavaBeans (EJB) container found no valid Enterprise JavaBeans (EJB) modules to start. A valid EJB module contains  a valid META-INF/ejb-jar.xml or classes with EJB annotations. This could be because no EJB module exists in the classpath, or that the javax.ejb.embeddable.modules property defined modules that do not exist.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Review the classpath and the javax.ejb.embeddable.modules property to determine which EJB modules should be started.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0204E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_ASYNC_METHOD_ELEMENT_SPECIFIED_PARMS_WITH_WILDCARD_METHOD_CNTR0204E" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_ASYNC_METHOD_ELEMENT_SPECIFIED_PARMS_WITH_WILDCARD_METHOD_CNTR0204E=CNTR0204E: The ejb-jar.xml file declares a parameter on a wildcard asynchronous method element for the {0} session bean. Parameters may not be specified on wildcards.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The ejb-jar.xml file incorrectly specifies a method-params element inside an async-method element which contains a wildcard (*) method-name element.  This is not allowed, per the EJB 3.1 specification.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Either remove the method-params element from the XML or change the method-name element to represent a specific method with the specified method-params parameters.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0035E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CAUGHT_EXCEPTION_THROWING_NEW_EXCEPTION_CNTR0035E" varFormat="Java">
    CAUGHT_EXCEPTION_THROWING_NEW_EXCEPTION_CNTR0035E=CNTR0035E: EJB container caught {0} and is throwing {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This exception is unexpected. The cause is not immediately known.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR9256E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="UNRECOGNIZED_PARAM_CNTR9256E" varFormat="Java">
    UNRECOGNIZED_PARAM_CNTR9256E=CNTR9256E: The {0} parameter is not recognized.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The parameter does not match any of the allowed input options.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Invoke the createEJBStubs command with the -help option to view the command syntax.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0156E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SFSB_FAILOVER_NOT_ALLOWED_WITH_EXTEND_PERSIST_CNTX_CNTR0156E" varFormat="Java">
    SFSB_FAILOVER_NOT_ALLOWED_WITH_EXTEND_PERSIST_CNTX_CNTR0156E=CNTR0156E: The {0} stateful session bean in the {1} module is configured for failover. However, the session bean is also configured to use extended-scope persistence context. These configuration settings conflict.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Stateful sessions beans cannot be configured for both failover support and extended-scope persistence context support.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Eliminate one of these two configuration settings for this bean.  Then, reinstall the application.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0135E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="REQUIRED_BINDING_NOT_FOUND_CNTR0135E" varFormat="Java">
    REQUIRED_BINDING_NOT_FOUND_CNTR0135E=CNTR0135E: The {0} message-driven bean (MDB) does not have a corresponding binding in the binding file.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A message-driven bean binding must exist in the binding file for each message driven bean.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check the ejb-jar-bnd.xml binding file for the MDB and ensure that a binding entry exists.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0212E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="AUTOMATIC_TIMER_SCHEDULE_VALUE_RANGE_CNTR0212E" varFormat="Java">
    AUTOMATIC_TIMER_SCHEDULE_VALUE_RANGE_CNTR0212E=CNTR0212E: The {0} enterprise bean in the {1} module has automatic timer metadata for the {2} method, but the {3} schedule field has a value that is out of range for that field.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified method has automatic timer metadata in the deployment descriptor or in a @Schedule or @Schedules annotation, but the specified field in the metadata has a value that is out of bounds for that field.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Change the field in the automatic timer metadata, or remove the automatic timer metadata.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR9240I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="NOT_EJB3_MODULE_CNTR9240I" varFormat="Java">
    NOT_EJB3_MODULE_CNTR9240I=CNTR9240I: The {0} Java archive (JAR) file is not an enterprise bean level 3.0 module.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The listed jar file is not configured as a level 3.0 module.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If this module should have contained enterprise bean level 3.0 components, check the Java source code annotations, or ejb-jar.xml configuration data.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR5028E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="JIT_NO_POSTCREATE_METHOD_CNTR5028E" varFormat="Java">
    JIT_NO_POSTCREATE_METHOD_CNTR5028E=CNTR5028E: The {2} method of the {1} home interface for the {0} entity bean does not define a corresponding ejbPostCreate method on the {3} class.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    According to the Enterprise JavaBeans (EJB) specification, the entity bean class must implement an ejbPostCreate method for every create method for a home interface.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Change the bean class to provide an ejbPostCreate method that corresponds to the method.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0203E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_ASYNC_METHOD_ELEMENT_MISSING_METHOD_NAME_CNTR0203E" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_ASYNC_METHOD_ELEMENT_MISSING_METHOD_NAME_CNTR0203E=CNTR0203E: The ejb-jar.xml declares an asynchronous method for the {0} session bean, but did not declare a method-name.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified session bean declares an asynchronous method in the ejb-jar.xml file, but did not specify the &quot;method-name&quot; element.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Modify the ejb-jar.xml file and specify a method-name for the method that should be asynchronous (or &quot;*&quot; for all methods).
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0329E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="EJB_CONTEXT_DATA_NOT_AVAILABLE_CNTR0329E" varFormat="Java">
    EJB_CONTEXT_DATA_NOT_AVAILABLE_CNTR0329E=CNTR0329E: The {0} type may only be injected into an enterprise bean instance or looked up within the context of an enterprise bean.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    When an enterprise bean context is not present, enterprise bean specific types, such as javax.ejb.EJBContext and javax.ejb.TimerService, are not available for injection or lookup.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Change the application to only inject or lookup enterprise bean specific types within the context of an enterprise bean.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR9257E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="TO_MANY_PARAMS_CNTR9257E" varFormat="Java">
    TO_MANY_PARAMS_CNTR9257E=CNTR9257E: Too many input parameters were specified.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The total number of allowed input parameters was exceeded.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Invoke createEJBStubs command with the -help option to view the command syntax.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0313W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_STATEFUL_TIMEOUT_TIMEOUT_CNTR0313W" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_STATEFUL_TIMEOUT_TIMEOUT_CNTR0313W=CNTR0313W: The system property {0} has a timeout value specified which is not a valid integer value: {1}.  The default value of {2} minutes will be used instead.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Only a positive integer can be specified for the stateful timeout value.  The default value will be used.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Change the value for the stateful timeout to a positive integer.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0046E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CONNECTION_FACTORY_BINDING_NOT_SPECIFIED_CNTR0046E" varFormat="Java">
    CONNECTION_FACTORY_BINDING_NOT_SPECIFIED_CNTR0046E=CNTR0046E: Bean &quot;{0}&quot; did not specify a connection factory binding.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Neither the bean specific nor the default connection factory binding is specified for the bean.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a binding for the connection factory when installing the bean.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0149E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="UNEXPECTED_EJB_START_FAILURE_CNTR0149E" varFormat="Java">
    UNEXPECTED_EJB_START_FAILURE_CNTR0149E=CNTR0149E: The start up process for the {0} enterprise bean in the {1} module failed with the following exception: {2}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An error has occurred during the initialization and start process for the bean.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the exception message to determine why the bean did not start. Also, check the log for other exception messages that are related to starting this bean.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0147E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="UNKNOWN_BINDINGS_FILE_CONFIG_ERROR_CNTR0147E" varFormat="Java">
    UNKNOWN_BINDINGS_FILE_CONFIG_ERROR_CNTR0147E=CNTR0147E: The {0} bindings file contained in the {1} module has a configuration error.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The bindings file contains either a simple syntax error, or a semantic violation.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the bindings file error and reinstall the application.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0189E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="STARTUP_SPECIFIED_ON_NON_SINGLETON_SESSION_BEAN_CNTR0189E" varFormat="Java">
    STARTUP_SPECIFIED_ON_NON_SINGLETON_SESSION_BEAN_CNTR0189E=CNTR0189E: The {0} bean class can not be designated as a Startup bean using Java annotations or within the XML deployment descriptor.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Only Singleton Session beans can be defined with the Startup annotation or XML deployment descriptor.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Eliminate the Startup Java annotation or XML deployment descriptor from this EJB class, or change the class to be a Singleton Session Bean.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0032W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ERROR_CREATING_CMP_PERSISTER_CNTR0032W" varFormat="Java">
    ERROR_CREATING_CMP_PERSISTER_CNTR0032W=CNTR0032W: Error creating CMP persister using datasource: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message immediately follows the CNTR0031W message and provides the Datasource name that is used when starting the entity bean.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Take the action described for the message CNTR0031W.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0065E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_CONFIGURATION_CMP_RESOLVER_APPLICATION_CNTR0065E" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_CONFIGURATION_CMP_RESOLVER_APPLICATION_CNTR0065E=CNTR0065E: CMP bean &quot;{0}&quot; attempted to use an unsupported Local Transaction resolution control value.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Only ContainerAtBoundary resolution control is supported for local transactions with container managed persistence (CMP) beans.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Using an assembly tool, change &quot;Resolution Control&quot; to &quot;ContainerAtBoundary&quot; within the IBM Extensions tab for the CMP bean, and restart the server.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0130E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_JNDI_BINDING_COMBINATION_CNTR0130E" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_JNDI_BINDING_COMBINATION_CNTR0130E=CNTR0130E: When a simple Java Naming and Directory Interface (JNDI) binding name is specified for a bean or home, specific JNDI bindings cannot be specified. The {0} bean in The {1} module either must use a simple JNDI binding name or specific JNDI bindings, but not use both options.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Simple JNDI binding name cannot be mixed with specific JNDI bindings for a given bean or home.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the bindings file settings for the bean or home in the specified module.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR9262E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CLASS_LOAD_ERROR_CNTR9262E" varFormat="Java">
    CLASS_LOAD_ERROR_CNTR9262E=CNTR9262E: The {0} interface class could not be loaded.  This can be caused by a spelling error, incorrect -cp option, failure to load parent class, or falure to load class on method parameter.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified class could not be loaded.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check for spelling errors, and make sure that all parent classes of this class are included in the input Java archive (JAR) file or enterprise archive (EAR) file, or are made available using the -cp option.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0208E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="AUTOMATIC_TIMER_XML_METHOD_PARAMS_CNTR0208E" varFormat="Java">
    AUTOMATIC_TIMER_XML_METHOD_PARAMS_CNTR0208E=CNTR0208E: The {0} enterprise bean in the {1} module has automatic timer metadata in the deployment descriptor for the {2} method, but the method parameter types are not valid for a timeout callback method.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An automatic timer can either have no parameters or a single javax.ejb.Timer parameter.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Change the method parameter types, or remove the automatic timer metadata.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0325E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SESSION_SYNCH_METHOD_NOT_FOUND_CNTR0325E" varFormat="Java">
    SESSION_SYNCH_METHOD_NOT_FOUND_CNTR0325E=CNTR0325E: The configured {0} session synchronization method {1} is not implemented by the {2} bean in the {3} module of the {4} application.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    All configured session synchronization methods must be implemented by the bean.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Change the bean implementation to include all configured session synchronization methods.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0191E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="TIMERSERVICE_NP_NUM_THREADS_INVALID_CNTR0191E" varFormat="Java">
    TIMERSERVICE_NP_NUM_THREADS_INVALID_CNTR0191E=CNTR0191E: The option to create a unique timer manager for non-persistent timers was chosen, but the number of timer threads has an unsupported value: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    When you share thread pools that are configured for persistent timers, you must configure multiple timer threads.  On the EJBTimer configuration object, when the uniqueTimerManagerForNP attribute is set to true, the numNPTimerThreads attribute must be set to 1 or greater.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    In the EJB timer service settings of the application server, specify a positive value for the number of non-persistent timer threads. As an alternative, you can configure the timer service to use a scheduler for non-persistent timers by selecting the option to share thread pool configured for persistent timers (Specify false for the uniqueTimerManagerForNP attribute on the EJBTimer configuration object).
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR5017E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="JIT_MUST_EXTEND_EJBHOME_CNTR5017E" varFormat="Java">
    JIT_MUST_EXTEND_EJBHOME_CNTR5017E=CNTR5017E: The {1} interface, which has been configured as the remote home interface for the {0} bean, must extend the javax.ejb.EJBHome interface.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    According to the Enterprise JavaBeans (EJB) specification, the configured remote home interface must extend the javax.ejb.EJBHome interface.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Change the interface to extend the javax.ejb.EJBHome interface or change the bean configuration to not specify the interface as the remote home interface.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0218E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="AUTOMATIC_TIMER_CREATION_FAILURE_CNTR0218E" varFormat="Java">
    AUTOMATIC_TIMER_CREATION_FAILURE_CNTR0218E=CNTR0218E: An error occurred while creating persistent automatic timers for the {0} module:
{1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Either the module has metadata that is not valid, or the scheduler for the EJB timer service was unable to create the automatic timers.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check the module metadata and scheduler configuration.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0214E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="AUTOMATIC_TIMER_SCHEDULE_INCREMENT_INTERVAL_CNTR0214E" varFormat="Java">
    AUTOMATIC_TIMER_SCHEDULE_INCREMENT_INTERVAL_CNTR0214E=CNTR0214E: The {0} enterprise bean in the {1} module has automatic timer metadata for the {2} method, but the {3} schedule field has an interval value that is not valid.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified method has automatic timer metadata in the deployment descriptor or in a @Schedule or @Schedules annotation, but the specified field in the metadata has an interval value that is not valid.  Increment values must be integers.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Change the field in the automatic timer metadata, or remove the automatic timer metadata.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0224E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_EXCLUDE_CLASS_INTERCEPTORS_CNTR0224E" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_EXCLUDE_CLASS_INTERCEPTORS_CNTR0224E=CNTR0224E: The {0} enterprise bean is missing a method-name tag on the exclude-class-interceptors element in the interceptor-binding element of the deployment descriptor.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The interceptor-binding element is using an exclude-class-interceptors element, which must specify a method-name tag.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the deployment descriptor by adding a method-name tag.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0145E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="NO_MESSAGE_DESTINATION_BINDING_CNTR0145E" varFormat="Java">
    NO_MESSAGE_DESTINATION_BINDING_CNTR0145E=CNTR0145E: The Enterprise JavaBeans (EJB) binding with the {0} Java Naming and Directory Interface (JNDI) name has a jca-adapter stanza that does not contain a destination-binding-name value.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    All bindings for message driven beans require a jca-adapter stanza containing a destination-binding-name value.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check the binding file and ensure that all message-driven bindings include a jca-adapter stanza with a destination-binding-name value.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR9402E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CNTR9402E_INIT_ERROR" varFormat="Java">
    CNTR9402E_INIT_ERROR=CNTR9402E: An error occurred while initializing the embeddable Enterprise JavaBeans (EJB) container {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The process of scanning for Enterprise JavaBeans (EJB) modules or initializing the embeddable EJB container failed and the container is no longer usable. Additional diagnostics might be found in FFDC output.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the exception type, and optionally, the FFDC output,  to determine the cause of the initialization failure. A common reason for this error is an invalid EJB module is in the classpath.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0022E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="TRANSACTION_COORDINATOR_NOT_AVAILABLE_CNTR0022E" varFormat="Java">
    TRANSACTION_COORDINATOR_NOT_AVAILABLE_CNTR0022E=CNTR0022E: Transaction coordinator not available. 
 {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This exception is unexpected. The cause is not immediately known.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0064E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SESSIONAL_CONCURRENT_TRANSACTION_ERROR_CNTR0064E" varFormat="Java">
    SESSIONAL_CONCURRENT_TRANSACTION_ERROR_CNTR0064E=CNTR0064E: A bean instance of type &quot;{0}&quot; with an activity session based activation policy attempted to become involved with multiple concurrent transactions.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An enterprise Java bean (EJB) that is activated within an activity session should only participate in serial transactions. Having transaction attributes that vary, like REQUIRES for one method and REQUIRES_NEW or NOT_SUPPORTED for another, can cause this error.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Review the transaction attributes that are assigned to the EJB methods, and verify that the sequence of the method calls do not result in multiple concurrent transactions for the same bean within an activity session.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0219I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="AUTOMATIC_TIMER_CREATION_CNTR0219I" varFormat="Java">
    AUTOMATIC_TIMER_CREATION_CNTR0219I=CNTR0219I: The server created {0} persistent automatic timer or timers and {1} non-persistent automatic timer or timers for the {2} module.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The server has created the specified number of automatic timers for the specified module.  If the server had previously created persistent automatic timers for this module, then no persistent automatic timers will be created on subsequent starts of the application.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    There is no user action required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0119E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_LIGHTWEIGHT_IMPL_CNTR0119E" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_LIGHTWEIGHT_IMPL_CNTR0119E=CNTR0119E: The user-provided class &quot;{0}&quot; may not implement the com.ibm.websphere.ejbcontainer.LightweightLocal interface.  Reason code = {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Only enterprise Java bean (EJB) V2.x or later entity beans with a local interface may implement the com.ibm.websphere.ejbcontainer.LightweightLocal interface. The reason code identifies the specific violation as follows: 
 1 - The EJB is not an Entity bean. 
 2 - The bean is an EJB V1.x or container-managed persistence (CMP) V1.x entity bean. 
 3 - The EJB does not have a local interface defined.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Change the EJB to be of the type &quot;Entity&quot;, change the EJB deployment to version 2.0 or greater, change the EJB deployment to specify a local interface, or change the implementation to not implement the com.ibm.websphere.ejbcontainer.LightweightLocal interface.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0026W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DATASOURCE_NAME_NULL_CNTR0026W" varFormat="Java">
    DATASOURCE_NAME_NULL_CNTR0026W=CNTR0026W: DataSource name for CMP bean &quot;{0}&quot; is null. Bean will be unavailable for use.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    No Datasource has been specified for the entity bean.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a Datasource for the entity bean, or specify a default Datasource for the module.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0159E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="BEAN_INHERITANCE_ERROR_CNTR0159E" varFormat="Java">
    BEAN_INHERITANCE_ERROR_CNTR0159E=CNTR0159E: The {0} module has a configuration error in the inheritance relationship that is specified between the {1} parent bean and the {2} child bean.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    There might be an error in the configuration extensions file for the module, or one of the two beans might not exist.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the configured inheritance relationship in the extensions XML file for the module or supply the missing bean implementation.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0041W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="FINDER_RESULT_EXCEEDED_LIMITS_CNTR0041W" varFormat="Java">
    FINDER_RESULT_EXCEEDED_LIMITS_CNTR0041W=CNTR0041W: Finder result collection exceeded limit. Only the first Integer.MAX_VALUE elements are processed.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The finder resulted in a collection that contains more than 2147483647 entity beans.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Change the finder so that it does not result in a collection of entity beans that is more than 2147483647.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0303W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="NON_COMPLIANT_WORK_MANAGER_CONFIG_CNTR0303W" varFormat="Java">
    NON_COMPLIANT_WORK_MANAGER_CONFIG_CNTR0303W=CNTR0303W: The work manager configuration that is used for the EJB timer service does not comply with the Enterprise JavaBeans (EJB) specification.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specification does not support any execution context information passed to the timeout method.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that the work manager instance is configured to not pass context information, as required by the specification.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0198E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SINGLETON_DEPENDS_ON_NONEXISTENT_BEAN_CNTR0198E" varFormat="Java">
    SINGLETON_DEPENDS_ON_NONEXISTENT_BEAN_CNTR0198E=CNTR0198E: The {0} singleton session bean in the {1} module depends on {2}, which does not exist.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The bean was configured to depend on another bean through the @DependsOn annotation or the depends-on element in the ejb-jar.xml file. However, the other bean does not exist.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Remove or change the dependency on the nonexistent bean.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0068W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="BMAS_DEFINES_CMAS_ATTRIBUTES_CNTR0068W" varFormat="Java">
    BMAS_DEFINES_CMAS_ATTRIBUTES_CNTR0068W=CNTR0068W: Bean &quot;{0}&quot; or its home attempted to use an invalid combination of Bean Managed Activity Sessions and method-level Activity Session attributes.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An enterprise Java bean (EJB) or its home with &quot;Bean Managed Transactions&quot; should not declare &quot;Container Managed Activity Session&quot; attributes for its methods.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Remove the &quot;Container Managed Activity Session&quot; attributes for the methods of this EJB or its home.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR5029E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="JIT_INVALID_POSTCREATE_RETURN_CNTR5029E" varFormat="Java">
    JIT_INVALID_POSTCREATE_RETURN_CNTR5029E=CNTR5029E: The {2} method with the {3} return type on the {1} class for the {0} entity bean must return void.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    According to the Enterprise JavaBeans (EJB) specification, the return type of all ejbPostCreate methods for an entity bean class must be void.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Change the return type of the method to void.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR9405I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CNTR9405I_START_MODULE" varFormat="Java">
    CNTR9405I_START_MODULE=CNTR9405I: The Enterprise JavaBeans (EJB) module, {0}, is starting.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The embeddable EJB container is starting the identified Enterprise JavaBeans (EJB) module. This includes binding the Enterprise JavaBeans (EJB) factories and homes to the JNDI and executing any EJB code that has been specified to run on startup.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    There is no user action required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0302W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="NON_COMPLIANT_WORK_MANAGER_CONFIG_CNTR0302W" varFormat="Java">
    NON_COMPLIANT_WORK_MANAGER_CONFIG_CNTR0302W=CNTR0302W: The work manager configuration that is used for asynchronous methods does not comply with the Enterprise JavaBeans (EJB) specification.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specification requires asynchronous methods to have security context information only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that the work manager instance is configured to pass security context only, as required by the specification.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR5020E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="JIT_WRONG_CREATE_RETURN_CNTR5020E" varFormat="Java">
    JIT_WRONG_CREATE_RETURN_CNTR5020E=CNTR5020E: The {2} method of the {1} interface, which has been configured as a home interface for the {0} bean, does not return the {3} component interface.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    According to the Enterprise JavaBeans (EJB) specification, all create methods on a home interface must return the component interface.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Change the create methods on the home interface to return the component interface.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0240E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CL_DUPLICATES_DL_CNTR0240E" varFormat="Java">
    CL_DUPLICATES_DL_CNTR0240E=CNTR0240E: The {1} enterprise bean specifies the {0} class-level interceptor, which duplicates a name in the following default interceptors list: {2}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This interceptor class cannot be in both the default interceptor list and the class-level interceptor list unless the default interceptors are excluded at the class level.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Remove the duplicate interceptor class from either the default or the class-level interceptor list. Or, exclude the default interceptors at the class level for this bean.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR5033E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="JIT_NO_EJBHOME_METHOD_CNTR5033E" varFormat="Java">
    JIT_NO_EJBHOME_METHOD_CNTR5033E=CNTR5033E: The {2} method of the {1} home interface for the {0} entity bean does not define a corresponding ejbHome method on the {3} class.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    TAccording to the Enterprise JavaBeans (EJB) specification, the entity bean class must implement an ejbHome method for every home interface home method.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Change the bean class to provide an ejbHome method that corresponds to the method.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0319E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="LEGACY_STARTUP_BEAN_IN_WAR_CNTR0319E" varFormat="Java">
    LEGACY_STARTUP_BEAN_IN_WAR_CNTR0319E=CNTR0319E: The {0} bean is a startup bean, and is packaged inside of a Web archive (WAR) module, which is not allowed.  Startup beans must be packaged inside of a stand-alone Enterprise JavaBean (EJB) module.  Start-up behavior for an EJB component packaged inside of a WAR module is obtained by using a singleton session bean that is marked with the @Startup annotation, or the corresponding XML element.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A startup bean must not be packaged inside of a .war file.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Package the startup bean inside a stand-alone EJB JAR module.  Alternatively, use a singleton session bean marked with the @Startup annotation or the corresponding XML element, and package the bean in either an EJB JAR module or a WAR module.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0309E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="STATEFUL_TIMEOUT_OVERFLOW_CNTR0309E" varFormat="Java">
    STATEFUL_TIMEOUT_OVERFLOW_CNTR0309E=CNTR0309E: The {0} Enterprise JavaBean (EJB) in the {1} module of the {2} application contains a stateful timeout value {3} with time unit {4}.  The conversion to milliseconds resulted in an overflow.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The stateful timeout is specified either via annotations or by deployment descriptor. The resulting conversion to milliseconds must be greater than zero and less than java.lang.Long.MAX_VALUE (9223372036854775807) to be valid.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the stateful timeout value for the Enterprise JavaBean identified by the message.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR9273E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="UNABLE_TO_CREATE_ROOT_DIRECTORY_FOR_STUBS_PROCESSING_CNTR9273E" varFormat="Java">
    UNABLE_TO_CREATE_ROOT_DIRECTORY_FOR_STUBS_PROCESSING_CNTR9273E=CNTR9273E: The {0} directory could not be created.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified directory can not be created.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that the file system permissions allow for directory creation.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR9278E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INCOMPATIABLE_OPTION_WITH_CLASS_NAME_INPUT_CNTR9278E" varFormat="Java">
    INCOMPATIABLE_OPTION_WITH_CLASS_NAME_INPUT_CNTR9278E=CNTR9278E: The input type of a fully qualified class name is not compatible with the {0} option.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The input type of fully qualified class name is not compatible with the specified option.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the usage statement and either change the input type or remove the specified option.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR9276I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="EAR_LIBRARY_DIRECTORY_DISABLED_CNTR9276I" varFormat="Java">
    EAR_LIBRARY_DIRECTORY_DISABLED_CNTR9276I=CNTR9276I: The {0} application has disabled the library directory. Java archive (JAR) and Web archive (WAR) files in the library directory will not be processed.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The application configuration data specified a library directory with a blank string for the library directory name.   This action disables the library directory.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the library directory for this application should not be disabled, modify the application.xml configuration file in the application enterprise archive (EAR) file.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0216E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="AUTOMATIC_TIMER_SCHEDULE_UNINCREMENTABLE_CNTR0216E" varFormat="Java">
    AUTOMATIC_TIMER_SCHEDULE_UNINCREMENTABLE_CNTR0216E=CNTR0216E: The {0} enterprise bean in the {1} module has automatic timer metadata for the {2} method, but the {3} schedule field uses an increment.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified method has automatic timer metadata in the deployment descriptor or in a @Schedule or @Schedules annotation, but the specified field in the metadata uses an increment.  You can use increments for the second, minute, and hour fields only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Change the field in the automatic timer metadata, or remove the automatic timer metadata.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0069E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_ACTIVITY_SESSION_POLICY_CNTR0069E" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_ACTIVITY_SESSION_POLICY_CNTR0069E=CNTR0069E: Bean &quot;{0}&quot; in an EJB 1.1 module attempted to use an invalid &quot;Activate at&quot; policy of &quot;Activity Session&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Activity Sessions are not supported for EJB V1.1 modules.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Select &quot;Once&quot; or &quot;Transaction&quot; for the &quot;Activate At&quot; policy.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0103E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SFB_CONTROLLER_KEYVALUE_CNTR0103E" varFormat="Java">
    SFB_CONTROLLER_KEYVALUE_CNTR0103E=CNTR0103E: Method {0} value is null.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified method was passed a entryKey value that is null.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    There is no user action required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0126E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="NO_MESSAGE_LISTENER_INTERFACE_CNTR0126E" varFormat="Java">
    NO_MESSAGE_LISTENER_INTERFACE_CNTR0126E=CNTR0126E: The {0} message-driven bean (MDB) class does not define a message listener interface.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A message-driven bean must define a message listener interface using XML, annotations, or the implements clause of the Enterprise JavaBeans (EJB) class.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check the XML and Java source for the MDB class and specify the message listener interface.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR8990I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ENGLISH_ONLY_INFO_MESSAGE_CNTR8990I" varFormat="Java">
    ENGLISH_ONLY_INFO_MESSAGE_CNTR8990I=CNTR8990I: This message is an English-only Informational message: {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This informational message is not translated.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See message for details.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0094E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_CACHE_RELOAD_POLICY_CNTR0094E" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_CACHE_RELOAD_POLICY_CNTR0094E=CNTR0094E: Entity bean &quot;{0}&quot; has been configured with a BeanCache LoadPolicy that will reload the Entity at an interval, but the Entity bean is not configured for EJB 2.x container managed persistence&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A Bean Cache LoadPolicy that reloads an entity bean at intervals is only supported for EJB V2.x container-managed persistence (CMP) beans.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Change the Bean Cache LoadPolicy to a value that is supported by the bean type, or change the bean to use EJB V2.x container-managed persistence.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0155E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="AMBIGUOUS_REFERENCE_TO_DUPLICATE_INTERFACE_CNTR0155E" varFormat="Java">
    AMBIGUOUS_REFERENCE_TO_DUPLICATE_INTERFACE_CNTR0155E=CNTR0155E: Another component is attempting to reference the {0} enterprise bean in the {1} module.  This bean supports both local and remote implementations of the {2} interface, which the other component is attempting to reference.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The component that is attempting to reference the bean has a configuration error. The component has not specified whether to invoke the local or remote interface on this bean.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Change the ejb-ref tag or @EJB annotation on the component that is attempting to reference this bean so that it specifies either the local or the remote interface of the bean. Check the log file for a related exception, which indicates the calling component that has the configuration error.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0124W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_EXCLUDE_LIST_XML_CNTR0124W" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_EXCLUDE_LIST_XML_CNTR0124W=CNTR0124W: XML configuration error in ejb-jar.xml for jar: &quot;{0}&quot;.  The exclude-list element in error for EJB: &quot;{1}&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    All ejb-name elements within the exclude-list element must match valid ejb-name elements within the enterprise-beans element.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the ejb-jar.xml file so that all ejb-name elements within the exclude-list element match valid ejb-name entries in the enterprise-beans element.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR9259E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="NO_COMPONENT_INTERFACE_CNTR9259E" varFormat="Java">
    NO_COMPONENT_INTERFACE_CNTR9259E=CNTR9259E: No component interface specified for the {0} home.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Each configured home must have a component interface.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the configuration data for this home.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0127W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_MAX_POOLTIMEOUT_CNTR0127W" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_MAX_POOLTIMEOUT_CNTR0127W=CNTR0127W: The maximum pool size timeout specified for bean {0} is not a valid integer: {1}. The default value of {2} seconds is used instead.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Only a positive integer or zero can be specified for the maximum pool size timeout. The default value will be used.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Change the value of the maximum pool size timeout to a positive integer or zero.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0210E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="AUTOMATIC_TIMER_METHOD_NOT_FOUND_CNTR0210E" varFormat="Java">
    AUTOMATIC_TIMER_METHOD_NOT_FOUND_CNTR0210E=CNTR0210E: The {0} enterprise bean in the {1} module has automatic timer metadata in the deployment descriptor for the {2} method, but no timeout callback method with that name was found.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The deployment descriptor contains automatic timer metadata for the specified method name, but no method with a timeout callback method signature was found by that name.  A timeout callback method must have a void return type, and it must either have no parameters or have a single parameter with the type javax.ejb.Timer.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Add a method with the specified name, change the method signature of an existing method with that name, or remove the timer from the deployment descriptor.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR5103E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="JIT_INVALID_SUBCLASS_RUNTIME_EX_CNTR5103E" varFormat="Java">
    JIT_INVALID_SUBCLASS_RUNTIME_EX_CNTR5103E=CNTR5103E: The {0} application exception that is defined on the {1} method of the {2} interface must not be defined as a subclass of the java.lang.RuntimeException exception.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    According to the Enterprise JavaBeans (EJB) specification, an application exception for a component interface must not be defined as a subclass of the java.lang.RuntimeException exception.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Change the application so that remote component interface methods are not defined with a java.lang.RuntimeException subclass on the throws clause.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0177E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WS_EJBPROXY_FAILURE_CNTR0177E" varFormat="Java">
    WS_EJBPROXY_FAILURE_CNTR0177E=CNTR0177E: Failure occurred attempting to create a Web service endpoint proxy for the {0} bean in the {1} module of the {2} application : {3}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A session bean is not allowed to implement both a Web service Provider interface and a JAX-RPC Web service endpoint interface.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Remove the configured JAX-RPC Web service endpoint interface from the ejb-jar.xml file, or change the bean implementation so that it does not implement the Web service Provider interface.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0020E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="NON_APPLICATION_EXCEPTION_METHOD_ON_BEAN_CNTR0020E" varFormat="Java">
    NON_APPLICATION_EXCEPTION_METHOD_ON_BEAN_CNTR0020E=CNTR0020E: EJB threw an unexpected (non-declared) exception during invocation of method &quot;{1}&quot; on bean &quot;{2}&quot;. Exception data: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An exception, which is not declared on the EJB method signature, was created when the EJB container attempted to invoke this EJB method.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the stack trace to determine the origin of the exception.  If the exception originates from customer-written code, correct the cause of the exception. If not, visit the IBM support Web site for information on problem determination.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0028W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="FAILED_TO_CLOSE_CONNECTION_CNTR0028W" varFormat="Java">
    FAILED_TO_CLOSE_CONNECTION_CNTR0028W=CNTR0028W: Failed to close connection: 
 {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An SQLException occurred when trying to close a Datasource connection.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See the vendor-specific documentation for the database product you are using.  Typically a vendor-specific exception code will be displayed as part of the SQLException.  This exception code can be used, in combination with the vendor-specific documentation, to determine the cause of the exception.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0172E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="NAME_ALREADY_BOUND_FOR_EJB_CNTR0172E" varFormat="Java">
    NAME_ALREADY_BOUND_FOR_EJB_CNTR0172E=CNTR0172E: The {0} interface of the {1} bean in the {2} module of the {3} application cannot be bound to the {4} name location. The {5} interface of the {6} bean in the {7} module of the {8} application has already been bound to the {4} name location.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Each enterprise bean interface must specify a unique binding location.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the binding file for one of these two bean interfaces so that each interface has a unique binding location.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0142W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INCOMPLETE_EJB_BINDING_CNTR0142W" varFormat="Java">
    INCOMPLETE_EJB_BINDING_CNTR0142W=CNTR0142W: The Enterprise JavaBeans (EJB) binding with the {0} Java Naming and Directory Interface (JNDI) name does not contain an enterprise bean stanza.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    All EJB bindings require an enterpriseBean stanza within the ibm-ejb-jar-bnd.xml file.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check the ibm-ejb-jar-bnd.xml file and ensure that all EJB bindings include an enterprise bean stanza.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR9414E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CNTR9414E_CONFIG_READ_FAIL" varFormat="Java">
    CNTR9414E_CONFIG_READ_FAIL=CNTR9414E: Failed to bind data source into JNDI using the name, {0}.  Exception: {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The embeddable Enterprise JavaBeans (EJB) container was unable to bind a javax.sql.DataSource instance into the JNDI namespace.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Resolve the failure by examining the exception, the logs, and the FFDC output.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0179W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="NP_TIMER_RETRY_LIMIT_REACHED_CNTR0179W" varFormat="Java">
    NP_TIMER_RETRY_LIMIT_REACHED_CNTR0179W=CNTR0179W: Non-persistent timer maximum number of retries {0} was reached.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The maximum number of retries configured on the EJB timer service (nonPersistentTimerRetryCount on the EJBTimer configuration object) has been reached.  No further retries will be attempted until a timout method succeeds.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Determine the cause of the failing timeout method, or increase the maximum number of retries.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0314E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="AUTOMATIC_TIMER_METHOD_AMBIGUOUS_CNTR0314E" varFormat="Java">
    AUTOMATIC_TIMER_METHOD_AMBIGUOUS_CNTR0314E=CNTR0314E: The {0} enterprise bean in the {1} module has timer metadata in the deployment descriptor that targets the {2} method, but does not indicate whether the targeted method accepts zero or one parameters.  Both a zero parameter and a one parameter version of the {2} method were found in the class hierarchy of the bean.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The deployment descriptor defines a timer that targets the specified method, but does not indicate how many parameters that method accepts.  Multiple methods have that same name in the class hierarchy of the bean, which are eligible to receive timer callbacks.  As a result, the EJB container is unable to determine which method the timer must target.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Change the deployment descriptor so that the timer explicitly indicates whether it targets the zero parameter or the one parameter version of the method.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0215E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="AUTOMATIC_TIMER_SCHEDULE_LIST_VALUE_CNTR0215E" varFormat="Java">
    AUTOMATIC_TIMER_SCHEDULE_LIST_VALUE_CNTR0215E=CNTR0215E: The {0} enterprise bean in the {1} module has automatic timer metadata for the {2} method, but the {3} schedule field has a list value that is not valid.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified method has automatic timer metadata in the deployment descriptor or in a @Schedule or @Schedules annotation, but the specified field in the metadata has a value for a list that is not valid.  List values must be integers, keywords, or ranges.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Change the field in the automatic timer metadata, or remove the automatic timer metadata.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0038W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="POTENTIAL_LOST_UPDATE_CNTR0038W" varFormat="Java">
    POTENTIAL_LOST_UPDATE_CNTR0038W=CNTR0038W: The TX attribute needs to be changed to eliminate potential lost updates to bean {0} when used concurrently by multiple transactions.  The bean should not be using the TX_NOT_SUPPORTED, TX_NEVER, or TX_SUPPORTS transaction attribute.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A transaction was started with the TX_NOT_SUPPORTED, TX_NEVER, or the TX_SUPPORTS transaction attribute. The transaction updated a container managed persistence (CMP) entity bean, and the transaction is storing the update to the persistent store. If a concurrent transaction uses the CMP entity bean with the same primary key value, the updates of one transaction might overlay the updates of the other transaction.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    The application must ensure that concurrent transactions never update a CMP entity bean with the same primary key value. If that cannot be done, then whichever bean begins the transaction must use a transaction attribute other than TX_NEVER, TX_NOT_SUPPORTED, or TX_SUPPORTS to ensure that data consistency is maintained.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0169E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ORPHAN_BINDING_ENTRY_CNTR0169E" varFormat="Java">
    ORPHAN_BINDING_ENTRY_CNTR0169E=CNTR0169E: The {0} enterprise bean, which is specified in the {1} binding within the {2} module, does not exist.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The enterprise bean name might be incorrect, or a binding might have been specified for a bean that does not exist.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the binding file.  Then, reinstall the application.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0084E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_MDB_TX_ATTR_CNTR0084E" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_MDB_TX_ATTR_CNTR0084E=CNTR0084E: Method {0} of MDB {1} is deployed with an incorrect transaction attribute.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A method of a message-driven bean (MDB) is required to be deployed with a transaction attribute of &quot;requires&quot;, &quot;not supported&quot;, or &quot;bean managed&quot;.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Redeploy the application using &quot;requires&quot;, &quot;not supported&quot;, or &quot;bean managed&quot; as the transaction attribute for the method of the MDB.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0180I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MDB_ACTIVATION_SPEC_INFO_CNTR0180I" varFormat="Java">
    MDB_ACTIVATION_SPEC_INFO_CNTR0180I=CNTR0180I: The {0} message-driven bean in the {1} module of the {2} application is bound to the {3} activation specification.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    When the message-driven bean starts, the specified activation specification will be used to activate the message endpoint.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR5032E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="JIT_INVALID_CUSTOM_EJBFIND_RETURN_CNTR5032E" varFormat="Java">
    JIT_INVALID_CUSTOM_EJBFIND_RETURN_CNTR5032E=CNTR5032E: The {2} method with the {3} return type on the {1} class for the {0} entity bean must return the {4} primary key class, the java.util.Collection class, or the java.util.Enumeration class.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    According to the Enterprise JavaBeans (EJB) specification, the return type of all custom ejbFind methods for an entity bean class must be the primary key class, the java.util.Collection class, or the java.util.Enumeration class.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Change the return type of the method to the primary key class, the java.util.Collection class, or the java.util.Enumeration class.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR9264E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MISSING_CLASSPATH_PARAM_CNTR9264E" varFormat="Java">
    MISSING_CLASSPATH_PARAM_CNTR9264E=CNTR9264E: The required class path name parameter was not specified.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    For the -cp option, the class path name must be provided as the next parameter.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the usage statement and provide the required class path name parameter.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0317E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="JAX_RPC_ENDPOINT_IN_WAR_CNTR0317E" varFormat="Java">
    JAX_RPC_ENDPOINT_IN_WAR_CNTR0317E=CNTR0317E: The {0} bean is packaged inside a WAR module and has been defined as a JAX-RPC endpoint using the ejb-jar.xml descriptor.  The {1} interface is declared as the JAX-RPC endpoint.  However, beans packaged in a WAR module are not supported as JAX-RPC endpoints.  Package the bean in an EJBJAR module, or remove the service endpoint interface from the deployment descriptor.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An Enterprise JavaBean may not be declared as a JAX-RPC endpoint and packaged inside a WAR module.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Package the Enterprise JavaBean in an EJBJAR module.  Or, update to ejb-jar.xml descriptor to no longer declare the Enterprise JavaBean as a JAX-RPC endpoint.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0150E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CONFLICTING_ANNOTATIONS_CONFIGURED_ON_METHOD_CNTR0150E" varFormat="Java">
    CONFLICTING_ANNOTATIONS_CONFIGURED_ON_METHOD_CNTR0150E=CNTR0150E: The {0} annotation and the {1} annotation cannot both be configured on the {2} method of the {3} enterprise bean class.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The annotations that are identified in this error message are in conflict with each other. Do not specify these annotations on the same method.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Change the Java source code by removing one or both of the annotations from the specified method.  Then, reinstall the application.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0012W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="COLLABORATOR_THREW_UNEXPECTED_EXCEPTION_CNTR0012W" varFormat="Java">
    COLLABORATOR_THREW_UNEXPECTED_EXCEPTION_CNTR0012W=CNTR0012W: Collaborator {0} threw unexpected exception - proceeding with remaining collaborators.
 Exception data:{1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This exception is unexpected. The cause is not immediately known.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0243E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_MDB_CALLBACK_METHOD_CNTR0243E" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_MDB_CALLBACK_METHOD_CNTR0243E=CNTR0243E: Because the {0} enterprise bean implements the javax.ejb.MessageDriven interface, the {1} method must be a {2} method and not a {3} method.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    For a message driven bean, the Enterprise JavaBeans 3.0 specification requires that the ejbCreate and ejbPassivate methods be treated as @PostConstruct and @PreDestroy life cycle callback interceptor methods, respectively.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the deployment descriptor or annotation so that the method is the correct type of life cycle callback interceptor.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0062W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="POOLSIZE_MISSING_EQUALS_SIGN_CNTR0062W" varFormat="Java">
    POOLSIZE_MISSING_EQUALS_SIGN_CNTR0062W=CNTR0062W: An equals sign was not found in the pool size specification string {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The format of a pool size specification is: bean_name=min,max .  An equals sign must be present between the bean name and the minimum value and the maximum value.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that an equals sign is present between the bean name and the minimum value and the maximum value.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR9253E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="BAD_LOG_FLIE_CNTR9253E" varFormat="Java">
    BAD_LOG_FLIE_CNTR9253E=CNTR9253E: The {0} log file name parameter is not correct.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The log file name must point to a file, including the directory path. Also, the log file name may not begin with &quot;-&quot;.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Invoke the createEJBStubs command with the -help option to view the command syntax.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0225E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_EXCLUDE_DEFAULT_INTERCEPTORS_CNTR0225E" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_EXCLUDE_DEFAULT_INTERCEPTORS_CNTR0225E=CNTR0225E: The exclude-default-interceptors element in the deployment descriptor is not valid for a style 1 interceptor-binding element.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The interceptor-binding element is using an exclude-default-interceptors element which is only valid for a style 2, style 3, or style 4 interceptor-binding element.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Eliminate the exclude-default-intercrptor element.  Or, change the ejb-name tag within the interceptor-binding element to provide a specific enterprise bean name.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0001W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CANNOT_PASSIVATE_STATEFUL_BEAN_CNTR0001W" varFormat="Java">
    CANNOT_PASSIVATE_STATEFUL_BEAN_CNTR0001W=CNTR0001W: A Stateful SessionBean could not be passivated: {0} {1} {2}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The container was not able to passivate a stateful session bean.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check that passivation directory exists, the process has write permissions in that directory, and that there is enough disk space.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0245E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DUPLICATE_STYLE_1_INTERCEPTOR_BINDING_CNTR0245E" varFormat="Java">
    DUPLICATE_STYLE_1_INTERCEPTOR_BINDING_CNTR0245E=CNTR0245E: The {0} module of the {1} application has more than one style 1 interceptor-binding in the deployment descriptor. Only one style 1 interceptor-binding is allowed.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    According to the Enterprise JavaBeans (EJB) specification, only one style 1 interceptor-binding can be used for the module.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct deployment descriptor so that only one style 1 interceptor-binding is used for the module.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0213E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="AUTOMATIC_TIMER_SCHEDULE_RANGE_BOUND_CNTR0213E" varFormat="Java">
    AUTOMATIC_TIMER_SCHEDULE_RANGE_BOUND_CNTR0213E=CNTR0213E: The {0} enterprise bean in the {1} module has automatic timer metadata for the {2} method, but the {3} schedule field has an range bound that is not valid.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified method has automatic timer metadata in the deployment descriptor or in a @Schedule or @Schedules annotation, but the specified field in the metadata has an range bound that is not valid.  The upper and lower bound for a range must be non-negative integers or keyword values.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Change the field in the automatic timer metadata, or remove the automatic timer metadata.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0125E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INJECTION_PROCESSING_FAILURE_CNTR0125E" varFormat="Java">
    INJECTION_PROCESSING_FAILURE_CNTR0125E=CNTR0125E: Unable to process injection information for class: {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The injection processors registered with the injection engine failed to identify and collect all the annotations associated with the class.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the ejb-jar.xml and annotations on the class.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR9420E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CNTR9420E_INVALID_CONNECTION_POOL_SPECIFIED" varFormat="Java">
    CNTR9420E_INVALID_CONNECTION_POOL_SPECIFIED=CNTR9420E: The embeddable Enterprise JavaBeans (EJB) container properties for the {0} data source contain a {1} ConnectionPool value that is not valid.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The properties that the embeddable Enterprise JavaBeans (EJB) container uses contain a data source with a ConnectionPool value that is not valid.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Change the ConnectionPool property value for this data source to a valid value.  Valid values are names of a connection pool.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0223E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DUPLICATE_INTERCEPTOR_METHOD_CNTR0223E" varFormat="Java">
    DUPLICATE_INTERCEPTOR_METHOD_CNTR0223E=CNTR0223E: Only one method in the {0} class is allowed to be a {1} interceptor method.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    More than one method of this class is specified as an interceptor method of the given type.  The Enterprise JavaBeans 3.0 specification does not allow you to have multiple interceptor methods of the same type for this class.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the Java source code annotations or deployment descriptor for this class so that it only contains a single interceptor method of the given type.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR9400I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CNTR9400I_SCANNING_MODULES" varFormat="Java">
    CNTR9400I_SCANNING_MODULES=CNTR9400I: The embeddable Enterprise JavaBeans (EJB) container is scanning for Enterprise JavaBeans (EJB) modules to start.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The embeddable container is scanning the classpath for valid Enterprise JavaBeans (EJB) modules. Valid EJB modules contain an ejb-jar.xml file or Enterprise JavaBeans (EJB) annotations.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    There is no user action required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0232E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_LIFECYCLE_SIGNATURE_CNTR0232E" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_LIFECYCLE_SIGNATURE_CNTR0232E=CNTR0232E: The {0} method does not have the required method signature for a {1} method of a interceptor class.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Enterprise JavaBeans 3.0 specification requires that life cycle methods of an interceptor class have the following signature, without a throws clause: void &amp;lt;METHOD&amp;gt; (InvocationContext)
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the method signature for this interceptor.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0096W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MISSING_APPLICATION_DRSSETTINGS_CNTR0096W" varFormat="Java">
    MISSING_APPLICATION_DRSSETTINGS_CNTR0096W=CNTR0096W: Application configuration for session bean &quot;{0}&quot; is missing override of memory-to-memory replication settings.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The session bean is configured to override the memory-to-memory replication settings at the application level, but no settings for memory-to-memory replication are provided at the application level.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Disable the override at the application level, or provide the settings for memory-to-memory replication for this session bean.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0230E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_AROUND_INVOKE_SIGNATURE_CNTR0230E" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_AROUND_INVOKE_SIGNATURE_CNTR0230E=CNTR0230E: The {0} method does not have the required method signature for a {1} method.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Enterprise JavaBeans 3.0 specification requires that around-invoke and around-timeout methods have the following signature: Object &amp;lt;METHOD&amp;gt;(InvocationContext) throws Exception
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the method signature of this interceptor.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0117I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="EJBSTORE_DISABLED_CNTR0117I" varFormat="Java">
    EJBSTORE_DISABLED_CNTR0117I=CNTR0117I: Container-managed ejbStore() call will be bypassed on bean: &quot;{0}&quot; if it has not been modified in the current transaction.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The bean has been configured to prevent the enterprise Java bean (EJB) container from invoking the ejbStore() method if the bean has not been modified. This behavior is not compliant with the EJB V2.0 or later specifications, but it can improve performance.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    There is no user action required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR5025E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="JIT_NO_INIT_METHOD_CNTR5025E" varFormat="Java">
    JIT_NO_INIT_METHOD_CNTR5025E=CNTR5025E: The {2} method of the {1} home interface for the {0} bean does not define a corresponding init or ejbCreate method on the {3} class.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    According to the Enterprise JavaBeans (EJB) specification, the bean class must implement an ejbCreate or init method for every create method for a home interface.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Change the bean class to provide an ejbCreate or init method that corresponds to the method.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0192E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SINGLETON_INVALID_ACCESS_TIMEOUT_CNTR0192E" varFormat="Java">
    SINGLETON_INVALID_ACCESS_TIMEOUT_CNTR0192E=CNTR0192E: The access timeout value {0} is not valid for the enterprise bean {1} method of the {2} class. The value must be -1 or greater and less than java.lang.Long.MAX_VALUE (9223372036854775807).
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The access timeout is specified either via annotations or by deployment descriptor. The value must be -1 or greater and less than java.lang.Long.MAX_VALUE (9223372036854775807).
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the access timeout value for the method identified by the message. A method name of &quot;*&quot; is used in deployment descriptor to indicate all methods of the singleton class. If annotation is used and @AccessTimeout annotation is not found on the method, correct the @AccessTimeout annotation at class level.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0231E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_LIFECYCLE_SIGNATURE_CNTR0231E" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_LIFECYCLE_SIGNATURE_CNTR0231E=CNTR0231E: The {0} method signature is not valid as a {1} method of an enterprise bean class.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Enterprise JavaBeans 3.0 specification requires that life cycle methods of an enterprise bean have the following signature, without a throws clause: void &amp;lt;METHOD&amp;gt;()
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the method signature for this interceptor.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0031W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ERROR_STARTING_CMP_BEAN_CNTR0031W" varFormat="Java">
    ERROR_STARTING_CMP_BEAN_CNTR0031W=CNTR0031W: Error starting CMP bean {0}: 
 {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An entity bean might have been bound to a Datasource using a Datasource name that is not valid or is not correct. If the Datasource name is correct, the Datasource might not be configured correctly.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the CNTR0026W message precedes this message, you need to provide the name of the Datasource. If CNTR0026W did not precede this message, check the datasource name that appears in the CNTR0032W message that follows this message. If a &apos;name not found&apos; exception occurred, the Datasource name is most likely not correct.  If the correct Datasource name is provided, then check the Datasource configuration. For example, you might have specified a database name, a user ID, or a password in the datasource configuration that is not correct.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0237E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INTERCEPTOR_CLASS_NOT_FOUND_CNTR0237E" varFormat="Java">
    INTERCEPTOR_CLASS_NOT_FOUND_CNTR0237E=CNTR0237E: The user-provided enterprise bean level 3.0 {0} interceptor class cannot be found or loaded.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An enterprise bean level 3.0 interceptor class cannot not be found or loaded.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the interceptor class is installed and configured correctly.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0197E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DEPENDS_ON_SPECIFIED_ON_NON_SINGLETON_BEAN_CNTR0197E" varFormat="Java">
    DEPENDS_ON_SPECIFIED_ON_NON_SINGLETON_BEAN_CNTR0197E=CNTR0197E: The {0} non-singleton enterprise bean has dependency metadata.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The bean was configured to depend on another bean through the @DependsOn annotation or the depends-on element in the ejb-jar.xml file. However, the bean is not a singleton session bean.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Remove the dependency metadata, or change the type of the bean.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR9401I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CNTR9401I_INIT" varFormat="Java">
    CNTR9401I_INIT=CNTR9401I: The embeddable Enterprise JavaBeans (EJB) container is initializing.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The embeddable container must initialize before the user code can access the enterprise beans.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    There is no user action required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0082E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ENDPOINT_RECOVERY_ID_UNKNOWN_CNTR0082E" varFormat="Java">
    ENDPOINT_RECOVERY_ID_UNKNOWN_CNTR0082E=CNTR0082E: Cannot enlist XAResource since recovery ID for resource adapter {0} for MDB {1} is not known.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This exception is unexpected. The cause is not immediately known.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0104E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SFB_CONTROLLER_KEYBYTES_CNTR0104E" varFormat="Java">
    SFB_CONTROLLER_KEYBYTES_CNTR0104E=CNTR0104E: Method {0} cannot convert entryKey to byte array.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The method that is specified was not able to convert the entryKey parameter to a byte array.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    There is no user action required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR8991W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ENGLISH_ONLY_WARN_MESSAGE_CNTR8991W" varFormat="Java">
    ENGLISH_ONLY_WARN_MESSAGE_CNTR8991W=CNTR8991W: This message is an English-only Warning message: {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This warning message is not translated.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See message for details.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0168W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SIMPLE_BINDING_NAME_MISSUSED_CNTR0168W" varFormat="Java">
    SIMPLE_BINDING_NAME_MISSUSED_CNTR0168W=CNTR0168W: The {0} enterprise bean in the {1} module within the {2} application is configured with a simple binding name, but has multiple local or remote interfaces.  The naming locations that are used to bind these interfaces will differ from the simple binding name that is specified.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Because the enterprise bean has multiple interfaces, each binding name must be extended to make it unique.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Complete one of the following actions: /n Look up the interfaces for this enterprise bean using the extended names. /n Change the configuration data for this bean to specify unique binding locations for each interface.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0076W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MISSING_RESREF_BINDING_CNTR0076W" varFormat="Java">
    MISSING_RESREF_BINDING_CNTR0076W=CNTR0076W: A reference to an ResourceRef could not be found in the deployment descriptor for the WebApp or EnterpriseBean with the display name {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Java Enterprise Edition (Java EE) component might have specified binding information that is not valid.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify the binding information in the deployment descriptor for the Java EE component is correct.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0195E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="TIMERSERVICE_WORKMANAGER_NOT_FOUND_CNTR0195E" varFormat="Java">
    TIMERSERVICE_WORKMANAGER_NOT_FOUND_CNTR0195E=CNTR0195E: The work manager associated with the {0} scheduler used by the EJB timer service could not be obtained.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An attempt was made to obtain the work manager.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that the timer service scheduler has a work manager configured.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0160E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="TIMER_BEAN_MUST_IMPLEMENT_EJBTIMEOUT_CNTR0160E" varFormat="Java">
    TIMER_BEAN_MUST_IMPLEMENT_EJBTIMEOUT_CNTR0160E=CNTR0160E: The {0} enterprise bean in the {1} module is configured as timer bean. However, the bean does not implement the following required timeout method: ejbTimeout
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Timer beans, which inherit from the TimedObject interface, must implement the following timeout method: ejbTimeout
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the bean implementation to include the required method.   Then, reinstall the application.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR5019E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="JIT_NO_CREATE_METHOD_CNTR5019E" varFormat="Java">
    JIT_NO_CREATE_METHOD_CNTR5019E=CNTR5019E: The {1} interface, which has been configured as a home interface for the {0} bean, does not define a create method.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    According to the Enterprise JavaBeans (EJB) specification, all home interfaces must define at least one create method.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Change the home interface to define a create method.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0301E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="AUTOMATIC_TIMER_VALIDATION_FAILED_CNTR0301E" varFormat="Java">
    AUTOMATIC_TIMER_VALIDATION_FAILED_CNTR0301E=CNTR0301E: The {0} enterprise bean in the {1} module of the {2} application has an automatic timer for the {3} method, but an incompatible change was made to the application since the server created the timer.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The server attempted to run a timeout callback method for an automatic timer, but an incompatible change was made to the application without removing the automatic timers.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Stop the application and run the removeAutomaticEJBTimers command for the AdminTask object to manually clear the contents of the database.  The server automatically recreates the timers when the application is restarted.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR9267W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="UNABLE_TO_DELETE_FILE_CNTR9267W" varFormat="Java">
    UNABLE_TO_DELETE_FILE_CNTR9267W=CNTR9267W: The createEJBStubs command could not delete the {0} file.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified file could not be deleted.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the file system permissions settings.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0307W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_STATEFUL_TIMEOUT_TIMEOUT_CNTR0307W" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_STATEFUL_TIMEOUT_TIMEOUT_CNTR0307W=CNTR0307W: The {0} Enterprise JavaBean (EJB) in the {1} module of the {2} application has a timeout value specified in the StatefulTimeout annotation or stateful-timeout deployment descriptor element which is not a valid integer: {3}.  The default value of {4} milliseconds will be used instead.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Only a positive integer can be specified for the stateful timeout value.  The default value will be used.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Change the value for the stateful timeout to a positive integer.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0235E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="AMBIGUOUS_INIT_ANNOTATION_CNTR0235E" varFormat="Java">
    AMBIGUOUS_INIT_ANNOTATION_CNTR0235E=CNTR0235E: The name of the adapted create&amp;lt;METHOD&amp;gt; method must be specified for either the {0} method or the {1} method of the {2} enterprise bean.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The @Init annotation is applied to multiple methods of the enterprise bean. The Enterprise JavaBeans 3.0 specification requires that the name of the adapted create&amp;lt;METHOD&amp;gt; method of the home or local home interface must be specified if there is any ambiguity.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Use the value element of the @Init annotation to specify the name of the create&amp;lt;METHOD&amp;gt; on one of the two specified methods.  This approach will remove the ambiguity.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR9106E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CNTR9106E" varFormat="Java">
    CNTR9106E=CNTR9106E: Missing required server name.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A server name must be specified.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the usage statement, and specify a server name.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0211E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="AUTOMATIC_TIMER_SCHEDULE_VALUE_CNTR0211E" varFormat="Java">
    AUTOMATIC_TIMER_SCHEDULE_VALUE_CNTR0211E=CNTR0211E: The {0} enterprise bean in the {1} module has automatic metadata for the {2} method, but the {3} schedule field has a value that is not valid.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified method has automatic timer metadata in the deployment descriptor or in a @Schedule or @Schedules annotation, but the specified field in the metadata has a value that is not valid.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Change the field in the automatic timer metadata, or remove the automatic timer metadata.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0093E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="EJB_START_FAILED_CNTR0093E" varFormat="Java">
    EJB_START_FAILED_CNTR0093E=CNTR0093E: Attempt to start EnterpriseBean {0} failed with exception: {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An error has occurred during the initialization and start of an EnterpriseBean.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Take action based upon the exception message in message CNTR0093E.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR9412E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CNTR9412E_JNDI_CLOSE_FAIL" varFormat="Java">
    CNTR9412E_JNDI_CLOSE_FAIL=CNTR9412E: An error occurred while shutting down the JNDI name space. Exception: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The embeddable EJB container was unable to close the java:global namespace. This means that some Enterprise JavaBeans or other objects bound into the namespace could be leaked.  Additionally, this could lead to JNDI problems if additional embeddable Enterprise JavaBeans (EJB) container instances are created.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Resolve the failure by examining the exception, the logs, and the FFDC output.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0175W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="STATEFUL_PERSISTENCE_CONTEXT_ACTIVATE_ONCE_CNTR0175W" varFormat="Java">
    STATEFUL_PERSISTENCE_CONTEXT_ACTIVATE_ONCE_CNTR0175W=CNTR0175W: The configured Activation Policy for the {0} bean in the {1} module of the {2} application has been changed from {3} to ONCE. A Stateful Session bean that references an extended persistence context must be configured with an Activation Policy of ONCE.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A Stateful Session bean that references an extended persistence context must be configured with an Activation Policy of ONCE.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Change the Activation Policy configured for the bean to ONCE.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR9105E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CNTR9105E" varFormat="Java">
    CNTR9105E=CNTR9105E: Missing required filter.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    One of the three filters must be specified: -all -timer -app
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the usage statement, and specify one of the three filters.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0075E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="BEANCLASS_NOT_FOUND_CNTR0075E" varFormat="Java">
    BEANCLASS_NOT_FOUND_CNTR0075E=CNTR0075E: The user-provided class &quot;{0}&quot; needed by the EnterpriseBean could not be found or loaded.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    One or more of the implementation, home interface, remote interface, local interface, or other similar class for the bean could not be found or could not be loaded.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that the implementation class, home interface, remote interface, and other classes for the bean are installed and configured correctly.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR9104W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CNTR9104W" varFormat="Java">
    CNTR9104W=CNTR9104W: EJB timer service {0} not available on server {1} in node {2}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The EJB timer service that is configured for the server that is specified is not available. The EJB timer service cannot start if there are no applications with TimedObject enterprise Java beans started on the server.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that an application with a TimedObject enterprise Java bean has been started on the server process that is specified.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR9266E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="UNABLE_TO_RENAME_FILE_CNTR9266E" varFormat="Java">
    UNABLE_TO_RENAME_FILE_CNTR9266E=CNTR9266E: The createEJBStubs command could not rename the {0} file to the {1} file.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified file could not be renamed.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the file system permissions settings. Also, make sure target file does not already exist.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR5107E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="JIT_INVALID_NOT_EXCEPTION_SUBCLASS_CNTR5107E" varFormat="Java">
    JIT_INVALID_NOT_EXCEPTION_SUBCLASS_CNTR5107E=CNTR5107E: The {0} application exception defined on the {1} method of the {2} class must be defined as a subclass of the java.lang.Exception class.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    According to the Enterprise JavaBeans (EJB) specification, an application exception for an interface must be defined as a subclass of either the java.lang.Exception class or the java.lang.RuntimeException class.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Change the application so that the exception is a subclass of either the java.lang.Exception class or the java.lang.RuntimeException class.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0311E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="NEGATIVE_STATEFUL_TIMEOUT_ANN_CNTR0311E" varFormat="Java">
    NEGATIVE_STATEFUL_TIMEOUT_ANN_CNTR0311E=CNTR0311E: The {0} Enterprise JavaBean (EJB) in the {1} module of the {2} application has a timeout value specified in the StatefulTimeout annotation which is negative: {3}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The stateful timeout must be postive, or 0 to indicate no timeout, or -1 to indicate infinite timeout.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Modify the StatefulTimeout annotation on the EJB.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0157E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="BEAN_DOES_NOT_IMPLEMENT_REQUIRED_METHOD_CNTR0157E" varFormat="Java">
    BEAN_DOES_NOT_IMPLEMENT_REQUIRED_METHOD_CNTR0157E=CNTR0157E: The {0} enterprise bean in the {1} module does not implement the {2} method.  This method is part of the bean interface.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Enterprise beans must implement all of the methods that are specified on their interface classes.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the bean implementation to include all of the required methods. Then, reinstall the application.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0059W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_POOLSIZE_COMBO_CNTR0059W" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_POOLSIZE_COMBO_CNTR0059W=CNTR0059W: Minimum pool size specified for bean {0} is greater than maximum pool size specified: ({1},{2})  Defaults used instead.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The maximum pool size must be greater than or equal to the minimum size. The default values will be used for the minimum pool size and the maximum pool size.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Change the maximum pool size to be a value that is greater than or equal to the minimum pool size.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR9103W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CNTR9103W" varFormat="Java">
    CNTR9103W=CNTR9103W: EJB timer {0} could not be found on server {1} in node {2}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The EJB timer that is specified does not exist on the server that is specified. The EJB timer might have expired, or it might have been cancelled.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the identity of the EJB timer and the server name have been specified correctly. If the EJB timer does exist, the identity name is correct, and server name is correct, see any previous exceptions for more information.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0226E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DUPLICATE_INTERCEPTOR_BINDING_CNTR0226E" varFormat="Java">
    DUPLICATE_INTERCEPTOR_BINDING_CNTR0226E=CNTR0226E: The {2} enterprise bean specifies a style 4 interceptor-binding element for the {0} method with the {1} signature.  A style 4 interceptor-binding cannot be used when a style 3 binding is also used for the same method of the same enterprise bean.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Style 3 and style 4 interceptor-binding elements cannot be specified on the same method of an enterprise bean.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Eliminate either the style 3 or the style 4 interceptor-binding element for the specified method of this bean.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR5027E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="JIT_INVALID_CREATE_RETURN_CNTR5027E" varFormat="Java">
    JIT_INVALID_CREATE_RETURN_CNTR5027E=CNTR5027E: The {2} method with the {3} return type on the {1} class for the {0} entity bean must return the {4} primary key class.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    According to the Enterprise JavaBeans (EJB) specification, the return type of all ejbCreate methods for an entity bean class must be the primary key type.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Change the return type of the method to the primary key class.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0111E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SFB_CONTROLLER_EVENTBYTES_CNTR0111E" varFormat="Java">
    SFB_CONTROLLER_EVENTBYTES_CNTR0111E=CNTR0111E: Method {0}  cannot convert event to byte array :  stoken = {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The method that is specified was not able to convert the event to a byte array.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    There is no user action required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0081E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="REASON_CODE_NOT_RECOGNIZED_CNTR0081E" varFormat="Java">
    REASON_CODE_NOT_RECOGNIZED_CNTR0081E=CNTR0081E: setTranEnlistmentNotNeeded called with an unrecognized reason code of {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This exception is unexpected. The cause is not immediately known.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR9409W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CNTR9409W_STOP_FAILURE" varFormat="Java">
    CNTR9409W_STOP_FAILURE=CNTR9409W: The embeddable Enterprise JavaBeans (EJB) container failed to stop. Exception: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The embeddable Enterprise JavaBeans (EJB) container failed to stop when the Close method was invoked due to the exception. Since this occurs after all the Enterprise JavaBeans (EJB) modules have been stopped, this is a problem with the embeddable Enterprise JavaBeans (EJB) container or its configuration.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Resolve the failure by examining the exception, the logs, the FFDC output, and review the configuration of the embeddable Enterprise JavaBeans (EJB) container.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0246E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DUPLICATE_STYLE_2_INTERCEPTOR_BINDING_CNTR0246E" varFormat="Java">
    DUPLICATE_STYLE_2_INTERCEPTOR_BINDING_CNTR0246E=CNTR0246E: The {0} module of the {1} application has more than one style 2 interceptor-binding in the deployment descriptor. Only one style 2 interceptor-binding is allowed.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    According to the Enterprise JavaBeans (EJB) specification, only one style 2 interceptor-binding can be used for each enterprise bean.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct deployment descriptor so that only one style 2 interceptor-binding is used for the enterprise bean.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0241E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_SLSB_CALLBACK_METHOD_CNTR0241E" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_SLSB_CALLBACK_METHOD_CNTR0241E=CNTR0241E: Because the {0} enterprise bean implements the javax.ejb.SessionBean interface, the {1} method must be a {2} method and not a {3} method.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    For a stateless session bean, the Enterprise JavaBeans 3.0 specification requires that the ejbCreate, ejbRemove, ejbActivate, and ejbPassivate methods be treated as @PostConstruct, @PreDestroy, @PostActivate, and @PrePassivate life cycle callback interceptor methods, respectively.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the deployment descriptor or annotation so that the method is the correct type of life cycle callback interceptor.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0217E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="AUTOMATIC_TIMER_SCHEDULE_MISSING_DAY_OF_WEEK_CNTR0217E" varFormat="Java">
    AUTOMATIC_TIMER_SCHEDULE_MISSING_DAY_OF_WEEK_CNTR0217E=CNTR0217E: The {0} enterprise bean in the {1} module has automatic timer metadata for the {2} method, but the {3} schedule field has an ordinal keyword without a day of the week.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified method has automatic timer metadata in the deployment descriptor or in a @Schedule or @Schedules annotation, but the specified field in the metadata has an ordinal keyword without a day of the week.  The 1st, 2nd, 3rd, 4th, and 5th keywords must be followed by a keyword for the day of the week.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Change the field in the automatic timer metadata, or remove the automatic timer metadata.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0019E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="NON_APPLICATION_EXCEPTION_METHOD_CNTR0019E" varFormat="Java">
    NON_APPLICATION_EXCEPTION_METHOD_CNTR0019E=CNTR0019E: EJB threw an unexpected (non-declared) exception during invocation of method &quot;{1}&quot;. Exception data: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An exception, which is not declared on the EJB method signature, was created when the EJB container attempted to invoke this EJB method.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the stack trace to determine the origin of the exception.  If the exception originates from customer-written code, correct the cause of the exception. If not, visit the IBM support Web site for information on problem determination.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0185E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_BEAN_TYPE_FOR_ASYNCH_METHOD_CNTR0185E" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_BEAN_TYPE_FOR_ASYNCH_METHOD_CNTR0185E=CNTR0185E: The {0} bean in the {1} module of the {2} application has one or more asynchronous methods configured, but is not a session bean.  Asynchronous methods can only be configured on session beans.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    You can configure asynchronous methods on session beans only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Remove the asynchronous method from the bean.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR9250E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="FIRST_PARAM_ERROR_CNTR9250E" varFormat="Java">
    FIRST_PARAM_ERROR_CNTR9250E=CNTR9250E: The first parameter must be a fully qualified class name, Java archive (JAR)file, Web archive (WAR)file, or enterprise archive (EAR) file.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The first parameter must be a fully qualified class name, a JAR file, a WAR file, or an EAR file.  JAR, WAR, and EAR files must include the complete directory path.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Invoke the createEJBStubs command with the -help option to view the command syntax.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0202E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_APPLICATION_EXCEPTION_FOR_VOID_ASYNCH_METHOD_CNTR0202E" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_APPLICATION_EXCEPTION_FOR_VOID_ASYNCH_METHOD_CNTR0202E=CNTR0202E: The {0} asynchronous method on the {1} bean has a return type of void and has the {2} application exception(s) on its throws clause.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The method was configured to be asynchronous through the @Asynchronous annotation or the asynch-method element in the ejb-jar.xml file.  Asynchronous methods with a void return type must not have application exceptions on the throws clause.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Change the return type of method, remove the application exception from the throws clause, or change the metadata for the method so that it is not asynchronous.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR9102E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CNTR9102E" varFormat="Java">
    CNTR9102E=CNTR9102E: Option {0} requires option {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    One of the options that is specified requires another option that has not been specified.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the usage statement, and specify the required option.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0089E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_TX_ATTR_CNTR0089E" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_TX_ATTR_CNTR0089E=CNTR0089E: Transaction attribute {0} is not allowed for method &quot;{1}&quot; on EJB {2}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The enterprise Java bean (EJB) Specification does not allow the transaction attribute that is configured for the EJB method. See the EJB Specification for further details.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Change the deployment descriptor to specify a transaction attribute that is allowed for the EJB method.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0136E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="IMPROPER_LOCAL_JNDI_BINDING_PREFIX_CNTR0136E" varFormat="Java">
    IMPROPER_LOCAL_JNDI_BINDING_PREFIX_CNTR0136E=CNTR0136E: The specific Java Naming and Directory Interface (JNDI) binding name provided for a local home or bean does not begin with ejblocal:. The {2} local binding name that is specified for the home or {0} bean in the {1} module does not begin with ejblocal:.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The local binding name for the specified bean or home does not begin with ejblocal:.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the local binding name for the bean or home in the specified module.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0085E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="NO_SUCH_MDB_METHOD_CNTR0085E" varFormat="Java">
    NO_SUCH_MDB_METHOD_CNTR0085E=CNTR0085E: MDB {0} must implement method {1} of interface {2}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The resource adapter is calling a method that is not implemented by the message-driven bean (MDB).
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Determine if the MDB was deployed to use the correct resource adapter. If the bean is bound to the correct resource adapter, change the MDB to provide an implementation for the method.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR5011E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="JIT_INTERFACE_NOT_INTERFACE_CNTR5011E" varFormat="Java">
    JIT_INTERFACE_NOT_INTERFACE_CNTR5011E=CNTR5011E: The {1} class has been configured as a business or component interface for the {0} bean. However, the class is not an interface.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    According to the Enterprise JavaBeans (EJB) specification, the configured business and component interfaces must be Java interfaces.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Change the bean configuration to provide Java interfaces.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR9101E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CNTR9101E" varFormat="Java">
    CNTR9101E=CNTR9101E: Incompatible options: {0} {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Two of the options that are specified are not compatible and cannot be specified together.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the usage statement, and remove one of the specified options.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0167I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="JNDI_BINDING_LOCATION_INFO_CNTR0167I" varFormat="Java">
    JNDI_BINDING_LOCATION_INFO_CNTR0167I=CNTR0167I: The server is binding the {0} interface of the {1} enterprise bean in the {2} module of the {3} application.  The binding location is: {4}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The interface has been bound at the specified naming location.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Use the specified naming location when attempting to look up this interface.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR5021E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="JIT_MISSING_CREATE_EX_CNTR5021E" varFormat="Java">
    JIT_MISSING_CREATE_EX_CNTR5021E=CNTR5021E: The {2} method of the {1} interface, which has been configured as a home interface for the {0} bean, does not define the javax.ejb.CreateException exception on the throws clause.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    According to the Enterprise JavaBeans (EJB) specification, the throws clause of all create methods on a home interface must contain the javax.ejb.CreateException exception.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Change the create methods on the home interface to throw javax.ejb.CreateException.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0049E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="COMMIT_OPTION_A_AND_OPTIMISTIC_CONCURRENCY_CONTROL_NOT_SUPPORTED_CNTR0049E" varFormat="Java">
    COMMIT_OPTION_A_AND_OPTIMISTIC_CONCURRENCY_CONTROL_NOT_SUPPORTED_CNTR0049E=CNTR0049E: Bean is attempting to use an invalid combination of Commit Option A and Optimistic Concurrency.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The user has specified Commit Option A and Optimistic Concurrency Control on an enterprise bean.  The Application Server does not support both Commit Option A and Optimistic Concurrency Control on an enterprise bean.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Change the enterprise bean to use either Commit Option A or Optimistic Concurrency Control, but not both.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0054W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="EXCEPTION_THROWN_BY_DISCARD_STRATEGY_CNTR0054W" varFormat="Java">
    EXCEPTION_THROWN_BY_DISCARD_STRATEGY_CNTR0054W=CNTR0054W: Exception thrown by discard strategy {0} {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This exception is unexpected. The cause is not immediately known.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR9100E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CNTR9100E" varFormat="Java">
    CNTR9100E=CNTR9100E: Exception {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A general exception condition has been discovered.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Combine this information with additional exception messages to perform additional problem determination.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0161E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="TIMEOUT_ANNOTATION_OVERSPECIFIED_CNTR0161E" varFormat="Java">
    TIMEOUT_ANNOTATION_OVERSPECIFIED_CNTR0161E=CNTR0161E: The {0} enterprise bean in the {1} module has specified the @Timeout annotation on more than one method.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Timer beans may only implement a single timeout method.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the bean implementation to include only one timeout method.   Then, reinstall the application.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0128I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="POOLSIZE_VALUES_CNTR0128I" varFormat="Java">
    POOLSIZE_VALUES_CNTR0128I=CNTR0128I: (Min,Max,Timeout) pool size is ({0},{1},{2}) for bean {3}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    These are the minimum pool size, maximum pool size, and maximum pool size timeout values that will be used for this bean type.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    There is no user action required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0176E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WS_ENDPOINT_PROVIDER_CONFLICT_CNTR0176E" varFormat="Java">
    WS_ENDPOINT_PROVIDER_CONFLICT_CNTR0176E=CNTR0176E: Web service Provider interface conflicts with the configured Web service endpoint interface {0} for the {1} bean in the {2} module of the {3} application.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This exception is unexpected. The cause is not immediately known.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0044W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_LOAD_POLICY_CNTR0044W" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_LOAD_POLICY_CNTR0044W=CNTR0044W: Bean &quot;{0}&quot; is attempting to use an invalid combination of Activation Policy: Transaction and Load Policy : Activation. Defaulting Load Policy to : Transaction.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The activation policy specified for the enterprise bean is not supported.  Option C, which is the default action taken, might not be the desired result. The combination of the Activation Policy and the Load Policy is the method in which the Application Server implements commit options A, B, and C in the Enterprise Java Bean (EJB) specification.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Redeploy the enterprise bean using a combination of valid settings to eliminate this message.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0088E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_TIMEDOBJECT_IMPL_CNTR0088E" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_TIMEDOBJECT_IMPL_CNTR0088E=CNTR0088E: The user-provided class &quot;{0}&quot; may not implement the javax.ejb.TimedObject interface.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Enterprise Java bean (EJB) V1.x, V2.0, and Stateful Session beans cannot implement the javax.ejb.TimedObject interface.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Change the EJB deployment to V2.1 or greater, change the implementation to not implement the javax.ejb.TimedObject interface, or change the EJB type.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0310W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="STATEFUL_TIMEOUT_ON_NON_SFSB_CNTR0310W" varFormat="Java">
    STATEFUL_TIMEOUT_ON_NON_SFSB_CNTR0310W=CNTR0310W: The {0} Enterprise JavaBean (EJB) in the {1} module of the {2} application contains the stateful-timeout deployment descriptor element.  stateful-timeout applies only to stateful session beans.  The EJB container will ignore the stateful-timeout on this bean.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This element applies only to stateful session beans.  The Enterprise JavaBean (EJB) container will ignore the stateful-timeout on this bean.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Remove the stateful-timeout deployment descriptor element from the specified bean, or make the bean a stateful session bean.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0112E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MDB_MUST_IMPLEMENT_INTERFACE_CNTR0112E" varFormat="Java">
    MDB_MUST_IMPLEMENT_INTERFACE_CNTR0112E=CNTR0112E: The user-provided class &quot;{0}&quot; must implement the &quot;{1}&quot; interface.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The enterprise Java bean (EJB) specification requires that message-driven beans implement the message listener interface for the messaging type that it supports.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Change the class so that it implements the interface, as required by EJB specification.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0306W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="STATEFUL_TIMEOUT_ON_INTERFACE_CNTR0306W" varFormat="Java">
    STATEFUL_TIMEOUT_ON_INTERFACE_CNTR0306W=CNTR0306W: The {0} business interface contains the @StatefulTimeout annotation.  This annotation is not valid on interface types, and the Enterprise JavaBean (EJB) container ignores it.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The @StatefulTimeout annotation is only applicable on bean classes, not business interfaces.  The EJB container ignores this annotations on interfaces.  Unless this annotation is specified on the bean class or a bean class method, or if the bean declares a stateful-timeout in the ejb-jar.xml deployment descriptor, the bean will use a default timeout value.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Remove the @StatefulTimeout annotation from the specified business interface, and verify that the annotations are specified correctly in the bean class.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0170E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="EJB_NO_TYPE_DEFINED_CNTR0170E" varFormat="Java">
    EJB_NO_TYPE_DEFINED_CNTR0170E=CNTR0170E: The {0} enterprise bean in the {1} module does not have a defined bean type.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Each enterprise bean must specify a bean type such as stateless session bean, message driven bean, and so on.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the Java source code annotation or the ejb-jar.xml configuration setting for this bean. Then, reinstall the application.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0236E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INIT_METHOD_NOT_FOUND_CNTR0236E" varFormat="Java">
    INIT_METHOD_NOT_FOUND_CNTR0236E=CNTR0236E: The {1} enterprise bean has an init-method element, which specifies the {0} method. This method is not a public method of this bean.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The init-method element specifies a method name that is not a public method of the enterprise bean class.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct either the method name or the method signature in the init-method element to specify a public method of this bean.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR5100E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="JIT_INVALID_ARG_RETURN_TYPE_CNTR5100E" varFormat="Java">
    JIT_INVALID_ARG_RETURN_TYPE_CNTR5100E=CNTR5100E: The {0} argument or return type of the {1} method on the {2} interface is not a valid type for Remote Method Invocation over the Internet Inter-ORB Protocol (RMI/IIOP).
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    According to the Enterprise JavaBeans (EJB) specification, the arguments and return types of all EJB remote business methods must be a valid type for RMI/IIOP.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Change the application method to only use valid types for RMI/IIOP. Also, you can change the application to not use the interface as an EJB remote interface.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0308W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="STATEFUL_TIMEOUT_WITHOUT_TIMEOUT_CNTR0308W" varFormat="Java">
    STATEFUL_TIMEOUT_WITHOUT_TIMEOUT_CNTR0308W=CNTR0308W: The {0} Enterprise JavaBean (EJB) in the {1} module of the {2} application contains the stateful-timeout deployment descriptor element, but is missing the required timeout element.  The Enterprise JavaBean (EJB) container will compute a default value.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The timeout value is required to be specified on the stateful-timeout deployment descriptor element.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Add a timeout value to the stateful-timeout deployment descriptor element for the specified bean.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0120W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_BOOLEAN_FORMAT_CNTR0120W" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_BOOLEAN_FORMAT_CNTR0120W=CNTR0120W: EJB java:comp/env context environment entry {0} of type Boolean, not set to a valid boolean value: {1}. Entry assigned a value of &quot;false&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An enterprise Java bean (EJB) java:comp/env context environment entry of the type Boolean should be assigned a value of  &apos;true&apos; or &apos;false&apos;.  Any other value will result in &apos;false&apos;, but it might be an indication of a problem in the configuration.  The application might not behave as expected.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Change the EJB java:comp/env context environment entry of type Boolean to either &apos;true&apos; or &apos;false&apos;.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0025W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="IOEXCEPTION_WRITING_FILE_FOR_STATEFUL_SESSION_BEAN_CNTR0025W" varFormat="Java">
    IOEXCEPTION_WRITING_FILE_FOR_STATEFUL_SESSION_BEAN_CNTR0025W=CNTR0025W: Unable to open output stream: {0} {1} {2}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The container encountered an IOException while attempting to write a file for a stateful session bean.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See the message in the IOException to determine the action to take. Ensure that the proper file permissions are set for the file.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0095W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MISSING_MODULE_DRSSETTINGS_CNTR0095W" varFormat="Java">
    MISSING_MODULE_DRSSETTINGS_CNTR0095W=CNTR0095W: EJB module configuration for session bean &quot;{0}&quot; is missing override of memory-to-memory replication settings.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The session bean is configured to override the settings for memory-to-memory replication at the enterprise Java bean (EJB) module level, but no settings for memory-to-memory replication are provided at the EJB module level.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Disable the override at the EJB module level, or provide the settings for memory-to-memory replication for this session bean.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0141E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="JNDI_BINDING_HAS_NO_CORRESPONDING_HOME_INTERFACE_CLASS_CNTR0141E" varFormat="Java">
    JNDI_BINDING_HAS_NO_CORRESPONDING_HOME_INTERFACE_CLASS_CNTR0141E=CNTR0141E: The {0} bean in the {1} module has specified a home Java Naming and Directory Interface (JNDI) binding. The binding does not have a matching home interface class.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Each home JNDI binding must have a matching home interface class configured.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the ejb-jar.xml file or source code annotations to configure a valid home interface class.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0207E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="AUTOMATIC_TIMER_ON_STATEFUL_SESSION_CNTR0207E" varFormat="Java">
    AUTOMATIC_TIMER_ON_STATEFUL_SESSION_CNTR0207E=CNTR0207E: The {0} stateful session bean in the {1} module has an automatic timer.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    You cannot specify automatic timers for stateful session beans.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Remove the automatic timer, or change the bean type.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0033E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="IGNORING_UNEXPECTED_EXCEPTION_CNTR0033E" varFormat="Java">
    IGNORING_UNEXPECTED_EXCEPTION_CNTR0033E=CNTR0033E: EJB container ignoring caught unexpected exception: {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This exception is unexpected. The cause is not immediately known.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0106E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SFB_CONTROLLER_NOPROXY_CNTR0106E" varFormat="Java">
    SFB_CONTROLLER_NOPROXY_CNTR0106E=CNTR0106E: Method {0}  cannot acquire proxy for stoken = {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The method that is specified was not able to obtain a proxy for processing the servant token.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    There is no user action required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0023W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PASSIVATION_DIRECTORY_DOES_NOT_EXIST_CNTR0023W" varFormat="Java">
    PASSIVATION_DIRECTORY_DOES_NOT_EXIST_CNTR0023W=CNTR0023W: Directory &quot;{0}&quot; does not exist. The EJB Container will use the current directory for passivating beans.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The container failed to open the passivation directory.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that the passivation directory exists.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0011W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_TYPE_IN_JAVA_COMP_ENV_CNTR0011W" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_TYPE_IN_JAVA_COMP_ENV_CNTR0011W=CNTR0011W: An invalid type was specified for a bean&apos;&apos;s java:comp/env context environment entry: &lt;env-entry-name&gt; {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The container encountered a type for an environment entry that is not valid.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that the environment entry type is one of : String, Integer, Boolean, Double, Byte, Short, Long or Float.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0253W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="UNABLE_TO_FIND_REMOVE_BINARIES_TASK_CNTR0253W" varFormat="Java">
    UNABLE_TO_FIND_REMOVE_BINARIES_TASK_CNTR0253W=CNTR0253W: Unable to find the RemoveBinaries task.  As a result, if automatically created EJB timers exist, they are not removed.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Use the removeAutomaticEJBTimers command to manually remove any automatic Enterprise Java Bean timers that are no longer valid.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    The processing to remove any automatic Enterprise Java Bean timers is triggered by another internal process, called RemoveBinaries, which was not found.  As a result, the processing to remove automatic Enterprise Java Bean timers did not run.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR5009E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="JIT_MISSING_ENTITYBEAN_CNTR5009E" varFormat="Java">
    JIT_MISSING_ENTITYBEAN_CNTR5009E=CNTR5009E: The {1} bean class for the {0} entity bean does not implement the javax.ejb.EntityBean class.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    According to the Enterprise JavaBeans (EJB) specification, the entity bean class must implement the javax.ejb.EntityBean class.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Change the bean class to implement the javax.ejb.EntityBean class.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0166E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="TIMEOUT_METHOD_STATIC_OR_FINAL_CNTR0166E" varFormat="Java">
    TIMEOUT_METHOD_STATIC_OR_FINAL_CNTR0166E=CNTR0166E: The {0} enterprise bean in the {1} module implements a {2} timeout method, which is declared as static or final.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Timeout methods must not be declared as static or final.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the implementation declaration for the timeout method. Then, reinstall the application.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0048W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="FINDER_COLLECTION_SCOPE_TIMEOUT_NO_TIMEOUT_CNTR0048W" varFormat="Java">
    FINDER_COLLECTION_SCOPE_TIMEOUT_NO_TIMEOUT_CNTR0048W=CNTR0048W: Bean&apos;&apos;s finder method &quot;{0}&quot; erroneously specifies a finder collection timeout scope of zero.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The finder method has a finder collection timeout scope specified, but the value is set to zero.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Provide a value that is not zero, if a finder collection timeout scope is desired.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0133E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_ENTITY_BEAN_INTERFACE_SPECIFIED_CNTR0133E" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_ENTITY_BEAN_INTERFACE_SPECIFIED_CNTR0133E=CNTR0133E: The {0} entity bean in the {1} module has an interface configured for a business, message listener, or Web service endpoint.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Entity beans cannot have any of these interface types configured.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the ejb-jar.xml file or source code annotation configuration settings for this bean.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR9263E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CLASS_PARM_LOAD_ERROR_CNTR9263E" varFormat="Java">
    CLASS_PARM_LOAD_ERROR_CNTR9263E=CNTR9263E: The {0} interface class could not be processed.  
The {1} method parameter class was not found.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A method parameter or a method return value class of the listed class could not be loaded.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check to make sure that all classes passed as method parameters, or used as method return values, on methods of the listed class are included in the input Java achive (JAR) file or enterprise archive (EAR) file, or are made available using the -cp option.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR5014E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="JIT_MUST_EXTEND_EJBLOCAL_CNTR5014E" varFormat="Java">
    JIT_MUST_EXTEND_EJBLOCAL_CNTR5014E=CNTR5014E: The {1} interface, which has been configured as the local component interface for the {0} bean, must extend the javax.ejb.EJBLocalObject interface.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    According to the Enterprise JavaBeans (EJB) specification, the configured local component interface must extend the javax.ejb.EJBLocalObject interface.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Change the interface to extend the javax.ejb.EJBLocalObject interface. Also, you can change the bean configuration to not specify the interface as a local component interface.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0209E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_TIMEOUT_CALLBACK_SIGNATURE_CNTR0209E" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_TIMEOUT_CALLBACK_SIGNATURE_CNTR0209E=CNTR0209E: The {0} enterprise bean in the {1} module has the {2} timeout callback method that does not have the required method signature.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Enterprise JavaBeans specification requires that timeout callback methods have the following signature: void &amp;lt;METHOD&amp;gt;() or void &amp;lt;METHOD&amp;gt;(Timer timer)
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the timeout callback method signature for this bean class.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR5022E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="JIT_INVALID_SL_HOME_METHOD_CNTR5022E" varFormat="Java">
    JIT_INVALID_SL_HOME_METHOD_CNTR5022E=CNTR5022E: The {1} home interface for the {0} bean has too many methods. The {2} method is not allowed.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    According to the Enterprise JavaBeans (EJB) specification, a home interface for a stateless session bean must have only one method. The method must be the create method.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Remove the method from the home interface.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0318E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MISSING_EJB_CLASS_ELEMENT_CNTR0318E" varFormat="Java">
    MISSING_EJB_CLASS_ELEMENT_CNTR0318E=CNTR0318E: No ejb-class element was specified for the {0} bean, in the {1} module, of the {2} application.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    When declaring an Enterprise JavaBean in the ejb-jar.xml file, users must provide a class name for the bean.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Modify the ejb-jar.xml file or application source code and re-install the application.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR5105E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="JIT_DUPLICATE_PROPERTY_METHODS_CNTR5105E" varFormat="Java">
    JIT_DUPLICATE_PROPERTY_METHODS_CNTR5105E=CNTR5105E: The {0} interface is not a valid remote interface. The IDL name for the {1} method conflicts with the {2} method.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    For remote interfaces, the Java Language to IDL Mapping specification states the following information:
 Methods that follow the JavaBeans design patterns for simple read-write properties or simple read-only properties are mapped to OMG IDL interface attributes. Both specified methods map to the same OMG IDL interface attribute. The interface is not a valid RMI/IIOP type.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Change the application by either renaming or removing one of the conflicting methods.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR9268E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="NEWFILE_NAME_NOT_ALLOWED_CNTR9268E" varFormat="Java">
    NEWFILE_NAME_NOT_ALLOWED_CNTR9268E=CNTR9268E: The {0} file name is not allowed for the -newfile option.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The name specified for the -newfile option is not allowed.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure the name is not the same as the input file.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0053W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="LRU_THREAD_CAUGHT_EXCEPTION_CNTR0053W" varFormat="Java">
    LRU_THREAD_CAUGHT_EXCEPTION_CNTR0053W=CNTR0053W: Caught an exception during LRU sweep {0} {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This exception is unexpected. The cause is not immediately known.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0305W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ASYNC_ON_INTERFACE_CNTR0305W" varFormat="Java">
    ASYNC_ON_INTERFACE_CNTR0305W=CNTR0305W: The {0} business interface contains an @Asynchronous annotation.  These annotations are not valid on interface types, and the Enterprise JavaBean (EJB) container ignores them.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The @Asynchronous annotation is only applicable on bean classes, not business interfaces.  The EJB container ignores these annotations on the interfaces.  Unless this annotation is specified on the bean class or a bean class method, or if the methods are declared asynchronous in the ejb-jar.xml deployment descriptor, the bean methods will run synchronously.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Remove any @Asynchronous annotation from the specified business interface, and verify that the annotations are specified correctly in the bean class.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0138E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="BLANK_JNDI_BINDING_NAME_CNTR0138E" varFormat="Java">
    BLANK_JNDI_BINDING_NAME_CNTR0138E=CNTR0138E: The {0} bean or home in the {1} module contains a blank string value for the Java Naming and Directory Interface (JNDI) binding name.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    JNDI binding names must not contain blank strings.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the ejb-jar-bnd.xml bindings file to give this bean a valid JNDI binding name.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0050E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PROTOCOL_ERROR_IN_CONTAINER_TRANSACTION_CNTR0050E" varFormat="Java">
    PROTOCOL_ERROR_IN_CONTAINER_TRANSACTION_CNTR0050E=CNTR0050E: Protocol error occurred in container transaction.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This exception is unexpected. The cause is not immediately known.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0005W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="UNABLE_TO_PASSIVATE_EJB_CNTR0005W" varFormat="Java">
    UNABLE_TO_PASSIVATE_EJB_CNTR0005W=CNTR0005W: An enterprise bean could not be passivated: {0} {1} {2}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The container was unable to passivate an enterprise bean.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Take action based upon the exception message in message CNTR0005W.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR9413E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CNTR9413E_CONFIG_READ_FAIL" varFormat="Java">
    CNTR9413E_CONFIG_READ_FAIL=CNTR9413E: Failed to read in the configuration file from {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The embeddable Enterprise JavaBeans (EJB) container failed to read the configuration properties from the specified file.  This can occur if the file is not a properly formed properties file.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the specified file exists on the file system and that it is a well formed properties file (i.e. &lt;property_name&gt;=&lt;property_value&gt;).
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0178E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WS_ENDPOINT_METHOD_MISSING_CNTR0178E" varFormat="Java">
    WS_ENDPOINT_METHOD_MISSING_CNTR0178E=CNTR0178E: Configured Web service endpoint method {0} is not implemented by the {1} bean in the {2} module of the {3} application.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    All configured Web service endpoint methods must be implemented by the bean.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Change bean implementation to include all Web service endpoint methods.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR5008E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="JIT_INVALID_FINALIZE_MTHD_CNTR5008E" varFormat="Java">
    JIT_INVALID_FINALIZE_MTHD_CNTR5008E=CNTR5008E: The {1} bean class for the {0} bean has defined the finalize method.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    According to the Enterprise JavaBeans (EJB) specification, the bean class must not define the finalize method.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Do not define the finalize method in the bean class.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0040E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="FINDER_CAUGHT_EXCEPTION_CNTR0040E" varFormat="Java">
    FINDER_CAUGHT_EXCEPTION_CNTR0040E=CNTR0040E: Finder failure as a result of exception {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This exception is unexpected. The cause is not immediately known.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0110E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SFB_CONTROLLER_VALUEBYTES_CNTR0110E" varFormat="Java">
    SFB_CONTROLLER_VALUEBYTES_CNTR0110E=CNTR0110E: Method {0}  cannot convert value to byte array.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The method that is specified was not able to convert the passed entryKey value to a byte array.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    There is no user action required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0229E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_INTERCEPTOR_METHOD_MODIFIER_CNTR0229E" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_INTERCEPTOR_METHOD_MODIFIER_CNTR0229E=CNTR0229E: The {0} interceptor method must not be declared as final or static.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Enterprise JavaBeans 3.0 specification does not allow an interceptor method to be final or static.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Remove the final or static modifier from this interceptor method.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0058W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_MAX_POOLSIZE_CNTR0058W" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_MAX_POOLSIZE_CNTR0058W=CNTR0058W: Maximum pool size specified for bean {0} not a valid integer: {1}. Default used instead.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Only a positive integer can be specified for the maximum pool size.  The default value will be used.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Change the value of the maximum pool size to a positive integer.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR0118I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="LIGHTWEIGHT_ENABLED_CNTR0118I" varFormat="Java">
    LIGHTWEIGHT_ENABLED_CNTR0118I=CNTR0118I: Container pre- and post-method processing for all local and local home methods will be bypassed on bean: &quot;{0}&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The bean has been configured to streamline the processing that occurs before and after calling the methods that are defined on the local home interface and local business interface. This behavior is not compliant with the enterprise Java bean (EJB) V2.0 and later specifications, but it can improve performance.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    There is no user action required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR5006E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="JIT_NOT_TOP_LEVEL_CLASS_CNTR5006E" varFormat="Java">
    JIT_NOT_TOP_LEVEL_CLASS_CNTR5006E=CNTR5006E: The {1} bean class for the {0} bean is not defined as a top level class.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    According to the Enterprise JavaBeans (EJB) specification, the bean class must be defined as a top level class.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Define the bean class as a top level class.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CNTR9258E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="UNEXPECTED_EXCEPTION_CNTR9258E" varFormat="Java">
    UNEXPECTED_EXCEPTION_CNTR9258E=CNTR9258E: An unexpected exception was caught.  The exception is: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An unexpected exception occurred during command processing.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Add the -verbose option to the createEJBStubs command invocation see more information.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<!-- END MESSAGES -->
</TMSSource>
