<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/css" href="../../resources/stylesheets/wasmsgxml.css"?>
<TMSSource name="TivoliMessages" tmsVersion="1.0" xml:lang="en">
<!-- CMVC MSG File Name = ws/code/proxy.impl/src/com/ibm/ws/proxy/channel/resources/channel.nlsprops -->
<!-- DO NOT EDIT THIS FILE - This file was generated by the XML/Html & Property emitter -->
<!-- BEGIN MESSAGES -->
<Message ID="PROX0109W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PROX0109W" varFormat="Java">
    PROX0109W=PROX0109W: The trusted security proxy host name/ip address {0} created an exception.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The proxy server received an exception when converting the text host name or ip address to an InetAddress object.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Configure the proxy server to use trusted security proxies by adding hostnames or ip addresses. Separate multiple entries on one line with a space or comma.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="PROX0111I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PROX0111I" varFormat="Java">
    PROX0111I=PROX0111I: The Proxy Server will retry socket connection to target {0}. Retry count {1}, retry limit {2}. An attempt to establish a socket connection failed with exception {3}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The http.connectRetryLimit custom property is used to configure the Proxy Server to retry failed socket connections.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required unless you want to disable the configuration setting.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="PROX0107W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PROX0107W" varFormat="Java">
    PROX0107W=PROX0107W: The proxy-environment.xml file in the cell-scope could not be located.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This configuration document contains the cell-wide definitions for the proxy server configuration. The file is missing or corrupted. This warning message could be ignored if generic server routing rules are not defined.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Review the proxy server creation. Contact the vendor if the configuration has not been customized.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="PROX0101I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PROX0101I" varFormat="Java">
    PROX0101I=PROX0101I: Proxy Server being started as {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The proxy server has started with the specified deployment type specified
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required for this type of message
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="PROX0108W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PROX0108W" varFormat="Java">
    PROX0108W=PROX0108W: The proxy-settings.xml file in the cluster/server-scope could not be located.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This configuration document contains the cluster and server definitions for the proxy server configuration. The file is missing or corrupted.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Review the proxy server creation. Contact the vendor if the configuration has not been customized.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="PROX0110I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PROX0110I" varFormat="Java">
    PROX0110I=PROX0110I: The server at {0} is a trusted security proxy.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Proxy Server is configured to recognize the identified server as a trusted intermediary. Special request headers received from that server will be forwarded to the application server.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="PROX0102I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PROX0102I" varFormat="Java">
    PROX0102I=PROX0102I: The proxy channel chains {0} have been started.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The channel chains that are identified by channel chain group have been started. The proxy server will receive requests on the associated ports.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required for this type of message
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<!-- END MESSAGES -->
</TMSSource>
