<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/css" href="../../resources/stylesheets/wasmsgxml.css"?>
<TMSSource name="TivoliMessages" tmsVersion="1.0" xml:lang="en">
<!-- CMVC MSG File Name = ws/code/wsba.impl/src/com/ibm/ws/wsba/resources/WSBAMessages.nlsprops -->
<!-- DO NOT EDIT THIS FILE - This file was generated by the XML/Html & Property emitter -->
<!-- BEGIN MESSAGES -->
<Message ID="CWWSB0004I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INF_CH_CHFE" varFormat="Java">
    INF_CH_CHFE=CWWSB0004I: A CompensationHandlerFailedException was caught from the compensation handler, {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The compensation handler threw a CompensationHanderFailedException and will not be retried.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action required. This message is for informational purposes only.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWSB0002E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ERR_CH_MISSING" varFormat="Java">
    ERR_CH_MISSING=CWWSB0002E: The user defined compensation hander class could not be found, {0}. Exception details follow: {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An error occurred trying to locate and create the user-defined compensation handler class. This class must exist and be available to the application.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that the specified class name is the fully qualified class name of the compensation hander and that the class name is on the application class path.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWSB0003E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ERR_CH_INTERFACE" varFormat="Java">
    ERR_CH_INTERFACE=CWWSB0003E: The user defined compensation handler, {0}, does not implement the {1} interface.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The user-defined compensation handler class must implement the appropriate CompensationHandler interface for it to be added to the Business Activity.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure the user-defined compensation handler class implements the appropriate CompensationHandler interface and that the corresponding UserBusinessActivity method is used to set the compensation data.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWSB0005E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ERR_CH_NULL" varFormat="Java">
    ERR_CH_NULL=CWWSB0005E: The compensation handler class name has not been specified on the application component.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    If an application component does not specify a compensation handler class name, it is not permitted to call the setCompensationDataImmediate() or setCompensationDataAtCommit() methods.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure the compensation handler class name is specified on your application component.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWSB0001E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ERR_WSBA_DISABLED" varFormat="Java">
    ERR_WSBA_DISABLED=CWWSB0001E: WS-BA has not been enabled.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    When the WS-BA function is disabled the application cannot make WS-BA API calls.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure the WS-BA functionality has been enabled on the application component.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<!-- END MESSAGES -->
</TMSSource>
