<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/css" href="../../resources/stylesheets/wasmsgxml.css"?>
<TMSSource name="TivoliMessages" tmsVersion="1.0" xml:lang="en">
<!-- CMVC MSG File Name = ws/code/migration/src/com/ibm/websphere/migration/WASUpgrade.nlsprops -->
<!-- DO NOT EDIT THIS FILE - This file was generated by the XML/Html & Property emitter -->
<!-- BEGIN MESSAGES -->
<Message ID="MIGR0493E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="profile.name.mismatch" varFormat="Java">
    profile.name.mismatch=MIGR0493E: The profile name {0} does not match the target profile {1}, the profile names must match for this migration.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This migration requires that the profile names match between the old and new releases.  A mismatch has been detected and migration cannot continue until the issue is resolved.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Create a new profile that matches the name of the source profile, and rerun migration with this matching profile as the target.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0478E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="port.value.missing.from.serverindex" varFormat="Java">
    port.value.missing.from.serverindex=MIGR0478E: The port value for the endpoint {0} in of the server {1} is invalid or missing.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Invalid port information exist for the specified entry.  This information is required for migration processing.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the port information for the specified server in the serverindex in the master repository (which resides on the Deployment Manager in distributed configurations), and then rerun migration.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0349E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.repository.locked" varFormat="Java">
    advise.repository.locked=MIGR0349E: The migration function cannot access the configuration directory.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Another Application Server process has a lock on the configuration directory.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Close any running Application Server processes, and run migration again.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0527I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.migrate.javasecurity" varFormat="Java">
    advise.migrate.javasecurity=MIGR0527I: The java.security file was migrated. Review the contents of the file to ensure the desired behavior. Additional changes may be needed.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The WASPostUpgrade process migrated the java.security file. The settings should be reviewed for correctness.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify and manually modify the java.security file for the target profile as needed.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0538W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.circular.variable.reference.found.in.path" varFormat="Java">
    advise.circular.variable.reference.found.in.path=MIGR0538W: Could not process the {0} path {1}, as it might contain a variable which resolves to a circular reference.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A variable being used in the path could not be resolved because a circular reference was detected.  Variable A references variable B which references variable A.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check to see if each variable being used in the path can be fully resolved without referencing itself.  Correct the variable causing the issue, or change the path to not reference the variable.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0900E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="client.usage.line1" varFormat="Java">
    client.usage.line1=MIGR0900E: The specified command is not valid.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This problem is usually caused by parameters that are misspelled or missing.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that all of the parameters are valid and spelled correctly. Type the command without parameters or arguments to get the correct syntax of the command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0497E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="invalid.backup.directory.location" varFormat="Java">
    invalid.backup.directory.location=MIGR0497E: The migration function cannot save files to the backup directory, it is an invalid location.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The directory specified does not pass validation to be used as a migration backup directory.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Select an empty directory outside of any WebSphere install directories that is on a filesystem with sufficient space.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0249E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.logging.update.error" varFormat="Java">
    advise.logging.update.error=MIGR0249E: An error occurred while updating the &lt;samp&gt;plugin-cfg.xml&lt;/samp&gt; file; exception {0} was caught. Run the GenPlugIncfg command manually.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An error occurred while calling the GenPlugInCfg command at the end of migration. The migration completed normally.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, see the problem determination information on the Application Server Support Web page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0341W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.appinstalldir.changed" varFormat="Java">
    advise.appinstalldir.changed=MIGR0341W: Application installation directory has been updated to {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified value application installation directory has been updated to use the common WebSphere variables
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required,
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0253E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.invalid.backup.notexist" varFormat="Java">
    advise.invalid.backup.notexist=MIGR0253E: The backup directory {0} does not exist.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The backup directory that was specified on the command line does not exist.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Rerun the command with a valid backup directory that was created by the WASPreUpgrade command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0434I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.logging.not.migrating.app" varFormat="Java">
    advise.logging.not.migrating.app=MIGR0434I: Will not be migrating object {0} of type {1}, it is already installed.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Applications that are already installed in the new profile will not be migrated.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0398E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.unsupported.wbi.resource" varFormat="Java">
    advise.unsupported.wbi.resource=MIGR0398E: An unsupported IBM WebSphere Business Integration Server Foundation resource is found in an application.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The application cannot be installed because the required supporting software is not available.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0285E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.unexpected.internal.error" varFormat="Java">
    advise.unexpected.internal.error=MIGR0285E: An unexpected internal error occurred with exception {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An unexpected error occurred.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, see the problem determination information on the Application Server Support Web page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0460E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="postupgrade.not.supported" varFormat="Java">
    postupgrade.not.supported=MIGR0460E: Application Server migration is not supported in this configuration.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This indicates that the specified backup cannot be migrated into this profile. Additional information can be found in other messages printed to the migration log files.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Resolve the issues causing the other failing messages, and then rerun the migration.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0310E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.invalid.value" varFormat="Java">
    advise.invalid.value=MIGR0310E: A value that is specified for {0} is not valid: {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified value is incorrect.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Consult the help text that is displayed with this message, and rerun the command with a correct value.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0615W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="warning.eol.sdk" varFormat="Java">
    warning.eol.sdk=MIGR0615W: Your target installation, WebSphere Application Server version {0}, is currently configured to use Java SE {1}.  Support for Java SE {1} ends in {2}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Support for this version of Java is coming to an end. No support will be provided for any WebSphere Application Server issues that continue to use this version of Java after its end of service date.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Update your current WebSphere Application Server installation with the latest Java SE version.  Update any existing servers to use the new Java SE version.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0910W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="client.usage.message14" varFormat="Java">
    client.usage.message14=MIGR0910W: No client Java archive (JAR) files are found.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The enterprise archive (EAR) file does not contain any client JAR files.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the specified EAR file is expected to contain client Java archive (JAR) files, correct the EAR file, and try the command again.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0909W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="client.usage.message13" varFormat="Java">
    client.usage.message13=MIGR0909W: No client Java archive (JAR) files are found by the name {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The enterprise archive (EAR) file does not contain any client Java archive (JAR) files by the specified name.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the EAR file contains the client JAR file that is specified.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0908W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="client.usage.message12" varFormat="Java">
    client.usage.message12=MIGR0908W: The enterprise archive (EAR) file name {0} is a directory.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified enterprise archive (EAR) file is a directory.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the specified EAR file is an EAR file and not a directory.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0907W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="client.usage.message11" varFormat="Java">
    client.usage.message11=MIGR0907W: The enterprise archive (EAR) file {0} does not exist.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Cannot find the specified EAR file in the given location.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the path is spelled correctly and that an EAR file exists in that location.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0483W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="empty.variable.greater.scope" varFormat="Java">
    empty.variable.greater.scope=MIGR0483W: Variable {0} at {1} scope has been defined with an emtpy value.  This variable has also been defined at a broader scope.  The broader scoped variable value will be hidden.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A variable has been redefined at a narrower scope which will override the broader scoped value.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Remove the offending variable from the narrower scope or replace the narrower scoped variables value with the broader scoped variables value.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0444W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.managed.node.cell.info.not.migrated" varFormat="Java">
    advise.managed.node.cell.info.not.migrated=MIGR0444W: Cell-level documents are not merged. Any changes that you make to the stand-alone cell-level documents before using the WASPostUpgrade command must be repeated on the new cell. For example, virtual hosts.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    During a managed node migration, any new  Version 7 configuration changes that existed prior to running WASPostUpgrade might need to be reapplied after the WASPostUpgrade process completes.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Reapply preexisting Version 7 cell level changes after the managed node migration has been completed.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0906W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="client.usage.message10" varFormat="Java">
    client.usage.message10=MIGR0906W: You must specify the enterprise archive (EAR) file location.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    No enterprise archive (EAR) file is specified.  This file name is the first argument that you pass in after the command. For example: clientUpgrade /ear/file/location/earfile.ear
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Rerun the command with an EAR file as the first argument.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0528E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.invalid.file" varFormat="Java">
    advise.invalid.file=MIGR0528E: Unable to read file {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The file cannot be read
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure the file exists in the backup directory and can be read. Run the WASPostUpgradeBLAHelper script after fixing the problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0344I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.processing.configuration.file" varFormat="Java">
    advise.processing.configuration.file=MIGR0344I: Processing configuration file {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Automated migration for the file is starting.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0214W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.logging.unable.to.copy.file" varFormat="Java">
    advise.logging.unable.to.copy.file=MIGR0214W: The migration function cannot copy the file. Source {0} does not exist.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An unexpected failure occurred when a configuration file was copied.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the source file must be used to create an enterprise application, use a development environment such as the Rational Application Developer to add the file to the appropriate location in the enterprise application.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0542W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.managedNodesIndeterminate.preupgrade.save" varFormat="Java">
    advise.managedNodesIndeterminate.preupgrade.save=MIGR0542W: A machine change migration has been detected. The previous deployment manager could not be contacted to determine whether there are resources registered with the associated job manager function. If there are registered resources, update the job manager URL for the registered resources after WASPostUpgrade.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A machine change migration has been detected. The previous deployment manager could not be contacted to determine whether there are resources registered with the associated job manager function. If there are registered resources, update the job manager URL for the registered resources after WASPostUpgrade.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If there are registered resources, update the job manager URL at these resources.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0123E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.import.object.failure" varFormat="Java">
    advise.import.object.failure=MIGR0123E: The migration function cannot import object {0} of type {1}, exception {2}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    During WASPostUpgrade processing, an error occurred while importing the specified object.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See the following errors in the migration log for further details. Correct the problem and rerun the command, or use the Application Server administrative interfaces to complete the configuration of the specified object.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0443E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.node.server.not.found.convertscriptcompatibility" varFormat="Java">
    advise.node.server.not.found.convertscriptcompatibility=MIGR0443E: {0} {1} does not exist, will not continue.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The node or server name specified does not exist.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Run the command again and specify existing node and server names.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0526W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.manually.migrate.javasecurity" varFormat="Java">
    advise.manually.migrate.javasecurity=MIGR0526W: The migration function cannot migrate the java.security file because the contents are not compatible between the source and target.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The WASPostUpgrade process cannot migrate the java.security file.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Manually modify the java.security file for the target profile as needed.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0121E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.unable.to.read.XML" varFormat="Java">
    advise.unable.to.read.XML=MIGR0121E: The migration function cannot read the import XML document {0}, exception {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An error occurred while reading the XML file to import during migration.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Rerun the command with a valid XML import file.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0402I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.transports.to.channels" varFormat="Java">
    advise.transports.to.channels=MIGR0402I: Existing transports are migrating into the transport channel service; see the information center for further information.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Transports are migrating to corresponding channels in the new release.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0284E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.unsupported.backup.version" varFormat="Java">
    advise.unsupported.backup.version=MIGR0284E: The version of WebSphere {0} in the specified backup directory cannot be migrated to profile {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified backup directory is created from an unsupported version of Application Server.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Rerun the migration command with a valid backup directory that was created by the WASPreUpgrade command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0104E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.cmd.line.currentWASDirectory" varFormat="Java">
    advise.cmd.line.currentWASDirectory=MIGR0104E: You must specify the currently installed Application Server directory name.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    You must access the currently installed Application Server directory to obtain the configuration information that is migrating to the new release.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Run the command again and specify the currently installed Application Server directory.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0440W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.application.failed.to.migrate" varFormat="Java">
    advise.application.failed.to.migrate=MIGR0440W: The migration of one or more applications terminated unexpectedly.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    During the application migration process, one or more applications failed to migrate.  Refer to the log files for details.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If possible, correct the problems that are recorded in the log files. One or more applications might need to be installed manually.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0571W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.library.path.not.resolved" varFormat="Java">
    advise.library.path.not.resolved=MIGR0571W: The library was not migrated because a variable in the following library path could not be resolved: {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The library path contains a variable that could not be resolved at the current scope.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Define the variable at a scope that can resolve the variable, or remove the variable from the path. You can edit the variable definition and library path in the administrative console or by using wsadmin scripting. For more information, see the documentation about editing variables, managing a shared library, and configuring a shared library using scripting.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0390E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.default.instance.missing" varFormat="Java">
    advise.default.instance.missing=MIGR0390E: The backup directory does not contain a default profile.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A default profile does not exist and the -oldProfile parameter was not specified.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Rerun the command with the correct profile name.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0430W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.failed.cloudscape.db.migration" varFormat="Java">
    advise.failed.cloudscape.db.migration=MIGR0430W: Cloudscape Database {0} failed to migrate to {1} Database.  See log {2}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The migration of Cloudscape to Derby has failed for this particular database.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Manual migration of the old dataBase to new database is required.  See the information center details.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0474I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="wasdd.migration.property" varFormat="Java">
    wasdd.migration.property=MIGR0474I: Do not remove this property until all Federated nodes have been migrated to v7.x and all application have been tested against the Microsoft driver.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This property is needed by XSL Transforms to down convert configuration data to pre v7.x Federated nodes.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Once all Federated nodes have been migrated to v7.x and all applications have been tested against the Microsoft driver you can then safely remove this property.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0302I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.information.preupgrade.save" varFormat="Java">
    advise.information.preupgrade.save=MIGR0302I: The existing files are being saved.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The files that you need to restore your configuration on the new release are being copied to the backup directory.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0283E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.error.reading.backup.options" varFormat="Java">
    advise.error.reading.backup.options=MIGR0283E: The migration function cannot read backup options file {0}, exception {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An unexpected error occurred while trying to read the specified file.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the user ID has sufficient file system authority to run the migration program. If the problem persists, see the problem determination information on the Application Server Support Web page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0576W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.library.target.dir.not.writable" varFormat="Java">
    advise.library.target.dir.not.writable=MIGR0576W: The library could not be copied to the following target directory: {0}. The following library was not migrated: {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The current user ID cannot write to the target directory.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the current user ID has permission to write to the specified directory. You must manually migrate the library to its new location and update the library path. You can edit the library path in the administrative console or by using wsadmin scripting. For more information, see the documentation about managing a shared library and configuring a shared library using scripting.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0108E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.invalid.WAS.directory" varFormat="Java">
    advise.invalid.WAS.directory=MIGR0108E: The directory {0} does not contain a WebSphere version that can be upgraded.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Migration support is provided for Application Server Version 5.1 and later.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If you are migrating to a supported release, verify that the directory name is correct and rerun the command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0429I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.successful.cloudscape.db.migration" varFormat="Java">
    advise.successful.cloudscape.db.migration=MIGR0429I: Cloudscape Database {0} was successfully migrated.  See log {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The migration of Cloudscape to Derby was successfully for this particular database.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0573W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.library.does.not.exist" varFormat="Java">
    advise.library.does.not.exist=MIGR0573W: The library was not copied because it was not found at the following path: {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The library path definition does not refer to a valid directory or file.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the library path is not correctly defined, remove the path or update it to a valid directory or file. Otherwise, you can leave the library path definition as is. You can edit the library path in the administrative console or by using wsadmin scripting. For more information, see the documentation about managing a shared library and configuring a shared library using scripting.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0227W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.logging.no.backup" varFormat="Java">
    advise.logging.no.backup=MIGR0227W: The migration function cannot make a backup copy of configuration file {0}; exception {1} occurred.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An unexpected failure occurred while copying a configuration file. Migration is expected to occur normally. A backup copy of the previous configuration file is not available.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the user ID has the appropriate file system authority to run the migration command. If the problem persists, see the problem determination information on the Application Server Support Web page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0488E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="dmgr.illegal.node.name" varFormat="Java">
    dmgr.illegal.node.name=MIGR0488E: The deployment manager node name in the new configuration ({0}) cannot be the same as a nodeagent node in the old configuration.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    While migrating a deployment manager node, the node names of the deployment manager in the new configuration must either be unique from all nodes in the old configuration or be identical to the deployment manager node name in the old release.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Create a new deployment manager profile in the new configuration where the node name for the deployment manager matches the node name from the old configuration.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0459I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="postupgrade.supported" varFormat="Java">
    postupgrade.supported=MIGR0459I: Application Server configuration files are being migration.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This indicates that a specific backup of Application Server files are being migrated into this configuration.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0403I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.transport.to.become.channel" varFormat="Java">
    advise.transport.to.become.channel=MIGR0403I: The transport with a port address of {0} is migrating to channel {1} and belongs to the {2} ThreadPool.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Each transport is migrated to a new channel and belongs to a new default thread pool.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0207W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.logging.unable.to.copy.is.directory" varFormat="Java">
    advise.logging.unable.to.copy.is.directory=MIGR0207W: The migration function cannot copy the directory {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The function cannot copy the directory. This problem might affect the migration.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the directory must be used to create an enterprise application, use a development environment like the Rational Application Developer to add the files from that directory to the appropriate location in the enterprise application.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0446I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.port.info" varFormat="Java">
    advise.port.info=MIGR0446I: Port conflicts were resolved during migration as shown below for document: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Application Server migration tooling updated the values of network ports. The resulting port values are listed for each file. All port settings for the document are listed even if they were unchanged.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    The Application Server migration tooling changed port settings to ensure that migrated values did not conflict with settings in the existing configuration. You can update the port settings using the administrative console or the wsadmin scripting interface as required by your environment.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0546E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.cell.rename.error" varFormat="Java">
    advise.cell.rename.error=MIGR0546E: The WebSphere Application Server migration function failed to rename the cell with the following message: {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    During the migration process a call was made to another WebSphere Application Server program, which failed to complete successfully.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, see the problem determination information on the Application Server Support Web page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0241I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.logging.capture.output" varFormat="Java">
    advise.logging.capture.output=MIGR0241I: Output of {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message follows another message in the log that shows a different program that is being called during migration. This message displays the results of that call.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0357W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.enterprise.extendedmessaging.disabled" varFormat="Java">
    advise.enterprise.extendedmessaging.disabled=MIGR0357W: The extended messaging service is disabled because the required IBM WebSphere Business Integration Server Foundation feature is not installed.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The IBM WebSphere Business Integration Server Foundation extended messaging feature must be installed to run the specified service.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Install the feature, and run the command again.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0570E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.profileRegistry.is.empty" varFormat="Java">
    advise.profileRegistry.is.empty=MIGR0570E: The profile registry in the following file does not contain any registered profiles: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The profile registry does not contain any registered profiles for the migration command to process. Either profiles have not been created in the source product release or the profileRegistry.xml file was corrupted.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If profiles do exist for the source product release, you must reconstruct the profileRegistry.xml file.  See the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support web page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0409E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.default.profile.missing" varFormat="Java">
    advise.default.profile.missing=MIGR0409E: The currently installed WebSphere does not contain a default profile.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A default profile does not exist and the correct profile parameter was not specified.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Rerun the command with the correct profile name.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0492W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="dmgr.soapport.changed.sync.required" varFormat="Java">
    dmgr.soapport.changed.sync.required=MIGR0492W: The SOAP port has changed from {0} to {1}, you must manually synchronize the managed nodes with the Deployment Manager.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Deployment Manager&apos;s SOAP_CONNECTOR_ADDRESS port number has been changed, in order for the managed nodes to communicate with the Deployment Manager, a manual synchronization must occur using new SOAP_CONNECTOR_ADDRESS port number.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Run syncNode from the effected Managed nodes using new SOAP_CONNECTOR_ADDRESS port number.  See the InfoCEnter for more information about executing syncNode manually with port information.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0407E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.name.parameter.not.found" varFormat="Java">
    advise.name.parameter.not.found=MIGR0407E: The {0} parameter {1} cannot be found in the profile.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The parameter was specified when running the command. The value that is specified cannot be found in the profile.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Run the command again with a correct value for the parameter.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0335I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.logging.updating.userreg" varFormat="Java">
    advise.logging.updating.userreg=MIGR0335I: Attributes of the {0} user registry are updating to reflect the information for server ID {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The attributes of the specified user registry are updated to reflect the information for the specified server ID.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0124E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.unable.read.xmlfile" varFormat="Java">
    advise.unable.read.xmlfile=MIGR0124E: The migration function cannot import XML data file {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An attempt to read the specified file failed.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the file exists, and rerun the command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0353E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.unable.configuration.create" varFormat="Java">
    advise.unable.configuration.create=MIGR0353E: The migration function cannot create configuration file {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The function cannot create the specified configuration file.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the WASPostUpgrade command has the necessary permissions to create files, and then try the command again.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0303I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.information.preupgrade.complete" varFormat="Java">
    advise.information.preupgrade.complete=MIGR0303I: The existing Application Server environment is saved.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The process of backing up your previous configuration is complete.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0331W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.port.inuse" varFormat="Java">
    advise.port.inuse=MIGR0331W: Port {0} in file {1} is migrated, but is already assigned in file {2}; this situation might result in port conflicts.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified port is already used in the reported file. The port assignment is migrated. The port assignment might cause a conflict if both ports are started at the same time.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Use the Application Server administrative interfaces to assign unique port values if necessary.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0537W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.could.not.resolve.variable.in.path" varFormat="Java">
    advise.could.not.resolve.variable.in.path=MIGR0537W: Could not process the {0} path {1}, as it contains an undefined variable.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A variable being used in the path could not be resolved using the defined variables.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check to see if the variable is being used for a valid reason.  If not, then no further action is required; if it is, then define the variable or adjust the path to not reference the variable.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0512E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.need.oldadminagent.info" varFormat="Java">
    advise.need.oldadminagent.info=MIGR0512E: Admin Agent information for the old release is invalid
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The admin agent profile path for the old release is invalid
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that the admin agent information for the old release is correct
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0419I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.migrating.usemetadatafrombinary.manual.intervention" varFormat="Java">
    advise.migrating.usemetadatafrombinary.manual.intervention=MIGR0419I: The -useMetaDataFromBinary attribute is set to false for application {0}.  The local changes are added to the repository.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Due to limitations in a mixed-node environment, the -useMetaDataFromBinary attribute has been set to false.  The local changes that were part of the enterprise archive (EAR) file are also located in the repository, so the behavior of the application does not change.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    When the application is used for Application Server Version 6.x profiles only, use the administrative console to modify this attribute.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0115E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.unable.to.execute" varFormat="Java">
    advise.unable.to.execute=MIGR0115E: The migration function cannot run program: {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    During migration processing, the function attempted to call another Application Server program; the call cannot be successfully completed.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, see the problem determination information on the Application Server Support Web page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0380E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.failed.jmx.connection" varFormat="Java">
    advise.failed.jmx.connection=MIGR0380E: The JMX connection is not established with the deployment manager node {0}, using connector type of {1} on port {2}. The WASPostMigration program is now closing. No changes are made to the local Application Server environment.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    During a federated migration, a JMX connection must be established with the deployment manager. That connection was not established during this migration attempt.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check the original error message and verify that all the connection information is correct.  If the information is correct, verify that the deployment manager is running, and that it is listening on the port that is specified in the error message. If the problem persists, see the problem determination information on the Application Server Support Web page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0307I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.information.postupgrade.complete" varFormat="Java">
    advise.information.postupgrade.complete=MIGR0307I: The restoration of the previous Application Server environment is complete.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The restoration of the previous Application Server configuration is complete.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Display the WASPostUpgrade log, and verify the results. The message that is displayed before this one indicates success, warning, or error.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0465E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="illegal.argument.syntax" varFormat="Java">
    illegal.argument.syntax=MIGR0465E: Error in command line after {0}, found unexpected text {1}.  All optional parameters must be prefixed by a label escaped by a leading - character.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Optional parameters must be prefixed by the escape character &apos;-&apos; and have at most one string argument.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the proper optional parameter syntax is being used.  Review the command line help for more information.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0514I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.manually.disabled.oldserver" varFormat="Java">
    advise.manually.disabled.oldserver=MIGR0514I: Cross machine migration detected.  You will need to manually disable the {0} server on the source machine.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The WASPostUpgrade process cannot disable the source profile because it is located on a different machine.  The -machineChange parameter was use by the WASPreUpgrade process to save the backup information.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Refer to the WebSphere InfoCenter on how to manually disable the source profile.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0437E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.two.dmgr.running.with.keepdmgrenabled" varFormat="Java">
    advise.two.dmgr.running.with.keepdmgrenabled=MIGR0437E: Detected current version of deployment manager running while -keepDMgrEnabled attribute set.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    To avoid having two deployment managers managing the same cell, you must shut down the current version of deployment manager when specifying -keepDMgrEnabled=true
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Shut down the current version of deployment manager, and perform the migration again.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0257E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.logging.internal.error" varFormat="Java">
    advise.logging.internal.error=MIGR0257E: The environment variable {0} was not set.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An internal error occurred. The specified environment variable must be set for the migration command to run.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, see the problem determination information on the Application Server Support Web page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0410W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.unable.to.add.to.coregroup" varFormat="Java">
    advise.unable.to.add.to.coregroup=MIGR0410W: Unable to add server {0} to the default coregroup
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    All servers must belong to some core group. This server could not be added to the default core group due to some error.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    The server must be added to some core group before it is able to run. This can be done by using the system management interfaces.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0406E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.servername.parameter.not.allowed" varFormat="Java">
    advise.servername.parameter.not.allowed=MIGR0406E: The -nodeName parameter must also be provided if the -serverName parameter is provided for this profile type.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The -serverName is provided, but the -nodeName parameter is missing. The profile that is being used has more than one node. The -nodeName parameter must also be provided.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Run the command again and provide both parameters.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0435W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.could.not.resolve.variable" varFormat="Java">
    advise.could.not.resolve.variable=MIGR0435W: Could not resolve variable {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A variable being used could not be resolved using the defined variables
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check to see if the variable is being used for a valid reason.  If not then no further action is required; if it is, then define the variable.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0251I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.logging.not.migrating.sample" varFormat="Java">
    advise.logging.not.migrating.sample=MIGR0251I: The migration does not include object {0} of type {1}; it is a Sample.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    No Samples are migrated by the WASPostUpgrade command.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0507E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.register.new.adminagent.unsuccessful" varFormat="Java">
    advise.register.new.adminagent.unsuccessful=MIGR0507E: Registration with new admin agent unsuccessful, manually register the migrated appserver to the new admin agent and job managers if applicable
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    When migrating an appserver that is managed by an admin agent, the appserver is registered to the new admin agent after migration completes successfully. There was a failure in this registration process.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check the logs to find out why registration process failed. The new admin agent may not be running. Start the new admin agent and manually register the migrated appserver if migration was successful.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0510E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.adminagent.security.credentials.required.commandline" varFormat="Java">
    advise.adminagent.security.credentials.required.commandline=MIGR0510E: Security is enabled in your managed application server.  -oldAdminAgentUsername, -oldAdminAgentPassword, -newAdminAgentUsername, -newAdminAgentPassword are required arguments.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Since security is enabled on your managed application server, security credentials are needed to unregister this managed appserver from the old admin agent and register with the new admin agent
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Rerun the WASPostUpgrade command with the -oldAdminAgentUsername, -oldAdminAgentPassword, -newAdminAgentUsername, -newAdminAgentPassword parameters
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0211I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.logging.copying.directory" varFormat="Java">
    advise.logging.copying.directory=MIGR0211I: The migration function is copying a directory {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The function is copying a directory and its contents.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0396W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.enterprise.bcd.disabled" varFormat="Java">
    advise.enterprise.bcd.disabled=MIGR0396W: IBM WebSphere Business Context Data service is disabled because the required IBM WebSphere Business Integration Server Foundation feature is not installed.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The IBM WebSphere Business Integration Server Foundation feature must be installed to run the specified service.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Install the feature, and rerun the command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0535E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.machinechange.flexmgmt.error" varFormat="Java">
    advise.machinechange.flexmgmt.error=MIGR0535E: Machine change is not supported for flexible management profile {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Profiles for Job Manager, Administrative Agents and Base Application Servers registered to an Administrative Agent are not allowed to migrate to a new machine.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Remove the &quot;-machineChange true&quot; parameter and run the WASPreUpgrade command again.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0489E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.invalid.WAS.combination.specific" varFormat="Java">
    advise.invalid.WAS.combination.specific=MIGR0489E: The migration backup directory profile is of type {0} which is not compatible with this profile type {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The migration requires that compatible profile types be used when migrating.  Of note, it is not possible to migrate into a target profile that is already federated into a Deployment Manager.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Create a new profile of a compatible type; specify a different profile to migrate; or use the Migration wizard, the z/OS Migration Management Tool, or the zMMT command to create the target profile automatically.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0529I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="usage.post.bla1" varFormat="Java">
    usage.post.bla1=MIGR0529I: The class name of the WASPostUpgradeBLAHelper command is WASPostUpgradeBLAHelper
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    None
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0616W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.manually.disabled.local.oldserver" varFormat="Java">
    advise.manually.disabled.local.oldserver=MIGR0616W: Node synchronization failed. After you manually synchronize the new node, disable the old {0} node on this system.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The WASPostUpgrade command did not disable the source profile on this system.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    To disable the old node, set all ports to 0 in the serverindex.xml file for this old node. Refer to the product documentation for details on how to disable the old node.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0449I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="unresolved.port.info" varFormat="Java">
    unresolved.port.info=MIGR0449I: The following ports were not changed as part of migration because no migrated servers contained these values.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Configurations can contain port listings that are not bound by servers at startup--for example, host aliases in a virtual host.  If the ports are not part of a server that was migrated during this Migration, the values will not be changed.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Update references to these unmodified ports manually as needed by your environment to resolve port conflicts.  Use the Application Server administrative interfaces or the wsadmin scripting interface to update these values.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0339I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.logging.using.wsadmin" varFormat="Java">
    advise.logging.using.wsadmin=MIGR0339I: Application {0} is deploying using the wsadmin command.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The migration function used the wsadmin command to deploy the specified application.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0439E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.trace.initialization.failed" varFormat="Java">
    advise.trace.initialization.failed=MIGR0439E: Can not initialize trace services.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Verification of the -traceFile location failed.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that the -traceFile location is not write protected and that the path entered is a valid path.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0494E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="refresh.backup.directory.unexpected.error" varFormat="Java">
    refresh.backup.directory.unexpected.error=MIGR0494E: An unexpected error occured during communication with the Deployment Manager, the migration cannot continue.  Resolve the error and rerun the WASPreUpgrade tool to create a new backup directory.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    As part of this migration, files must be copied from the Deployment Manager to this node.  These files will be stored in the backup directory.  An error occured during this process that may have resulted in corruption of the backup directory.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Investigate the original error.  Common causes include network issues in communicating with the Deployment Manager, and insufficient space or permissions on the backup directory filesystem.  Resolve the issue and rerun both the WASPreUpgrade and WASPostUpgrade tools because the backup directory may not be valid.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0486I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.deprecated.attribute" varFormat="Java">
    advise.deprecated.attribute=MIGR0486I: The {0} setting in file {1} is deprecated.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The identified setting is deprecated. This value is still used for this release, but it will be removed in a later release.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See the information center for information about an alternative or replacement setting.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0476E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="run.command.on.dmgr.node" varFormat="Java">
    run.command.on.dmgr.node=MIGR0476E: This command is required to be run against the Deployment Manager&apos;s configuration and the changes manually sychronize to the Managed nodes.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    It was detected that the command was run against a Managed node&apos;s configuration.  The command needs to be run against the Deployment Manager&apos;s configuration.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Run command against the Deployment Managers&apos;s configuration.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0202W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.logging.initialized.failure" varFormat="Java">
    advise.logging.initialized.failure=MIGR0202W: The migration function is unable to initialize log file {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified log file cannot be initialized. No data is saved in a log file, but output is still routed to the administrative console for you to view.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check the user file permissions before you run the command again.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0228E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.logging.no.save" varFormat="Java">
    advise.logging.no.save=MIGR0228E: The migration function cannot save configuration files; exception {0} occurred.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An unexpected error occurred while trying to save the migrated configuration.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the user ID has sufficient file system authority to run the migration command. If the problem persists, see the problem determination information on the Application Server Support Web page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0272E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.logging.completed.with.failures" varFormat="Java">
    advise.logging.completed.with.failures=MIGR0272E: The migration function cannot complete the command.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The migration command failed.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    For additional information; check the log file that was created by the migration command in the logs directory, and correct the problems if required. The log name includes a time stamp, so check the log file with the latest creation date.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0395W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.enterprise.event.disabled" varFormat="Java">
    advise.enterprise.event.disabled=MIGR0395W: IBM WebSphere Application Event service is disabled because the required IBM WebSphere Business Integration Server Foundation feature is not installed.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The IBM WebSphere Business Integration Server Foundation feature must be installed to run the specified service.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Install the feature, and rerun the command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0378E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.node.name.must.match" varFormat="Java">
    advise.node.name.must.match=MIGR0378E: The node name of the new configuration must be the same as the old configuration: {0} for this environment.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    While migrating a federated node, the node names of the old and new configurations did not match. This configuration cannot be migrated because the old configuration exists in the deployment manager with the old node name. Using the new node name causes an unacceptable configuration in the deployment manager.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Uninstall and reinstall Application Server using the same node name as the old configuration, or remove the old node from the deployment manager configuration and manually add this node.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0523I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.properties.security.provider.renumbered" varFormat="Java">
    advise.properties.security.provider.renumbered=MIGR0523I: The following security provider(s) were renumbered due to migration. Duplicate entries were removed.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    When a security provider from the old file is inserted in the new file, the security providers in the new file are renumbered.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required, but you might want to review the file and determine if the security providers are configured as desired.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0216W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.logging.unable.to.copy" varFormat="Java">
    advise.logging.unable.to.copy=MIGR0216W: The migration function cannot copy the file and transfer from source {0} to destination {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An unexpected failure occurred while copying a configuration file.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the user ID has the appropriate file system authority to run the  migration program. If the problem persists, see the problem determination information on the Application Server Support Web page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0508I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.deregistering.from.old.adminagent" varFormat="Java">
    advise.deregistering.from.old.adminagent=MIGR0508I: Deregistering from old admin agent
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Since this is a managed application server, migration will try to deregister the application server from the old admin agent first.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that the old admin agent is running
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0498E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.derby.database.in.use" varFormat="Java">
    advise.derby.database.in.use=MIGR0498E: Derby database lock file detected.  Cannot migrate Derby database {0} while in use.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    There is a Derby database lock file detected. Cannot migrate Derby database while in use.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Please shutdown Derby database and be sure all lock files have been removed.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0466E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="illegal.argument.required.value" varFormat="Java">
    illegal.argument.required.value=MIGR0466E: No value was found for the argument {0}.  This argument requires a value{1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This optional parameters require an argument.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the proper optional parameter syntax is being used.  Review the command line help for more information.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0541W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.managedNodesPresent.preupgrade.save" varFormat="Java">
    advise.managedNodesPresent.preupgrade.save=MIGR0541W: A machine change migration has been detected. There are resources registered with the job manager function associated with the previous deployment manager. Update the job manager URL for the registered resources after WASPostUpgrade.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A machine change migration has been detected. There are resources registered with the job manager function associated with the previous deployment manager. Update the job manager URL for the registered resources after WASPostUpgrade.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Update the job manager URL at the registered resources.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0463I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="no.factories.enabled" varFormat="Java">
    no.factories.enabled=MIGR0463I: Nothing to migrate at this time.  The current profile has already been migrated with all information from enabled features.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message indicates that all features in the backup directory that are enabled in the current configuration have already been migrated.  If information that you expected is not available in the current configuration, review the installed products and ensure that the correct features are installed.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0484E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.invalid.profile.name" varFormat="Java">
    advise.invalid.profile.name=MIGR0484E: No profiles or instances found with name {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    WASPreUpgrade command did not find any profiles or instances with the name specified.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Run WASPreUpgrade command again specifying a profile or instance name that exists.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0433E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.conflicting.parameters" varFormat="Java">
    advise.conflicting.parameters=MIGR0433E: Conflicting parameters, -keepAppDirectory true and -appInstallDirectory, have both been specified.  If -appInstallDirectory is specified, -keepAppDirectory must be false.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This error occurs when -keepAppDirectory true and -appInstallDirectory are both specified.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Select only one of the two parameters, or specify -keepAppDirectory false.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0457W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.nodeagent.conflict.nodisable" varFormat="Java">
    advise.nodeagent.conflict.nodisable=MIGR0457W: Do not use the node agent in the old configuration.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The migration of the Managed node to the latest release is successful. This migration creates the same port definitions that are in the existing Application Server configuration. The node agent of the existing configuration must be stopped before starting the deployment manager in the new configuration. The deployment manager of the new configuration must be used to manage the environment.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If you want to use the old environment you will need to restart the prior version of the Deployment Manager and Managed node.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0110E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.unsupported.version" varFormat="Java">
    advise.unsupported.version=MIGR0110E: The currently installed version of Application Server is not supported by this command.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The WASPostUpgrade command is running against an unsupported version of Application Server. The WASPostUpgrade command that was invoked might not be using the current version of the Application Server directories.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Invoke the command in the current Application Server directory structure.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0408I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.logging.saved.configuration.success" varFormat="Java">
    advise.logging.saved.configuration.success=MIGR0408I: The configuration is saved successfully.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The configuration is saved.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0385I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.information.instance.start" varFormat="Java">
    advise.information.instance.start=MIGR0385I: Starting to save profile {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The series of steps needed to save the existing configuration information for the profile is starting.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0543W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.logging.unable.to.copy.not.writable" varFormat="Java">
    advise.logging.unable.to.copy.not.writable=MIGR0543W: The migration function cannot copy into the read-only target directory {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The function cannot copy the file or directory because the destination is a read-only location. This problem might cause the migration to fail.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that you have permission to write to the directory and copy files manually.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0522W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.logging.unable.to.write.file.target" varFormat="Java">
    advise.logging.unable.to.write.file.target=MIGR0522W: The migration function cannot write the destination file {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A failure occurred while copying a configuration file.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If changes are needed to the destination file, the file will need to be modified manually after changing the access permissions to allow the file to be written.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0461I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="postupgrade.not.enabled" varFormat="Java">
    postupgrade.not.enabled=MIGR0461I: Application Server has already been migrated.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This indicates that the base Application Server files have already been migrated.  They will not be migrated again.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0544W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.logging.unable.to.copy.source.empty" varFormat="Java">
    advise.logging.unable.to.copy.source.empty=MIGR0544W: The migration function cannot compress an empty directory {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The function cannot compress the directory because it is empty.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the directory is not needed, delete the directory.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0117E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.invalid.WAS.directory.product" varFormat="Java">
    advise.invalid.WAS.directory.product=MIGR0117E: The specified Application Server directory does not contain a valid product file {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified directory on the migration command does not contain a valid &lt;samp&gt;properties/com/ibm/websphere/product.xml&lt;/samp&gt; file.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Rerun the command with a valid Application Server XML file name.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0206W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.logging.unable.to.copy.no.source" varFormat="Java">
    advise.logging.unable.to.copy.no.source=MIGR0206W: The migration function cannot copy the directory. The source file {0} does not exist.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The function cannot find or copy an expected directory. This missing directory might affect the migration.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If this source file must be used to create an enterprise application, use a development environment like the Rational Application Developer to add the file to the appropriate location in the enterprise application.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0394W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.enterprise.srs.disabled" varFormat="Java">
    advise.enterprise.srs.disabled=MIGR0394W: IBM WebSphere Web Service Reference service is disabled because the required IBM WebSphere Business Integration Server Foundation feature is not installed.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The IBM WebSphere Business Integration Server Foundation feature must be installed to run the specified service.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Install the feature, and rerun the command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0490I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.changing.performance.settings" varFormat="Java">
    advise.changing.performance.settings=MIGR0490I: Changing the {0} setting from {1} to {2} in the file {3} to meet performance requirements.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The migration has adjusted a value that was configured outside the recommended minimum or maximum for the specified performance tuning option.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Customers should be aware that the migrated server may require more resources than previous releases.  The change has been made to conform to recommended values, but if you determine that this is beyond the needs of your system you may change the value.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0367I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.information.backup.start" varFormat="Java">
    advise.information.backup.start=MIGR0367I: Backing up the current Application Server environment.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The existing configuration is saved in the &lt;samp&gt;temp&lt;/samp&gt; directory.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0319E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.already.federated" varFormat="Java">
    advise.already.federated=MIGR0319E: This node is already federated into a cell manager configuration.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This node is already added to the cell manager configuration. Migration does not run because the configuration is controlled by the cell manager.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If you want to migrate the node, remove the node from the cell manager configuration, and rerun the command. However, proceed with caution because the configuration is already being managed.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0421W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.logging.waspreupgrade.completed.warning" varFormat="Java">
    advise.logging.waspreupgrade.completed.warning=MIGR0421W: The first step of migration completed with warnings.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The migration completed with some warning messages, but no errors occurred.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check the log file that the migration command created in the logs directory, and correct the problems if required. The log name includes a time stamp, so check the log file with the latest creation date.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0386E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.new.profile.incorrect" varFormat="Java">
    advise.new.profile.incorrect=MIGR0386E: Profile {0} is not found in the currently installed Application Server.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The profile must exist before a migration can be performed.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Rerun the command with the correct profile name, or use the wasprofile command to create the correct profile.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0288I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.logging.saved.success" varFormat="Java">
    advise.logging.saved.success=MIGR0288I: Configuration file {0} ready to be saved.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified configuration file is ready to be saved.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0432W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.unsupported.servertype" varFormat="Java">
    advise.unsupported.servertype=MIGR0432W: Found server {0} to be of type {1} which is unsupported in current product version.  {0} will not be migrated.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This error occurs when an unsupported server type is encountered.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Use the migration utilities for the product that this server type belongs too.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0365W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.enterprise.membermanager.disabled" varFormat="Java">
    advise.enterprise.membermanager.disabled=MIGR0365W: The member manager service is disabled because the required IBM WebSphere Business Integration Server Foundation feature is not installed.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The IBM WebSphere Business Integration Server Foundation member manager feature must be installed to run the specified service.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Install the feature, and run the command again.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0518W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="microsoft.property.notmapped" varFormat="Java">
    microsoft.property.notmapped=MIGR0518W: The Microsoft SQL Server JDBC driver property {0} was not set.  Unable to determine proper value based on the value supplied by the WebSphere Connect JDBC driver property {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Microsoft Data Source property was not set because the mapping from the WebSphere Connect Data Source property or properties could not be properly determined.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See information center for further details.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0524I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.logging.unable.to.create.file.target.alreadyexist" varFormat="Java">
    advise.logging.unable.to.create.file.target.alreadyexist=MIGR0524I: The migration function cannot create the destination file {0}. It already existed. The source file {1} cannot be migrated.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A failure occurred while copying a configuration file. The existence of the destination file indicates the source file was already migrated in a previous migration.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Since the source file was migrated during a previous migration, no action should be needed.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0454I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.deprecated.attribute.transporttype" varFormat="Java">
    advise.deprecated.attribute.transporttype=MIGR0454I: The {0} setting in file {1} is deprecated.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The identified setting is deprecated. This value is still used for this release, but it will be removed in a later release.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See the information center for information about an alternative or replacement setting.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0491W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.logging.too.many.open.files" varFormat="Java">
    advise.logging.too.many.open.files=MIGR0491W: The migration function cannot continue because there are too many open files.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The number of open files is limited by the operating system, and the current setting has insufficient file handles for running migration program.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Configure more available file descriptors in the session that runs the migration program, and restart the migration.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0107E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.cmd.line.illegal.number.arg" varFormat="Java">
    advise.cmd.line.illegal.number.arg=MIGR0107E: An incorrect format for an optional parameter is specified.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Specify optional parameters by entering the name of the parameter, followed by the value of the parameter.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Run the command again with the correct format for optional parameters.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0480E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="wasdd.invalid.node.release" varFormat="Java">
    wasdd.invalid.node.release=MIGR0480E: The node {0} specified for the -nodeName parameter is not at the current release.  Migrate node to current release and run tool again.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Tool will only work against nodes that have been migrated and are at the current release level.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Migrate your node to the current release level and then run the tool again.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0350W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.synchronize.failed" varFormat="Java">
    advise.synchronize.failed=MIGR0350W: Synchronization with the deployment manager using the {0} protocol failed.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The deployment manager might not have been running during migration.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the deployment manager is currently running. Either manually run the syncNode command to update the configuration, or enable the node agent to perform this task automatically the next time that you run the startNode command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0431E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.failed.node.already.federated" varFormat="Java">
    advise.failed.node.already.federated=MIGR0431E: Federated node {0} already exists in current configuration.  Migration cannot continue.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This error occurs if the new deployment manager configuration contains a node with the same name as a node in the prior release.  This happens if the user does an &quot;addNode&quot; in the current release prior to migration.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    UnFederate the node in the current release, and rerun migration.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0229I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.logging.updating.entry" varFormat="Java">
    advise.logging.updating.entry=MIGR0229I: The migration function is updating the attributes of {0} entry {1}. This entry is already defined in the existing model.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified entry already exists in the configuration of the new Application Server version. The attributes of this entry are being updated.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0122E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.invalid.configuration" varFormat="Java">
    advise.invalid.configuration=MIGR0122E: The migration function cannot read configuration file {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The function cannot read the specified configuration file.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the file is part of the current Application Server configuration, restore the configuration from a previous backup and rerun the command. The WASPostUpgrade command saves backup copies of all the configuration files that it attempts to modify. The backup files are in the same directory structure and have time stamps as part of their names.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0215W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.logging.unable.to.copy.file.target" varFormat="Java">
    advise.logging.unable.to.copy.file.target=MIGR0215W: The migration function cannot copy the file and open the destination file {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An unexpected failure occurred while copying a configuration file.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the user ID has the appropriate file system authority to run the migration program. If the problem persists, see the problem determination information on the Application Server Support Web page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0217W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.logging.unable.to.close" varFormat="Java">
    advise.logging.unable.to.close=MIGR0217W: The migration function cannot close file {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An unexpected failure occurred while closing a configuration file.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the user ID has the appropriate file system authority to run the migration program. If the problem persists, see the problem determination information on the Application Server Support Web page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0525W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.logging.unable.to.create.file.target" varFormat="Java">
    advise.logging.unable.to.create.file.target=MIGR0525W: The migration function cannot create the destination file {0}. The source file {1} cannot be migrated.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A failure occurred while copying a configuration file.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the user ID has the appropriate file system authority to run the migration program.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0281W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.corba.servers.disabled" varFormat="Java">
    advise.corba.servers.disabled=MIGR0281W: All CORBA servers are disabled because the corresponding IBM WebSphere Business Integration Server Foundation feature is not installed.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The IBM WebSphere Business Integration Server Foundation CORBA C++ SDK must be installed to run CORBA applications.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Install the feature, and rerun the command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0412W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.node.already.exists" varFormat="Java">
    advise.node.already.exists=MIGR0412W: Node name {0} already exists in the configuration at the current Application Server version level. It will not be updated.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    While processing a deployment manager configuration, an attempt was made to add a node to the configuration from the old configuration. However, a node with that name already exists in the configuration at a higher Application Server version than exists in the old configuration. It will not be updated.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0400I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.adding.coregroup.server" varFormat="Java">
    advise.adding.coregroup.server=MIGR0400I: Server {0} is added to the default core group.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    All servers must belong to a core group. This server is added to the default core group.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0495E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="corrupted.backup.directory" varFormat="Java">
    corrupted.backup.directory=MIGR0495E: The migration function cannot use the specified backup directory, it is invalid.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The directory specified does not pass validation to be used as a migration backup directory.  This may be the result of a failure during WASPreUpgrade, or corruption by a previous run of WASPostUpgrade.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the wrong directory was specified, rerun the tool with a valid backup directory.  If the directory specified is correct, then the backup directory has been corrupted.  Rerun the WASPreupgrade tools to create a new migration backup directory.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0499I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.application.install.successful" varFormat="Java">
    advise.application.install.successful=MIGR0499I: Application {0} successfully deployed using the wsadmin command.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The migration function used the wsadmin command to successfully deploy the specified application.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0102E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.invalid.cmd.line" varFormat="Java">
    advise.invalid.cmd.line=MIGR0102E: An unsupported command line parameter was used.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The command parameters are incorrectly specified.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that all of the parameters are valid and spelled correctly.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0001I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="usage.pre.line1" varFormat="Java">
    usage.pre.line1=MIGR0001I: The class name of the WASPreUpgrade command is WASPreUpgrade
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    None
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0536E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.profileRegistry.file.not.found" varFormat="Java">
    advise.profileRegistry.file.not.found=MIGR0536E: The profileRegistry.xml file cannot be found in the following location: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The migration command could not find the profileRegistry.xml file, which contains the profile registry definitions.  Either profiles were not created in the source product release, or the profileRegistry.xml file was corrupted or deleted.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If profiles do exist for the source product release, you must reconstruct the profileRegistry.xml file.  See the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support web page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0427W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.node.unmanageable" varFormat="Java">
    advise.node.unmanageable=MIGR0427W: Node {0} has been migrated, but may not be manageable in current release.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This release of Application Server cannot manage nodes prior to Version 6.0.2.0 without a fix.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Install the required fix to Version 6.0.0.x and 6.0.1.y nodes prior to migration.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0103E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.cmd.line.backupDirectory" varFormat="Java">
    advise.cmd.line.backupDirectory=MIGR0103E: You must specify the backup directory name.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The backup directory is used to store the configuration information that is migrated to the new release.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Run the command again and specify the backup directory.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0467W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="user.defined.datasource.helper" varFormat="Java">
    user.defined.datasource.helper=MIGR0467W: A user defined data source helper {0} has been detected.  It will be migrated, but it must be reimplemented to work correctly.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Your data source helper will need to be reimplemented to inherit from ConnectJDBCDataStoreHelper or MicrosoftSQLServerDataStoreHelper.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Reimplement data source helper to inherit from ConnectJDBCDataStoreHelper or MicrosoftSQLServerDataStoreHelper.  See the information center for more details.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0259I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.logging.completed" varFormat="Java">
    advise.logging.completed=MIGR0259I: The migration has successfully completed.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The migration has completed with no warning or error messages.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0464E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="failure.stop.nodeagent" varFormat="Java">
    failure.stop.nodeagent=MIGR0464E: Failed to stop prior release nodeagent.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This indicates that we were unsuccessful in stopping the prior release nodeagent.  Migration will not continue.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Shut down nodeagent of prior release and perform Migration again.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0113E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.backup.directory.notcreatable" varFormat="Java">
    advise.backup.directory.notcreatable=MIGR0113E: The specified backup directory cannot be used because it cannot be created.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The system is unable to create a directory with the name that you specified.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Determine why the directory cannot be created and run the command again. If the problem persists, see the problem determination information on the Application Server Support Web page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ or consult the appropriate operating system documentation.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0438W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.cannot.copy.file.exists" varFormat="Java">
    advise.cannot.copy.file.exists=MIGR0438W: Not copying file or directory {0} because a version of the file or directory already exists in current version.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The file or directory might already exist.  To avoid overwriting a valid file or directory, the file or directory will not be copied.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the file or directory is required, then manually search the WASPreUpgrade backup directory for the file or directory and copy it into the new environment.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0506E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.deregister.old.adminagent.unsuccessful" varFormat="Java">
    advise.deregister.old.adminagent.unsuccessful=MIGR0506E: Deregistration from old admin agent unsuccessful, make sure old admin agent process is running and the soap port is correct
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    When migrating an appserver that is managed by an admin agent, the appserver is first deregistered from the old admin agent. There was a failure in this deregistration process.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check the logs to find out why the deregistration failed. The old admin agent may not be running. Start the old admin agent and rerun the postupgrade the command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0255E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.invalid.substitution" varFormat="Java">
    advise.invalid.substitution=MIGR0255E: The migration function found an unacceptable substitution value {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The substitution values can be replaced in the input XML file during migration. These values are specified with the WASPostUpgrade command.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Rerun the migration command using a valid substitution value.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0534E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.cmd.line.remote.WASPreUpgrade" varFormat="Java">
    advise.cmd.line.remote.WASPreUpgrade=MIGR0534E: The {0} option must be specified when using the remote version of the WASPreUpgrade command.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The remote version of the WASPreUpgrade command must include the &quot;-machineChange true&quot; parameter.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Run the WASPreUpgrade command again while specifying the &quot;-machineChange true&quot; parameter.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0111E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.invalid.backup.directory" varFormat="Java">
    advise.invalid.backup.directory=MIGR0111E: The migration function cannot use the specified backup directory because it is a file.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Specify a directory so that files containing the configuration information for the current release can be saved.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Run the command again and specify the name of a directory.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0441I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.logging.copying.element" varFormat="Java">
    advise.logging.copying.element=MIGR0441I: The migration function is copying {0} entry {1} to the model.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified object is being copied to the configuration of the new Application Server version.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0304I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.information.postupgrade.start" varFormat="Java">
    advise.information.postupgrade.start=MIGR0304I: The previous WebSphere environment is being merged into this profile.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The migration of the previous Application Server environment to the configuration of the new WebSphere version has begun.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0453W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.not.migrating.zos.jdbcprovider" varFormat="Java">
    advise.not.migrating.zos.jdbcprovider=MIGR0453W: Not migrating DB2 for zOS Local JDBC Provider (RRS) JDBC Provider.  This JDBC Provider will be copied over as-is but will be disabled at runtime.  In order for this JDBC Provider to function at runtime it will need to be migrated to a DB2 Universal JDBC Driver Provider using the DB2 Universal Driver.  This can be done manually or by using the IBM Application Server JDBC Migration Utility for DB2 on z/OS, available as a web download.  Contact IBM support for details.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The DB2 for zOS Local JDBC Provider (RRS) JDBC provider is not supported in the targeted Application Server version.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Manually create the DB2 Universal Driver provider.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0471W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="microsoft.property.modified" varFormat="Java">
    microsoft.property.modified=MIGR0471W: Property {0} has been modified or replaced to conform to Microsoft SQL Server JDBC Driver requirements.  Validate changes made.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Property has been modified to conform to Microsoft data source requirements.  These changes should be validated for correctness on your system.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See information center for further details.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0485W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.ha.process.size.exceeding.recommended.threshold" varFormat="Java">
    advise.ha.process.size.exceeding.recommended.threshold=MIGR0485W: Process count exceeds the maximum recommended limit of {0} processes per coregroup.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Performance may degrade with coregroups of large size.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Redistribute coregroup processes to smaller coregroup groupings.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0425I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.old.environment.recovery" varFormat="Java">
    advise.old.environment.recovery=MIGR0425I: A deployment manager migration is detected.  Before continuing with the WASPostUpgrade process, run the backupConfig command on your federated nodes.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Certain files in the Application Server Version 5 or 6 environment might be modified during the migration of a version 7 deployment manager that manages version 5 or 6 nodes.  By running the backupConfig command against your version 5 or 6 environment, you provide yourself with an error recovery path.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Run the backupConfig command against all the version 5 or 6 nodes that are managed by the version 7 deployment manager.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0436W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.could.not.finish.processing.resource" varFormat="Java">
    advise.could.not.finish.processing.resource=MIGR0436W: Could not process resource {0} due to variable issues.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A variable being used could not be resolved using the defined variables
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check to see if the variable is being used for a valid reason.  If not then no further action is required; if it is, then define the variable.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0363W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.enterprise.wbia.disabled" varFormat="Java">
    advise.enterprise.wbia.disabled=MIGR0363W: The IBM WebSphere Business Integration adapter service is disabled because the required IBM WebSphere Business Integration Server Foundation feature is not installed.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The IBM WebSphere Business Integration Server Foundation other services feature must be installed to run the specified service.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Install the feature, and run the command again.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0201I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.logging.initialized" varFormat="Java">
    advise.logging.initialized=MIGR0201I: The migration function initialized log file {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified log file is initialized. A new log file is created for each invocation of the migration commands.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0213E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.logging.unable.to.create.directory" varFormat="Java">
    advise.logging.unable.to.create.directory=MIGR0213E: The migration function cannot create a directory {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An unexpected failure occurred during the creation of a directory.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the user ID has sufficient file system authority to run the migration command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0468W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="microsoft.new.properties.performance" varFormat="Java">
    microsoft.new.properties.performance=MIGR0468W: Adding properties unique to the Microsoft SQL Server JDBC Driver.  Review the default values to ensure the desired behavior.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Adding properties unique to the Microsoft SQL Server JDBC Driver.  Review the default values to ensure the desired behavior.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See information center for further details.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0481E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="wasdd.invalid.name" varFormat="Java">
    wasdd.invalid.name=MIGR0481E: The {0} {1} specified for the {2} parameter does not exist.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Could not find node or server in the configuration.  Most likely cause is that the node or server name was misspelled.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify node or server name was spelled correctly.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0287I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.logging.create.success" varFormat="Java">
    advise.logging.create.success=MIGR0287I: The migration function successfully created configuration file {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified configuration file, which did not exist in the new Application Server configuration, is successfully created.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0371I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.properties.leftover" varFormat="Java">
    advise.properties.leftover=MIGR0371I: The name-value pairs that existed in the old file are not found in the new file.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Leftover properties that are found in the old file are not found in the new file.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required, but you might want to review the file and determine why some properties are missing.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0352I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.synchronize.attempt.successful" varFormat="Java">
    advise.synchronize.attempt.successful=MIGR0352I: The synchronization with the deployment manager is successful.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The configuration is successfully synchronized.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0472I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="converting.provider.resource" varFormat="Java">
    converting.provider.resource=MIGR0472I: Converting WebSphere Connect JDBC Provider &quot;{0}&quot; to {1} Provider.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Performing conversion on WebSphere Applilcation Server DataDirect resource.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    None
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0515W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="hostname.ipaddress.check.failed" varFormat="Java">
    hostname.ipaddress.check.failed=MIGR0515W: Cannot validate if the source hostname ({0}) has the same IP address as the target hostname ({1}).  Hostname changes were made to one or more of the server&apos;&apos;s endpoints.  You must validate these changes.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The migration received an UnknownHostException or a SecurityException while trying to determine the IP address of the source and/or target hostname.  The migration assumed the hostname change is valid and continued.  The migration updated the hostname for one or more endpoints.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    You must verify these settings.  Or, to avoid this change, recreate the target profile using the hostname from the source profile and run the migration again.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0300I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.information.preupgrade.start" varFormat="Java">
    advise.information.preupgrade.start=MIGR0300I: The migration function is starting to save the existing Application Server environment.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The required steps that save the existing configuration information have started.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0252W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.logging.no.restore" varFormat="Java">
    advise.logging.no.restore=MIGR0252W: The migration function cannot restore configuration file {0}. An exception {1} occurred.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    While attempting to restore the specified file, an unexpected error occurred. The configuration file might not match the rest of the configuration.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If possible, use one of the backup files with the same name to restore the configuration.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0455W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="connect.driver.removed" varFormat="Java">
    connect.driver.removed=MIGR0455W: WebSphere Connect JDBC driver support has been removed.  Data source {0} will need to be modified to make use of either Microsoft SQL Server JDBC Driver or DataDirect Connect JDBC driver.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    WebSphere Connect JDBC driver support has been removed.  Any WebSphere Connect type data sources need to be modified to use either the Microsoft SQL Server JDBC Driver or DataDirect Connect JDBC driver.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See the information center for information about an alternative or replacement setting.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0469W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="datadirect.specific.properties.dropped" varFormat="Java">
    datadirect.specific.properties.dropped=MIGR0469W: Removing properties unique to the WebSphere Connect JDBC driver.  These features are no longer available:
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Properties do not have a direct mapping from DataDirect data source to Microsoft data source thus will be dropped.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See information center for further details.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0387E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.old.instance.incorrect" varFormat="Java">
    advise.old.instance.incorrect=MIGR0387E: The backup directory does not contain profile {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The profile did not exist in the previously installed WebSphere.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Rerun the command with the correct profile name.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0519I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.this.msg.is.ok" varFormat="Java">
    advise.this.msg.is.ok=MIGR0519I: The certificate exchange related messages can be ignored.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The certificate exchange related messages can be ignored.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ignore the certificate exchange related messages.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0372I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.policy.leftover" varFormat="Java">
    advise.policy.leftover=MIGR0372I: Migrated grant permissions follow.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Leftover grants that are found in the old file are not found in the new file.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0360W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.enterprise.staff.disabled" varFormat="Java">
    advise.enterprise.staff.disabled=MIGR0360W: The staff service is disabled because the required IBM WebSphere Business Integration Server Foundation feature is not installed.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The IBM WebSphere Business Integration Server Foundation process choreographer feature must be installed to run the specified service.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Install the feature, and run the command again.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0210I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.logging.creating.directory" varFormat="Java">
    advise.logging.creating.directory=MIGR0210I: The migration function is creating a directory {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The directory was created during normal processing.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0413W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.node.already.exists.convert" varFormat="Java">
    advise.node.already.exists.convert=MIGR0413W: Node name {0} does not exist in the configuration at the current Application Server version level. It will not be updated.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    While processing a configuration, an attempt was made to convert a node from script compatibility mode. However, that node is not at the latest Application Server version. It will not be updated.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0473I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="converting.datasource.resource" varFormat="Java">
    converting.datasource.resource=MIGR0473I: Converting WebSphere Connect JDBC driver data source &quot;{0}&quot; to {1} data source.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Performing conversion on WebSphere Applilcation Server DataDirect resource.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    None
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0445W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.jdbc.provider.type.missing" varFormat="Java">
    advise.jdbc.provider.type.missing=MIGR0445W: The JDBC provider, {0}, is no longer a valid.  You will not be able to create any new data sources for this provider until you either use the WebSphereConnectJDBCDriverConversion tool or create a new JDBC provider.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A JDBC provider in the previous version did not have a provider type defined.  This is a required attribute.  The provider type could not be resolved during migration.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that each JDBCProvider has a providerType.  For WebSphere Connect JDBC providers, consider using the WebSphereConnectJDBCDriverConversion tool.  For all other providers, it is recommended that it be deleted, unless you have previously configured data sources that still use it.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0539W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.path.adjustment.made" varFormat="Java">
    advise.path.adjustment.made=MIGR0539W: The {0} path {1} was change to {2} during migration due to path or variable resolution issues.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The path or variables contained in the path definition could not be properly adjusted to reflect its post-migration location.  However, an equivalent path definition was inserted in its place.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    None needed.  However, the user can manually adjust the variables in the new post-migrated environment and then readjust the path to use those variables.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0540W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.additional.java.security.detected" varFormat="Java">
    advise.additional.java.security.detected=MIGR0540W: An additional java.security file was detected, but not migrated.  If needed, migrate the java.security file manually.  The java.security file is found under: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An additional installation of java was found.  This java installation might require the java.security file to be configured.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check if the java installation found in the specified directory is being used.  If not, then no further action is required. If it is, then verify the java.security file is set up correctly.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0289E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.invalid.configuration.entry" varFormat="Java">
    advise.invalid.configuration.entry=MIGR0289E: The entry {0} in entry {1} does not exist.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified entry in the configuration file does not exist as expected. This configuration file is not valid.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Either restore a valid backup from a previous configuration, or use the Application Server administrative interfaces to fix the settings in the file.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0451W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.copy.files.nooverwrite" varFormat="Java">
    advise.copy.files.nooverwrite=MIGR0451W: Migration copied file originally located at {0} to local path {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Migration copied the file because it had not already been processed during migration.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0545I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.migrate.washome.properties" varFormat="Java">
    advise.migrate.washome.properties=MIGR0545I: The WebSphere Application Server installation configuration file {0} was migrated successfully. However, the changes should be reviewed and updated if necessary.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified WebSphere Application Server installation configuration file might contain settings which are incompatible with the new installation.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify and manually modify the settings in the specified file as needed.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0271W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.logging.completed.with.warnings" varFormat="Java">
    advise.logging.completed.with.warnings=MIGR0271W: Migration completed successfully, with one or more warnings.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The migration completed with some warning messages, but no errors occurred.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    For further information; check the log file that was created by the migration command in the logs directory, and correct the problems if required.  The log name includes a time stamp, so check the log file with the latest creation date.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0487I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ignore.oldprofile.parameter" varFormat="Java">
    ignore.oldprofile.parameter=MIGR0487I: The {0} parameter not required in this scenario, and is being ignored.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The identified parameter is not needed for the current migration.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is neccessary.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0456W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.deployment.manager.conflict.nodisable" varFormat="Java">
    advise.deployment.manager.conflict.nodisable=MIGR0456W: Do not use the existing deployment manager in the old configuration.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The migration of a deployment manager to the latest release is successful. This migration creates the same port definitions as those on the existing Application Server configuration. Stop the deployment manager of the existing configuration before starting the deployment manager in the new configuration. Use the deployment manager of the new configuration to manage the environment.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If you want to use the old environment, restart the prior version Deployment Manager.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0517W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="microsoft.property.modified3" varFormat="Java">
    microsoft.property.modified3=MIGR0517W: The following properties: {0} were used to determine the {1} setting for the Microsoft SQL Server JDBC Driver requirements.  Validate changes made.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A set of properties were used to determine the final setting for a Microsoft data source property.  These changes should be validated for correctness on your system.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See information center for further details.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0516W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="microsoft.property.modified2" varFormat="Java">
    microsoft.property.modified2=MIGR0516W: Property {0} has been mapped to conform to Microsoft SQL Server JDBC Driver requirements.  Validate changes made to {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Property has been converted to conform to Microsoft data source requirements.  These changes should be validated for correctness on your system.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See information center for further details.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0511E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.need.newadminagent.info" varFormat="Java">
    advise.need.newadminagent.info=MIGR0511E: Admin Agent information for the new release is invalid
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The admin agent profile path for the new release is invalid
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that the admin agent information for the new release is valid
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0513W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="machine.change.hostname.check.identical" varFormat="Java">
    machine.change.hostname.check.identical=MIGR0513W: A cross machine migration detected. However, the source and target hostnames are identical - hostname={0}   You will need to validate the host name setting of your endpoints.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The WASPostUpgrade detected that the WASPreUpgrade command used the -machineChange true parameter.  This usually indicates a hostname change.  WASPostUpgrade detected that the new and the old host names are identical.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    After migration, you will need to validate that the each endpoint has the correct host name assigned.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0530E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.bad.command" varFormat="Java">
    advise.bad.command=MIGR0530E: Unable to run command {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The command cannot be run
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure the command is correct. Run the WASPostUpgradeBLAHelper script after fixing the problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0379W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.deployment.manager.conflict" varFormat="Java">
    advise.deployment.manager.conflict=MIGR0379W: Do not use the existing deployment manager in the old configuration. It has been disabled.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The migration of a deployment manager to the latest release is successful. This migration creates the same port definitions as those on the existing Application Server configuration. Stop the deployment manager of the existing configuration before starting the deployment manager in the new configuration, and do not use it. Use the deployment manager of the new configuration to manage the environment.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If you want to roll back to use the previous Application Server Version 5.1, 6.0 or 6.1 environment instead of Version 7.0, you must re-enable that configuration. To do this, go to the /bin directory of the previous Version 5.1 6.0 or 6.1 installation and run the migrationDisablementReversal.jacl script.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0114E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.setupCmdLine.file.not.valid" varFormat="Java">
    advise.setupCmdLine.file.not.valid=MIGR0114E: The migration function cannot find the setupCmdLine setting {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The migration function cannot find a specific property in an IBM-supplied file.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See the problem determination information on the Application Server Support Web page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0351I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.synchronize.attempt" varFormat="Java">
    advise.synchronize.attempt=MIGR0351I: The migration function is attempting to synchronize with the deployment manager using the {0} protocol.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The function is trying to connect to the deployment manager using the specified protocol.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0428E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.incorrect.repository.connection" varFormat="Java">
    advise.incorrect.repository.connection=MIGR0428E: Incorrect Deployment Manager connection established.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The deployment manager to which this node belongs is not the deployment manager currently running.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Shut down the incorrect deployment manager, and start the deployment manager that is currently managing the node to be migrated.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0112E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.backup.directory.notwriteable" varFormat="Java">
    advise.backup.directory.notwriteable=MIGR0112E: The specified backup directory cannot be used because it is not writable.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Specify a writable directory so that files containing the configuration information for the current release can be saved.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Run the command again and specify the name of a writeable directory.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0462I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="preupgrade.supported" varFormat="Java">
    preupgrade.supported=MIGR0462I: Application Server factor is saving base configuration files.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This indicates that a backup of the existing configuration is being saved for use during the WASPostUpgrade step of migration.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0531E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.bad.jythonfile" varFormat="Java">
    advise.bad.jythonfile=MIGR0531E: Unable to run jython file {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The jython file cannot be run
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure the jython file and its contents are correct. Run the WASPostUpgradeBLAHelper script after fixing the problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0223I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.logging.adding.element" varFormat="Java">
    advise.logging.adding.element=MIGR0223I: The migration function is adding {0} entry {1} to the model.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified object is being added to the configuration of the new Application Server version.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0106E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.cmd.line.illegal" varFormat="Java">
    advise.cmd.line.illegal=MIGR0106E: The illegal argument {0} is specified.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified parameter is not supported by the command.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check the spelling of the parameter and run the command again.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0574W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.library.not.copied" varFormat="Java">
    advise.library.not.copied=MIGR0574W: The following library was not copied: {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The library was not copied to the new location because of insufficient disk space, file handles, system memory, or permissions, or other system causes.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    You must manually migrate the library to its new location and update the library path. You can edit the library path in the administrative console or by using wsadmin scripting. For more information, see the documentation about managing a shared library and configuring a shared library using scripting.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0533E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.commands.notsaved" varFormat="Java">
    advise.commands.notsaved=MIGR0533E: Commands not saved {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The commands could not be saved
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check the logs to see why the commands could not be saved. Run the WASPostUpgradeBLAHelper script after fixing the problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0905W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="client.usage.message9" varFormat="Java">
    client.usage.message9=MIGR0905W: An unacceptable parameter was specified {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A specified parameter is not recognized as a valid parameter.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify spelling and run the command alone, without any parameters or arguments, to get the correct syntax of the command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0450W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.copy.files.general" varFormat="Java">
    advise.copy.files.general=MIGR0450W: Some files were copied directly without being processed by migration, review MIGR0451W messages in the log file.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Application Server migration tooling did not process some files that were saved during WASPreUpgrade.  This is part of tooling to support migration from one machine to another and is an expected message when migrating to a different machine
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Review the log from migration WASPostUpgrade, and check for MIGR0451W messages in the log file.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0904W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="client.usage.message8" varFormat="Java">
    client.usage.message8=MIGR0904W: The enterprise archive (EAR) file {0} is not valid.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The enterprise archive (EAR) file name is either not an EAR file, or the contents and structure of the EAR file do not conform to a supported Java Platform Enterprise Edition, Java EE, specification.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the path is spelled correctly and that a valid EAR file is in that location.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0903W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="client.usage.message7" varFormat="Java">
    client.usage.message7=MIGR0903W: A value for attribute {0} is missing.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    No argument is provided for the specified attribute. For example, the parameter &apos;-traceFile&apos; was used, but &apos;-traceFile /some/path/to/log/file.txt&apos; was required.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Supply an argument for the specified parameter.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0901W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="client.usage.message5" varFormat="Java">
    client.usage.message5=MIGR0901W: You must use the -traceString parameter with the -traceFile parameter.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    When you specify a file trace, you must also specify the level of detail to write out to trace through the -traceString parameter.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Add the -traceString parameter. For example: -traceString &quot;*=all=enabled&quot; You must include the quotation marks.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0002I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="usage.post.line1" varFormat="Java">
    usage.post.line1=MIGR0002I: The class name of the WASPostUpgrade command is WASPostUpgrade
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    None
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0237I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.logging.read.success" varFormat="Java">
    advise.logging.read.success=MIGR0237I: The migration function read configuration file {0} successfully.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The configuration file was successfully read.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0286E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.logging.completed.with.errors" varFormat="Java">
    advise.logging.completed.with.errors=MIGR0286E: The migration failed to complete.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The migration failed to complete because errors occurred during migration.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    For additional information; check the log file that was created by the migration command in the logs directory, and correct the problems if required. The log name includes a time stamp, so check the log file with the latest creation date.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0234W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.logging.object.locate" varFormat="Java">
    advise.logging.object.locate=MIGR0234W: The migration function cannot locate object {0} of type {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The migration function cannot locate the object of the specified type when attempting to migrate it.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the object exists in the backup environment that results from the WASPreUpgrade command. If the problem persists, see the problem determination information on the Application Server Support Web page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0509I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.registering.with.new.adminagent" varFormat="Java">
    advise.registering.with.new.adminagent=MIGR0509I: Registering with new admin agent, make sure new admin agent process is running
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Since this is a managed application server, migration will try to register the application server to the new admin agent after migration of the appserver completes successfully.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that the new admin agent is running
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0346I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.logging.not.migrating.admin.app" varFormat="Java">
    advise.logging.not.migrating.admin.app=MIGR0346I: Object {0} of type {1} is not migrating; it is an administrative application.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    No administrative applications are migrated during the WASPostUpgrade process.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0345E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.invalid.WAS.combination" varFormat="Java">
    advise.invalid.WAS.combination=MIGR0345E: The migration backup directory is not compatible with this Application Server version.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The migration function cannot apply the version of Application Server that is designated as a backup in the specified directory. Either the version in the backup directory is not supported, or the WebSphere products are not compatible.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the combination of WebSphere product types is in the backup directory and that the current versions are compatible.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0420I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.logging.waspreupgrade.completed.successfully" varFormat="Java">
    advise.logging.waspreupgrade.completed.successfully=MIGR0420I: The first step of migration completed successfully.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The migration completed with no warning or error messages.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0520E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.unable.to.run.retrieveSigners" varFormat="Java">
    advise.unable.to.run.retrieveSigners=MIGR0520E: The migration function cannot exchange the signer certificates. Run the retrieveSigners command to exchange the certificates manually.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    During migration processing, the retrieveSigners command was attempted, but did not complete.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Manually run the retrieveSigners command. After the command completes successfully, re-run the WASPostUpgrade command if it did not complete.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0415E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.cell.not.match" varFormat="Java">
    advise.cell.not.match=MIGR0415E: The cell name {0} from the old configuration does not match the cell name {1} in the target profile. No migration can occur.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    While processing a deployment manager configuration the cell names of the old and new configurations did not match. This is not a supported migration path.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Perform migration again using a profile name with the matching cell name.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0212E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.logging.unable.to.create.directory.file" varFormat="Java">
    advise.logging.unable.to.create.directory.file=MIGR0212E: The migration function cannot create the directory {0}. A file with this name already exists.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An unexpected failure occurred during the creation of a directory.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Delete or rename the directory, and rerun the function using either the WASPreUpgrade or the WASPostUpgrade command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0389I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.logging.includeapps.false" varFormat="Java">
    advise.logging.includeapps.false=MIGR0389I: Applications will not be migrated, the -includeApps attribute was set to false.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    When the -includeApps attribute is set to false, no user applications are installed on the new version.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Install the application using the Application Server administration interfaces.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0521W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.not.migrating.zos.variable" varFormat="Java">
    advise.not.migrating.zos.variable=MIGR0521W: Not migrating variable {0} for zOS.  The default value will be used in the target profile.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The default value is recommended.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If a value other than the default is needed, the value can be updated after the migration.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0458E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.security.credentials.required.commandline" varFormat="Java">
    advise.security.credentials.required.commandline=MIGR0458E: Security is enabled in your prior configuration.  -username and -password are required arguments.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    WASPostUpgrade requires the user name and password to perform administrative functions against the prior configuration.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Rerun WASPostUpgrade and supply the user name and password of your prior configuration.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0532I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.commands.saved" varFormat="Java">
    advise.commands.saved=MIGR0532I: The commands have been saved
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The wsadmin commands have been saved
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No further action needed to install BLAs
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0221I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.logging.XMLConfig.readFile" varFormat="Java">
    advise.logging.XMLConfig.readFile=MIGR0221I: The migration function is reading the previously saved configuration file {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified configuration file from a previous Application Server version is being read. This file is the source for importing objects into the new Application Server configuration.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0505E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.need.adminagent.info" varFormat="Java">
    advise.need.adminagent.info=MIGR0505E: Need adminagent information from old and new versions
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    While migrating an appserver that is managed by an admin agent, the path, soap port, username and password of both the old and new admin agents are required.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Run the postupgrade command by passing in parameters for the old and new admin agents
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0575W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.library.migration.blocked" varFormat="Java">
    advise.library.migration.blocked=MIGR0575W: The following library was not migrated to avoid corrupting the new application server installation or target profile: {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Migrating the directory defined in the library path will corrupt the new installation or profile.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    You must manually migrate the library to its new location and update the library path to refer to a file or set of files instead of the directory. You can edit the library path in the administrative console or by using wsadmin scripting. For more information, see the documentation about managing a shared library and configuring a shared library using scripting.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0340W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.unable.to.deploy.app" varFormat="Java">
    advise.unable.to.deploy.app=MIGR0340W: Application {0} did not deploy.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The call to the wsadmin command failed, and the specified application is not deployed.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    To determine why the call to the wsadmin command failed, check the &lt;samp&gt;wsadmin.traceout&lt;/samp&gt; file in the logs directory of the installation root of the new version.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0417I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.adding.nodegroup.node" varFormat="Java">
    advise.adding.nodegroup.node=MIGR0417I: Node {0} is added to the default node group.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    All nodes must belong to a node group. This node is added to the default node group.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0366W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.enterprise.businessprocesscontainer.disabled" varFormat="Java">
    advise.enterprise.businessprocesscontainer.disabled=MIGR0366W: The business process container is disabled because the required IBM WebSphere Business Integration Server Foundation feature is not installed.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The IBM WebSphere Business Integration Server Foundation process choreographer feature must be installed to use the container.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Install the feature, and run the command again.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0404W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.nodeagent.conflict" varFormat="Java">
    advise.nodeagent.conflict=MIGR0404W: Do not use the node agent in the old configuration. It has been disabled.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The migration of a deployment manager to the latest release is successful. This migration creates the same port definitions that are in the existing Application Server configuration. The node agent of the existing configuration must be stopped before starting the deployment manager in the new configuration. The deployment manager of the new configuration must be used to manage the environment.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If you want to roll back to use the previous Application Server Version 5.1, 6.0 or 6.1 environment instead of Version 7.0, you must re-enable that configuration. To do this go to the /bin directory of the previous Version 5.1, 6.0 or 6.1 installation and run the migrationDisablementReversal.jacl script.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0452W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.unresolved.files" varFormat="Java">
    advise.unresolved.files=MIGR0452W: Migration could not locate a file matching {0} when migrating {1}.  The reference has not been modified.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Migration found a reference to a file that could not be found as part of migration.  This means the file was either not backed up during WASPreUpgrade or not copied forward during WASPostUpgrade.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Copy the missing file to the location specified and rerun migration, or update the reference after migration has completed.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0397W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.jmsserver.to.jetstream.migration.failed" varFormat="Java">
    advise.jmsserver.to.jetstream.migration.failed=MIGR0397W: Service Integration Bus migration failed.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The migration of Embedded JMS to Service Integration Bus failed to migrate properly.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See the information center for further action; if the answer is not found in the information center, contact IBM support.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0572W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.library.system.root.dir" varFormat="Java">
    advise.library.system.root.dir=MIGR0572W: The library was not migrated because the following library path refers to a system root directory: {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Library paths that refer to a system root directory are not automatically migrated.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the library is at the defined path, you must manually migrate the library to its new location and update the library path. Otherwise, remove the library path. You can edit the library path in the administrative console or by using wsadmin scripting. For more information, see the documentation about managing a shared library and configuring a shared library using scripting.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0477I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="sync.required" varFormat="Java">
    sync.required=MIGR0477I: The Deployment Manager&apos;s configuration has been updated.  A synchronization with the effected Managed nodes must occur before using these updated settings.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Deployment Manager&apos;s configuration has been updated, but in order to have the settings consistent a synchronization must occur either automatically by the Deployment Manager or manually invoked.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Synchronize the Deployment Manager&apos;s configuration with the effected Managed nodes.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0426E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.zos.invalid.direct.invocation" varFormat="Java">
    advise.zos.invalid.direct.invocation=MIGR0426E: {0} command not supported on z/OS for direct invocation from the Unix shell.  Use z/OS Migration Management Tool under WebSphere Customization Tools instead.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The direct invocation of WASPreUpgrade and WASPostUpgrade is not supported.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Use z/OS Migration Management Tool under WebSphere Customization Tools to create your migration definitions.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0332I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.logging.updating.authmech" varFormat="Java">
    advise.logging.updating.authmech=MIGR0332I: The attributes of the {0} authentication mechanism are updating.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The attributes of the specified authentication mechanism are being updated.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0327E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="usage.earmigrate.failure" varFormat="Java">
    usage.earmigrate.failure=MIGR0327E: A failure occurred with {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An unexpected error occurred.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the user ID has sufficient file system authority to run the migration program. If the problem persists, see the problem determination information on the Application Server Support Web page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0479E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="host.value.missing.from.serverindex" varFormat="Java">
    host.value.missing.from.serverindex=MIGR0479E: The host value for the endpoint {0} in  of the server {1} is invalid or missing.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Invalid host information exist for the specified entry.  This information is required for migration processing.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the host information for the specified server in the serverindex in the master repository (which resides on the Deployment Manager in distributed configurations), and then rerun migration.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0313E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.invalid.config" varFormat="Java">
    advise.invalid.config=MIGR0313E: More than one {0} directory exists; specify a directory using the {1} parameter.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    More than one directory exists in the Application Server configuration.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Rerun the command specifying the requested directory name by including the noted parameter.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0482E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.cmd.line.pre.requires.currentwasdirectory.and.backup" varFormat="Java">
    advise.cmd.line.pre.requires.currentwasdirectory.and.backup=MIGR0482E: You must specify the &lt;backupDirectoryName&gt; and &lt;currentWebSphereDirectory&gt;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    WASPreUpgrade requires that the &lt;backupDirectoryName&gt; and &lt;currentWebSphereDirectory&gt; be specified.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Run WASPreUpgrade again supplying the required parameters.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0280W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.brbeans.disabled" varFormat="Java">
    advise.brbeans.disabled=MIGR0280W: Application {0} is disabled because the required IBM WebSphere Business Integration Server Foundation feature is not installed.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The business rule beans that are featured in IBM WebSphere Business Integration Server Foundation must be installed to run business rule beans applications.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Install the feature, and rerun the command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="MIGR0496W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="advise.specific.application.failed.to.migrate" varFormat="Java">
    advise.specific.application.failed.to.migrate=MIGR0496W: The migration of {0} terminated unexpectedly.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    During the application migration process, one or more applications failed to migrate.  Refer to the log files for details.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If possible, correct the problems that are recorded in the log files. One or more applications might need to be installed manually.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<!-- END MESSAGES -->
</TMSSource>
