<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/css" href="../../resources/stylesheets/wasmsgxml.css"?>
<TMSSource name="TivoliMessages" tmsVersion="1.0" xml:lang="en">
<!-- CMVC MSG File Name = ws/code/hamanager.impl/src/com/ibm/ws/hamanager/nls/HAManagerMessages.nlsprops -->
<!-- DO NOT EDIT THIS FILE - This file was generated by the XML/Html & Property emitter -->
<!-- BEGIN MESSAGES -->
<Message ID="HMGR0235W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0235" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0235=HMGR0235W: The core group member {0} reported a problem. The member reporting the problem logged the reason using message {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This process received a message that another core group member has reported a problem.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    For more information, locate the specified message ID in the log file for the core group member that reported the problem. If necessary, stop or terminate the failing process.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0234W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0234" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0234=HMGR0234W: The active coordinator detected that the state rebuild operation did not complete within the expected time.  Waiting for state messages from the following process set: {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The active coordinator was in the process of rebuilding state, but did not receive the expected state messages from all core group processes within the expected time limit.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Review the log files for the specified set of processes that failed to send state messages to determine the problem.  If necessary, stop or terminate the failing processes.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0233E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0233" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0233=HMGR0233E: The active coordinator received a message from {0} with inconsistent {1} state for subject {2}, the post contents were {3} with {4} existing state.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An internal inconsistency was detected. The active coordinator ignores the incoming message.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    The root cause of the problem appears to be an internal error. See the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page, http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support, for help in determining the cause of this problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0232E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0232" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0232=HMGR0232E: The active coordinator received a message from {0} indicating this process is a core group bridge; however, there are no core group bridges {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An internal inconsistency was detected. The active coordinator ignores the incoming message.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    The root cause of the problem appears to be an internal error. See the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page, http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support, for help in determining the cause of this problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0231W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0231" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0231=HMGR0231W: The active coordinator detected a unexpected condition while processing the {0} component of a message with {1} mode from {2}, a {3} was expected. Current state is {4}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This is an indication of internal state mismatch between coregroup members and should not frequently occur, the message is ignored by the active coordinator.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    The root cause of the problem appears to be an internal error. See the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page, http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support, for help in determining the cause of this problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0230E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0230" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0230=HMGR0230E: Core group bridge ownership of subject {0} is in contention between bridges {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An internal inconsistency was detected.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    The root cause of the problem appears to be an internal error. See the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page, http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support, for help in determining the cause of this problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR1310E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR1310" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR1310=HMGR1310E: The MBean operation did not complete within {0} seconds.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The high availability manager did not receive a response to a MBean operation within the time limit set for a JMX command.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Retry the failing command.  If the problem persists, see the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page, http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support, for help in determining the cause of this problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0229I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0229" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0229=HMGR0229I: A new data stack view has been installed. The view identifier is {0}. The data stack name is {1} and the number of members in the new view is {2}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Processes have been added or removed from the existing view.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0228I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0228" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0228=HMGR0228I: The Coordinator is not an Active Coordinator for core group {0}. The active coordinator set is {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The coordinator in this process is not an active coordinator for the specified core group.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0227E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0227" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0227=HMGR0227E: The request to create a Core Group Bridge on this server has failed. The request is invalid.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A core group bridge can only be created on a server that is part of a network deployment configuration.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Create the core group bridge on an eligible server.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0226I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0226" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0226=HMGR0226I: The core stack configuration parameter {0} has been set to {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A core stack custom property was used to override the default value for the specified configuration parameter.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0225E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0225" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0225=HMGR0225E: A parsing error occurred for core group custom property {0}. The value is {1} and the exception is {2}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified value is not valid for this custom property.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See the product documentation to determine the values that can be specified for this custom property.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0224E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0224" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0224=HMGR0224E: The core group custom property {0} is out of range. Value {1} is not allowed.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified value is not valid for this custom property.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See the product documentation to determine the values that can be specified for this custom property.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0223W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0223" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0223=HMGR0223W: An unrecoverable error has occurred on the DCS core stack for core group {0}. The exception is {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An error was received from the DCS transport channel.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the error does not resolve itself, see the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page, http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support, for help in determining the cause of this problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0222W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0222" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0222=HMGR0222W: A request to move the active member of a group from one server to another cannot be performed. The group is not stable. The group is {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The high availability group is currently undergoing a state transition that cannot be interrupted.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Wait for the transition to complete and retry the operation.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0221W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0221" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0221=HMGR0221W: A request to activate or deactivate a member cannot be performed. The requested state is {0}, the member identifier is {1} and the group is {2}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified member could not be activated or deactivated because it is already in that state.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If you need to deactivate a member, select a member that is in the active state, and retry the operation. If you need to activate a member, select a member that is in the inactive state, and retry the operation.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0220W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0220" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0220=HMGR0220W: A request to move the active member of a group from one server to another cannot be performed. One of the members does not exist. The member identifier is {0} and the group is {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The identified member was not moved because it is not a member of the specified core group.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Select a member that is defined as a member of this core group, and retry the operation.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR1309E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR1309" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR1309=HMGR1309E: The group name string is invalid.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified high availability group name must be either a comma delimited string of name=value pairs, or an asterisk character.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a valid group name, a valid subset of a group name, or an asterisk character, and retry the command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR1308E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR1308" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR1308=HMGR1308E: An unexpected failure occurred.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    During processing of a high availability manager MBean, an unexpected error condition occurred.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Retry the failing command.  If the problem persists, see the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page, http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support, for help in determining the cause of this problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR1307E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR1307" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR1307=HMGR1307E: The member {0} is not in {1} state.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The high availability manager MBean operation cannot be performed because the indicated member is not in the required state.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Either wait for the member to reach the required state, and then retry this command, or specify a different high availability group member when you issue the command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR1306E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR1306" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR1306=HMGR1306E: The specified member {0} does not exist.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified Node and ServerName parameters do not match any existing high availability group members.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a valid member and retry the command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR1305E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR1305" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR1305=HMGR1305E: The specified group does not exist.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The name specified for the GroupName parameter does not match any existing high availability groups.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a valid high availability group name for the GroupName parameter, and retry the command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR1304E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR1304" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR1304=HMGR1304E: The GroupName parameter must specify a group governed by a {0} policy.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The policy for the specified high availability group is not of the required type.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify the name of a high availability group that is associated with the indicated policy type as the value for the GroupName parameter, and retry the command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR1303E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR1303" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR1303=HMGR1303E: A send message problem has occurred.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A problem has occurred while attempting to send a message to the active coordinator.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Retry the command.  If the problem persists, see the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page, http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support, for help in determining the cause of this problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR1302E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR1302" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR1302=HMGR1302E: View is changing. Retry command after the view has stabilized.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A high availability manager MBean operation could not be completed because the view is changing. The view might be changing because servers are being started, or servers have been stopped or have failed.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Wait for the core group view to stabilize and then retry the command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR1301E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR1301" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR1301=HMGR1301E: No active coordinators for core group {0} could be found.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A high availability manager MBean operation could not be completed because no active coordinator could be found for the core group.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that at least two of the servers that are members of this core group are running.  If two servers are running, check their messages log files for additional messages that might indicate a problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR1300E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR1300" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR1300=HMGR1300E: {0} parameter is null.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A high availability manager MBean operation detected a null parameter.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check the product documentation for the correct settings for the specified paramenter, and retry the command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0219I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0219" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0219=HMGR0219I: An unrecognized view change event was received from the DCS transport. The view identifier is {0} and the event is {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The type of the event is not recognized. The high availability manager could not respond to the view change event that it received from the DCS transport because it did not recognize the specified event type.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page, http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support, for help in determining the cause of this problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0218I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0218" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0218=HMGR0218I: A new core group view has been installed. The core group is {0}. The view identifier is {1}. The number of members in the new view is {2}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Processes have been added or removed from the existing view.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0213E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0213" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0213=HMGR0213E: A request to activate or deactivate a group member was made while the policy was unstable. The GroupName is {0} The policy type is {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The high availability manager detected an internal inconsistency.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page, http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support, for help in determining the cause of this problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0212I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0212" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0212=HMGR0212I: A request to remove the group member for server {0} from the group state aggregion for group name {1} cannot be honored. The group does not currently exist.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The high availability manager detected an internal inconsistency.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0211E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0211" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0211=HMGR0211E: Unable to create the group state aggregation object on the active coordinator for group {0} in response to a group join from server {1}. The policy for the group cannot be determined. The exception is {2}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The policy for the specified high availability group cannot be found on the server. However, the policy was available on the server when the join was done.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0210I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0210" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0210=HMGR0210I: Unable to run the policy for group {0}. The group may have been deleted.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    In response to a change in the state of a high availability group, the high availability manager tried to apply the policy for that group. The policy could not be applied because the high availability group currently has no members, and might have been deleted.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0209E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0209" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0209=HMGR0209E: An internal error occured while processing the policy for group {0}. The exception is {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The high availability manager detected an internal logic error. See the description of the exception for more information.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page, http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support, for help in determining the cause of this problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0208E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0208" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0208=HMGR0208E: The Coordinator could not process a message. The coordinator is in FAILED state. The message is {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The high availability manager has detected an internal logic error.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page, http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support, for help in determining the cause of this problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0207I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0207" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0207=HMGR0207I: The Coordinator was previously an Active Coordinator for core group {0} but has lost leadership. The active coordinator set is {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The coordinator in this process is no longer an active coordinator.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0206I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0206" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0206=HMGR0206I: The Coordinator is an Active Coordinator for core group {0}. The active coordinator set is {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The coordinator in this process has been elected as an active coordinator.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0205E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0205" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0205=HMGR0205E: The Coordinator could not process a message. The state and the message are inconstent. The state is {0} and the message is {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The high availability manager has detected an internal logic error.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page, http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support, for help in determining the cause of this problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0204E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0204" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0204=HMGR0204E: The Coordinator could not process a message. The message is {0} and the exception is {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The high availability manager has detected an internal logic error.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page, http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support, for help in determining the cause of this problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0203E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0203" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0203=HMGR0203E: The active Coordinator was found to be in an invalid state and could not process a message. The state is {0}, the message is {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The high availability manager has detected an internal logic error.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page, http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support, for help in determining the cause of this problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0201E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0201" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0201=HMGR0201E: A communication exception occured while sending a message. The message type is {0}. The GroupName is {1} and the exception is {2}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An attempt to send a message failed with a exception in the communication stack. See the description of the exception for more information.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the stack trace to determine the cause of the exception. Ensure that all network communications are operating properly. If the root cause of the problem cannot be determined, see the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page, http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support, for help in determining the cause of this problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR3002E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR3002" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR3002=HMGR3002E: An unexpected condition was encountered during this admin task. The class is {0}, the method is {1} and internal details {2}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An unexpected internal error occurred. See the description of the specified exception for more information.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the stack trace to determine the cause of the exception. If the root cause of the problem cannot be determined, see the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page, http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support, for help in determining the cause of this problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR3001E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR3001" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR3001=HMGR3001E: A failure occured while removing server {0} on node {1} from core group {2}. The exception is {3}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified server was not removed from the indicated core group. See the exception stack trace for more information.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the root cause of the problem and retry the operation. If the root cause cannot be determined, see the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page, http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support, for help in determining the cause of this problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR3000E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR3000" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR3000=HMGR3000E: A failure occured while adding server {0} on node {1} to core group {2}. The exception is {3}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified server was not added to the indicated core group. See the exception stack trace for more information.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the root cause of the problem and retry the operation. If the root cause cannot be determined, see the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page, http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support, for help in determining the cause of this problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0099E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0099" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0099=HMGR0099E: This process received an updated configuration document from the {0} and it is no longer a member of core group {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This process was given an updated configuration document and it was removed from the core group it was started in.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Synchronize the nodeagent that this process is located on with the deployment manager. After synchronization, restart this process.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0098E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0098" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0098=HMGR0098E: Unable to obtain a reference to the admin service.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Unable to obtain a reference to the admin service.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Contact IBM Service.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0097E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0097" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0097=HMGR0097E: Unknown error was encountered when trying to push configuration to core group {0}. See exception for more information. Exception: {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An unknown error was encountered when trying to push configuration to a core group member, the core group did not receive new configuration data.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the stack trace to determine the cause of the exception. If the root cause of the problem cannot be determined, contact IBM service.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0096E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0096" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0096=HMGR0096E: An error was encountered when trying to pull configuration from Deployment Manager. See exception for more information. Exception: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An error was encountered when trying to pull configuration from the Deployment Manager, this process may be running on old configuration data.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the stack trace to determine the cause of the exception. If the root cause of the problem cannot be determined, contact IBM service.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0095I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0095" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0095=HMGR0095I: Unable to locate any running processes for core group {0} that are not in single server mode. Core group configuration was not updated dynamically.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Deployment Manager was unable to locate any HAManager MBeans on a process that is not running in single server mode for the specified core group.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ignore this message if there are no running processes, or if all running processes are in single server mode. Otherwise ensure that node agents are running when performing configuration changes.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0094E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0094" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0094=HMGR0094E: The query for MBean {0} failed.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Malformed ObjectName exception encountered.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Contact IBM Service.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0093E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0093" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0093=HMGR0093E: Unable to create an Admin Client connection to the deployment manager. Exception: {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Unable to create an Admin Client connection to the deployment manager.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Contact IBM Service.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0092W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0092" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0092=HMGR0092W: Unable to get HA Manager MBean on the Deployment Manager, object name used for query is {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Unable to get the HA Manager MBean on the Deployment Manager.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the Deployment Manager is running, otherwise contact IBM Service.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0091I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0091" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0091=HMGR0091I: An outdated core group configuration was read from the repository. The current configuration is {0}. The configuration just read is {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The core group configuration might not have been updated correctly.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0090W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0090" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0090=HMGR0090W: An attempt to update the High Availability manager configuration has failed. The required documents are not available on this node.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The core group configuration could not be updated correctly.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Manually synchronize the configuration from the master repository on the deployment manager. Application servers on the affected node might need to be recycled.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0089E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0089" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0089=HMGR0089E: A configuration available message could not be delivered. The configuration version is {0} and the exception is {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The core group configuration could not be updated correctly.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page, http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support, for help in determining the cause of this problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0088I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0088" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0088=HMGR0088I: HA Policy information from the new core group configuration was not applied. There were {0} errors in the new configuration.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Policy errors are tolerated when the configuration is read, but these errors prevent policy information from being updated.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Scan the SystemOut.log file for information related to the parsing errors and correct the errors.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0087I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0087" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0087=HMGR0087I: An unrecoverable error was encountered while merging the core group configuration. The version is {0}. The exception is {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The high availability manager encountered an unrecoverable error while updating the core group configuration settings.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Synchronize the configuration to the node in question, then restart the server. If synchronizing the configuration does not solve the problem, see the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page, http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support, for additional help in determining the cause of this problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0086I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0086" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0086=HMGR0086I: This server is updating its core group configuration. The new document version is {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The core group document is being updated.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0085I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0085" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0085=HMGR0085I: This server received a message that a new core group document is available. This server is already running on that document version.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The server is already using the new core group document.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0083E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0083" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0083=HMGR0083E: An error was encountered merging configuration information. The element type is {0}. The exception is {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The coregroup.xml configuration document contains a syntax error or has been corrupted.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page, http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support, for help in determining the cause of this problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0081E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0081" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0081=HMGR0081E: An error was received while reloading a configuration document. The document name is {0} and the exception is {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified configuration document has an unknown problem.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Scan the SystemOut.log file for error messages relating to failures in loading this configuration document. See the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page, http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support, for additional help in determining the cause of this problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0080E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0080" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0080=HMGR0080E: Unable to obtain a reference to the ConfigRepository. Configuration documents cannot be updated dynamically.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An unknown problem exists with the ConfigRepository management bean definition table.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page, http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support, for help in determining the cause of this problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0071E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0071" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0071=HMGR0071E: The coreGroupName attribute in the HAManagerService is null.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The coreGroupName attribute must be set to the core group with which this server is associated. Null is not allowed.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page, http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support, for help in determining the cause of this problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0070E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0070" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0070=HMGR0070E: An error was encountered while processing the hamanagerservice.xml document. The exception is {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The hamanagerservice.xml configuration document contains a syntax error or has been corrupted.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page, http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support, for help in determining the cause of this problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0503I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0503" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0503=HMGR0503I: The message path of the internal data stack named {0} is highly congested.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The message path of the internal data stack that is used by the partitioned managed group has reached its upper congestion limit.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0502E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0502" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0502=HMGR0502E: An error occurred while using the internal data stack named {0}. The exception is {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The high availability manager detected problem with the internal data stack that is used by the partitioned managed group. See the exception stack trace for more information.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the root cause of the problem. If the root cause cannot be determined and corrected, see the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page, http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support, for help in determining the cause of this problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0501E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0501" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0501=HMGR0501E: Encountered an abnormal termination of the internal data stack named {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The internal data stack of the view synchronous high-availability manager group encountered an unexpected termination event. See the exception stack trace for more information.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the root cause of the problem. If the root cause cannot be determined and corrected, see the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page, http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support, for help in determining the cause of this problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0064W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0064" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0064=HMGR0064W: Resolution of IP Addresses for host name {0} found only the loopback address. The loopback address will be used.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    There might be a problem with the host name or domain name service (DNS) name resolution. Under normal circumstances, a non-loopback address is expected.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the host name or the DNS name resolution problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0063W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0063" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0063=HMGR0063W: The DCS_UNICAST_ADDRESS end point for server {0} on node {1} has an invalid value. {2} Will be used instead.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A null or empty string was found. Valid values include the host name, a textual IP address, or *.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Enter the proper host name in the DCS_UNICAST_ADDRESS field.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0062I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0062" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0062=HMGR0062I: A DCS_UNICAST_ADDRESS end point does not exist for server {0} on node {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This end point is required and should be allocated when the process is created.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page, http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support, for help in determining the cause of this problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0061E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0061" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0061=HMGR0061E: An error was encountered while processing the coregroup. The entry for server {0}, node {1} failed. The exception is {2}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An incorrect server entry exists in the core group configuration document.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See the description of the specified exception for more information about what caused the problem, and correct the problem. See the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page, http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support, for additional help in determining the cause of this problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0060W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0060" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0060=HMGR0060W: An error was encountered while obtaining the host and port information for server {0} on node {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The serverindex.xml file for the specified node appears to be out of date.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem does not resolve itself, perform a full resynchronize from the master repository.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0049E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0049" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0049=HMGR0049E: A duplicate policy name was found in the configuration data. The policy name is {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Two policy definitions were found that have the same name. Each policy definition must have a unique name.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Assign a different name to one of the policies. This name must be unique from any other policy name.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0048E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0048" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0048=HMGR0048E: A failure occurred while attempting to create a default HAManager policy. The name of the policy is {0} and the exception is {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An internal initialization error occurred. See the description of the exception for more information.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Look for previous messages in the SystemOut.log file that contain initialization failure information. If, after analyzing these messages, you cannot determine the cause of the export problem,See the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page, http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support, for additional help in determining the cause of this problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0047E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0047" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0047=HMGR0047E: An error occured while processing the policy configuration information. The specified PolicyFactory class {0} was not instantiable. The exception is {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The name of the policy factory specified in the configuration data is incorrect.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Either the policy factory name is entered incorrectly or that policy factory class is not available on this server. Determine which of these situations has occurred, and correct the problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0046E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0046" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0046=HMGR0046E: An error occured while processing the policy configuration information. The specified PolicyFactory class {0} is not a PolicyFactory.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The name of the policy factory specified in the configuration data is incorrect.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Enter a valid name for the policy factory class.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0045W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0045" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0045=HMGR0045W: The server list for policy {0} is empty. This policy requires at least one server.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The server list for the specified policy is empty.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the configuration state.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0044E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0044" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0044=HMGR0044E: An unrecoverable error was encountered while loading HA Policies. The exception is {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    See the description of the specified exception for more information about the root cause of the problem.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the cause of the problem. See the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page, http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support, for help in determining the cause of this problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0043E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0043" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0043=HMGR0043E: All HA Policies failed parsing.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    High availability policies were located in the core group but none of the policies could be successfully parsed.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the configuration state.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0042W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0042" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0042=HMGR0042W: An error was encountered reading policy attributes from the configuration for policy {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The configuration state is not valid. The high availability manager could not read the attributes for a high availability policy.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the configuration state.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0041E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0041" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0041=HMGR0041E: An HA Policy without a name was found in the core group.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    All high availability policies must have a unique name.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Assign the policy a unique name.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0040I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0040" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0040=HMGR0040I: No HA Policies were found in the core group.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The core group configuration read by this server did not contain any high availability policies.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0035I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0035" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0035=HMGR0035I: Core group {0} is starting with a non-default liveness provider. The factory name is {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The core group liveness provider has been changed from the default setting.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required. Informational only.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR5016E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR5016" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR5016=HMGR5016E: An attempt to inform the controller that the servant initialization completed has failed. The exception is {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An unrecoverable error has been detected.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page, http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support, for help in determining the cause of this problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0034I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0034" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0034=HMGR0034I: Core group {0} is starting with a discovery interval of {1} seconds.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The core group discovery interval has been changed from the default setting.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required. Informational only.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR5015E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR5015" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR5015=HMGR5015E: An attempt to create a Server Power Controller failed. The class name is {0} and the exception is {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An unrecoverable error has been detected.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page, http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support, for help in determining the cause of this problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0033I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0033" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0033=HMGR0033I: Core group {0} is starting with a heart beat transmission interval of {1} milliseconds and a heart beat timeout of {2} milliseconds.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The core group heart beating has been changed from the default setting.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required. Informational only.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR5014E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR5014" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR5014=HMGR5014E: An attempt to remove Bulletin Board posts for subject {0} failed. There are no posts for this subject.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An inconsistent internal state has been detected.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page, http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support, for help in determining the cause of this problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0032I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0032" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0032=HMGR0032I: Core group {0} is starting with a configured transport memory size of {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The core group transport memory size has been changed from the default setting.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required. Informational only.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR5013E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR5013" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR5013=HMGR5013E: An internal error was encountered. The class is {0}, the method is {1}, the local state is {2}. the cause is {3} and the stack trace is {4}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An unexpected condition occurred.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check the stack trace for a message that may help indicate the cause of the problem. If the problem cannot be solved, contact IBM Service.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0031E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0031" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0031=HMGR0031E: A conflicting IP address and port has been detected for the DCS_UNICAST_ADDRESS end point. {0} members are configured to use the IP address and port combination of  {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Multiple core group members that share the same IP address and port were detected. However, each core group member must have a unique IP address and  port combination.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the problem by assigning a different port to each of the conflicting core group members.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR5012E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR5012" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR5012=HMGR5012E: An internal error was encountered while processing a HAManager MBean request.  The group name is {0}, the member was {1} and the member action was {2}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An internal inconsistency was detected. The high availability manager MBean request could not be processed. No recovery was possible.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page, http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support, for help in determining the cause of this problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0030E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0030" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0030=HMGR0030E: The configuration document {0} could not be read from the repository.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Either the configuration XML file could not be found, or is corrupted, or there is a problem with the repository service.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page, http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support, for help in determining the cause of this problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR5011E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR5011" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR5011=HMGR5011E: An attempt to initialize the UserCallbacks service failed. The service is already initialized. The execution stack trace is {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An initialization operation failed.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page, http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support, for help in determining the cause of this problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR5010E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR5010" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR5010=HMGR5010E: An attempt to reconstruct a streamed map has failed. The map has no entries. The execution stack trace is {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A streamed map could not be reconstructed.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page, http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support, for help in determining the cause of this problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0029E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0029" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0029=HMGR0029E: The network configuration for process {0} has a port value of {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The port specified for this process is not valid.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page, http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support, for help in determining the cause of this problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0028E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0028" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0028=HMGR0028E: A duplicate DCS_UNICAST_ADDRESS port has been detected. Members {0} and {1} on host {2} are both configured to use port {3}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Multiple processes on the same host cannot be configured to use the same port.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the problem by changing the port assignment for one of the core group members.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR5009E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR5009" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR5009=HMGR5009E: The host name for a process has changed. The execution stack trace is {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A configuration update operation failed.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page, http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support, for help in determining the cause of this problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0027W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0027" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0027=HMGR0027W: A duplicate host to IP Address mapping has been detected. IP Address {0} has a mapping to host names {1} and {2}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An IP Address that maps to multiple hosts is unusual. The duplicate mapping might be intentional and required to support another product such as the IBM Edge Server.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the duplicate mapping is unintentional, correct the mapping. If the mapping is intentional, configure the DCS_UNICAST_ADDRESS endpoints for all processes in the core group to use a specific, unique IP Address.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR5008E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR5008" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR5008=HMGR5008E: A bulletin board change notification has been received, but there is no data. The execution stack trace is {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A bulletin board operation failed.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page, http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support, for help in determining the cause of this problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0026E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0026" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0026=HMGR0026E: An invalid value for an HA Manager configuration attribute was found. The document is {0}, the attribute is {1} and the value found is {2}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified attribute value is not valid. A default value has been assigned.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the specified attribute value.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR5007E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR5007" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR5007=HMGR5007E: An attempt to use the DCS provider to send a message has failed. The execution stack trace is {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A distribution and consistency services (DCS) send message operation was requested, but the caller has no identity.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page, http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support, for help in determining the cause of this problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0025W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0025" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0025=HMGR0025W: An invalid value for an HA Manager configuration attribute was found. The document is {0}, the attribute is {1} and the value found is {2}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified attribute value is not valid. A default value has been assigned.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the specified attribute value.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR5006E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR5006" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR5006=HMGR5006E: The DCS provider has not been initialized. The execution stack trace is {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A distribution and consistency services (DCS) operation was requested, but the DCS provider has not been initialized.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page, http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support, for help in determining the cause of this problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0024W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0024" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0024=HMGR0024W: An error was encountered while looking up the IP address for the host name of a core group member. The host name is {0} and the exception is {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The high availability manager was unable to resolve the IP address for the indicated host. Either the host is unknown or has mappings to duplicate IP addresses.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See the description of the specified exception for more information. Correct the host name lookup problem and retry.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR5005E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR5005" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR5005=HMGR5005E: No active coordinators were found. The execution stack is {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An inconsistent internal state was detected. Processing should not continue.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page, http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support, for help in determining the cause of this problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0023E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0023" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0023=HMGR0023E: An error was encountered reading a untyped attribute from the configuration. The name is {0}, the value is {1} and the type is {2}. The exception is {3}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The configuration state is not valid. The specified attribute could not be read.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the configuration state.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR5004E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR5004" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR5004=HMGR5004E: An unexpected internal state was encountered while attempting to activate a group member. No group members exists. The group is {0} and the execution stack is {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An inconsistent internal state was detected. No group member was activated because there were no members defined for this high availability group. Processing should not continue.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page, http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support, for help in determining the cause of this problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0022E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0022" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0022=HMGR0022E: An error was encountered reading a typed attribute from the configuration. The name is {0}, the value is {1} and the type is {2}. The exception is {3}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The configuration state is not valid. The specified attribute could not be read.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the configuration state.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR5003E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR5003" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR5003=HMGR5003E: An internal error was encountered while processing a group membership change for group name {0}. The old member was {1} and the new member was {2}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An internal inconsistency was detected. The high availability group membership change was not processed. No recovery was possible.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page, http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support, for help in determining the cause of this problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0021E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0021" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0021=HMGR0021E: An error was encountered while processing the core group document. The exception is {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The coregroup.xml configuration document contains a syntax error or has been corrupted.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page, http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support, for help in determining the cause of this problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR5002E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR5002" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR5002=HMGR5002E: An internal error was encountered while processing a group member state change for group name {0}. The old state was {1} and the new state was {2}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An internal inconsistency was detected. The member state change could not be completed. No recovery was possible.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page, http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support, for help in determining the cause of this problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0020E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0020" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0020=HMGR0020E: The configuration document {0} could not be read from the repository.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Either the configuration XML file could not be found, is corrupted, or there is a problem with the repository service.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page, http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support, for help in determining the cause of this problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR5001E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR5001" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR5001=HMGR5001E: An invalid configuration action has been attempted. The execution stack is {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An inconsistent internal state was detected. The requested configuration change could not be made. Processing cannot continue.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page, http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support, for help in determining the cause of this problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR1109I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR1109" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR1109=HMGR1109I: Unable to make group consistent with the specified policy. There are no available members to deactivate. The group name is {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    While performing policy processing, the high availability manager discovered that the specified high availability group is not consistent with its policy. The high availability manager tried to correct the problem, but was unable to make the high availability group consistent with its policy.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    This is probably a temporaty condition that will be resolved when current high availability group members reach a stable state. If the problem persists, check for problems with the component that is associated with the high availability group name.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR5000E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR5000" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR5000=HMGR5000E: An attempt to access configuration data has failed. The configuration data has not been initialized. The execution stack is {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An inconsistent internal state was detected. The requested configuration data could not be accessed. Processing cannot continue.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page, http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support, for help in determining the cause of this problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR1108I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR1108" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR1108=HMGR1108I: Unable to make group consistent with the specified policy. There are no available members to activate. The group name is {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    While performing policy processing, the high availability manager discovered that the specified high availability group is not consistent with its policy. The high availability manager tried to correct the problem, but was unable to make the high availability group consistent with its policy.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    This is probably a temporaty condition that will be resolved when current high availability group members reach a stable state. If the problem persists, check for problems with the component that is associated with the high availability group name.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR1107I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR1107" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR1107=HMGR1107I: Unable to make group consistent with the specified policy. There are no available members to activate. The group name is {0}. The exception is {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    While performing policy processing, the high availability manager discovered that the specified high availability group is not consistent with its policy. The high availability manager tried to correct the problem, but was unable to make the high availability group consistent with its policy.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required. If this message frequently reoccurs, check previous messages for the original source of the problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR1106I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR1106" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR1106=HMGR1106I: An out of specification group was found while processing the policy for group {0}. Too many members are active.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    While performing policy processing, the high availability manager discovered that more members of the specified high availability group are active then should be active.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required. If this message frequently reoccurs, check previous messages for the original source of the problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR1105I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR1105" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR1105=HMGR1105I: Group {0} active member moved to {1} in {2} milliseconds
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The HAManager MBean migrateActiveMember operation was used to move the active member.  The move was completed in the specified time.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0013E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0013" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0013=HMGR0013E: An unexpected error has occurred while trying to create a BBSON bulletin board factory. The exception is {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An unexpected error occurred while loading a class. See the exception for more details.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page, http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support, for help in determining the cause of this problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0012E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0012" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0012=HMGR0012E: The bulletin board service is configured incorrectly. Both the High Availability Manager and BBSON are configured to be the bulletin board provider.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A configuration problem exists. Other HMGR messages in the log  indicate which configuration settings are incorrect.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the configuration and restart the server.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0011I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0011" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0011=HMGR0011I: The High Availability Manager is configured to be the bulletin board provider.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    You must enable the High Availability Manager for the bulletin board to function properly.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0010I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0010" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0010=HMGR0010I: The High Availability Manager has been disabled. Services that rely on the High Availability Manager might not work as expected.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The administrator has disabled the High Availability Manager.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0009E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0009" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0009=HMGR0009E: An HA Manager configuration update was processed and this server is no longer a member of core group {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The server appears to have been deleted or moved to a new core group. Running servers must not be deleted or moved to a new core group.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify the core group configuration and determine why this server is not a member of the specified core group.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0008W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0008" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0008=HMGR0008W: The high availability manager has detected that core group {0} has {1} configured processes. The recommended limit is {2}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This warning message alerts the user that they need to be aware of the implications of having a large core group. Failing to due so may result in degraded WebSphere performance.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See the IBM information center for more information regarding Core group scaling considerations.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0007W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0007" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0007=HMGR0007W: An attempt to start High Availability Manager PMI statistics failed. The exception is {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The high availability manager management bean that collects PMI statistics failed to start.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page, http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support, for help in determining the cause of this problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0006I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0006" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0006=HMGR0006I: Starting the transport for Core Stack {0} using IP Address {1}, port {2}, transport type {3}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The high availability manager communication transport is starting.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0005I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0005" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0005=HMGR0005I: The Single Server DCS Core Stack transport has been started for core group {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Single Server DCS Core Stack transport was started for the core group because the high availability manager was disabled on the server.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0004E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0004" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0004=HMGR0004E: An attempt to start an HA Manager Management Bean (MBean) failed. The MBean id is {0}. The exception is {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The high availability manager management bean failed to start.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page, http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support, for help in determining the cause of this problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0003E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0003" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0003=HMGR0003E: Unable to export service {0}. The service was not found.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The indicated service could not be exported. Recovery was not possible.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Look for previous messages in the SystemOut.log file that contain initialization failure information. If, after analyzing these messages, you cannot determine the cause of the export problem, see the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0002E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0002" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0002=HMGR0002E: HA Manager services on this process were not started. This server is not a member of core group {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The high availability manager requires that every server be a member of a core group. Since this server is not a member of a core group, the high availability manager services cannot be started.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify the core group configuration and determine why this server is not a member of the specified core group.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0001I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0001" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0001=HMGR0001I: The DCS Core Stack transport has been started for core group {0}. There are {1} members.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The high availabilty manager communication transport has started.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0302W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0302" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0302=HMGR0302W: Multiple policies match the group named {0}, Matching Policies are {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    All groups must exactly match only one policy rule. There are multiple policies that match the specified high availability group.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make the match sets for the other policies more specific, or delete the extra policies so that only one policy matches this high availability group.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0301W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0301" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0301=HMGR0301W: No policy was located for the group named {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    All groups must exactly match only one policy rule. There is no policy match for the specified high availability group.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Create a policy for the specified high availability group if a policy does not already exist for that group.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR3101I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR3101" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR3101=HMGR3101I: The work queue dump threshold changed to {0} for queue {1}. The data from threshold {2} is {3}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    HA Manager detected that the work queue dump threshold changed.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    An informational message. No action required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR3100I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR3100" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR3100=HMGR3100I: The HA Manager work queue statistics detected a non-default value. The new base threshold is {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    HA Manager detected that the JVM property websphere.hamanager.workqueue.threshold is configured for this process.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    An informational message. No action required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR2006E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR2006" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR2006=HMGR2006E: For the manager set named {0}, the partitioned manager group failed to receive state messages from {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The partitioned manager group expected state messages from other members but never received them.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the root cause of the problem. If the root cause cannot be determined, see the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page, http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support, for help in determining the cause of this problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR2005I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR2005" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR2005=HMGR2005I: Corresponding to the manager set named {0}, the partitioned manager group event handler application of group {1} has indicated that is it not alive. The JVM will be terminated.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The partitioned manager group event handler application has requested process termination.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR2004E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR2004" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR2004=HMGR2004E: Partitioned manager group received an inbound message associated with the {0} header. The header is not an existing manager set name.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A partitioned manager group received an inbound state distribution or application message that is associated with an unexpected header.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the root cause of the problem. If the root cause cannot be determined, see the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page, http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support, for help in determining the cause of this problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR2003E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR2003" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR2003=HMGR2003E: Partitioned manager group received an inbound message which does not contain a valid header. The header is either absent or malformed.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The partitioned manager group received an inbound state distribution or application message containing header information that is not valid.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the root cause of the problem. If the root cause cannot be determined, see the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page, http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support, for help in determining the cause of this problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR2002E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR2002" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR2002=HMGR2002E: For the manager set named {0}, the partitioned manager group method {1} received an exception from the partitioned manager event handling method {2}. The exception is {3}. The partitioned manager group member will relinquish its membership in the underlying high-availability manager group.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A partitioned manager event handling method passed an unhandled exception to the partitioned manager group. See the exception stack trace for more information.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    The partitioned manager group member has been terminated. If you want this instance of partitioned manager group to be functional, stop and restart it.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR2001E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR2001" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR2001=HMGR2001E: An error occurred while sending local state to the {0} manager. The exception is {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An unexpected error occurred. See the exception stack trace for more information.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the root cause of the problem. If the root cause cannot be determined, see the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page, http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support, for help in determining the cause of this problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR2000I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR2000" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR2000=HMGR2000I: An unusual event occurred while sending local state to the {0} manager. The exception is {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The intended partitioned manager group receiver member, might have already left the high availability group.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0170E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0170" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0170=HMGR0170E: The High Availability Manager detected a state inconsistency with the active coordinator while processing a subscriber update message, updating {0} state in {1} mode and received unexpected {2}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An internal logic error has been detected.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    The root cause of the problem appears to be an internal error. See the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page, http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support, for help in determining the cause of this problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0169E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0169" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0169=HMGR0169E: The High Availability Manager detected a state inconsistency while attempting to notify {0} subscribers, the subscription for the subject {1} has already been closed.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An internal logic error has been detected.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    The root cause of the problem appears to be an internal error. See the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page, http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support, for help in determining the cause of this problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0167E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0167" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0167=HMGR0167E: The High Availability Manager received an improper subscriber update message from the active coordinator, an unexpected {0} was encountered.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An internal logic error has been detected.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    The root cause of the problem appears to be an internal error. See the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page, http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support, for help in determining the cause of this problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0166E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0166" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0166=HMGR0166E: Cannot create a proxy post because {0} is a member of the local core group.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An internal logic error has been detected.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    The root cause of the problem appears to be an internal error. See the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page, http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support, for help in determining the cause of this problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0165E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0165" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0165=HMGR0165E: The core group bridge service on this process has violated bridge rebuild protocol by attempting to end a bridge rebuild period without first beginning it.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An internal logic error has been detected.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    The root cause of the problem appears to be an internal error. See the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page, http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support, for help in determining the cause of this problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0164E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0164" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0164=HMGR0164E: The core group bridge service on this process has violated bridge rebuild protocol by providing membership content with no active bridges.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An internal logic error has been detected.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    The root cause of the problem appears to be an internal error. See the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page, http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support, for help in determining the cause of this problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0163E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0163" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0163=HMGR0163E: The core group bridge service on this process has violated bridge rebuild protocol. Both the previous and current set of active bridges was specified as {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An internal logic error has been detected.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    The root cause of the problem appears to be an internal error. See the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page, http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support, for help in determining the cause of this problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0162W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0162" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0162=HMGR0162W: There is no thread pool specified for TCP Channel {0}. The channel may not operate properly.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The TCP channel should have a dedicated thread pool defined for proper operation.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Create a thread pool for the specified TCP Channel and retry the operation.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0161E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0161" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0161=HMGR0161E: The HA Manager has been configured to use an external Failure Detection and Discovery provider. A plug-in factory class name has not been specified.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The external provider cannot be created because the factory class name has not been specified.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify the appropriate factory class name.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0160E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0160" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0160=HMGR0160E: An attempt to update the state of High Availability Group {0} failed because the member is in an unknown state. The current member state is {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A member of the specified core group is in an unknown state.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page, http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support, for help in determining the cause of this problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0159E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0159" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0159=HMGR0159E: An attempt to administratively enable High Availability Group {0} failed because the member is not in the disabled state. The current member state is {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A member of the specified core group is not in the disabled state.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check the current state of the members of the specified core group, and determine which member is not in the disabled state.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0158E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0158" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0158=HMGR0158E: The attempt to power down suspect server {0} failed.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The high availability manager has determined that the specified server, which is hosting a member of a critical cluster, has failed. An attempt to shutdown this server to allow safe failover has failed.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Try to determine why the server failed. If possible, fix the problem and start the server again so that it can rejoin the cluster.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0157E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0157" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0157=HMGR0157E: The channel chain {0} has failed to start after {1} retries. The process will be terminated.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The DCS transport channel failed to start. The port that is designated for the DCS transport channel is probably not available. This situation can occur if the process was previously terminated abnormally.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Wait for the operating system to release the port and restart the process. You should also check the SystemOut.log file for other channel transport chain related messages.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0152W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0152" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0152=HMGR0152W: CPU Starvation detected. Current thread scheduling delay is {0} seconds.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Threads are not being dispatched in a timely manner, and this may affect system stability.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Thread scheduling delays can have many different causes. High CPU utilization or low memory resulting in long garbage collection times or paging to disk are possibilities. Perform resource analysis to determine the proper course of action. This message will disappear when the thread scheduling delay has been corrected.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0151E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0151" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0151=HMGR0151E: A problem was encountered while updating the core group member list. The exception is {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The core group member list could not be dynamically updated.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, see the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page, http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support, for help in determining the cause of this problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0150E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0150" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0150=HMGR0150E: An attempt to create a token to secure the High Availability Manager connection failed. The exception is {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An unexpected internal error has occurred. See the description of the specified exception for more information.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page, http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support, for help in determining the cause of this problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0149E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0149" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0149=HMGR0149E: An attempt to open a connection to core group {0} has been rejected. The sending process has a name of {1} and an IP address of {2}. Global security in the local process is {3}. Global security in the sending process is {4}. The received token starts with {5}. The exception is {6}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The high availability manager has rejected a connection attempt.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that global security is either enabled on both processes or disabled on both processes, and ensure that both the sending and receiving processes are members of the same core group.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0148I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0148" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0148=HMGR0148I: The channel chain transport for core group {0} contains an SSL channel.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified core group is using a secure transport chain.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0147E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0147" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0147=HMGR0147E: An error was encountered during liveness checking. The exception is {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The high availability manager encountered an error while verifying that core group members are alive. Further verification will not occur and failover processing might not function properly.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page, http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support, for help in determining the cause of this problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0146W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0146" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0146=HMGR0146W: Group {0} is not scheduled for liveness checking.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An internal inconsistency was detected. This inconsistency might affect failover for the indicated group.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page, http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support, for help in determining the cause of this problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0145W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0145" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0145=HMGR0145W: The cluster {0} is now critical.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This specified cluster is currently online but the loss of one more cluster members will cause it to terminate.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Bring one or more of the other cluster members online or use the administrative console to remove the offline cluster members from the cluster. Lowering the number of servers that are part of the cluster lowers the number of cluster members that must remain active in order to achieve quorum.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0144I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0144" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0144=HMGR0144I: Powering down suspect server {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The high availability manager has determined that the specified server, which is hosting a member of a critical cluster, has failed. The server is being shutdown to allow safe failover.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check the server to determine why it failed. If you can fix the problem, start the server again so it can rejoin the cluster.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0143E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0143" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0143=HMGR0143E: An error occurred when the High Availability Manager attempted to dispatch a thread. The exception is {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An unrecoverable thread dispatch error occurred.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page, http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support, for help in determining the cause of this problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0142E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0142" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0142=HMGR0142E: An error occurred in a component called back by the High Availability Manager. The exception is {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The called component did not detect that an error occurred.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Use the stack trace to determine which component failed, and perform diagnostics for that component. For additional help in determining why the component failed, see the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0141E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0141" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0141=HMGR0141E: Sending local state information to an active coordinator failed. The exception is {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The group state could not be synchronized correctly.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem does not resolve by itself, stop the server and then start the server again. If the problem still exists, see the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page, http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support, for help in determining the cause of this problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0140E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0140" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0140=HMGR0140E: An event indicating that the core group membership is inconsistent was received. Recovery failed. The exception is {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The core group membership could not be updated correctly.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Synchronize the configuration to the node in question, then restart the server. If synchronizing the configuration does not solve the problem, see the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page, http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support, for help in determining the cause of this problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR1228W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR1228" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR1228=HMGR1228W: The Administrative request could not be completed because the specified member or group is not in the correct state. The request is &quot;{0}&quot;, the member is &quot;{1}&quot; and the group name is &quot;{2}&quot;.  Reason = &quot;{3}&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An asynchronous administrative operation was requested, and during background processing, it was determined that the specified high availability member or high availability group is not in the correct state for the requested action. Therefore, no action was taken.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Because of the timing of asynchronous operations, it is normal for the high availability manager to occasionally  encounter this situation.  Verify that the current state of the high availability member or high availability group, and if necessary, retry the command that failed.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR1227W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR1227" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR1227=HMGR1227W: The Administrative request could not be completed because the core group membership is not stable. The request is &quot;{0}&quot;, the member is &quot;{1}&quot; and the group name is &quot;{2}&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An asynchronous administrative operation was requested, and during background processing, the high availability manager determined that the core group membership is changing. Therefore, no action was taken.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Because of the timing of asynchronous operations, it is normal for the high availability manager to occasionally encounter this situation.  Wait for the servers in this core group to enter a steady state (are either in a started or stopped state) and retry the command that failed.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR1226W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR1226" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR1226=HMGR1226W: The Administrative request could not be completed because the specified member does not exist.  The request is &quot;{0}&quot; the member is &quot;{1}&quot;, the group is &quot;{2}&quot;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An asynchronous administrative operation was requested, and during background processing, the specified high availability group member could not be found. Therefore, no action was taken.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Retry the failing command with valid NodeName and ServerName parameters.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR1225W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR1225" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR1225=HMGR1225W: The Administrative request could not be completed because the specified group does not exist.  The request is &quot;{0}&quot; and the group name is &quot;{1}&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An asynchronous administrative operation was requested, and during background processing, the specified high availability group could not be found. Therefore, no action was taken.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Retry the failing command with a valid GroupName parameter.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0139I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0139" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0139=HMGR0139I: A non-core stack event has been routed to the core stack. The event is {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The core stack received an event that is not a core stack event. The specified event is ignored.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0138I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0138" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0138=HMGR0138I: Terminate has been called on a core stack. The core stack {0} will be terminated.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified core stack has been shut down.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0137I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0137" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0137=HMGR0137I: Terminate has been called on the default core stack. This is not allowed.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Only the high availability manager can terminate the default core group stack.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0136I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0136" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0136=HMGR0136I: No such cluster defined {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This happens because if a cluster is added then its definition is pushed asynchronously to all nodes. Some nodes might not know about a cluster when other do as a result. This problem will correct itself in a few seconds.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If this persists do a manual nodesync on the problem nodes, if this fails then see the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page, http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support, for help in determining the cause of this problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0135I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0135" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0135=HMGR0135I: Cluster {0} has quorum.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified cluster has quorum.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0134I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0134" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0134=HMGR0134I: Cluster {0} is waiting for quorum. Currently {1} members online. At least {2} votes of {3} votes required for quorum.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The cluster has services which cannot activate without the cluster having quorum. Normally, each server has a single vote and the majority of the servers must be online for quorum. If the number of servers is even then the first server has two votes.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Start more cluster members to achieve quorum.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0133E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0133" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0133=HMGR0133E: Exception constructing cluster {0}, exception {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Quorum is enabled for an unknown cluster.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page, http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support, for help in determining the cause of this problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0132I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0132" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0132=HMGR0132I: The local member of group {0} failed to respond properly to a health check. The exception is {1}. The JVM will be terminated.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The JVM is being terminated because the local member of the specified group is no longer functioning properly.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0131I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0131" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0131=HMGR0131I: The local member of group {0} has not responded to a health check. The JVM will be terminated.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The JVM is being terminated because the local member of the specified group is no longer functioning properly.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0130I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0130" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0130=HMGR0130I: The local member of group {0} has indicated that is it not alive. The JVM will be terminated. This server was shut down to prevent damage and maintain high availability in this cluster. Address any exceptions from this member. After the server restarts, the member is rejoined to the group.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The JVM is being terminated because the local member of the specified group is no longer functioning properly.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0129I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0129" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0129=HMGR0129I: The local member of group {0} has been disabled. The reason is {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The local member of the specified core group was disabled at your request.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0128E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0128" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0128=HMGR0128E: The wrong context object was passed on a callback to the AsynchOperationComplete interface. The method is {0}, the group is {1}, the context object is {2} and the expected context is {3}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified programming error was detected.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0127I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0127" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0127=HMGR0127I: The HA Manager has discarded a request to activate or deactivate a group member. The member is disabled. The group is {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The policy for the specified high availability group initiated a request to activate or deactivate a group member. The high availability manager determined that the requested member is disabled.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0126I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0126" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0126=HMGR0126I: The method {0} has been called on the HAGroup object for group {1}, but the member has already left that group.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An unusual condition was detected. This condition might be the result of a programming error.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0125I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0125" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0125=HMGR0125I: An activate or deactive request for the local member of group {0} failed. The reason is {1}, the data is {2} and the exception is {3}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A group member failed to perform the requested action. The group member will be disabled.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0124I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0124" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0124=HMGR0124I: An activate or deactive request for the local member of group {0} failed. The reason is {1} and the data is {2}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A group member failed to perform the requested action. The group member will be disabled.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0123I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0123" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0123=HMGR0123I: A GroupUpdate message was received for a group that does not exist. The group name is {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An unusual situation has occured. This situation might be the result of message latency.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0122E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0122" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0122=HMGR0122E: An error occurred sending a DCS Multicast message. The message type is {0}. The exception is {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An unexpected error occurred. See the exception stack trace for more detail.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the root cause of the problem. If the root cause cannot be determined, see the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page, http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support, for help in determining the cause of this problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0121E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0121" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0121=HMGR0121E: An error occurred sending a DCS Unicast message. The target member is {0}. The message type is {1}. The exception is {2}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An unexpected error occurred. See the exception stack trace for more detail.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the root cause of the problem. If the root cause cannot be determined, see the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page, http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support, for help in determining the cause of this problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0120E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0120" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0120=HMGR0120E: An error occurred processing a callback from DCS. The method is {0}. The exception is {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An unexpected error occurred. See the exception stack trace for more detail.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the root cause of the problem. If the root cause cannot be determined, see the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page, http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support, for help in determining the cause of this problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR1203I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR1203" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR1203=HMGR1203I: HA Manager administrative action requested. Operation is &quot;{0}&quot;, current active member is &quot;{1}&quot;, requested active member is &quot;{2}&quot;, the group is &quot;{3}&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified high availability manager administrative action was requested.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR1202I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR1202" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR1202=HMGR1202I: HA Manager administrative action requested. Operation is &quot;{0}&quot;, the member is &quot;{1}&quot;, the group is &quot;{2}&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified high availability manager administrative action was requested.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR1201I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR1201" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR1201=HMGR1201I: HA Manager administrative action requested. Operation is &quot;{0}&quot;, the group is &quot;{1}&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified high availability manager administrative action was requested.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR1200I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR1200" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR1200=HMGR1200I: HA Manager administrative action requested. Operation is &quot;{0}&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified high availability manager administrative action was requested.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0119I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0119" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0119=HMGR0119I: The GMS service has requested that the server be terminated. The reason is {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Group Membership Service (GMS) requested termination. The GMS should have logged the reason for this request.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0117E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0117" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0117=HMGR0117E: Quorum on group {0} with members {1} has been lost and the process contains active HA Group members. The process must be terminated.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A cluster member that contains quorum sensitive groups has lost quorum but has active members. The process must be terminated.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Restart the failed servers or correct the network partition.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0114E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0114" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0114=HMGR0114E: An unexpected error occurred while forwarding group change information to the active coordinator. The exception is {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A message could not be sent because of an unrecoverable error.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the stack trace to determine the cause of the exception. If the root cause of the problem cannot be determined, see the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page, http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support, for help in determining the cause of this problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0113E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0113" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0113=HMGR0113E: A communication error occurred while forwarding group change information to the active coordinator. The exception is {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A message could not be sent because of a failure in the communication stack.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the stack trace to determine the cause of the exception. If the root cause of the problem cannot be determined, see the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page, http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support, for help in determining the cause of this problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0112E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0112" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0112=HMGR0112E: An unexpected error occurred during object Serialization. The object class is {0} and the exception is {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An unexpected internal error occurred. See the description of the specified  exception for more information.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the stack trace to determine the cause of the exception. If the root cause of the problem cannot be determined, see the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page, http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support, for help in determining the cause of this problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0111E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0111" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0111=HMGR0111E: An unexpected internal error occured during a joinGroup operation. The GroupName is {0}, the instance is {1} and the exception is {2}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An unexpected internal error occurred. See the description of the specified exception for more information.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the stack trace to determine the cause of the exception. If the root cause of the problem cannot be determined, see the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page, http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support, for help in determining the cause of this problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0109E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0109" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0109=HMGR0109E: An unexpected exception was encountered while the HAManager was processing a callback from a using program. The class is {0}, the method is {1} and the exception is {2}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A problem occurred while processing an application callback.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    A programming error by a high availability manager user is probably the cause of this problem. Use the information in the message to find and correct the root cause of the problem. If you cannot determine the root cause of the problem, see the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page, http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support, for help in determining the cause of this problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0108E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0108" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0108=HMGR0108E: An unexpected internal state was encountered. The class is {0}, the method is {1} and the exception is {2}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An inconsistent internal state was detected.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    The root cause of the problem appears to be an internal error. See the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page, http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support, for help in determining the cause of this problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0107E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0107" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0107=HMGR0107E: An attempt to activate or deactivate a member failed. An internal failure has occurred. The group is {0} and the exception is {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An inconsistent internal state was detected.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    The root cause of the problem appears to be an internal error. See the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page, http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support, for help in determining the cause of this problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0105E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0105" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0105=HMGR0105E: An attempt to activate or deactivate a member failed. There local member was not in the proper state. The group is {0}. The local member is {1} and the current state is {2}. The execution stack is {3}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An inconsistent internal state was detected.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    The root cause of the problem appears to be an internal error. See the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page, http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support, for help in determining the cause of this problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0103I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0103" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0103=HMGR0103I: An attempt to activate or deactivate a member failed. There are no local group members for group {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An activate or deactivate message was received but there are no local members in the group to activate or deactivate. This situation can occur under normal conditions, depending on the timing of messages.  For example when members are leaving a group, one of them could receive an activate message that was sent just before that member left.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0408E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0408" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0408=HMGR0408E: The synchronous data stack {0} encountered an unexpected exception processing method {1}.  The exception is {2}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An unexpected synchronous data stack exception occurred. See the description of the exception for more information.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page, http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support, for help in determining the cause of this problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0407E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0407" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0407=HMGR0407E: A request data command on synchronous data stack {0} failed.  The exception is {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An unexpected error occurred attempting to peform a synchronous request for data. See the description of the exception for more information.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page, http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support, for help in determining the cause of this problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0406E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0406" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0406=HMGR0406E: The data stack {0} encountered an unexpected exception calling method {1}.  The exception is {2}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An unexpected data stack exception occurred. See the description of the exception for more information.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page, http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support, for help in determining the cause of this problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0405E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0405" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0405=HMGR0405E: The data stack {0} detected an unknown event. The unrecognized event is {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The high availability manager encountered an unknown data stack event. No harm was caused by this condition.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page, http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support, for help in determining the cause of this problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0404E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0404" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0404=HMGR0404E: The data stack {0} could not process a received message. The message is {1} and the exception is {2}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The high availability manager encountered a problem while trying to process a received data stack message. See the description of the exception for more information.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page, http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support, for help in determining the cause of this problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0403E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0403" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0403=HMGR0403E: Data stack {0} invoked the call back method {1} and it failed.  The exception is {2}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The data stack implementation detected a failure invoking a method on the registered call back class. See the description of the exception for more information.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Use the associated exception name, message and stack trace to determine the root cause of the failure. If the root cause is an application error, correct the cause of the failure and retry the operation. If the root cause is an internal error, see the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page, http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support, for help in determining the cause of this problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0402E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0402" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0402=HMGR0402E: Sending a message on the data stack {0} failed.  The exception is {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An unexpected error occurred attempting to send a data stack message. See the description of the exception for more information.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page, http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support, for help in determining the cause of this problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR0401E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR0401" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR0401=HMGR0401E: Creation of data stack {0} failed.  The exception is {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An unexpected error occurred while creating the data stack. See the description of the exception for more information.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page, http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support, for help in determining the cause of this problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR1019W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR1019" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR1019=HMGR1019W: This process received a message that does not map to an AgentClass channel or to any known Agent channel.  The channel name from message is {0}.  The sender is {1}. The local AgentClass channel is {2}.  The known local Agent Channels are [{3}].
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A message was sent via the high availability manager Agent framework and received by this member.  However, the channel name included in the message does not match any existing AgentClass or Agent channel name.  It is possible for this to occur if the receiving component associated with the channel name in the message was removed while the message was in flight.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page, http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support, for help in determining the cause of this problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR1018I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR1018" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR1018=HMGR1018I: An attempt to cancel creation of a backup Agent has failed. The AgentClass does not have a request scheduled for Agent {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The high availability manager detected the indicated internal inconsistency.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR1017I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR1017" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR1017=HMGR1017I: An attempt to create a backup Agent has failed. The message could not be delivered to the target. The Agent is {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The high availability manager encountered a communication problem while trying to send a message to the target.  The high availability manager will try to resend the message.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that all network paths are operating properly.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR1016E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR1016" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR1016=HMGR1016E: An internal failure occured in an AgentClass. The AgentClass name is {0}. The exception is {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An internal failure occured in the specified AgentClass. See the description of the exception for more information.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page, http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support, for help in determining the cause of this problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR1015E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR1015" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR1015=HMGR1015E: An internal failure occured in an Agent. The Agent name is {0}. The exception is {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An internal failure occured in the specified agent. See the description of the exception for more information.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page, http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support, for help in determining the cause of this problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR1014E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR1014" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR1014=HMGR1014E: A failure occured while processing a membership change for AgentClass {0}. The exception is {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    There are several reasons why a failure might have occurred while processing a membership change for the specified agent, including application errors, configuration problems and internal errors. See the description of the exception for more information.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Use the associated exception name, message and stack trace to determine the root cause of the failure. If the root cause is an application error or a configuration error, correct the cause of the failure and retry the operation. If the root cause is an internal error, see the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page, http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support, for help in determining the cause of this problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR1013E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR1013" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR1013=HMGR1013E: A failure occured while processing a membership change for Agent {0}. The exception is {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    There are several reasons why a failure might have occurred while processing a membership change for the specified agent, including application errors, configuration problems and internal errors. See the description of the exception for more information.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Use the associated exception name, message and stack trace to determine the root cause of the failure. If the root cause is an application error or a configuration error, correct the cause of the failure and retry the operation. If the root cause is an internal error, see the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page, http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support, for help in determining the cause of this problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR1012E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR1012" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR1012=HMGR1012E: An attempt to register AgentClass {0} with the agent framework has failed. The exception is {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    There are several reasons why an attempt to to register the specified AgentClass might have failed, including application errors, configuration problems and internal errors. See the description of the exception for more information.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Use the associated exception name, message and stack trace to determine the root cause of the failure. If the root cause is an application error or a configuration error, correct the cause of the failure and retry the operation. If the root cause is an internal error, see the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page, http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support, for help in determining the cause of this problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR1009E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR1009" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR1009=HMGR1009E: An attempt to destroy a secondary instance of Agent {0} failed. The exception is {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    When a primary agent is destroyed, the secondary agents associated with the primary are also destroyed. There are several reasons why an attempt to destroy the secondary agents might have failed, including application errors, configuration problems and internal errors. See the description of the exception for more information.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Use the associated exception name, message and stack trace to determine the root cause of the failure. If the root cause is an application error or a configuration error, correct the cause of the failure and retry the operation. If the root cause is an internal error, see the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page, http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support, for help in determining the cause of this problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR1008E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR1008" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR1008=HMGR1008E: An attempt to destroy the primary instance of Agent {0} failed. The exception is {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    There are several reasons why an attempt to destroy the primary instance of an agent might have failed, including application errors, configuration problems and internal errors. See the description of the exception for more information.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Use the associated exception name, message and stack trace to determine the root cause of the failure. If the root cause is an application error or a configuration error, correct the cause of the failure and retry the operation. If the root cause is an internal error, see the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page, http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support, for help in determining the cause of this problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR1007E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR1007" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR1007=HMGR1007E: A problem has been detected while attempting to send a message of type {0} for Agent {1}. The exception is {2}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The high availability manager encountered an unknown or unexpected problem while attempting to send a message. See the description of the exception for more information.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the stack trace to determine the root cause of the problem and correct it. If the root cause cannot be determined or is due to an internal error, see the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page, http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support, for help in determining the cause of this problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR1006W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR1006" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR1006=HMGR1006W: A problem has been detected while attempting to send a message of type {0} for Agent {1}. The exception is {2}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The high availability manager encountered a communication problem. The high availability manager will try to resend the message.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that all network paths are operating properly.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR1005E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR1005" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR1005=HMGR1005E: A problem has been detected while attempting to send a message of type {0} for Agent {1}. The exception is {2}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The high availability manager detected the indicated internal inconsistency.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page, http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support, for help in determining the cause of this problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR1004W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR1004" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR1004=HMGR1004W: Method {0} for Agent {1} was called unexpectedly. The execution stack is {2}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The high availability manager detected the indicated internal inconsistency.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page, http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support, for help in determining the cause of this problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR1003W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR1003" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR1003=HMGR1003W: Method {0} for AgentClass {1} was called unexpectedly. The execution stack is {2}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The high availability manager detected the indicated internal inconsistency.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page, http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support, for help in determining the cause of this problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR1002W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR1002" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR1002=HMGR1002W: AgentClass {0} has been notified that a request to add a secondary Agent {1} has completed. There is no record of that request. The execution stack is {2}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The high availability manager detected the indicated internal inconsistency.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page, http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support, for help in determining the cause of this problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR1001W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR1001" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR1001=HMGR1001W: An attempt to receive a message of type {0} for Agent {1} in AgentClass {2} failed. The exception is {3}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This failure is unexpected. Secondary agents might not have been created or destroyed, as expected.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page, http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support, for help in determining the cause of this problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="HMGR1000E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HMGR1000" varFormat="Java">
    HMGR1000=HMGR1000E: An attempt to create an Agent instance of type {0} in AgentClass {1} failed. The exception is {2}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    There are several reasons why an attempt to create an agent might have failed, including application errors, configuration problems, and internal errors. See the description of the specfied exception for more information.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Use the associated exception name, message and stack trace to determine the root cause of the failure. If the root cause is an application error or configuration error, correct the cause of the failure and retry the  operation. If the root cause is an internal error, see the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page, http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support, for help in determining the cause of this problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<!-- END MESSAGES -->
</TMSSource>
