<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/css" href="../../resources/stylesheets/wasmsgxml.css"?>
<TMSSource name="TivoliMessages" tmsVersion="1.0" xml:lang="en">
<!-- CMVC MSG File Name = SERV1/ws/code/admin.appmgmt/src/com/ibm/ws/management/resources/BindEarCmd.nlsprops -->
<!-- DO NOT EDIT THIS FILE - This file was generated by the XML/Html & Property emitter -->
<!-- BEGIN MESSAGES -->
<Message ID="BNDE0010W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="BNDEAR0010" varFormat="Java">
    BNDEAR0010=BNDE0010W: CMP Bean {0} does not have a data source binding
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    There is no Datasource binding for both the container-managed persistence (CMP) bean that is specified and in the JAR file to which it belongs.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Rerun default bindings by providing the Java Naming and Directory Interface (JNDI) name for a default Datasource or specify the Datasource binding during application installation.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="BNDE0009W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="BNDEAR0009" varFormat="Java">
    BNDEAR0009=BNDE0009W: CMP Bean {0} does not have a connection factory binding
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    There is no connection factory binding for both the  container-managed persistence (CMP) bean that is specified and in the JAR file to which it belongs.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Rerun the default bindings by providing the Java Naming and Directory Interface (JNDI) name for the default connection factory or specify the connection factory binding when you install the application.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="BNDE0008W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="BNDEAR0008" varFormat="Java">
    BNDEAR0008=BNDE0008W: ambiguous EJB reference to {0} - use &lt;ejb-link&gt; to clarify
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    There is more than one matching enterprise Java bean (EJB) with the same home interface that is specified by the EJB reference.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Add the EJB link element that includes the path name of the JAR file for the EJB that contains the enterprise bean that is being referenced. Validate your application using the Application Assembly Tool.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="BNDE0007W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="BNDEAR0007" varFormat="Java">
    BNDEAR0007=BNDE0007W: EJB reference could not be resolved: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An enterprise Java bean (EJB) with the home interface that is specified by the EJB reference does not exist in the application.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Validate your application using the Application Assembly Tool.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="BNDE0006W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="BNDEAR0006" varFormat="Java">
    BNDEAR0006=BNDE0006W: &lt;ejb-link&gt; could not be resolved: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An enterprise Java bean (EJB) with the name that is specified in the EJB link element does not exist in the application.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Validate your application using the Application Assembly Tool.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="BNDE0005W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="BNDEAR0005" varFormat="Java">
    BNDEAR0005=BNDE0005W: Duplicate &lt;ejb-name&gt; encountered: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An enterprise Java bean (EJB) with the same name already exists in the application.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    There is no user action required if the same name is used in an EJB that belongs to a different JAR file for the EJB. If same name is used in the same JAR file for the EJB, then validate your application using the Application Assembly Tool.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="BNDE0004E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="BNDEAR0004" varFormat="Java">
    BNDEAR0004=BNDE0004E: Could not bind virtual host(s): {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An error occurred generating the bindings for the virtual host for all the web modules in the application.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Validate your application using the Application Assembly Tool.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="BNDE0003E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="BNDEAR0003" varFormat="Java">
    BNDEAR0003=BNDE0003E: Could not bind resource-env references: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An error occurred while generating the bindings for all of the resource-env references in the application.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Validate your application using the Application Assembly Tool.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="BNDE0002E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="BNDEAR0002" varFormat="Java">
    BNDEAR0002=BNDE0002E: Could not bind resource references: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An error occurred generating the bindings for all of the resource references in the application.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Validate your application using the Application Assembly Tool.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="BNDE0001E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="BNDEAR0001" varFormat="Java">
    BNDEAR0001=BNDE0001E: Could not bind EJB references: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An error occurred generating the bindings for all of the references for the enterprise Java beans (EJBs) in the application.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Validate your application using the Application Assembly Tool.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="BNDE0000E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="BNDEAR0000" varFormat="Java">
    BNDEAR0000=BNDE0000E: Could not bind EJBs: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An error occurred generating the default bindings for all of the enterprise Java beans (EJBs) that are contained in the application.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Validate your application using the Application Assembly Tool.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<!-- END MESSAGES -->
</TMSSource>
