<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/css" href="../../resources/stylesheets/wasmsgxml.css"?>
<TMSSource name="TivoliMessages" tmsVersion="1.0" xml:lang="en">
<!-- CMVC MSG File Name = UDDI/ws/code/uddi.install/src/com/ibm/uddi/install/cscreateMessages.nlsprops, -->
<!-- DO NOT EDIT THIS FILE - This file was generated by the XML/Html & Property emitter -->
<!-- BEGIN MESSAGES -->
<Message ID="CWUDD4002E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="cscreate.abexit" varFormat="Java">
    cscreate.abexit=CWUDD4002E: Abnormal exit from creation of UDDI Derby database
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The UDDI Derby database has not been successfully created.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the accompanying error messages to determine the reason for the error.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWUDD4008E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="cscreate.bad.attr" varFormat="Java">
    cscreate.bad.attr=CWUDD4008E: Invalid attribute Attr found in DDL File List file. Value should be true or false. Value is:
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The attribute in the DDL File List file that is shown in the message was not valid.   UDDIDerbyCreate.jar, which is the file that includes the DDL File List file, might be corrupted.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check that you have a valid version of UDDIDerbyCreate.jar.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWUDD3021I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="cscreate.eof" varFormat="Java">
    cscreate.eof=CWUDD3021I: End of file reached
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.  The end of the current data definition language (DDL) file has been reached.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWUDD3002I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="cscreate.pathtoscripts" varFormat="Java">
    cscreate.pathtoscripts=CWUDD3002I: Path to scripts
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.  It indicates the location (path) of the scripts for creating the UDDI database.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWUDD3016I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="cscreate.populate.attempt" varFormat="Java">
    cscreate.populate.attempt=CWUDD3016I: Attempting to populate the database container with schema structures
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.  There is an attempt to add schemas to the UDDI Derby database container.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWUDD4014E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="cscreate.sqlstring" varFormat="Java">
    cscreate.sqlstring=CWUDD4014E: Exception Exc occurred while processing SQL statement Str. Character positions within Str shown by StrPos. Values are:
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The exception shown occurred while processing an SQL statement used to create the UDDI Derby database. The message shows the SQL string that was being processed and the character positions in that string.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the exception message to determine the cause of the problem.  If the message shows the position at which the problem occurred, use the character positions to identify that position in the SQLstring.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWUDD4015E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="cscreate.ddlfile.nosql" varFormat="Java">
    cscreate.ddlfile.nosql=CWUDD4015E: There were no SQL statements in the DDL file
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    No SQL statements have been found in the data definition language (DDL) file that is currently being processed.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the accompanying error messages to find out the path to the database scripts (DDL files), and the DDL file that is currently being processed. Find the DDL file and check that it is valid.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWUDD3004I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="cscreate.dbname" varFormat="Java">
    cscreate.dbname=CWUDD3004I: database name
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.  It indicates the name to be used for the UDDI Derby database.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWUDD3023I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="cscreate.dbexists.deleted" varFormat="Java">
    cscreate.dbexists.deleted=CWUDD3023I: UDDI Derby database deleted
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.  The existing Derby database was deleted as requested.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWUDD3017I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="cscreate.jdbcload.attempt" varFormat="Java">
    cscreate.jdbcload.attempt=CWUDD3017I: Atempting to load the Derby JDBC driver
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.  There is an attempt to load the JDBC driver class for the Derby database.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWUDD4012E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="cscreate.jdbcload.notfound" varFormat="Java">
    cscreate.jdbcload.notfound=CWUDD4012E: Exception Exc occurred while trying to find the Derby JDBC driver. Value is:
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An exception occurred while trying to find the Derby JDBC driver class.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the exception message to determine the cause of the problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWUDD3024I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="cscreate.dbexists.return" varFormat="Java">
    cscreate.dbexists.return=CWUDD3024I: UDDI Derby database already exists. Requested to keep
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.  A UDDI Derby database exists and there is a user request to keep this database and not to create a new one.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWUDD4007E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="cscreate.ddllist.err" varFormat="Java">
    cscreate.ddllist.err=CWUDD4007E: DDL File List file not found
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The DDL File List file, used to specify the data definition language (DDL) files to be used to create the UDDI Derby database, could not be found.  UDDIDerbyCreate.jar, which is the file that should include the DDL File List file, might be corrupted.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check that you have a valid version of UDDIDerbyCreate.jar.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWUDD3018I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="cscreate.jdbcload.good" varFormat="Java">
    cscreate.jdbcload.good=CWUDD3018I: Derby JDBC driver successfully loaded
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.  The JDBC driver for Derby has been successfully loaded.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWUDD4010E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="cscreate.populate.err" varFormat="Java">
    cscreate.populate.err=CWUDD4010E: SQL exception Exc encountered during database population. Value is:
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An SQL exception has occurred while populating the UDDI Derby database.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the SQL exception message to determine the cause of the problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWUDD4009E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="cscreate.insuff.attr" varFormat="Java">
    cscreate.insuff.attr=CWUDD4009E: Insufficient attributes found in DDL File List file
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The DDL File List file did not contain enough attributes. UDDIDerbyCreate.jar, which is the file that includes the DDL File List file, might be corrupted.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check that you have a valid version of UDDIDerbyCreate.jar.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWUDD4020E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="cscreate.badparm.default" varFormat="Java">
    cscreate.badparm.default=CWUDD4020E: Invalid value specified for Default Profile parameter Parm, value should be GoodParm. Values are:
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The value shown for the default profile parameter in the request issued to create the Derby database is not valid. The message also shows  the value that was expected.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Retry the request. Either specify a valid value for the default profile parameter, or, if you do not want to create the UDDI Derby database with a default profile, omit this parameter. If this message is issued when using the uddiDeploy.jacl script with the default option, check that you are using a valid version of uddiDeploy.jacl.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWUDD4019E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="cscreate.noparm.dbname" varFormat="Java">
    cscreate.noparm.dbname=CWUDD4019E: Name of database not specified
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The request issued to create the Derby database has not specified a name for the UDDI Derby database.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Retry the request, providing a name for the UDDI Derby database. If this message is issued when using the uddiDeploy.jacl script with the default option, check that you are using a valid version of uddiDeploy.jacl.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWUDD3009I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="cscreate.create.good" varFormat="Java">
    cscreate.create.good=CWUDD3009I: UDDI Derby database creation completed normally
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.  The UDDI Derby database has been successfully created.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWUDD4003E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="cscreate.insuff.args" varFormat="Java">
    cscreate.insuff.args=CWUDD4003E: Insufficient arguments supplied
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The command to create the UDDI Derby database requires more arguments than were supplied.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine any accompanying error messages for more information, then retry the request, supplying the correct number of arguments.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWUDD3015I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="cscreate.skip.default" varFormat="Java">
    cscreate.skip.default=CWUDD3015I: Skipping the Default Profile record because Default Profile was not requested
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.  The default UDDI profile was not requested, and therefore the record in the DDL File List file for setting up the default profile will not be used.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWUDD4017E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="cscreate.noparm.script" varFormat="Java">
    cscreate.noparm.script=CWUDD4017E: Location of database scripts not specified
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The request issued to create the Derby database has not specified a location for the database scripts.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Retry the request, providing a location for the database scripts. If this message is issued when using the uddiDeploy.jacl script with the default option, check that you are using a valid version of uddiDeploy.jacl.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWUDD3020I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="cscreate.ddlfile.good" varFormat="Java">
    cscreate.ddlfile.good=CWUDD3020I: DDL file successfully processed. N statements processed. Value is:
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.  The current DDL file has been successfully processed, and the number of statements indicated were processed.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWUDD4006E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="cscreate.connect.err" varFormat="Java">
    cscreate.connect.err=CWUDD4006E: SQL exception Exc encountered during database container creation. Value is:
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An SQL exception occurred when attempting to create the database container for the UDDI Derby database.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the exception message to determine the cause of the problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWUDD3030I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="cscreate.goodexit" varFormat="Java">
    cscreate.goodexit=CWUDD3030I: Request to create UDDI Derby database successfully completed
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.  Creation of the UDDI Derby database has completed successfully.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWUDD3001I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="cscreate.start" varFormat="Java">
    cscreate.start=CWUDD3001I: Commencing UDDI Derby database creation
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.  Creation of the UDDI Derby database is being started.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWUDD4018E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="cscreate.noparm.ddlloc" varFormat="Java">
    cscreate.noparm.ddlloc=CWUDD4018E: Location of database not specified
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The request issued to create the Derby database has not specified a location for the UDDI Derby database.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Retry the request, providing a location for the UDDI Derby database. If this message is issued when using the uddiDeploy.jacl script with the default option, check that you are using a valid version of uddiDeploy.jacl.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWUDD3005I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="cscreate.default.true" varFormat="Java">
    cscreate.default.true=CWUDD3005I: Default profile requested
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.  The UDDI Derby database will be created as a default UDDI database, using the default UDDI profile.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWUDD3008I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="cscreate.connect.good" varFormat="Java">
    cscreate.connect.good=CWUDD3008I: Successfully connected to UDDI Derby database container
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.  The database container for the UDDI Derby database has been connected to successfully.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWUDD3032I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="cscreate.unknown.response" varFormat="Java">
    cscreate.unknown.response=CWUDD3032I: Please enter Yes or No
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The required response is Yes, Y, No, or N (these are not case sensitive).
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Enter Yes to create a new UDDI Derby database, or No to keep the existing database.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWUDD4013E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="cscreate.jdbcload.advice" varFormat="Java">
    cscreate.jdbcload.advice=CWUDD4013E: Ensure that the Derby libraries are on the classpath
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An exception occurred when trying to find the Derby JDBC driver class.  The class path might not include the path to the Derby class library.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that you specified the Derby class library on the request to create the  UDDI Derby database. Depending on the request that was issued, specify the class path either on the wsadmin command used to invoke uddiDeploy.jacl, or on the java -jar command used to invoke the UDDIDerbyCreate.jar file.  Refer to the Information Center information about setting up and deploying UDDI for more details.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWUDD3007I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="cscreate.connect.attempt" varFormat="Java">
    cscreate.connect.attempt=CWUDD3007I: Attempting to create or connect to UDDI Derby database container
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.  There is an attempt to create, or connect to, the database container for the UDDI Derby database.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWUDD4022E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="cscreate.dbexists.deleteErr" varFormat="Java">
    cscreate.dbexists.deleteErr=CWUDD4022E: Unable to delete UDDI Derby database. Exception value is:
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An Exception occurred while attempting to delete the existing UDDI Derby database.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the exception message to determine the cause of the problem.  Ensure that the database is not being used by a server.  Restart the Application Server.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWUDD3014I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="cscreate.ignore.attr" varFormat="Java">
    cscreate.ignore.attr=CWUDD3014I: Extraneous attributes will be ignored
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.  There are more attributes specified than are required. The surplus attributes will be ignored.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWUDD4004E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="cscreate.usage" varFormat="Java">
    cscreate.usage=CWUDD4004E: Usage is: java -jar &lt;thisjar&gt; &lt;arg1&gt; &lt;arg2&gt; &lt;arg3&gt; &lt;arg4&gt; 
where
&lt;thisjar&gt;= name of jar file for creating UDDI Derby Database,
&lt;arg1&gt;= path to DDL (SQL) files,
&lt;arg2&gt;= path to location for UDDI Derby database,
&lt;arg3&gt;= name of UDDI Derby database,
&lt;arg4&gt;= (optional), if specified must be the string DEFAULT
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message shows the syntax of the command to create a UDDI Derby database.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Use the command with the syntax shown in the message.  Ensure that you specify the Derby class library on the class path, by using the -cp parameter on the Java command.  See the Information Center information about setting up and deploying UDDI for more details.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWUDD3006I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="cscreate.default.false" varFormat="Java">
    cscreate.default.false=CWUDD3006I: Default profile not requested
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.  The UDDI Derby database will be created as a non-default UDDI database.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWUDD4005E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="cscreate.badexit" varFormat="Java">
    cscreate.badexit=CWUDD4005E: Creation of UDDI Derby database was unsuccessful
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The UDDI Derby database has not been successfully created.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the accompanying error messages to determine the reason for the error.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWUDD4001E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="cscreate.exception" varFormat="Java">
    cscreate.exception=CWUDD4001E: An exception Exc occurred during creation of UDDI Derby database. Value is:
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An exception occurred during the attempt to create the UDDI Derby database.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the exception message to determine the cause of the problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWUDD3012I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="cscreate.comment" varFormat="Java">
    cscreate.comment=CWUDD3012I: Comment from file:
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.  A comment line has been read from the DDL File List file.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWUDD3011I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="cscreate.ddllist.read" varFormat="Java">
    cscreate.ddllist.read=CWUDD3011I: Reading the contents of the DDL File List file and verifying
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.  The contents of the DDL File List file are being read and verified.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWUDD3022I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="cscreate.sqlconvert" varFormat="Java">
    cscreate.sqlconvert=CWUDD3022I: Converting SQL string Str to Derby syntax. Value is:
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.  The SQL string shown is being converted into an SQL syntax that the Derby database recognises.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWUDD3019I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="cscreate.ddlfile.process" varFormat="Java">
    cscreate.ddlfile.process=CWUDD3019I: Processing DDL file DDLFile using Term as the terminator. Values are:
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.  The DDLFile shown is being processed, with the character shown being used as terminator.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWUDD3010I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="cscreate.ddllist.attempt" varFormat="Java">
    cscreate.ddllist.attempt=CWUDD3010I: Attempting to open DDL File List file of name FileName. Value is:
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.  The DDL File List file shown, which lists the data definition language (DDL) files (database scripts) to be used to create the UDDI Derby database, has been successfully opened.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWUDD3031I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="cscreate.recreate" varFormat="Java">
    cscreate.recreate=CWUDD3031I: Derby database already exists. Do you want to recreate (Yes/No)?
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The request to create the UDDI Derby database has detected that a database already exists.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Enter Yes to create a new UDDI Derby database, or No to keep the existing database.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWUDD4016E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="cscreate.ddlfile.err" varFormat="Java">
    cscreate.ddlfile.err=CWUDD4016E: Exception Exc occurred while processing DDL file. Value is:
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An exception occurred while processing the current data definition language (DDL) file.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the exception message to determine the cause of the problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWUDD4021E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="cscreate.jdbcload.err" varFormat="Java">
    cscreate.jdbcload.err=CWUDD4021E: An error occurred while loading the Derby JDBC driver
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An error occurred while attempting to load the Derby JDBC driver class.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the accompanying messages for more information.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWUDD4011E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="cscreate.dbexists.advice" varFormat="Java">
    cscreate.dbexists.advice=CWUDD4011E: Delete existing UDDI Derby database if it is to be overwritten with a new one
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An exception has occurred while populating the UDDI Derby database. This might be because a UDDI Derby database already exists.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If you want to keep the existing data in the existing UDDI Derby Database, ignore this message. If you want to overwrite this database with a new UDDI Derby database, examine the accompanying messages for the location and name of the existing database. Delete the existing database, then re-run the request.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWUDD3003I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="cscreate.pathtodb" varFormat="Java">
    cscreate.pathtodb=CWUDD3003I: Path of database
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.  It indicates the location (path) to be used for the UDDI Derby database.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWUDD3013I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="cscreate.noncomment" varFormat="Java">
    cscreate.noncomment=CWUDD3013I: Line from file:
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.  A non-comment line has been read from the DDL File List file.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<!-- END MESSAGES -->
</TMSSource>
