<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/css" href="../../resources/stylesheets/wasmsgxml.css"?>
<TMSSource name="TivoliMessages" tmsVersion="1.0" xml:lang="en">
<!-- CMVC MSG File Name = SERV1/ws/code/scheduler/src/com/ibm/ws/scheduler/resources/SchedulerMessages.nlsprops -->
<!-- DO NOT EDIT THIS FILE - This file was generated by the XML/Html & Property emitter -->
<!-- BEGIN MESSAGES -->
<Message ID="SCHD0073E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0073E" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0073E=SCHD0073E: The Scheduler implementation class attribute is missing for scheduler {0} ({1}).  The scheduler resource will not be created.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The scheduler implementation class for the specified scheduler resource is missing.  An implementation class is required.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a valid scheduler implementation class.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0033I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0033I" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0033I=SCHD0033I: The Scheduler {0} has initialized.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified Scheduler instance has initialized and is ready to accept requests.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0137E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0137E" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0137E=SCHD0137E: Unable to create EJB instance for {0}: {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    There was an error when attempting to create the specified EJB instance.  See the nested exception for details on the cause of the problem.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the EJB, Application, Host and Port are available.  If no longer available, cancel or suspend the task.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0136W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0136W" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0136W=SCHD0136W: The lease manager tables are missing for scheduler {0} ({1}) which will reduce performance in a clustered environment.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The lease manager tables are required to reduce the contention between redundant or clustered schedulers.  If the tables are absent, there will be a large amount of collisions.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Use the supplied DDL files to create the lease manager tables or use the createTables operation on the WASSchedulerCfgHelper MBean or administrative console to add the new tables.  See the information center for details.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0140I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0140I" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0140I=SCHD0140I: EJB information:  Host: {0}, Port: {1}, J2EE component: {2}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message displays information about an EJB&apos;s remote destination, which includes the remote host, port and Java Platform, Enterprise Edition component that the EJB is a member of.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0072E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0072E" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0072E=SCHD0072E: Scheduler resource {0} has a JNDI name attribute value of {1}, which is the same as the value of the work manager JNDI name attribute.  The scheduler resource is not created.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The JNDI name of the specifed scheduler resource is the same as the work manager JNDI name attribute.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Use the administrative console to modify either the work manager JNDI name in the Work Manager resource or modify the JNDI name of the scheduler resource.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0308E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0308E" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0308E=SCHD0308E: No chained exception available
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A message with a chained exception was generated, but there was no chained exception.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Review the message details and stack trace for the root exception.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0100I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0100I" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0100I=SCHD0100I: Scheduler tables verified successfully.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Scheduler tables were verified in the database.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0032I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0032I" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0032I=SCHD0032I: The Scheduler {0} is initializing.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified Scheduler instance is initializing.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0068E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0068E" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0068E=SCHD0068E: The task failed to execute because an error occurred.  See the previous messages for the cause of the error.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The scheduler attempted to run the task, but an error occurred preventing the task from running.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See the previous messages for the cause of the error.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0135W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0135W" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0135W=SCHD0135W: Value out of range for custom property {0} for scheduler {1} ({2}).  Valid values include: {3}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A custom property was set for the specified scheduler, but the value is not valid.  This property will be ignored.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Update the custom property value to be valid.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0071E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0071E" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0071E=SCHD0071E: Scheduler resource {0} has JNDI name attribute value of {1} which is the same as the value of the data source JNDI name attribute.  The scheduler resource is not created.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The JNDI name of the scheduler resource is the same as the scheduler resource data source JNDI name attribute.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Use the administrative console to modify either the data source JNDI name or the JNDI name of the scheduler resource.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0307E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0307E" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0307E=SCHD0307E: The lease for resource {0} is disabled.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The lease has been disabled.  Operations on a lease are only available when the lease has been acquired.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    The lease must be enabled prior before the lease can be acquired or renewed.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0031I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0031I" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0031I=SCHD0031I: The Scheduler Service is starting.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Scheduler Service is starting.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0067E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0067E" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0067E=SCHD0067E: An error occurred while calculating the next fire time or the start by interval.  See the previous error message for the cause of the error.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An error occurred while calculating the next fire time or the start by interval.  The previous message contains the cause of the error.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See the previous message for the cause of the error.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0070E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0070E" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0070E=SCHD0070E: The Task Store is not available.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Task Store object for this scheduler is null.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See previously listed error messages to determine the cause.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0134I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0134I" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0134I=SCHD0134I: Scheduler {0} ({1}) has lost its lease and will no longer run tasks on this application server.  Tasks will now run on server {2}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The scheduler uses a lease to allow clustered scheduler servers to avoid contention.  Only one scheduler instance per server may hold the lease at one time.  All tasks will run on the scheduler instance who holds the lease.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0306E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0306E" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0306E=SCHD0306E: The lease for component {0} has expired.  No other operations are permitted until the lease is reaquired.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The component has lost the lease because it has expired.  Operations on a lease are only available when the lease has been acquired.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Attempt to acquire a lease before running the operation.  If the lease is already acquired by another owner, then the lease can only be forcibly acquired.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0066E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0066E" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0066E=SCHD0066E: The following error occurred in scheduler {0} ({1}) while applying the default User Calendar to the current time: {2}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An error occurred attempting to calculate the next fire time using the default User Calendar.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See the message that contains the cause of the error.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0026E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0026E" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0026E=SCHD0026E: Scheduler instance {0} failed to initialize because the following error occurred: {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified scheduler could not be initialized and is unable to poll for scheduled tasks.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the Scheduler resource is configured correctly and that the associated database is active.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0133I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0133I" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0133I=SCHD0133I: Scheduler {0} ({1}) has acquired the lease and will run all tasks on this application server.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The scheduler uses a lease to allow clustered scheduler servers to avoid contention.  Only one scheduler instance per server may hold the lease at one time.  All tasks will run on the scheduler instance who holds the lease.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0029W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHEDULER_DISABLED" varFormat="Java">
    SCHEDULER_DISABLED=SCHD0029W: Scheduler service disabled due to previous errors.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Scheduler service experienced an error during initialization. The service is inaccessible on the given server. The root error should have been logged previously.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Try to resolve the previously logged errors. If unable to do so, contact IBM support.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0305E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0305E" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0305E=SCHD0305E: The lease for component {0} was cancelled.  No Other operations are permitted until the lease is reaquired.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The lease has been cancelled.  Operations on a lease are only available when the lease has been acquired.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Attempt to acquire a lease before running the operation.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0065E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0065E" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0065E=SCHD0065E: The following error occurred while scheduler {0} ({1}) attempted to roll back the transaction: {2}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The scheduler tried to roll back the transaction, but an error occurred.  See the message that contains the cause of the error.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See the message that contains the cause of the error.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0129E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0129E" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0129E=SCHD0129E: The {0} MBean for for scheduler {1} could not be started: {2}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An unexpected error occurred while starting the specified MBean.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Review the error, solve the problem and retry the operation.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0132W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0132W" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0132W=SCHD0132W: Task {0} for scheduler {1} ({2}) has exceeded the failure threshold limit and has been deactivated.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The scheduled task has failed multiple times consecutively and will no longer run on this application server.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Review other related error messages to determine what the problem is.  Once the problem is resolve, either suspend and resume the task using the scheduler API methods, or restart this scheduler daemon.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0304E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0304E" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0304E=SCHD0304E: No database connections could be obtained in the required time for operation: {0} and resource: {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A connection to the database could not be obtained before the connection manager timed-out.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Increase the number of connections or continue to retry the operation until a connection can be retrieved.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0064E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0064E" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0064E=SCHD0064E: An error occurred while attempting to commit the transaction by the scheduler {0} ({1}). The transaction is rolled back.  The following error occurred: {2}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The scheduler tried to commit the transaction, but an error occurred.  The transaction is rolled back.  See the message that contains the cause of the error.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See the message that contains the cause of the error.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0128E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0128E" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0128E=SCHD0128E: The daemon for scheduler {0} could not be started: {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An unexpected error occurred.  See the FFDC logs and the associated exception for details.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See the server log files for detailed exception data.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0131W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0131W" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0131W=SCHD0131W: Task {0} on thread {1} for scheduler {2} ({3}) has been running for {4} milliseconds and may be hung.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The scheduled task has been running for a long period of time.  If this behavior is by design, then no further action is necessary.  When the thread completes, a WSVR0606W message is logged.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the task is running longer than expected, then the task and thread should be examined to determine if is running properly. If the task is hung, the thread should be interrupted or the application server ended and the task should be suspended or cancelled until the problem can be resolved.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0059W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0059W" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0059W=SCHD0059W: The task information for task ID {0} for scheduler {1} ({2}) cannot be removed from the database because the task does not exist or the task information has already been removed by another Scheduler.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The task with the specified task ID cannot be removed from the database because it does not exist.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0303E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0303E" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0303E=SCHD0303E: The database connection required for operation: {0} and resource: {1} is stale.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The operation could not complete because the database connection is stale.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine database logs and other messages to determine if there is a configuration problem and retry the operation.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0099E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0099E" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0099E=SCHD0099E: Exception occurred while deserializing object {0}: {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An unexpected error occurred.  See the FFDC logs and the associated exception for details.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See the server log files for detailed exception data.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0063E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0063E" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0063E=SCHD0063E: A task with ID {0} failed to run on Scheduler {1} ({2}) because of an exception: {3}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Scheduled task failed to run due to an unexpected error and was rolled-back.  See the service log for the detailed exception stack trace.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See the message that contains the cause of the error.  The task will continue to run until the problem is resolved or the task is cancelled.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0127E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0127E" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0127E=SCHD0127E: Access Denied. A task cannot be modified from a different application than it was created with.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An application attempted to modify or change a task created by another application.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check the task ID and verify that the correct application is being used to access that task, or use the WASScheduler JMX MBean to administer the task.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0130W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0130W" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0130W=SCHD0130W: Failed to {0} the scheduler tables because of an error: {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The scheduler tables cannot be created, dropped or verified because of the specified error.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Resolve the error and try the operation again or use the supplied SQL or DDL files to create or drop your tables.  See the information center for details.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0019E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0019E" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0019E=SCHD0019E: Data source with JNDI name {0} could not be found.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A data source was specified on a Scheduler resource, however the data source with the specified JNDI name is not present.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the specified data source exists in the global name space.  If it does not exist create it or alter the Scheduler resource to use an alternate JNDI name.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0058W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0058W" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0058W=SCHD0058W: The task information for task ID {0} for scheduler {1} ({2}) cannot be updated in the database because the task record is lock by another process.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The task with the specified task ID cannot be updated in the database because the task record is locked by another process. This can occur when another Scheduler is updating the same task record.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0302E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0302E" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0302E=SCHD0302E: The lease owner: {0} is not the current owner of the lease for resource {1}.  Operation: {2} was unable to complete.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The lease has not been acquired.  Operations on a lease are only available when the lease has been acquired.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Attempt to acquire a lease before running the operation.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0098E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0098E" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0098E=SCHD0098E: Could not determine the task operation for method {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This exception is unexpected. The cause is not immediately known.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0062E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0062E" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0062E=SCHD0062E: The task version field value of {0} for task ID {1} is not supported by this level of the Scheduler.  The supported task versions are {2}.  This task will not run.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Scheduler is attempting to run the specified task, however, the version of the task record is not supported by this scheduler.  This can occur when a task is created on a later version of the Application Server and then run on an earlier version of the Application Server.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure the version of the Application Server product is at the same or later version than the version of the Application Server that created the task.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0126E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0126E" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0126E=SCHD0126E: The scheduler service singleton has not been set.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The instance API method was called before the scheduler service was initialized.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check the startup time values specified for the component.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0018E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0018E" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0018E=SCHD0018E: Work Manager with JNDI name {0} could not be found.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A WorkManager was specified on a Scheduler resource, however, the WorkManager with the specified JNDI name is not present.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the specified work manager exists in the global name space.  If it does not exist, create it or alter the Scheduler resource to use the default WorkManager.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0057W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0057W" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0057W=SCHD0057W: The task information for task ID {0} for scheduler {1} ({2}) cannot be updated in the database because the task has already been run by another Scheduler, the task information was changed, or the task was cancelled.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The task with the specified task ID cannot be updated in the database because it was already updated.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0027E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ERR_MISSING_KEY" varFormat="Java">
    ERR_MISSING_KEY=SCHD0027E: Message key {0} was not found in any searched resource bundles.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A key was passed into the Messages class to resolve to a string, but a properties file for the locale could not be found and the appropriate message could not be retrieved.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Determine why the message catalog could not be found.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0030E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ERR_NO_SERVICE" varFormat="Java">
    ERR_NO_SERVICE=SCHD0030E: Scheduler service could not resolve the {0} service.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Scheduler service could not resolve the specified service, which is required for the Scheduler service. Look through the log to see if the specified service started successfully.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If you wish to use the Scheduler service, correct the problem with the specified service. If you are unable to correct the problem, contact IBM support.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0301E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0301E" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0301E=SCHD0301E: The lease for resource {0} does not exist.  Operation: {1} was unable to complete.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The lease for the specified resource does not exist.    Operations on a lease are only available when the lease has been acquired.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Attempt to acquire a lease before running the operation.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0097E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0097E" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0097E=SCHD0097E: The task operation {0} is not supported by task type {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The supplier of the specified task type has indicated that the specified task operation is not allowed.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Change your application so it does not call the specified operation.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0061E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0061E" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0061E=SCHD0061E: The task information for task ID {0} and owner token {1} was not found in the database.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The task with the specified task ID and owner token is not in the database.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify another task ID and try the request again.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0021I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0021I" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0021I=SCHD0021I: Exception trace information follows: {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An unexpected exception has occurred.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check for other messages that contain exceptions further in the log.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0125E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0125E" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0125E=SCHD0125E: Unexpected exception while processing the {0} operation: {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An unexpected exception occurred while processing the specified operation.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Review the error, solve the problem and retry the operation.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0060W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0060W" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0060W=SCHD0060W: The task information for task ID {0} for scheduler {1} ({2}) cannot be removed from the database because the task record is locked by another process.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The task with the specified task ID cannot be removed from the database because the task record is locked by another process.  This can occur when another Scheduler is updating or removing the same task record.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0017E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0017E" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0017E=SCHD0017E: The {0} attribute must be specified when creating a {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    When creating or scheduling objects, this attribute is required.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Provide the missing attribute and try again.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0056W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0056W" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0056W=SCHD0056W: The task information for task ID {0} for scheduler {1} ({2}) cannot be inserted into the database because the task already exists.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The task with specified task ID cannot be inserted into the database because the task already exists in the database.  This can occur when another Scheduler inserts the same task into the database table.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0300E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0300E" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0300E=SCHD0300E: Error during Database operation, localized message is {0}, Vendor Error Code is {1}, ANSI-92 SQLState is {2}, cause: {3}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A database operation threw an SQLException.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Review the cause or chained SQLException and documentation for the database or database driver throwing the exception to resolve the problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0096E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0096E" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0096E=SCHD0096E: The current user is not in the appropriate role to use the {0} method.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The current user is not in a role that has authority to run the specified method. All Scheduler API and Mbean methods are protected by role-based security.  In general, to modify scheduler tasks or scheduler runtime attributes the user must be in a operator or higher role.  To view tasks or scheduler runtime attributes the user must be in a monitor or higher role.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Either login with a user id which is in the appropriate role or add this user to the appropriate role.  Adding users to roles is performed using the administrative console.  Please see the information center for more information.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0020I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0020I" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0020I=SCHD0020I: Invalid scheduler configuration: {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified configuration information is not valid or missing.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the configuration attributes for the Scheduler resource are present and valid.  Use the administrative console to verify the Scheduler resource.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0124E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0124E" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0124E=SCHD0124E: Unable to initialize {0} due to error: {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified object could not be initialized.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Review the error, solve the problem and retry the operation.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0095E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0095E" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0095E=SCHD0095E: The SQL statement for statement key {0} cannot be found for table key {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This exception is unexpected. The cause is not immediately known.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0123E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0123E" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0123E=SCHD0123E: The {0} field or attribute is invalid.  Valid values include: {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified field or attribute is not valid.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the field or attribute value with a value in the proper format or range.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0055E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0055E" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0055E=SCHD0055E: The NotificationSink object for task ID {0} for scheduler {1} ({2}) cannot be retreived because the following error occurred: {3}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An error occurred that prevented the NotificationSink object to be retreived from the task information.  See the message that contains the cause of the error.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See the user action for the message that contains the cause of the error.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0119E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0119E" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0119E=SCHD0119E: Invalid numeric value specified: {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified value is not numeric.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the method or object call to specify a number.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0094E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0094E" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0094E=SCHD0094E: End index of {0} is smaller than beginning index of {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified end index value is less than the specified beginning index value.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Modify the index values so the beginning index is smaller than the end index and submit the request again.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0122E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0122E" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0122E=SCHD0122E: The {0} attribute must also be specified if the {1} is set while creating a {2}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A dependent attribute was not set or was null.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Set the attribute and retry the operation.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0054E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0054E" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0054E=SCHD0054E: TaskInfo object {0} could not be created because the following error occurred: {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The TaskInfo object could not be created because an error occurred.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See the user action for the message that contains the cause of the error.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0118E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0118E" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0118E=SCHD0118E: Unable to acquire lock for {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Scheduler uses synchronization locks to maintain consistency.  The thread waiting for the lock either timed-out or was interrupted.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Try running the operation again.  If the application server is shutting down at the time of the error, then no action is necessary.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0014E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0014E" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0014E=SCHD0014E: An error occured while publishing a notification: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Notification Sink session bean specified by this task could not be contacted.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the session bean is available.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0093E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0093E" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0093E=SCHD0093E: End index of {0} cannot be negative.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified end index value is less than 0.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Modify the end index value so it is equal or greater than 0 and submit the request again.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0028I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHEDULER_CANNOT_BE_DISABLED" varFormat="Java">
    SCHEDULER_CANNOT_BE_DISABLED=SCHD0028I: Scheduler service cannot be disabled.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Scheduler service has been disabled in the configuration, but will continue to run because because of service dependencies.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Re-enable the scheduler service in the configuration to avoid receiving this message in the future.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0089I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0089I" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0089I=SCHD0089I: Table {0} cannot be dropped because it does not exist in the database.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified table cannot be dropped because it does not exist in the database.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0121E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0121E" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0121E=SCHD0121E: The LeaseManager database is not correctly configured.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The LeaseManager tables are missing or the database is inaccessible.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Create the missing LeaseManager tables using the instructions found under the Scheduler topic in the information center and verify that the Scheduler can communicate correctly with the database.  The Scheduler will continue to function without the LeaseManager tables, but performance will be decreased when using redundant or clustered Schedulers.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0053E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0053E" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0053E=SCHD0053E: The task (taskId={0}) cannot be suspended because it has been cancelled or is already completed.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified task has already run or has been canceled and cannot be suspended.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0117E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0117E" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0117E=SCHD0117E: Unexpected tokens detected for term: {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified CRON calendar interval string term is formatted incorrectly and has too many tokens.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the CRON calendar interval string to use the correct terms. See the API documentation for class com.ibm.websphere.scheduler.UserCalendar for details.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0049E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0049E" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0049E=SCHD0049E: The start-by time must be greater than the start time for non-repeating tasks.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Creating a new task using a start-by time less than the start time for a non-repeating task is not a valid operation.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Modify the StartByTime, the StartTime, StartTimeInterval, or the NumberOfRepeats and submit the request again.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0013E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0013E" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0013E=SCHD0013E: The following error occurred while accessing the UserCalendar with JNDI Name {0} and specifier {1} : {2}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The UserCalendar session bean specified by this task could not be contacted.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the session bean is available.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0009I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0009I" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0009I=SCHD0009I: The Scheduler Service is not enabled.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A scheduler instance cannot be used on this server while the scheduler service is disabled.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See the documentation found under the Scheduler topic in the information center about enabling the Scheduler service.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0092E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0092E" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0092E=SCHD0092E: Beginning index of {0} cannot be negative.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified beginning index value is less than 0.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Modify the beginning index value so it is equal or greater than 0 and submit the request again.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0088I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0088I" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0088I=SCHD0088I: Index {0} created successfully.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified index was created in the database.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0120E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0120E" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0120E=SCHD0120E: Invalid term detected: {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The SIMPLE calendar interval string supports the following terms: seconds, minutes, hours, days, weeks, months and years.  An incorrect term was specified.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the SIMPLE calendar interval string to use the correct terms. See the API documentation for class com.ibm.websphere.scheduler.UserCalendar for details.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0052E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0052E" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0052E=SCHD0052E: The task (taskId={0}) has a current state of {1}, however the task must have the state of TaskStatus.COMPLETE ({2}) or TaskStatus.CANCELLED ({3}) before it can be purged.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Attempt was made to purge the task, however, the task is not in the correct state to be purged.  The task must be in COMPLETE state or it must be CANCELLED.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Allow the task to run before purging or cancel the task first and then submit the purge request again.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0116E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0116E" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0116E=SCHD0116E: Invalid range format string specified: {0}.  Valid range format is: &lt;low&gt;-&lt;high&gt;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The CRON calendar interval string allows terms with range values.  The specified range is not of the correct syntax.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the CRON calendar interval string to use the correct terms. See the API documentation for class com.ibm.websphere.scheduler.UserCalendar for details.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0048E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0048E" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0048E=SCHD0048E: The task attribute NumberOfRepeats must be non-zero number.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The NumberOfRepeats attribute must not be zero.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Set the NumberOfRepeats attribute to a value other than zero and submit the request again.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0091E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0091E" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0091E=SCHD0091E: Beginning index of {0} is larger than the end index of {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified beginning index value is larger than the specified end index value.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Modify the index values so the beginning index is smaller than the end index and submit the request again.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0087I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0087I" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0087I=SCHD0087I: Scheduler tables created successfully.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Scheduler tables were created in the database.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0051E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0051E" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0051E=SCHD0051E: The task (taskId={0}) has been cancelled or is complete.  Cancelled or completed tasks cannot be resumed.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified task has already run or has been cancelled and cannot be resumed.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0115E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0115E" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0115E=SCHD0115E: Unable to parse CRON term {0}: {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified CRON calendar interval string has an incorrect term at the specified position.  Positions are from 1 to 6.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the CRON calendar interval string to use the correct terms. See the API documentation for class com.ibm.websphere.scheduler.UserCalendar for details.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0047E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0047E" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0047E=SCHD0047E: The TaskInfo class {0} must have a registered implementation.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified TaskInfo class type cannot be used because it is not of a registered type.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Modify the application to use a TaskInfo class that has a registered implementation and submit the create request again.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0007E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0007E" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0007E=SCHD0007E: Error while accessing the persistent store: {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The data store used by this scheduler instance could not be reached.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See the server log files for detailed exception data.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0090I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0090I" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0090I=SCHD0090I: Scheduler tables dropped successfully.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Scheduler tables were dropped from the database.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0086I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0086I" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0086I=SCHD0086I: Table {0} cannot be created because it already exists in the database.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified table already exists in the database.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0050E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0050E" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0050E=SCHD0050E: The task attribute InitialState has an invalid value of {0}.  Valid values are TaskStatus.SCHEDULED ({1}) and TaskStatus.SUSPENDED ({2}).
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified InitialState value is not valid at this time.  The valid values are SCHEDULED or SUSPENDED.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Set the InitialState value to either SCHEDULED or SUSPENDED and submit the request again.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0114E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0114E" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0114E=SCHD0114E: Invalid repeat value of {0} for term {1}.  The value must be between 1 and {2}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The CRON calendar interval string allows terms with repeat values.  Each repeating term type has a lower limit of 1 and an upper limit based on the term position.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the CRON calendar interval string to use the correct terms. See the API documentation for class com.ibm.websphere.scheduler.UserCalendar for details.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0046E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0046E" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0046E=SCHD0046E: The table {0} in datasource {1} used by scheduler resource {2} ({3}) is missing or is not accessible.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified table cannot be found in the configured database for the specified scheduler resource.  The possible causes are: An incorrect data source JNDI name has been configured, an incorrect table prefix has been configured, or the scheduler tables have not been created in the database.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Use the administrative console to verify the data source JNDI name and the table prefix configuration.  To create the scheduler database tables, see the &quot;Creating the database for scheduler&quot; article in the information center.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0085E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0085E" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0085E=SCHD0085E: Unable to find datasource JNDI name {0}. The following configuration files were searched: {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Scheduler was unable to find the data source for the specified JNDI name in the message.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the specified data source exists in the configuration and it exists at the same or higher scope than the scheduler configuration.  If it does not exist, create it or alter the Scheduler resource to use an existing datasource.  See the information center for more information about creating data sources and modifying scheduler configurations.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0113E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0113E" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0113E=SCHD0113E: Term value &apos;?&apos; is invalid for the specified term.  The &apos;?&apos; token is only valid for terms DayOfMonth or DayOfWeek.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The CRON calendar interval string requires that either the DayOfMonth or DayOfWeek is specified, but not both.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the CRON calendar interval string to use the correct terms. See the API documentation for class com.ibm.websphere.scheduler.UserCalendar for details.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0045E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0045E" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0045E=SCHD0045E: An exception occurred retrieving the Data source Alias configuration information for scheduler resource {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An exception occurred while retrieving the authentication alias for the data source configuration information.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Use the administrative console to verify the authentication alias for the data source is configured correctly.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0084W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0084W" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0084W=SCHD0084W: The lease manager tables in datasource {0} used by scheduler resource {1} ({2}) are missing, are not accessible, or are not configured correctly.  The scheduler function will run normally without these tables, however multiple schedulers using the same task tables may experience a high rate of task collisions which may impact overall performance.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Scheduler attempted to find the lease manager tables and they are missing.  The lease manager tables must reside in the specified data source and have names that begin with the configured table prefix and end with &quot;LMGR&quot; and &quot;LMPR&quot;.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See the information center for information on creating scheduler tables.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0109E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0109E" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0109E=SCHD0109E: Invalid value detected.  The value for field {0} must be a valid non-null value.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified field or argument must not be null.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Change the method or object call to set the appropriate argument or verify that the field value is properly set.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0044W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0044W" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0044W=SCHD0044W: The Poll Interval attribute value of {0} seconds for the scheduler resource {1} is not within the valid range.  The valid range is {2} to {3}. The scheduler resource is created using a poll interval of {4} seconds.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The configured poll interval value is not in the specified range, however, the scheduler resource is created with the specified poll interval. The poll interval value specifies the length of time in seconds the scheduler polls the database for tasks.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Use the administrative console to configure the poll interval value for the specified scheduler resource.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0112E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0112E" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0112E=SCHD0112E: The DayOfMonth or DayOfWeek term must be specified, but not both.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The CRON calendar interval string requires that either the DayOfMonth or DayOfWeek is specified, but not both.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the CRON calendar interval string to use the correct terms. See the API documentation for class com.ibm.websphere.scheduler.UserCalendar for details.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0108E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0108E" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0108E=SCHD0108E: Unable to de-serialize a home handle due to error: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Scheduler is attempting to read a HomeHandle object from an input stream, but the Home is unavailable.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    This error is typically caused when the application, module or EJB is not available.  Review the full error to determine the cause of the problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0083E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0083E" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0083E=SCHD0083E: Unable to find the scheduler configuration for resource URI {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Scheduler attempted to find the configuration described in the message but could not locate it.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the URI and try your request again.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0111E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0111E" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0111E=SCHD0111E: Incorrect number of terms specified.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The CRON calendar interval string requires 6 terms: second minute HourOfDay DayOfMonth Month DayOfWeek
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the CRON calendar interval string to use the correct terms. See the API documentation for class com.ibm.websphere.scheduler.UserCalendar for details.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0079E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0079E" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0079E=SCHD0079E: The Scheduler {0} ({1}) was unable to reschedule failed task {2} due to an unexpected error: {3}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Scheduler attempted to re-run a task that previously failed due to an error.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See previous messages and the included exception for further information.  Once the error is resolved, the Scheduler will attempt to re-run the failed task.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0043E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0043E" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0043E=SCHD0043E: The JNDI name for scheduler resource {0} is missing.  The scheduler resource is not created.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A scheduler resource requires a JNDI name, however, the JNDI name in the configuration information for the specified scheduler resource is blank or null.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Use the administrative console to configure a JNDI name for the specified scheduler resource.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0039I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0039I" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0039I=SCHD0039I: The Scheduler Daemon for instance {0} has been stopped.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Scheduler Service has stopped for the specified Scheduler instance.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0107E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0107E" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0107E=SCHD0107E: A byte array read field {0} with an unexpected type of {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Scheduler is attempting to read an object from an input stream, but the object&apos;s type number was unexpected.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    This error is typically caused by a mismatch in product versions or an unexpected product error.  Verify that the version of the Scheduler that logged this error is compatible with the version of the Scheduler that created the task.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0003E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0003E" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0003E=SCHD0003E: An error occured while starting the scheduler service: {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An unexpected error occurred.  See the FFDC logs and the associated exception for details.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See the server log files for detailed exception data.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0082E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0082E" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0082E=SCHD0082E: Unable to determine the configuration location for resource URI {0}.  The URI resolved to object name {1} with location properties {2}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Scheduler attempted to find the server, node or cell name from the URI.  The URI does not contain the expected key field names server or node or cell.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the URI and try your request again.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0078I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0078I" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0078I=SCHD0078I: The Scheduler Service has completed starting the Schedulers.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Scheduler Service has initialized and has started each configured Scheduler instance.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0110E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0110E" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0110E=SCHD0110E: The DayOfWeek term must be between 1 and 7.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The DayOfWeek term for the CRON calendar interval string is not in the correct range.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Update the DayOfWeek term in the calendar interval string to use a number between 1 and 7.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0042E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0042E" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0042E=SCHD0042E: The Work Manager JNDI name for scheduler resource {0} ({1}) is missing. The scheduler resource is not created.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A scheduler resource requires a work manager JNDI name, however, the Work Manager JNDI name in the configuration information for the specified scheduler resource is missing.  This can occur for the following reasons: The Work Manager attribute for the specified scheduler resource is blank or not configured, the configured Work Manager&apos;s JNDI name attribute is blank or null, or the configured Work Manager cannot be found in the configuration information.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Use the administrative console to verify a Work Manager is configured for the specified scheduler resource.  Also, verify the configured Work Manager&apos;s configuration contains a valid JNDI name attribute.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0038I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0038I" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0038I=SCHD0038I: The Scheduler Daemon for instance {0} has started.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Scheduler Daemon has started for the specified Scheduler instance.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0002I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0002I" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0002I=SCHD0002I: The Scheduler Service has stopped.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Scheduler Service has stopped and is no longer scheduling tasks.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0106E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0106E" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0106E=SCHD0106E: A byte array expected field with id {0} but read id {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Scheduler is attempting to read an object from an input stream, but a field is incorrect or out of order.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    This error is typically caused by a mismatch in product versions or an unexpected product error.  Verify that the version of the Scheduler that logged this error is compatible with the version of the Scheduler that created the task.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0081E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0081E" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0081E=SCHD0081E: The Scheduler was unable to create the task handler EJB home for JNDI name {0} due to an unexpected error: {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Scheduler attempted to create an instance of the defined task hander EJB home, but failed to do so because of an unexcepted error.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See the message that contains the cause of the error.  The server log files may contain additional failure details.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0077I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0077I" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0077I=SCHD0077I: The Scheduler Service is starting the Schedulers.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Scheduler Service has initialized and is starting each configured Scheduler instance.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0041E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0041E" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0041E=SCHD0041E: The Data source JNDI Name attribute for scheduler resource {0} ({1})is missing. The scheduler resource is not created.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A scheduler resource requires a data source JNDI name, however the data source JNDI Name attribute in the configuration information for the specified scheduler resource is blank or null.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Use the administrative console to configure a data source JNDI name for the specified scheduler resource.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0037I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0037I" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0037I=SCHD0037I: The Scheduler Service has been initialized.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Scheduler Service has been initialized.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0001I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0001I" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0001I=SCHD0001I: The Scheduler Service has started.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Scheduler Service is started.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0105E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0105E" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0105E=SCHD0105E: A byte array expected field {0} with version {1} but read version {2}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Scheduler is attempting to read an object from an input stream, but the object&apos;s version number was unexpected.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    This error is typically caused by a mismatch in product versions or an unexpected product error.  Verify that the version of the Scheduler that logged this error is compatible with the version of the Scheduler that created the task.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0080E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0080E" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0080E=SCHD0080E: The Scheduler was unable to create the task handler EJB home object due to an unexpected error: {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Scheduler attempted to create an instance of the defined task hander EJB home, but failed to do so because of an unexcepted error.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See previous messages and the included exception for further information.  Once the error is resolved, the Scheduler will attempt to re-run the failed task.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0040I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0040I" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0040I=SCHD0040I: The Scheduler Service is stopping.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Scheduler Service is stopping.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0076E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0076E" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0076E=SCHD0076E: Scheduler resource {0} ({1}) was unable to fire a notification event of {2} for task with task id {3} because the following error occurred: {4}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An unexpected error occurred while the specified scheduler resource was firing the specified notification event for the specified task.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See the message that contains the cause of the error.  The server log files may contain additional failure details.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0036I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0036I" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0036I=SCHD0036I: The Scheduler Service is initializing.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Scheduler Service is initialized.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0104E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0104E" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0104E=SCHD0104E: The Scheduler poll daemon {0} ({1}) failed to load tasks from the database due to an exception: {2}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Scheduler is attempting to load tasks from the database, but was unable to complete due to an unexpected exception.  Some tasks will fail to run until the problem is resolved.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Review the error and resolve the problem. The daemon will continue to attempt to poll the database.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0103W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0103W" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0103W=SCHD0103W: The Scheduler {0} ({1}) was unable to run task {2} because the application or module is unavailable: {3}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Scheduler is attempting to run a task, but the application or module that the task was created with is not available.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Start or install the application, module or component.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0075E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0075E" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0075E=SCHD0075E: The following error occurred in scheduler resource {0} ({1}) while cancelling task for task id {2}: {3}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An unexpected error occurred while the specified scheduler resource was cancelling the specified task.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See the message that contains the cause of the error.  The server log files may contain additional failure details.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0035I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0035I" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0035I=SCHD0035I: The Scheduler {0} has stopped.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified Scheduler instance and daemon have stopped.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0139E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0139E" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0139E=SCHD0139E: Unable to invoke the {0} EJB: {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    There was an error when attempting to invoke a method using the specified EJB.  See the nested exception for details on the cause of the problem.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Review the details from the nested exception stack to determine the cause of the error.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0074E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0074E" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0074E=SCHD0074E: The Scheduler {0} ({1}) was not able to acquire a read lock for the AsynchScope because the following error occurred: {2}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An error occurred which prevented the specified scheduler from acquiring a read lock for the AsynchScope.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See the message that contains the cause of the error.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0102I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0102I" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0102I=SCHD0102I: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This exception is unexpected. The cause is not immediately known.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0034I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0034I" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0034I=SCHD0034I: The Scheduler {0} is stopping.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified Scheduler instance and daemon are stopping.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0138E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0138E" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0138E=SCHD0138E: Unable to retrieve {0} from a javax.ejb.HomeHandle.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    There was an error when attempting to retrieve the EJBHome instance from a HomeHandle.  See the nested exception for details on the cause of the problem.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the EJB and Application are available.  If no longer available, cancel or suspend the task.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SCHD0069W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SCHD0069W" varFormat="Java">
    SCHD0069W=SCHD0069W: The Scheduler {0} ({1}) was unable to execute the task for task ID {2} because a task collision occurred. Task collisions occur when another Scheduler updates or executes the same task.  The cause of the collision is: {3}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Another scheduler ran or updated the task prior to this scheduler updating or running the task.  The task was run or updated by another scheduler.  This can occur when the two or more schedulers compete for the same tasks.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See the information center for information on reducing task collisions.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<!-- END MESSAGES -->
</TMSSource>
