<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/css" href="../../resources/stylesheets/wasmsgxml.css"?>
<TMSSource name="TivoliMessages" tmsVersion="1.0" xml:lang="en">
<!-- CMVC MSG File Name = SERV1/ws/code/ssl.channel.impl/src/com/ibm/ws/ssl/channel/resources/sslchannelmessages.nlsprops -->
<!-- DO NOT EDIT THIS FILE - This file was generated by the XML/Html & Property emitter -->
<!-- BEGIN MESSAGES -->
<Message ID="SSLC0002E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="invalid.security.properties" varFormat="Java">
    invalid.security.properties=SSLC0002E: The SSL channel cannot be started due to the following incorrect settings:
 {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    One or more settings for security in the SSL channel were not valid.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    The SSL channel security settings should be modified to the correct values.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SSLC0005E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="no.pkcs.keystore" varFormat="Java">
    no.pkcs.keystore=SSLC0005E: Unable to get a PKCS keystore.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The token information provided did not identify a valid PKCS keystore.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Review and update the token information to identify a valid PKCS keystore.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SSLC0001W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="invalid.security.level" varFormat="Java">
    invalid.security.level=SSLC0001W: {0} in an invalid security level.  Default of high will be used.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Valid values for security level are low, medium and high.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that the security level is set to a valid value.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SSLC0006E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="unable.to.read.config" varFormat="Java">
    unable.to.read.config=SSLC0006E: Error reading the SSL channel configuration, exception: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An exception was created when reading the SSL channel configuration.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Problems in the SSL channel configuration should be fixed.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SSLC0008E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="handshake.failure" varFormat="Java">
    handshake.failure=SSLC0008E: Unable to initialize SSL connection.  Unauthorized access was denied or security settings have expired.  Exception is {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A new connection failed to complete a successful secure handshake.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check security settings.  The certificate might have expired.  Alternatively, an unauthorized client connection might have been denied.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SSLC0003E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="security.repertoire.not.found" varFormat="Java">
    security.repertoire.not.found=SSLC0003E: Alias {0} does not map to a known security repertoire.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    If a configuration alias is specified on the SSL channel, it must map to a security repertoire.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    The SSL channel configuration must be updated to reference a valid security repertoire.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SSLC0009E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="hwcrypto.not.supported" varFormat="Java">
    hwcrypto.not.supported=SSLC0009E: Hardware crypto is not supported.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Support for hardware cryptography cards is not available.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Change the security settings to disable the use of hardware cryptography.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SSLC0013E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="invalid.keystore.password" varFormat="Java">
    invalid.keystore.password=SSLC0013E: Invalid password for keystore {0}.  Internal exception {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The password provided for the keystore is not compatible.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check the keystore password in the security settings, or specify a new keystore and password.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SSLC0012E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="null.truststore" varFormat="Java">
    null.truststore=SSLC0012E: Invalid truststore name of null.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The truststore name is not present in the security configuration.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Update the security settings to specify a valid truststore file.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SSLC0004W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="provider.not.fips.enabled" varFormat="Java">
    provider.not.fips.enabled=SSLC0004W: FIPS support has been requested, but the specified provider {0} might not support it.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Not enough information is available to determine if the specified provider is FIPS enabled.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the specified provider has the appropriate FIPS support.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SSLC0011E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="no.keystore.and.hwcrypto" varFormat="Java">
    no.keystore.and.hwcrypto=SSLC0011E: No keystore specified and no hardware crypto defined.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A keystore or hardware cryptography setting is required in the security configuration, but neither exist.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Update the security settings to specify a keystore or to enable hardware cryptography.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SSLC0007W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="security.ssl.config.initialization.warning.invalidkeystoretype" varFormat="Java">
    security.ssl.config.initialization.warning.invalidkeystoretype=SSLC0007W: The keystore or truststore type specified is invalid.  Automatically adjusting to use the correct type, however, please correct the SSL configuration for performance reasons.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The keystore or truststore type specified is not valid.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Modify the SSL configuration so that the keystore or truststore type is a valid type.  You can check the keystore and truststore types by loading them in WebSphere&apos;s IKeyMan tool.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="SSLC0010E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="empty.keystore" varFormat="Java">
    empty.keystore=SSLC0010E: Keystore file exists, but is empty: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The keystore from the configuration was found, but had no contents.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Replace the current keystore file with valid keystore.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<!-- END MESSAGES -->
</TMSSource>
