<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/css" href="../../resources/stylesheets/wasmsgxml.css"?>
<TMSSource name="TivoliMessages" tmsVersion="1.0" xml:lang="en">
<!-- CMVC MSG File Name = ws/code/i18nctx/src/server/com/ibm/ws/i18n/context/rsrc/i18nctx.nlsprops --> 
<!-- DO NOT EDIT THIS FILE - This file was generated by the XML/Html & Property emitter -->
<!-- BEGIN MESSAGES -->
<Message ID="I18N0003I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INF.CTX.INVALID" varFormat="Java">
    INF.CTX.INVALID=I18N0003I: The Internationalization context element [{0}] is invalid on {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified type of context element is malformed.  See the product documentation for details about well-formed locale and time zone elements. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    When using the [CMI, Run-As-Specified] internationalization context management policy, reassemble the application component and correct the problematic context element. For application-managed internationalization, correct the problematic context element within the application source. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="I18N9004E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ERR.CTX.SECURITY.ACCESS.EXC" varFormat="Java">
    ERR.CTX.SECURITY.ACCESS.EXC=I18N9004E: A Security exception occurred while accessing a default Internationalization context element ({0}) on {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Java security framework is prohibiting access to the default Java Virtual Machine locale or time zone. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Modify the Java security framework permissions to allow access to the default locale or time zone. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="I18N9009E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ERR.NO.ASYNCHBEANS.SUPPORT" varFormat="Java">
    ERR.NO.ASYNCHBEANS.SUPPORT=I18N9009E: AsynchBeans service is unavailable on {0}.
The AsynchBeans environment cannot support Internationalization context.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The internationalization context is not supported in the specified asynchronous beans runtime environment, if it is running. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the application server must support asynchronous beans, verify that asynchbeans.jar resides in the class path and review the trace log for error conditions related to asynchronous beans. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="I18N0013I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INF.STATE.BLOCKING" varFormat="Java">
    INF.STATE.BLOCKING=I18N0013I: The Internationalization service is suspended (blocked) due to a previous condition on {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Indicates a change in the quality of the internationalization service.  If a serious problem occurs, service might be suspended. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Review the trace log for error conditions that might result in suspension of service. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="I18N9001E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ERR.MISSING.KEY" varFormat="Java">
    ERR.MISSING.KEY=I18N9001E: Message key {0} was not found in any searched resource bundles.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The message key supplied to retrieve a message is not valid. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    None. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="I18N9005E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ERR.CTX.CMI.ACCESS.EXC" varFormat="Java">
    ERR.CTX.CMI.ACCESS.EXC=I18N9005E: Application components can set invocation context elements under the Application-managed (AMI) Internationalization context management policy, only; the current applicable policy {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The internationalization context API throws an IllegalStateException exception whenever an application component attempts to set its invocation locale while running under a container-managed internationalization context policy (for example, [CMI, Run-As-Caller]). 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Reassemble the application and associate the application-managed internationalization context management policy to the specified application component. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="I18N0006I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INF.ATTR.MISSING" varFormat="Java">
    INF.ATTR.MISSING=I18N0006I: The Internationalization context management policy is unavailable on {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The internationalization context element for the application component was unavailable during a particular action, such as handling an outgoing request or completing an internationalization context API method invocation. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Reassemble the application and assign an internationalization context management policy to the component indicated.  Otherwise, the service uses the default policy. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="I18N9014E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ERR.NO.API.SUPPORT" varFormat="Java">
    ERR.NO.API.SUPPORT=I18N9014E: The Internationalization context API is unavailable on {0}.
Application components will be unable to access Internationalization context API references.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A serious error has occurred: Without API support, application components cannot access internationalization context elements. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    None. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="I18N0007I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INF.ATTR.INVALID" varFormat="Java">
    INF.ATTR.INVALID=I18N0007I: The Internationalization context management policy is invalid on {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The content of an internationalization context management policy is not valid. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Reassemble the application and ensure that the specified internationalization context management policy is supported. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="I18N9008E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ERR.NO.IIOP.SUPPORT" varFormat="Java">
    ERR.NO.IIOP.SUPPORT=I18N9008E: Activity service is unavailable on {0}.
The Internationalization service cannot propagate or receive context on IIOP requests.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A serious error has occurred: Without the activity service, internationalization context cannot be propagated over IIOP requests. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Review the trace log for activity service error conditions. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="I18N9002E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ERR.INTRNL.EXC" varFormat="Java">
    ERR.INTRNL.EXC=I18N9002E: An unexpected exception occurred while providing Internationalization service on {0}:
{1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The service encountered an unexpected condition. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Enable tracing for the internationalization service and examine the trace log for statements that indicate both the actual problem and the resulting quality of service. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="I18N0001I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INF.CTX.DEFAULT.USED" varFormat="Java">
    INF.CTX.DEFAULT.USED=I18N0001I: The default Internationalization context element [{0}] was used on {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The internationalization service API and propagation mechanisms provide default values for internationalization context elements that are either unavailable or not valid. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    The service provides local process default elements for any caller context elements that are missing from an incoming request.
For invocation context elements, specify the invocation locales and time zones through the internationalization context API before issuing outgoing requests. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="I18N9010E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ERR.NO.EJB.SUPPORT" varFormat="Java">
    ERR.NO.EJB.SUPPORT=I18N9010E: EJB container service is unavailable on {0}.
The Internationalization service cannot support EnterpriseBeans.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A serious error has occurred: Without Enterprise JavaBeans (EJB) container support, internationalization context cannot be scoped properly to EJB methods. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Review the trace log for EJB container-related error conditions. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="I18N9015E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ERR.NO.JNDI.SUPPORT" varFormat="Java">
    ERR.NO.JNDI.SUPPORT=I18N9015E: The Internationalization context API cannot be bound into the namespace on {0}.
Application components will be unavailable on {0}.
Application components will be unable to access Internationalization context API references.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A serious error has occurred: Without naming service (JNDI) support, application components cannot obtain internationalization context API references. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Review the trace log for error conditions related to the naming service. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="I18N0011I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INF.STATE.ALREADY" varFormat="Java">
    INF.STATE.ALREADY=I18N0011I: The Internationalization service is already {0} on {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Indicates a re-attempted action on the internationalization service. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="I18N0005I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INF.ATTR.DEFAULT.USED" varFormat="Java">
    INF.ATTR.DEFAULT.USED=I18N0005I: The default Internationalization context management policy {0} was used on {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The internationalization service applies the default context management policy [CMI, Run-As-Caller] for internationalization context management deployment descriptors that are either unavailable or not valid. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.  If you prefer a context management policy other than the default, reassemble the application and assign internationalization context management policies to all components. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="I18N9006E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ERR.NO.ORB.SUPPORT" varFormat="Java">
    ERR.NO.ORB.SUPPORT=I18N9006E: The ORB has failed on {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A serious error has occurred: The internationalization service cannot handle IIOP requests with an object request broker (ORB). 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Review the trace log for related error conditions. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="I18N9012E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ERR.NO.WEBSERVICE.SUPPORT" varFormat="Java">
    ERR.NO.WEBSERVICE.SUPPORT=I18N9012E: SOAP support is unavailable on {0}.
The Internationalization service cannot support Web Services. 
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A serious error has occurred: Without SOAP handling support, internationalization context cannot be scoped properly to Web services. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Review the trace log for any Web service-related error conditions. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="I18N9003E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ERR.MINOR.CODE" varFormat="Java">
    ERR.MINOR.CODE=I18N9003E: Minor code: {0}; refer to the Troubleshooting section of the Internationalization service Programmer&apos;&apos;s Guide.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A minor code indicates a particular system error. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    None.  Minor codes are not implemented in this release of the internationalization service. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="I18N0010I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INF.STATE" varFormat="Java">
    INF.STATE=I18N0010I: The Internationalization service is {0} on {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Specifies the current state, configuration, or quality of the internationalization service. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="I18N9007E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ERR.NO.TCM.SUPPORT" varFormat="Java">
    ERR.NO.TCM.SUPPORT=I18N9007E: The Thread Context Manager is not operational on {0}.
The Internationalization service cannot manage context.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A serious error has occurred: The internationalization service cannot scope context elements without the thread context manager. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Review the trace log for related error conditions. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="I18N0004I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INF.CTX.UNSUPPORTED.FORMAT" varFormat="Java">
    INF.CTX.UNSUPPORTED.FORMAT=I18N0004I: Unsupported context format on {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The format of an internationalization context element detected on an incoming request is not supported by this release of the internationalization service. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.  By default, the service uses the format of the local process. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="I18N0002I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INF.CTX.MISSING" varFormat="Java">
    INF.CTX.MISSING=I18N0002I: The Internationalization context element [{0}] is not available on {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified internationalization context element was unavailable during a particular action, such as handling an incoming request or completing an internationalization context API method invocation. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    A context element can be missing from an incoming request (for instance, a request from a client that is not using the internationalization service).
For caller context, enable the internationalization service on the client, if possible. For missing invocation context elements, specify them through the internationalization context API. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="I18N0012I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INF.STATE.NOT" varFormat="Java">
    INF.STATE.NOT=I18N0012I: The Internationalization service is not {0} on {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified action on the internationalization service has not occurred. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="I18N9011E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ERR.NO.WEB.SUPPORT" varFormat="Java">
    ERR.NO.WEB.SUPPORT=I18N9011E: Web container service is unavailable on {0}.
The Internationalization service cannot support Servlets and JSPs. 
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A serious error has occurred: Without Web container support, internationalization context cannot be scoped properly to servlets and JavaServer Pages components. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Review the trace log for any Web container-related error conditions. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="I18N0008I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INF.ATTR.LACKING" varFormat="Java">
    INF.ATTR.LACKING=I18N0008I: The {0}, {1}, lacks Internationalization context management policy information on {2}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    No internationalization context management information was detected for the specified application component. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Reassemble the application and assign an internationalization context management policy to the specified component.  Otherwise, the service uses the default policy. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="I18N9013E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ERR.NO.METADATA.SUPPORT" varFormat="Java">
    ERR.NO.METADATA.SUPPORT=I18N9013E: MetaData service is unavailable on {0}.
The Internationalization service cannot process Internationalization deployment descriptors. 
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A serious error has occurred: Without the metadata service, internationalization context management policies default to [CMI, Run-As-Caller]. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Review the trace log for error conditions related to the metadata service. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<!-- END MESSAGES -->
</TMSSource>
