<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/css" href="../../resources/stylesheets/wasmsgxml.css"?>
<TMSSource name="TivoliMessages" tmsVersion="1.0" xml:lang="en">
<!-- CMVC MSG File Name = ws/code/sib.mfp.api/com/ibm/websphere/sib/CWSIKMessages.nlsprops -->
<!-- DO NOT EDIT THIS FILE - This file was generated by the XML/Html & Property emitter -->
<!-- BEGIN MESSAGES -->
<Message ID="CWSIK0101W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DELIVERY_ERROR_SIRC_101" varFormat="Java">
    DELIVERY_ERROR_SIRC_101=CWSIK0101W: The message {0} has been re-routed to the exception destination {1} because the mediation {2} at destination {3} caused the exception {4}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The message was given to the specified mediation; that mediation generated an exception and as a result, the message has been rerouted to the exception destination.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the mediation should not have rerouted the message, investigate the cause of the exception.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSIK0044E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DELIVERY_ERROR_SIRC_44" varFormat="Java">
    DELIVERY_ERROR_SIRC_44=CWSIK0044E: A message could not be delivered to destination {0} as the queue point for that destination is held on a WebSphere MQ server bus member and the message has been sent from foreign bus {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Messages can not be sent from a foreign bus directly to a destination whose queue point is held on WebSphere MQ and accessed using a WebSphere MQ server bus member.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Either reconfigure the sending application to connect to the local bus or allow the WebSphere MQ destination to be accessed using a WebSphere MQ foreign bus connection and route the message via the foreign bus rather than via a WebSphere MQ server bus member.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSIK0043E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DELIVERY_ERROR_SIRC_43" varFormat="Java">
    DELIVERY_ERROR_SIRC_43=CWSIK0043E: A message could not be delivered to a destination in the forward routing path as the maximum depth of the forward routing path ({0}), was exceeded.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A message was redirected along a forward routing path. The number of redirects exceeded the maximum allowed. The message was therefore sent to the exception destination.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check the forward routing path for cycles. Alternatively increase the maximum value via the custom property, sib.processor.maxForwardRoutingPath.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSIK0042E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DELIVERY_ERROR_SIRC_42" varFormat="Java">
    DELIVERY_ERROR_SIRC_42=CWSIK0042E: The MQ link with uuid {0} was not found on messaging engine {1} on bus {2}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The named MQ link is unknown on the local messaging engine.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check the MQ link name is defined and has the correct case sensitive spelling.  If the MQ link is undefined, either use an MQ link which does exist or define a new MQ link.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSIK0041E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DELIVERY_ERROR_SIRC_41" varFormat="Java">
    DELIVERY_ERROR_SIRC_41=CWSIK0041E: There are no links defined to connect to the foreign bus with name {0} on messaging engine {1} on bus {2} due to error {3}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An application has attempted to send a message to a destination on a foreign bus but there are no links defined between the local bus and the foreign bus.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Define a link between the local bus and the foreign bus in the administrative console and resend the message.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSIK0200E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DELIVERY_ERROR_SIRC_200" varFormat="Java">
    DELIVERY_ERROR_SIRC_200=CWSIK0200E: An Object of class {0} has been set into the message payload but it cannot be serialized.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An Object Message sent with the producerDoesNotModifyPayloadAfterSet flag enabled on its ConnectionFactory was sent with a payload that was not serializable by the system.  This message data has been lost
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Disable the producerDoesNotModifyPayloadAfterSet on the ConnectionFactory.  Without the flag enabled the JMS application which sets the object into the message will receive any serialization exception immediately.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSIK0040E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DELIVERY_ERROR_SIRC_40" varFormat="Java">
    DELIVERY_ERROR_SIRC_40=CWSIK0040E: The foreign bus link with name {0} was not found on messaging engine {1} on bus {2}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The named foreign bus link is unknown on the local messaging engine.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check that the foreign bus name is correct and has links defined.  If no links are defined, define a new foreign bus link between the two buses.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSIK0009E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DELIVERY_ERROR_SIRC_9" varFormat="Java">
    DELIVERY_ERROR_SIRC_9=CWSIK0009E: The destination {0} on messaging engine {1} is a port, but the connecting application requested a topic space.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An application has connected to the messaging engine and requested a destination type which does not match the underlying destination type.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the connecting application, or alter the destination to the required type using the administrative console.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSIK0008E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DELIVERY_ERROR_SIRC_8" varFormat="Java">
    DELIVERY_ERROR_SIRC_8=CWSIK0008E: The destination {0} on messaging engine {1} is a port, but the connecting application requested a queue.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An application has connected to the messaging engine and requested a destination type which does not match the underlying destination type.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the connecting application, or alter the destination to the required type using the administrative console.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSIK0007E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DELIVERY_ERROR_SIRC_7" varFormat="Java">
    DELIVERY_ERROR_SIRC_7=CWSIK0007E: The destination {0} on messaging engine {1} is a service, but the connecting application requested a port.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An application has connected to the messaging engine and requested a destination type which does not match the underlying destination type.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the connecting application, or alter the destination to the required type using the administrative console.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSIK0006E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DELIVERY_ERROR_SIRC_6" varFormat="Java">
    DELIVERY_ERROR_SIRC_6=CWSIK0006E: The destination {0} on messaging engine {1} is a service, but the connecting application requested a topic space.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An application has connected to the messaging engine and requested a destination type which does not match the underlying destination type.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the connecting application, or alter the destination to the required type using the administrative console.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSIK0005E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DELIVERY_ERROR_SIRC_5" varFormat="Java">
    DELIVERY_ERROR_SIRC_5=CWSIK0005E: The destination {0} on messaging engine {1} is a service, but the connecting application requested a queue.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An application has connected to the messaging engine and requested a destination type which does not match the underlying destination type.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the connecting application, or alter the destination to the required type using the administrative console.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSIK0004E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DELIVERY_ERROR_SIRC_4" varFormat="Java">
    DELIVERY_ERROR_SIRC_4=CWSIK0004E: The destination {0} on messaging engine {1} is a queue, but the connecting application requested a port.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An application has connected to the messaging engine and requested a destination type which does not match the underlying destination type.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the connecting application, or alter the destination to the required type using the administrative console.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSIK0003E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DELIVERY_ERROR_SIRC_3" varFormat="Java">
    DELIVERY_ERROR_SIRC_3=CWSIK0003E: The destination {0} on messaging engine {1} is a queue, but the connecting application requested a service
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An application has connected to the messaging engine and requested a destination type which does not match the underlying destination type.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the connecting application, or alter the destination to the required type using the administrative console.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSIK0002E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DELIVERY_ERROR_SIRC_2" varFormat="Java">
    DELIVERY_ERROR_SIRC_2=CWSIK0002E: The destination {0} on messaging engine {1} is a queue, but the connecting application requested a topic space.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An application has connected to the messaging engine and requested a destination type which does not match the underlying destination type.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the connecting application, or alter the destination to the required type using the administrative console.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSIK0001E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DELIVERY_ERROR_SIRC_1" varFormat="Java">
    DELIVERY_ERROR_SIRC_1=CWSIK0001E: An internal error occurred.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This exception is unexpected. The cause is not immediately known.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSIK0039E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DELIVERY_ERROR_SIRC_39" varFormat="Java">
    DELIVERY_ERROR_SIRC_39=CWSIK0039E: The foreign bus with name {0} was not found on messaging engine {1} on bus {2} due to error {3}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The named foreign bus is unknown on the local messaging engine.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check that the foreign bus name is correct.  Check that the foreign bus link has been defined and retry the command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSIK0038E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DELIVERY_ERROR_SIRC_38" varFormat="Java">
    DELIVERY_ERROR_SIRC_38=CWSIK0038E: The foreign bus with name {0} was not found on messaging engine {1} on bus {2}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The named foreign bus is unknown on the local messaging engine.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check that the foreign bus name is correct.  Check that the foreign bus link has been defined and retry the command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSIK0037E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DELIVERY_ERROR_SIRC_37" varFormat="Java">
    DELIVERY_ERROR_SIRC_37=CWSIK0037E: The message could not be delivered because its routing path contained an incorrect destination {0}. The last valid destination was {2} on messaging engine {3}. The destination was incorrect because of exception {3}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A message could not pass through its supplied routing path because the path contains an incorrect destination.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check the destinations on the routing path are available.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSIK0036E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DELIVERY_ERROR_SIRC_36" varFormat="Java">
    DELIVERY_ERROR_SIRC_36=CWSIK0036E: The message {0} was administratively rerouted from {1} on messaging engine {2}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The message was removed from the given destination and moved to the exception destination.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSIK0035E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DELIVERY_ERROR_SIRC_35" varFormat="Java">
    DELIVERY_ERROR_SIRC_35=CWSIK0035E: A message cannot be delivered to destination {0} on messaging engine {1} because it has rolled back more times than its redelivery threshold.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message cannot be delivered because every attempt to commit the transaction that would deliver the message did not succeed.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Investigate the cause of the transaction rollbacks. For further information on resolving this error, see the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webserver/appserv/was/support.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSIK0034E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DELIVERY_ERROR_SIRC_34" varFormat="Java">
    DELIVERY_ERROR_SIRC_34=CWSIK0034E: The forward routing path does not contain any entries for this service destination: {0} on this messaging engine: {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An attempt to use a service destination when the forward routing path is empty has been made.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    A service destination has to have mediated destinations in its forward routing path. Correct the path and retry.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSIK0033E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DELIVERY_ERROR_SIRC_33" varFormat="Java">
    DELIVERY_ERROR_SIRC_33=CWSIK0033E: The message reliability value {0} is greater than the destination reliability value {1} for destination {2} on messaging engine {3}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An attempt was made to route a message to a destination, but the message has a higher reliability than the destination can support.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Update the destination so that it can support messages of a higher reliability or reduce the reliability of the message to be sent.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSIK0032E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DELIVERY_ERROR_SIRC_32" varFormat="Java">
    DELIVERY_ERROR_SIRC_32=CWSIK0032E: The destination or foreign bus {0} has been deleted on messaging engine {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The destination or foreign bus is no longer usable because it has been deleted.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a valid destination or foreign bus name when sending messages.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSIK0031E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DELIVERY_ERROR_SIRC_31" varFormat="Java">
    DELIVERY_ERROR_SIRC_31=CWSIK0031E: The destination {0} already exists.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The named destination is already known on the local messaging engine, so an attempt to create one failed.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure the destination configuration is correct in the administrative console and restart the server.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSIK0030E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DELIVERY_ERROR_SIRC_30" varFormat="Java">
    DELIVERY_ERROR_SIRC_30=CWSIK0030E: The link with name {0} and UUID {1} was not found when creating bus {2}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The named link is unknown on the local messaging engine, so the attempt to create the named bus failed.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check that the link name is correct and defined in the administrative console for the bus.  Check that the messaging engine has the latest configuration applied to it.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSIK0029E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DELIVERY_ERROR_SIRC_29" varFormat="Java">
    DELIVERY_ERROR_SIRC_29=CWSIK0029E: An error occurred because the alias destination {0} targets a service destination {1} on the path {2} on messaging engine bus {3}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The alias destination is not valid because its target is a service destination.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Remove the service destination target by changing aliases in the resolution path in the administrative console.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSIK0028E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DELIVERY_ERROR_SIRC_28" varFormat="Java">
    DELIVERY_ERROR_SIRC_28=CWSIK0028E: The alias destination {0} cannot be resolved because the target destination {1} does not exist in the alias path {2}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The target destination in the alias path is unknown on the local messaging engine.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Define the target destination or correct the incorrect alias in the administrative console.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSIK0027E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DELIVERY_ERROR_SIRC_27" varFormat="Java">
    DELIVERY_ERROR_SIRC_27=CWSIK0027E: The destination with name {0} is corrupt
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The destination with the given name is corrupt and cannot be used.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Reset the destination from the administrative console.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSIK0026E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DELIVERY_ERROR_SIRC_26" varFormat="Java">
    DELIVERY_ERROR_SIRC_26=CWSIK0026E: No permitted addressable message points found for destination {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An attempt was made to use a destination but no message points of that destination were addressable due to restrictions, possibly via use of an alias or binding to a now deleted message point.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If this is a reply message, a messaging engine may have been specified in the original request message, the message point for this destination may since have been deleted. If an alias destination that restricts the addressable message points of the target destination was used, correct the alias to identify a correct set of message points.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSIK0025E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DELIVERY_ERROR_SIRC_25" varFormat="Java">
    DELIVERY_ERROR_SIRC_25=CWSIK0025E: The destination {0} on messaging engine {1} is not available because the high limit for the number of messages for this destination has already been reached.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Either all queue points of the named destination or the transmission queues on this messaging engine leading to the destination have already reached their configured high limit therefore the message cannot be accepted.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check that the configured high messages limit for the destination is correct.  If the destination exists on another messaging engine, ensure that communication with the other messaging engine is working.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSIK0024E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DELIVERY_ERROR_SIRC_24" varFormat="Java">
    DELIVERY_ERROR_SIRC_24=CWSIK0024E: The destination {0} is send disallowed for messaging engine {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An attempt has been made to send a message to a destination and a check has been made to ensure that a queue point is available for this destination.  This check failed as the only queue point for this destination is send disallowed.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Update the queue point for the destination so it is send allowed and retry the send operation.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSIK0023E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DELIVERY_ERROR_SIRC_23" varFormat="Java">
    DELIVERY_ERROR_SIRC_23=CWSIK0023E: An attempt to route a message to an exception destination on destination {3} caused by forward routing path destination {0} failed due to reason {1} with related error {2}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The next destination in the forward routing path could not be found. The message was routed to the exception destination but there was an error when the message was routed to the exception destination.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSIK0022E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DELIVERY_ERROR_SIRC_22" varFormat="Java">
    DELIVERY_ERROR_SIRC_22=CWSIK0022E: The connection is closed to messaging engine {0} and cannot be used.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The connection has been closed and cannot be used for any operation.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Create a new connection to the messaging engine.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSIK0021E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DELIVERY_ERROR_SIRC_21" varFormat="Java">
    DELIVERY_ERROR_SIRC_21=CWSIK0021E: Producer Session is closed on destination {0} on messaging engine {1} and cannot be used.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The producer has been closed and cannot be used on the specified destination.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Create a new producer session to the specified destination.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSIK0020E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DELIVERY_ERROR_SIRC_20" varFormat="Java">
    DELIVERY_ERROR_SIRC_20=CWSIK0020E: Send access to discriminator {1} on destination {0} was denied for user with subject {2}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A user is not authorized to send to the destination using the specified topic.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the user should have authority to send messages on the given topic, update the users authorization rights for the topic on the given destination.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSIK0019E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DELIVERY_ERROR_SIRC_19" varFormat="Java">
    DELIVERY_ERROR_SIRC_19=CWSIK0019E: The user {1} is not authorized to send to temporary destinations with prefix {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A user is not authorized to send to temporary destinations with the named prefix.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the user should have authority to send messages on the given temporary destination, update the users authorization rights for the temporary destination.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSIK0018E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DELIVERY_ERROR_SIRC_18" varFormat="Java">
    DELIVERY_ERROR_SIRC_18=CWSIK0018E: Send access to destination {0} was denied for user with subject {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A user is not authorized to send to the destination.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the user should have authority to send messages on the given destination, update the users authorization rights for the destination.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSIK0017E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DELIVERY_ERROR_SIRC_17" varFormat="Java">
    DELIVERY_ERROR_SIRC_17=CWSIK0017E: The destination with name {0} on messaging engine {1} is send disallowed.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An attempt has been made to send a message to a destination and a check has been made to ensure that this destination is send allowed.  This check failed as the destination is send disallowed.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Update the destination so it is send allowed and resend the message.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSIK0016E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DELIVERY_ERROR_SIRC_16" varFormat="Java">
    DELIVERY_ERROR_SIRC_16=CWSIK0016E: The transaction used for send on the destination: {0} has already been completed.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An attempt was made to use a transaction that has already been completed.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that the transaction used is a new transaction.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSIK0015E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DELIVERY_ERROR_SIRC_15" varFormat="Java">
    DELIVERY_ERROR_SIRC_15=CWSIK0015E: The destination {0} was not found on messaging engine {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The named destination is unknown on the local messaging engine.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check that the destination name is correct and that you have created the destination on the bus.  If the destination exists on another messaging engine, ensure that communication with the other messaging engine is working.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSIK0014E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DELIVERY_ERROR_SIRC_14" varFormat="Java">
    DELIVERY_ERROR_SIRC_14=CWSIK0014E: The destination {0} on messaging engine {1} is of type {2}, but the connecting application requested an unknown type {3}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An application has connected to the messaging engine and requested a destination type which does not match the underlying destination type.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the connecting application, or alter the destination to the required type using the administrative console.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSIK0013E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DELIVERY_ERROR_SIRC_13" varFormat="Java">
    DELIVERY_ERROR_SIRC_13=CWSIK0013E: The destination {0} on messaging engine {1} is a topic space, but the connecting application requested a port.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An application has connected to the messaging engine and requested a destination type which does not match the underlying destination type.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the connecting application, or alter the destination to the required type using the administrative console.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSIK0012E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DELIVERY_ERROR_SIRC_12" varFormat="Java">
    DELIVERY_ERROR_SIRC_12=CWSIK0012E: The destination {0} on messaging engine {1} is a topic space, but the connecting application requested a service.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An application has connected to the messaging engine and requested a destination type which does not match the underlying destination type.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the connecting application, or alter the destination to the required type using the administrative console.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSIK0011E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DELIVERY_ERROR_SIRC_11" varFormat="Java">
    DELIVERY_ERROR_SIRC_11=CWSIK0011E: The destination {0} on messaging engine {1} is a topic space, but the connecting application requested a queue.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An application has connected to the messaging engine and requested a destination type which does not match the underlying destination type.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the connecting application, or alter the destination to the required type using the administrative console.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSIK0010E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DELIVERY_ERROR_SIRC_10" varFormat="Java">
    DELIVERY_ERROR_SIRC_10=CWSIK0010E: The destination {0} on messaging engine {1} is a port, but the connecting application requested a service.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An application has connected to the messaging engine and requested a destination type which does not match the underlying destination type.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the connecting application, or alter the destination to the required type using the administrative console.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSIK0905E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DELIVERY_ERROR_SIRC_905" varFormat="Java">
    DELIVERY_ERROR_SIRC_905=CWSIK0905E: An internal destination configuration error occurred to destination {2} in {0}, {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This exception is unexpected. The cause is not immediately known.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSIK0901E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DELIVERY_ERROR_SIRC_901" varFormat="Java">
    DELIVERY_ERROR_SIRC_901=CWSIK0901E: An internal messaging error occurred in {0}, {1}, {2}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This exception is unexpected. The cause is not immediately known.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSIK0900E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DELIVERY_ERROR_SIRC_900" varFormat="Java">
    DELIVERY_ERROR_SIRC_900=CWSIK0900E: An internal messaging error occurred in {0}, {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This exception is unexpected. The cause is not immediately known.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSIK0106E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DELIVERY_ERROR_SIRC_106" varFormat="Java">
    DELIVERY_ERROR_SIRC_106=CWSIK0106E: WebSphere MQ has raised an error. The WebSphere MQ return and reason codes are {0} and {1}, respectively.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The message cannot be processed due to an error condition raised by WebSphere MQ.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the WebSphere MQ return and reason codes, and the WebSphere MQ error logs, to determine the cause of the error. You may need to contact your WebSphere MQ administrator to help resolve the problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSIK0105E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DELIVERY_ERROR_SIRC_105" varFormat="Java">
    DELIVERY_ERROR_SIRC_105=CWSIK0105E: There is a message format error.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The message cannot be processed because of a format error.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check the connection.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSIK0104E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DELIVERY_ERROR_SIRC_104" varFormat="Java">
    DELIVERY_ERROR_SIRC_104=CWSIK0104E: The message is too big to be handled by remote MQ; sending to exception destination: message size {0}, maximum message size {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The message is too big.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check the MQ settings.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSIK0103E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DELIVERY_ERROR_SIRC_103" varFormat="Java">
    DELIVERY_ERROR_SIRC_103=CWSIK0103E: The message {0} cannot progress further along its forward routing path after being mediated by mediation {1} at destination {2} because the message is not well formed.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    After being mediated by the specified mediation, the message properties contained objects that could not be serialized, or the data graph is not valid.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Investigate how and why the specified mediation has modified the message so that it is no longer valid.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSIK0102E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DELIVERY_ERROR_SIRC_102" varFormat="Java">
    DELIVERY_ERROR_SIRC_102=CWSIK0102E: The message {0} cannot progress further along its forward routing path after being mediated by mediation {1} at destination {2} because the message does not conform to the message format {3}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    After being mediated by the specified mediation, the message does not conform to the message format specified. The mediation has either changed the message contents, changed the message format, or both of these. The original version of the message has been rerouted to the exception destination.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Investigate how and why the specified mediation has modified the message so that it does not conform to the specified message format.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<!-- END MESSAGES -->
</TMSSource>
