<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/css" href="../../resources/stylesheets/wasmsgxml.css"?>
<TMSSource name="TivoliMessages" tmsVersion="1.0" xml:lang="en">
<!-- CMVC MSG File Name = SERV1/ws/code/naming.client/src/com/ibm/ws/naming/util/WsnMessages.nlsprops -->
<!-- DO NOT EDIT THIS FILE - This file was generated by the XML/Html & Property emitter -->
<!-- BEGIN MESSAGES -->
<Message ID="NMSV0305E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="urlNextElement" varFormat="Java">
    urlNextElement=NMSV0305E: A NamingException occurred while getting the next object in the UrlBindingEnumeration.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This exception is unexpected. The cause is not immediately known.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="NMSV0756W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="nsxmlNullCtxURL" varFormat="Java">
    nsxmlNullCtxURL=NMSV0756W: Invalid binding found in the XML file &quot;{0}&quot;.  The entry for name &quot;{1}&quot; has a nameBindingType value of &quot;contextURL&quot; but the insURL value is null.  This binding is being ignored. Updates to the corresponding persistent name space partition have been disabled.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    During server startup, while the name server was reading in the specified XML file, a binding entry that is not valid was found. The entry is being ignored.  Until the problem is corrected, update operations on contexts backed by the specified XML file are disabled.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Remove the binding entry that is not valid from the XML file. The object can then be rebound if necessary.  If necessary, delete the file entirely.  Deleting the file effectively removes all persistent bindings from the associated name space partition.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="NMSV0007E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="nsInitImplTypeBad" varFormat="Java">
    nsInitImplTypeBad=NMSV0007E: Name server initialization failed. Name server implementation type of &quot;{0}&quot; is not recognized as a valid type.
{1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This exception is unexpected. The cause is not immediately known.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="NMSV0717W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="cfBindingInvalidParam" varFormat="Java">
    cfBindingInvalidParam=NMSV0717W: Configured Bindings: The value &quot;{0}&quot; for the &quot;{1}&quot; field is invalid.
	Configured binding type: {2}
	Binding name: {3}
	Name in name space: {4}
	Scope: {5}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A configured binding was defined with a parameter value that is not valid.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the configured binding setting shown in the error message.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="NMSV0019I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="nsBootstrapPortDisabled" varFormat="Java">
    nsBootstrapPortDisabled=NMSV0019I: Opening of the bootstrap port has been suppressed by the setting of name server custom property &quot;BootstrapPortEnabled&quot; to a value of &quot;false&quot;.  Bootstrap port {0} not open.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This is an informational message indicating that the bootstrap port has been disabled.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is necessary.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="NMSV0603E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="jndiUnavailGenErr" varFormat="Java">
    jndiUnavailGenErr=NMSV0603E: Naming Service unavailable. Could not get the root context.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An unknown error occurred while attempting to obtain the initial context from the ORB.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    For more information about the root cause, refer to any additional trace output accompanying this message.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="NMSV0801W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="cfExceptionOnLoadingClusterXML" varFormat="Java">
    cfExceptionOnLoadingClusterXML=NMSV0801W: Exception encountered loading file &quot;{0}&quot; from clusters directory &quot;{1}&quot;.  Cluster configuration information has been ignored.
{2}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An error occurred when loading the specified configuration file. As a result, the name server&apos;s system name space structure might not reflect the entire cell configuration.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    The action required depends on the root cause of the problem. Refer to the diagnostic data provided to determine the root cause of the problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="NMSV0718W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="cfForeignCellBindingNoBootstrapAddrs" varFormat="Java">
    cfForeignCellBindingNoBootstrapAddrs=NMSV0718W: No bootstrap address specified for foreign cell binding &quot;{0}&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified foreign cell binding does not contain any bootstrap address information.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the foreign cell binding specified in the error message.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="NMSV0002W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="nsBootNoProps" varFormat="Java">
    nsBootNoProps=NMSV0002W: WsnNameService bootstrap object created with no properties.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    No properties were supplied to the name server to create a bootstrap object.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    This message is to aid in problem diagnosis and can be ignored if no external symptoms are experienced.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="NMSV0907E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="cannotInvokeMethod" varFormat="Java">
    cannotInvokeMethod=NMSV0907E: Could not invoke method &quot;{0}&quot; on object of type &quot;{1}&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This exception is unexpected. The cause is not immediately known.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="NMSV0605W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="jndiGetObjInstErr" varFormat="Java">
    jndiGetObjInstErr=NMSV0605W: A javax.naming.Reference object looked up from the context &quot;{0}&quot; with the name &quot;{1}&quot; was sent to the JNDI Naming Manager and an exception resulted. Reference data follows:
Reference Factory Class Name: {2}
Reference Factory Class Location URLs: {3}
{4}
Exception data follows:
{5}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    While executing a JNDI lookup or listBindings operation on a javax.naming.Reference object, a call to the JNDI Naming Manager to process the object failed. It is possible that some class required by the Reference object&apos;s factory could not be loaded or some exception occurred while instantiating the factory object. It is also possible that some class required by the factory to instantiate an object from the Reference object could not be loaded, or that some exception occurred while the factory was instantiating the object.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that the factory class can be loaded from the calling environment and that the class instantiated by the factory can be loaded. Actions on exceptions originating from the factory depend on the specific factory&apos;s implementation.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="NMSV0722W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="cfForeignCellBindingUndefVar" varFormat="Java">
    cfForeignCellBindingUndefVar=NMSV0722W: Configuration for foreign cell binding &quot;{0}&quot; contains an undefined variable reference.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The configuration for the specified foreign cell binding contains a variable reference that cannot be resolved.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the name of the variable being referenced or createa definition for the variable.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="NMSV0754W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="nsxmlNullJavaObject" varFormat="Java">
    nsxmlNullJavaObject=NMSV0754W: Invalid binding found in the XML file &quot;{0}&quot;.  The entry for name &quot;{1}&quot; has a nameBindingType value of &quot;objectJava&quot;, but the serializedBytesAsString value is null.  This binding is being ignored.  Updates to the corresponding persistent name space partition have been disabled.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    During server startup, while the name server was reading in the specified XML file, a binding entry that is not valid was found. The entry is being ignored.  Until the problem is corrected, update operations on contexts backed by the specified XML file are disabled.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Remove the binding entry that is not valid from the XML file. The object can then be rebound if necessary.  If necessary, delete the file entirely.  Deleting the file effectively removes all persistent bindings from the associated name space partition.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="NMSV0010E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="nsInitWlmErr" varFormat="Java">
    nsInitWlmErr=NMSV0010E: Name server initialization failed. Initialization of the WLM Bootstrap Service failed.
{0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This exception is unexpected. The cause is not immediately known.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="NMSV0302E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="urlNullUrlCtx" varFormat="Java">
    urlNullUrlCtx=NMSV0302E: NamingManager.getURLContext returned a null Context for the scheme &quot;{0}&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A URL was passed to a JNDI Context method, which then invoked the JNDI Naming Manager to return the Context identified by the URL. The Naming Manager method which was invoked returned a null value.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    This problem is probably the result of an incorrect configuration. Make sure that the factory for the scheme of the specified URL can be located from the value of the property, java.naming.factory.url.pkgs, found in the Context&apos;s environment.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="NMSV0761E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="nsxmlCheckinError" varFormat="Java">
    nsxmlCheckinError=NMSV0761E: An error occurred on a file checkin operation for the persistent name binding XML file &quot;{0}&quot;.  Persistent name binding update could not be completed.  Error information follows:
{1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    In order to process an update operation on a persistent name binding, the name server must check out the persistent name binding XML file from the Configuration Respository, update the file, and check it in.  The checkin operation failed.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Restart the server. Refer to the diagnostic data provided to determine the root cause of the problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="NMSV0752W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="nsxmlNotCtxIOR" varFormat="Java">
    nsxmlNotCtxIOR=NMSV0752W: Invalid binding found in the XML file &quot;{0}&quot;.  The entry for name &quot;{1}&quot; has a nameBindingType value of &quot;contextIOR&quot;, but the object for the IOR is not a context.  This binding is being ignored.   Updates to the corresponding persistent name space partition have been disabled.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    During server startup, while the name server was reading in the specified XML file, a binding entry that is not valid was found. The entry is being ignored. Until the problem is corrected, update operations on contexts backed by the specified XML file are disabled.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Remove the binding entry that is not valid from the XML file. The context can then be rebound if necessary.  If necessary, delete the file entirely.  Deleting the file effectively removes all persistent bindings from the associated name space partition.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="NMSV0016E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="nsCosConvErr" varFormat="Java">
    nsCosConvErr=NMSV0016E: Internal implementation error. Unexpected InvalidNameException thrown by WsnName while converting an internally generated name string &quot;{0}&quot; to a CosName. Throwing a CosNaming InvalidName exception.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This exception is unexpected. The cause is not immediately known.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="NMSV0715W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="cfBindingInvalidServer" varFormat="Java">
    cfBindingInvalidServer=NMSV0715W: Configured Bindings: The server &quot;{1}&quot; or node &quot;{0}&quot; specified in an EJB configured binding does not exist.  Configured binding info:
	Binding name: {2}
	Name in name space: {3}
	Scope: {4}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The non-clustered application server with name and node specified in the XML file has not been configured in this cell.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure the node name and server name identify a configured non-clustered server.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="NMSV0753W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="nsxmlNullCtxIOR" varFormat="Java">
    nsxmlNullCtxIOR=NMSV0753W: Invalid binding found in the XML file &quot;{0}&quot;.  The entry for name &quot;{1}&quot; has a nameBindingType value of &quot;contextIOR&quot;, but the stringifiedIOR value is null.  This binding is being ignored.  Updates to the corresponding persistent name space partition have been disabled.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    During server startup, while the name server was reading in the specified XML file, a binding entry that is not valid was found. The entry is being ignored. Until the problem is corrected, update operations on contexts backed by the specified XML file are disabled.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Remove the binding entry that is not valid from the XML file.  The object can then be rebound if necessary.  If necessary, delete the file entirely.  Deleting the file effectively removes all persistent bindings from the associated name space partition.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="NMSV0015E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="nsBuildSNS" varFormat="Java">
    nsBuildSNS=NMSV0015E: Name server initialization failed. Could not build the System Name Space.
{0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This exception is unexpected. The cause is not immediately known.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="NMSV0306E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="urlNoSchemeOrPkg" varFormat="Java">
    urlNoSchemeOrPkg=NMSV0306E: The scheme or package name for a URL-based name space was not set.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This exception is unexpected. The cause is not immediately known.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="NMSV0001W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="nsAlreadyInit" varFormat="Java">
    nsAlreadyInit=NMSV0001W: Name server already initialized, ignoring this request to initialize again.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The name server should be initialized only once, but there was an attempt to initialize it a second time.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    This message is to aid in problem diagnosis and can be ignored if no external symptoms are experienced.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="NMSV0100E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="cosNewCtxUnsupp" varFormat="Java">
    cosNewCtxUnsupp=NMSV0100E: new_context: Unbound context instances not allowed. Throwing NO_IMPLEMENT exception.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The method, new_context, part of the CosNaming::NamingContext interface, is not supported.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    A client program invoked the new_context method, which is not supported. Clients should use the bind_new_context method.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="NMSV0804W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="cfMissingHostName" varFormat="Java">
    cfMissingHostName=NMSV0804W: Missing host name in bootstrap address of server &quot;{0}&quot; in node &quot;{1}&quot;. Skipping this server configuration and continuing.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The bootstrap address configuration for the specified server does not contain a host name. As a result, the name server&apos;s system name space structure will not include the specified server.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure all bootstrap addresses include a host name and port number.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="NMSV0701W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="indJndiLookupEmptyName" varFormat="Java">
    indJndiLookupEmptyName=NMSV0701W: An IndirectJNDILookup object was created with an empty name. Lookups using this object will fail.
{0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An IndirectJNDILookup object was created with an empty name. Indirect lookups require non-empty names.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Do not create IndirectJNDILookup objects with empty names.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="NMSV0501W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="jcosInvPropIgnored" varFormat="Java">
    jcosInvPropIgnored=NMSV0501W: Ignored an InvalidPropertyName exception from the CosNaming name server.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This exception is unexpected. The cause is not immediately known.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="NMSV0601E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="jndiUnavailNullCtx" varFormat="Java">
    jndiUnavailNullCtx=NMSV0601E: Naming Service unavailable. Null initial context returned from ORB.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This exception is unexpected. The cause is not immediately known.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="NMSV0721W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="cfCustomPropUndefVar" varFormat="Java">
    cfCustomPropUndefVar=NMSV0721W: Custom property name &quot;{0}&quot; or value &quot;{1}&quot; contains an undefined variable reference.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The configuration for the specified custom property contains a variable reference that cannot be resolved.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the name of the variable being referenced or create a definition for the variable.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="NMSV0807W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="cfDupPortSkipConfig" varFormat="Java">
    cfDupPortSkipConfig=NMSV0807W: The bootstrap address &quot;{0}&quot; configured for server &quot;{1}&quot; on node &quot;{2}&quot; conflicts with the bootstrap port of another server. Ignoring the specified server.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Encountered two servers configured with the same bootstrap address. The one specified in the error message is being ignored. As a result, the name server&apos;s system name space structure may not reflect the entire cell configuration.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that all servers in the cell are configured with the correct bootstrap host and that all bootstrap ports on a host are unique.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="NMSV0808W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="cfClusterMemberNotFound" varFormat="Java">
    cfClusterMemberNotFound=NMSV0808W: Configuration for cluster &quot;{2}&quot; specifies a non-existent member server. Ignoring server &quot;{0}&quot; on node &quot;{1}&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Cannot find the specified server in the cell configuration.  A cluster member is probably incorrectly specified in the cluster configuration.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that members configured for a cluster include only servers which exist in the cell configuration.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="NMSV0309W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="updateEnvNamingContextErr" varFormat="Java">
    updateEnvNamingContextErr=NMSV0309W: The operation on the context &quot;{0}&quot; cannot be completed.  All contexts under java:comp/env are environment contexts and are read-only.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Enterprise beans only have read access to environment naming contexts.  Environment name contexts include java:comp/env and its subcontexts.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    You cannot perform update operations on environment naming contexts.  If you want to bind a new object, use a name that does not start with java:comp/env.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="NMSV0401W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="jldapInvName" varFormat="Java">
    jldapInvName=NMSV0401W: The name &quot;{0}&quot; is invalid. The LDAP plug-in for JNDI could not perform an internal name conversion.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This exception is unexpected. The cause is not immediately known.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="NMSV0713W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="cfBindingError" varFormat="Java">
    cfBindingError=NMSV0713W: Configured Bindings: Cannot create the configured binding &quot;{0}&quot; relative to the context &quot;{1}&quot; because of an unexpected error.
{2}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Some error occurred when creating an intermediate context for a configured binding.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure the name is valid and that it does not conflict in any way with existing bindings in the name space.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="NMSV0612W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="indirectNameNotFound" varFormat="Java">
    indirectNameNotFound=NMSV0612W: A NameNotFoundException occurred on an indirect lookup on the name &quot;{0}&quot;. The name &quot;{0}&quot; maps to a JNDI name in deployment descriptor bindings for the application performing the JNDI lookup. Make sure that the JNDI name mapping in the deployment descriptor binding is correct. If the JNDI name mapping is correct, make sure the target resource can be resolved with the specified name relative to the default initial context. NameNotFoundException data follows:
{1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The target resource cannot be resolved with the specified name relative to the default initial context.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that the JNDI name mapping in the deployment descriptor binding is correct. If the name mapping is correct, make sure the target resource can be resolved with the specified name relative to the default initial context.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="NMSV0502W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="jcosCNFactDepr" varFormat="Java">
    jcosCNFactDepr=NMSV0502W: The class &quot;com.ibm.ejs.ns.jndi.CNInitialContextFactory&quot; has been deprecated. It has been replaced with &quot;com.ibm.websphere.naming.WsnInitialContextFactory&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The initial context factory for WebSphere has changed. The old one will work, but some time in the future it will no longer be available.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Begin using the new initial context factory as soon as possible.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="NMSV0610I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="jndiNamingException" varFormat="Java">
    jndiNamingException=NMSV0610I: A NamingException is being thrown from a javax.naming.Context implementation. Details follow:
Context implementation: {0}
Context method: {1}
Context name: {2}
Target name: {3}
Other data: {4}
Exception stack trace: {5}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Some javax.naming.Context implementation has raised an exception. Data related to the exception is included with the message.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the exception triggering this message is the result of normal operation, the message can be ignored. If the exception is not expected, refer to the diagnostic information included with the message to help determine the cause.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="NMSV0719W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="cfForeignCellBindingMissingAttr" varFormat="Java">
    cfForeignCellBindingMissingAttr=NMSV0719W: Attribute &quot;{0}&quot; is not set in foreign cell binding &quot;{1}&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A required attribute is missing in the specified foreign cell binding.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the foreign cell binding attribute specified in the error message.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="NMSV0402E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="jldapJndiToLdapConv" varFormat="Java">
    jldapJndiToLdapConv=NMSV0402E: Cannot convert the JNDI name &quot;{0}&quot; to an LDAP name string.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This exception is unexpected. The cause is not immediately known.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="NMSV0101E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="badNameSyntax" varFormat="Java">
    badNameSyntax=NMSV0101E: The name syntax property &quot;{0}&quot; is set to an unrecognized value of &quot;{1}&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This exception is unexpected. The cause is not immediately known.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="NMSV0105E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="cosCosToInsConv" varFormat="Java">
    cosCosToInsConv=NMSV0105E: Cannot convert a CosName to a valid INS name.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This exception is unexpected. The cause is not immediately known.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="NMSV0806W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="cfDupPortReplaceConfig" varFormat="Java">
    cfDupPortReplaceConfig=NMSV0806W: The bootstrap address &quot;{0}&quot; configured for this server conflicts with the bootstrap address configured for server &quot;{1}&quot; on node &quot;{2}&quot;. Ignoring the conflicting server.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Encountered another server configured with the same bootstrap host and port as this server.  The conflicting server is being ignored. As a result, the name server&apos;s system name space structure may not reflect the entire cell configuration.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that all servers are configured with the correct bootstrap addresses and that all bootstrap ports on a host are unique.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="NMSV0760E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="nsxmlCheckoutError" varFormat="Java">
    nsxmlCheckoutError=NMSV0760E: An error occurred on a file checkout operation for the persist name binding XML file &quot;{0}&quot;.  Persistent name binding update could not be completed.  Error information follows:
{1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    In order to process an update operation on a persistent name binding, the name server must check out the persistent name binding XML file from the Configuration Respository.  The checkout operation failed.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Restart the server. Refer to the diagnostic data provided to determine the root cause of the problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="NMSV0716W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="cfBindingInvalidCluster" varFormat="Java">
    cfBindingInvalidCluster=NMSV0716W: Configured Bindings: The cluster &quot;{0}&quot; specified in an EJB configured binding does not exist.  Configured binding info:
	Binding name: {1}
	Name in name space: {2}
	Scope: {3}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The cluster with the name specified in the XML file has not been configured in this cell.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure the cluster name indentifies a configured cluster.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="NMSV0110E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="cosInvServantErr" varFormat="Java">
    cosInvServantErr=NMSV0110E: CosNaming server caught exception: InvalidServantException.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This exception is unexpected. The cause is not immediately known.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="NMSV0720W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="cfForeignCellBindingInvalidValue" varFormat="Java">
    cfForeignCellBindingInvalidValue=NMSV0720W: The value &quot;{0}&quot; of attribute &quot;{1}&quot; is invalid in foreign cell binding &quot;{2}&quot;.
{3}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified foreign cell binding is defined with an invalid value.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the foreign cell binding attribute specified in the error message.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="NMSV0816W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="cfPropChangedSvrRestart" varFormat="Java">
    cfPropChangedSvrRestart=NMSV0816W: Name server custom property &quot;{0}&quot; has been changed. This will require a manual server restart.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Changes have been made to the name server custom property which affect the name server running in the process associated with this message.  The server process must be restarted for these changes to take effect.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Restart the server which received this warning message.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="NMSV0904W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="invCosNameIgnored" varFormat="Java">
    invCosNameIgnored=NMSV0904W: Ignored InvalidNameException while converting a CosName to a String for internal processing.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This exception is unexpected. The cause is not immediately known.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="NMSV0812W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="cfSvrRestartRequired" varFormat="Java">
    cfSvrRestartRequired=NMSV0812W: Configuration changes have occurred which require this server to be restarted.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Changes have been made to the configuration which affect the name server running in the process associated with this message.  The server process must be restarted for these changes to take effect.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Restart the server which received this warning message.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="NMSV0103E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="cosEmptyName" varFormat="Java">
    cosEmptyName=NMSV0103E: A zero-length CosNaming::NameComponent array was specified. Throwing InvalidName exception.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An empty name (zero name components) was passed to the CosNaming server. Empty names are not valid.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the CosNaming client is a customer-provided application, this is a user error.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="NMSV0609W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="jndiGetObjInstNoop" varFormat="Java">
    jndiGetObjInstNoop=NMSV0609W: A Reference object looked up from the context &quot;{0}&quot; with the name &quot;{1}&quot; was sent to the JNDI Naming Manager and was returned unprocessed. Reference data follows:
Reference Factory Class Name: {2}
Reference Factory Class Location URLs: {3}
{4}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    While executing a JNDI lookup or listBindings operation on a javax.naming.Reference object, a call to the JNDI Naming Manager to process the object returned the original Reference object, indicating that no processing was done. This is most likely not the intended result. It is possible that the factory class required to process the Reference could not be determined or loaded.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that the Reference object contains a factory class name. Ensure that the factory class can be loaded from the calling environment.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="NMSV0905E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="cannotGetClassObj" varFormat="Java">
    cannotGetClassObj=NMSV0905E: Failed to create Class object for the class &quot;{0}&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This exception is unexpected. The cause is not immediately known.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="NMSV0818I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="cfCustomProperty" varFormat="Java">
    cfCustomProperty=NMSV0818I: Name server custom property &quot;{0}&quot; set to &quot;{1}&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This is an informational message indicating a name server custom property setting.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is necessary.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="NMSV0012E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="nsInitCos" varFormat="Java">
    nsInitCos=NMSV0012E: Name server initialization failed. Cannot create the CosNaming name tree.
{0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This exception is unexpected. The cause is not immediately known.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="NMSV0714W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="cfgInvalidDupPort" varFormat="Java">
    cfgInvalidDupPort=NMSV0714W: Invalid Configuration: 
	The port number &quot;{0}&quot; of end point named &quot;{1}&quot; is being used by end point &quot;{2}&quot; in server &quot;{3}&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A duplicate port number has been assigned in the same server. The server might not work properly.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that each endpoint in each server configuration has an unique port number assigned, then restart the server.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="NMSV0762E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="nsxmlUnlockError" varFormat="Java">
    nsxmlUnlockError=NMSV0762E: An error occurred on a file unlock operation for the persistent name binding XML file &quot;{0}&quot;.  Error information follows:
{1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    After experiencing some problem processing a persistent name binding XML file, a Configuration Respository request to unlock the file failed.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Restart the server. Refer to the diagnostic data provided to determine the root cause of the problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="NMSV0815W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="cfInvalidProperty" varFormat="Java">
    cfInvalidProperty=NMSV0815W: Name server custom property value &quot;{0}&quot; is invalid for name server custom property: &quot;{1}&quot;. Will use default value instead.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A wrong value has been specified in name server custom property.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure the property value is valid. For BootstrapPortEnabled name server custom property, the value must be either &quot;true&quot; or &quot;false&quot;. For naming.systemNameSpace.scope, valid values are &quot;cell&quot;, &quot;node&quot;, and &quot;server&quot;.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="NMSV0009E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="nsInitBootObjErr" varFormat="Java">
    nsInitBootObjErr=NMSV0009E: Name server initialization failed. Unable to create name server bootstrap object.
{0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This exception is unexpected. The cause is not immediately known.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="NMSV0757W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="nsxmlInvalidName" varFormat="Java">
    nsxmlInvalidName=NMSV0757W: Invalid binding found in the XML file &quot;{0}&quot; under the context with the name &quot;{1}&quot;.  The binding has a nameComponent value of &quot;{2}&quot;, which is an invalid name component.  This binding is being ignored. Updates to the corresponding persistent name space partition have been disabled.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The binding name for the entry is not valid.  The name must be a valid CORBA INS name string for a single name component.  The entry is being ignored.  Until the problem is corrected, update operations on contexts backed by the specified XML file are disabled.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Change the binding name to a valid name which does not conflict with other binding names, or remove the binding entry that is not valid from the XML file and rebind the object if necessary.  If necessary, delete the file entirely.  Deleting the file effectively removes all persistent bindings from the associated name space partition.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="NMSV0310E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="inWrongThreadContext" varFormat="Java">
    inWrongThreadContext=NMSV0310E: A JNDI operation on a &quot;java:&quot; name cannot be completed because the server runtime is not able to associate the operation&apos;&apos;s thread with any J2EE application component. This condition can occur when the JNDI client using the &quot;java:&quot; name is not executed on the thread of a server application request. Make sure that a J2EE application does not execute JNDI operations on &quot;java:&quot; names within static code blocks or in threads created by that J2EE application. Such code does not necessarily run on the thread of a server application request and therefore is not supported by JNDI operations on &quot;java:&quot; names. Exception stack trace: 
{0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A JNDI operation on a &quot;java:&quot; name must be performed on the thread of a server application request
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that a J2EE application does not execute JNDI operations on &quot;java:&quot; names within static code blocks or in threads created by that J2EE application.  Such code does not necessarily run on the thread of a server application request and therefore is not supported by JNDI operations on &quot;java:&quot; names.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="NMSV0751W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="nsxmlAddBindingErr" varFormat="Java">
    nsxmlAddBindingErr=NMSV0751W: Could not add binding &quot;{1}&quot; to the name space.  The binding data is contained in the XML file &quot;{0}&quot;. Updates to the corresponding persistent name space partition have been disabled.  Error information follows:
{2}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    During server startup, while the name server was reading in the specified XML file, an error occurred while attempting to add the binding to the name space.  The entry is being ignored. Until the problem is corrected, update operations on contexts backed by the specified XML file are disabled.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem cannot be resolved with the included error information, remove the binding entry that is not valid from the XML file. The context can then be rebound if necessary.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="NMSV0006E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="nsInitImplNotSupp" varFormat="Java">
    nsInitImplNotSupp=NMSV0006E: Name server initialization failed. Name server implementation type of &quot;{0}&quot; is not supported in this release.
{1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This exception is unexpected. The cause is not immediately known.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="NMSV0304W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="javaAccessorSet" varFormat="Java">
    javaAccessorSet=NMSV0304W: There was an attempt to set the java URL name space accessor more than once.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This exception is unexpected. The cause is not immediately known.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="NMSV0755W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="nsxmlBadJavaObject" varFormat="Java">
    nsxmlBadJavaObject=NMSV0755W: Invalid binding found in the XML file &quot;{0}&quot;.  The entry for name &quot;{1}&quot; has a nameBindingType value of &quot;objectJava&quot; and the serializedBytesAsString value is invalid.  This binding is being ignored. Updates to the corresponding persistent name space partition have been disabled.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    During server startup, while the name server was reading in the specified XML file, a binding entry that is not valid was found. The entry is being ignored.  Until the problem is corrected, update operations on contexts backed by the specified XML file are disabled.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Remove the binding entry that is not valid from the XML file. The object can then be rebound if necessary.  If necessary, delete the file entirely.  Deleting the file effectively removes all persistent bindings from the associated name space partition.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="NMSV0003E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="nsInitNoHost" varFormat="Java">
    nsInitNoHost=NMSV0003E: Name server initialization failed. Cannot obtain host name for this host.
{0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This exception is unexpected. The cause is not immediately known.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="NMSV0819W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="NMSV0819W" varFormat="Java">
    NMSV0819W=NMSV0819W: No deployments directory found for application.  Ignoring application &quot;{0}&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An inconsistency in the configuration for the specified application was detected.  The applications sections of the name space structure might not reflect the application correctly.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="NMSV0607E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="jndiNullName" varFormat="Java">
    jndiNullName=NMSV0607E: The Context at name path &quot;{0}&quot; was passed a null name to the method &quot;{1}&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A JNDI context method was passed a null name. Null names are not valid.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Use an appropriate name for the desired JNDI operation.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="NMSV0822W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="NMSV0822W" varFormat="Java">
    NMSV0822W=NMSV0822W: Duplicate module name encountered. Ignoring module &quot;{0}&quot; (URI: {1}) in application &quot;{2}&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Two modules with the same name were found in the specified node.  As a result, the name server&apos;s application name space structure may not reflect the entire application configuration. All module names within an application must be unique.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that all module names are unique within an application.  In particular, verify that the deployment descriptors for two modules do not specify the same module name.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="NMSV0602E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="jndiUnavailCommErr" varFormat="Java">
    jndiUnavailCommErr=NMSV0602E: Naming Service unavailable. A communications error occurred.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A connection to the name server could not be made when attempting create an initial context.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Typical causes are that the provider URL is incorrect or that the name server identified by the provider URL is not running. Make sure that the name server is running and that the host and port in the provider URL are correct. Also, make sure that the host identified in the provider URL can be ping&apos;ed from the machine on which the JNDI client is running. Refer to the trace output accompanying this message for more information about the root cause.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="NMSV0303E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="urlGetUrlCtxErr" varFormat="Java">
    urlGetUrlCtxErr=NMSV0303E: Exception occurred in NamingManager.getURLContext for the scheme: &quot;{0}&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A URL was passed to a JNDI Context method, which then invoked the JNDI Naming Manager to return the Context identified by the URL. The Naming Manager invocation failed.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    This problem is probably the result of an incorrect configuration. Make sure that the factory for the scheme of the specified URL can be located from the value of the property, java.naming.factory.url.pkgs, found in the Context&apos;s environment. The trace output may contain additional diagnostic information.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="NMSV0008E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="nsInitIorErr" varFormat="Java">
    nsInitIorErr=NMSV0008E: Name server initialization failed. Could not create a root context IOR. The name server implementation type is &quot;{0}&quot;.
{1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This exception is unexpected. The cause is not immediately known.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="NMSV0800W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="cfExceptionOnLoadingServerXML" varFormat="Java">
    cfExceptionOnLoadingServerXML=NMSV0800W: Exception encountered loading configuration file &quot;{0}&quot;.
{1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An error occurred when loading configuration file. As a result, name server custom property settings might be ignored.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    The action required depends on the root cause of the problem. Refer to the diagnostic data provided to determine the root cause of the problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="NMSV0805W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="cfMissingPortNumber" varFormat="Java">
    cfMissingPortNumber=NMSV0805W: Missing port number in bootstrap address of server &quot;{0}&quot; in node &quot;{1}&quot;. Skipping this server configuration and continuing.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The bootstrap address configuration for the specified server does not contain a port number. As a result, the name server&apos;s system name space structure will not include the specified server.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure all bootstrap addresses include a host name and port number.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="NMSV0821W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="NMSV0821W" varFormat="Java">
    NMSV0821W=NMSV0821W: An unexpected error occurred while reading application deployment data. Error data:
{0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Could not build the applications section of the name space because of an unexpected error.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="NMSV0723W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="cfUndefVar" varFormat="Java">
    cfUndefVar=NMSV0723W: Configuration data for name space binding &quot;{0}&quot; in the {1} location of namebindings.xml contains an undefined variable reference.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The configuration for the specified name space binding contains a variable reference that cannot be resolved.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the name of the variable being referenced or create a definition for the variable.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="NMSV0759E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="nsxmlExtractError" varFormat="Java">
    nsxmlExtractError=NMSV0759E: An error occurred on a file extract operation for the persistent name binding XML file &quot;{0}&quot;.  Persistent name binding information could not be read in.  Error information follows:
{1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    In order to read in persistent name binding data from an XML file during name server initialization, the name server must extract the XML file from the Configuration Respository.  The extract operation failed.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Restart the server. Refer to the diagnostic data provided to determine the root cause of the problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="NMSV0107E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="cosUnexpectedErr" varFormat="Java">
    cosUnexpectedErr=NMSV0107E: An unexpected error occurred. Mapping to CORBA UNKNOWN.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An error occurred when processing a CosNaming name server request.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See the trace output for more details about the origin of the problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="NMSV0606E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="jndiCannotBindObj" varFormat="Java">
    jndiCannotBindObj=NMSV0606E: Object is not of any type which can be bound.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The JNDI bind or rebind method was passed an object which is of a type that cannot be bound. Allowed object types include CORBA objects (which includes deployed enterprise beans), JNDI contexts of the same type as the context object being invoked, javax.naming.Referenceable, javax.naming.Reference, and java.io.Serializable.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Attempt to bind or rebind only objects of the above types.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="NMSV0758E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="nsxmlRepoRefError" varFormat="Java">
    nsxmlRepoRefError=NMSV0758E: The name server could not acquire a Configuration Repository handle. Persistent name binding data cannot be processed.  Error information follows:
{1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    In order for the name server to process any persistent name binding information, it needs a Configuration Repository client handle to access persistent name binding XML files.  An attempt to acquire a Configuration Repository handle failed.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Restart the server. Refer to the diagnostic data provided to determine the root cause of the problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="NMSV0903E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="deserializationErr" varFormat="Java">
    deserializationErr=NMSV0903E: An error occurred while deserializing an object.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An error occurred while attempting to deserialize an object. This error probably occurred during a JNDI lookup or listBindings operation.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    The most likely cause for this problem is not having the required class or classes in the JNDI client CLASSPATH. The trace output should contain more details, such as the class name that could not be found.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="NMSV0820W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="NMSV0820W" varFormat="Java">
    NMSV0820W=NMSV0820W: No deployment configuration found for application. Ignoring deployment &quot;{1}&quot; of application &quot;{0}&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An inconsistency in the configuration for the specified application deployment was detected.  The applications sections of the name space structure might not reflect the application correctly.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="NMSV0608E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="jndiEmptyName" varFormat="Java">
    jndiEmptyName=NMSV0608E: The Context at name path &quot;{0}&quot; was passed an empty name to the method &quot;{1}&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A JNDI context method was passed an empty name. JNDI context methods except for lookup, list, and listBindings, do not accept empty names.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Use an appropriate name for the desired JNDI operation.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="NMSV0802W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="cfInvalidConfigLocation" varFormat="Java">
    cfInvalidConfigLocation=NMSV0802W: Found the configuration document &quot;{0}&quot; as part of the deployment manager&apos;&apos;s node configuration.  The deployment manager&apos;&apos;s node is not a valid location for node-scoped configured name bindings.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Name bindings were found in the deployment manager&apos;s node configuration.  Node-scoped configured bindings are bound in the name space under the node&apos;s node persistent root.  Since there is no node persistent persistent root for the deployment manager&apos;s node, this node is not a valid location for node-scoped configured name bindings.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that you have selected the right node and scope for the configured bindings.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="NMSV0611E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="getRefReturnNull" varFormat="Java">
    getRefReturnNull=NMSV0611E: A Referenceable.getReference() returns null.
Object to bind: {0}
Referenceable object: {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    While processing a JNDI bind or rebind operation on a javax.naming.Referenceable object, a call to the method, getReference(), on the object returns null, which violates the JNDI API.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the method getReference() on the Referenceable object returns a non-null Reference object. According to the JNDI API, getReference() on a Referenceable object should return a non-null Reference of this object.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="NMSV0710W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="cfBindingEmptyParam" varFormat="Java">
    cfBindingEmptyParam=NMSV0710W: Configured Bindings: &quot;{0}&quot; field was not set in {1}
	object: {2}
	name in name space: {3}
	XML location: {4} level of &quot;namebindings.xml&quot; file.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Some required fields or attributes are missing (or empty) in a name space binding defined in the specified namebindings.xml file.  Either the file was edited incorrectly or became corrupted for some reason.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Delete the problem namebindings.xml file and recreate the configured bindings for that configuration scope through wsadmin or the administrative console.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="NMSV0910E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="generalWithInsert" varFormat="Java">
    generalWithInsert=NMSV0910E: A Naming error occurred. Details follow:
{0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An undocumented naming error occurred.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Refer to the diagnostic data provided to determine the root cause of the problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="NMSV0712W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="cfNonleafConflict" varFormat="Java">
    cfNonleafConflict=NMSV0712W: Configured Bindings: Cannot create an intermediate context for the configured binding &quot;{0}&quot; relative to the context &quot;{1}&quot; because of a name conflict with an object other than another configured context binding.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    When a binding with a compound name is configured, all intermediate contexts must either not already exist or be contexts created from other configured bindings.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Use a different name or make sure the configured binding is in the correct place in name space.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="NMSV0017E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="nsInitRegInitRefErr" varFormat="Java">
    nsInitRegInitRefErr=NMSV0017E: Name server initialization failed. Unable to register initial reference &quot;{0}&quot;.
{1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This exception is unexpected. The cause is not immediately known.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="NMSV0711W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="cfBindingAlreadyBound" varFormat="Java">
    cfBindingAlreadyBound=NMSV0711W: Configured Bindings: name already bound. Exception data:
	{0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A binding already exists in the name space with the same name as this configured binding.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Use a different name or make sure the configured binding is in the correct place in name space.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="NMSV0911E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="noInitCtxFactoryImpl" varFormat="Java">
    noInitCtxFactoryImpl=NMSV0911E: No initial context factory implementation is defined for com.ibm.naming.websphere.WsnInitialContextFactory.  Make sure a WebSphere jar file that contains com/ibm/websphere/naming/jndiprovider.properties can be located by the class loader.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A property in the file com/ibm/websphere/naming/jndiprovider.properties is set with the class name of the initial context factory implementation to use.  Since the property is not set, the class loader is apparently not locating the containing jar file.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    In your specific WebSphere installation, find the jar file that contains com/ibm/websphere/naming/jndiprovider.properties and make sure your runtime environment is set up so that the class loader will be able to locate it.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="NMSV0811W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="cfWarningsIssued2" varFormat="Java">
    cfWarningsIssued2=NMSV0811W: Name Server Configuration Warning: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Name Server configuration warning have been issued with some additional information.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Look into this additional information to resolve this warning.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="NMSV0810W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="cfWarningsIssued1" varFormat="Java">
    cfWarningsIssued1=NMSV0810W: Name Server Configuration Warning: Due to previous warnings it is possible the name space will not be constructed correctly.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Some Name Server configuration warning have been issued prior to this message. Most likely the name space will not be constructed correctly.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Try to resolve previous warnings first.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="NMSV0902E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="serializationErr" varFormat="Java">
    serializationErr=NMSV0902E: An error occurred while serializing an object.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An error occurred while attempting to serialize an object. This error probably occurred during a JNDI bind or rebind operation.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    One possible cause is that some object encountered during the serialization process is not serializable. For more information about the root cause, see the trace output which accompanies this message.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="NMSV0763E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="nsxmlRepoFileUpdateError" varFormat="Java">
    nsxmlRepoFileUpdateError=NMSV0763E: An error occurred while processing the persistent name binding XML file &quot;{0}&quot;.  Update operation could not be completed. Error information follows:
{1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The name server experienced some problem processing a persistent name binding XML file.  The update operation failed.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Restart the server. Refer to the diagnostic data provided to determine the root cause of the problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="NMSV0109E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="cosAdapterExistsErr" varFormat="Java">
    cosAdapterExistsErr=NMSV0109E: CosNaming server caught exception: AdapterAlreadyExistsException.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This exception is unexpected. The cause is not immediately known.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="NMSV0102E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="cosInsToCosConv" varFormat="Java">
    cosInsToCosConv=NMSV0102E: Unexpected InvalidNameException thrown by WsnName while converting the INS name string &quot;{0}&quot; to another format.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The CosNaming name server cannot convert a name conversion for internal processing. The name specified for a configured name binding might not be valid.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the message is accompanied with another Name Service warning related to configured name bindings, change the configured binding name to a valid binding name.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="NMSV0906E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="cannotCreateObj" varFormat="Java">
    cannotCreateObj=NMSV0906E: Could not create an instance of the class &quot;{0}&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This exception is unexpected. The cause is not immediately known.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="NMSV0005E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="nsInitLdap" varFormat="Java">
    nsInitLdap=NMSV0005E: Name server initialization failed. Cannot create the LDAP name tree.
{0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This exception is unexpected. The cause is not immediately known.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="NMSV0111W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="cosServerFederation" varFormat="Java">
    cosServerFederation=NMSV0111W: A WebSphere Base Application Server name space is being federated to another WebSphere Application Server name space.  This type of name space federation is not supported and may produce incorrect results.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Naming Service has detected that the name space federation between two application servers is not valid. As a result, the lookup operation might not work correctly.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the name space federation between the two application servers.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="NMSV0750W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="nsxmlLinkedNullCtxID" varFormat="Java">
    nsxmlLinkedNullCtxID=NMSV0750W: Invalid binding found in the XML file &quot;{0}&quot;.  The entry for name &quot;{1}&quot; has a nameBindingType value of &quot;contextLinked&quot;, but its contextId value is null.  This binding is being ignored.  Updates to the corresponding persistent name space partition have been disabled.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    During server startup, while the name server was reading in the specified XML file, a binding entry that is not valid was found in the XML file. The entry is being ignored. Until the problem is corrected, update operations on contexts backed by the specified XML file are disabled.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Remove the binding entry that is not valid from the XML file.  The context can then be rebound if necessary.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="NMSV0018I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="nsBootstrapPortOpen" varFormat="Java">
    nsBootstrapPortOpen=NMSV0018I: Name server available on bootstrap port {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This is an informational message indicating the port number opened as the bootstrap port.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is necessary.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="NMSV0813W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="cfErrorDuringUpdate" varFormat="Java">
    cfErrorDuringUpdate=NMSV0813W: An error occurred while updating the name space in response to configuration changes.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Changes have been made to the configuration which affect the name server running in the process associated with this message.  An error occurred while attempting to update the name space.  The name space may not accurately reflect the current configuration.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Restart the server which received this warning message.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="NMSV0604E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="jndiGetRefErr" varFormat="Java">
    jndiGetRefErr=NMSV0604E: Exception thrown in Referenceable.getReference().
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    While processing a JNDI bind or rebind operation on a javax.naming.Referenceable object, a call to the method, getReference(), on the object resulted in an exception.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    The Referenceable object could not be processed for some unknown reason. Refer to the trace output accompanying this message for more details on the root cause.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="NMSV0814W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="cfNoUpdate" varFormat="Java">
    cfNoUpdate=NMSV0814W: An error occurred while updating the name space in response to configuration changes.  Error data:
{0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Changes have been made to the configuration which affect the name server running in the process associated with this message.  An error occurred while processing the new configuration data in an effort to update the name space to reflect the configuration changes.  The name space may not accurately reflect the current configuration.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Restart the server which received this warning message.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="NMSV0011E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="nsInitBootSvrErr" varFormat="Java">
    nsInitBootSvrErr=NMSV0011E: Unable to start bootstrap server using port {0}. Verify that no servers or other processes are already using the bootstrap server port. Also verify that the bootstrap server is being started with a user ID which has sufficient (e.g., root, Administrator) privileges.
{1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The name server cannot be initialized. An error occurred while attempting to start the bootstrap server.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure the bootstrap server port is not already in use by any other server processes. This error can occur when the product name server has already been started. In addition, make sure that the bootstrap server is being started with a user ID which has sufficient user privileges. On AIX, HP-UX, Linux and Solaris operating systems, the server must be running as root. On Windows operating systems, the user ID must must be a local Windows user ID that is in the administrative group and has the advanced user rights &quot;Act as part of the operating system&quot; and &quot;Log on as a service.&quot; Refer to installation topics in the information center for more information.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="NMSV0104E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="cosNullIdOrKind" varFormat="Java">
    cosNullIdOrKind=NMSV0104E: CosNaming::NameComponent[{0}] contains a null id or kind field. Throwing InvalidName exception.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A component in a name passed to a method in the product name server implementation of CosNaming::NamingContext contained a null id or kind field. A null value for an id or kind field is not valid.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the CosNaming client is a customer-provided application, this is a user error.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="NMSV0908W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="jndiproviderProperties" varFormat="Java">
    jndiproviderProperties=NMSV0908W: The file com/ibm/websphere/naming/jndiprovider.properties could not be loaded.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The com/ibm/websphere/naming/jndiprovider.properties file could not be loaded
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that the .jar file containing the com/ibm/websphere/naming/jndiprovider.properties file is located where it can be found by the class loader. If the file is accessable to the class loader, look for any other messages that may identify the problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="NMSV0809W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="cfNoSupportDisableBootstrap" varFormat="Java">
    cfNoSupportDisableBootstrap=NMSV0809W: Opening of the bootstrap port cannot be disabled in a server not configured as a standalone server.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Every server opens the bootstrap port defined for it unless it has been disabled.  The bootstrap port of a server can be disabled only if the server is running as a standalone server.  Managed servers, node agents, and deployment managers, for example, cannot have their bootstrap port disabled.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Do not set the BootstrapPortEnabled name server custom property to false for a server not configured as a standalone server.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="NMSV0301E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="urlReadObjectErr" varFormat="Java">
    urlReadObjectErr=NMSV0301E: An error occurred during deserialization of the JNDI context &quot;{0}&quot; in a local name space such as a java: URL name space.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This exception is unexpected. The cause is not immediately known.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="NMSV0803W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="cfDuplicateServerName" varFormat="Java">
    cfDuplicateServerName=NMSV0803W: Duplicate server name encountered. Ignoring server &quot;{0}&quot; on node &quot;{1}&quot; (endpoint: {2}).
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Two servers with the same name were found in the specified node.  As a result, the name server&apos;s system name space structure may not reflect the entire cell configuration. All server names within a node must be unique.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that all server names are unique within a node.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="NMSV0307E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="javaAccessorNotSet" varFormat="Java">
    javaAccessorNotSet=NMSV0307E: A java: URL name was used, but Naming was not configured to handle java: URL names. The likely cause is a user in error attempting to specify a java: URL name in a non-J2EE client or server environment. Throwing ConfigurationException.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Only JNDI clients which are running in a J2EE client or server environment can specify java: URL names in JNDI interface method calls.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that the JNDI client using a java: URL name is running in a J2EE client or server environment.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="NMSV0308W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="javaNameSpaceNotAccessible" varFormat="Java">
    javaNameSpaceNotAccessible=NMSV0308W: javaURLContextFactory cannot create a javaURLContext object because there is no java URL name space currently accessible from the executing thread.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This exception is unexpected. The cause is not immediately known.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="NMSV0901E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="unexpectedErr" varFormat="Java">
    unexpectedErr=NMSV0901E: An unexpected error occurred.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Some unexpected error occurred.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Refer to the diagnostic data provided to determine the root cause of the problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<!-- END MESSAGES -->
</TMSSource>
