<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/css" href="../../resources/stylesheets/wasmsgxml.css"?>
<TMSSource name="TivoliMessages" tmsVersion="1.0" xml:lang="en">
<!-- CMVC MSG File Name = ws/code/admin.jmx/src/com/ibm/ws/management/resources/bundle.nlsprops -->
<!-- DO NOT EDIT THIS FILE - This file was generated by the XML/Html & Property emitter -->
<!-- BEGIN MESSAGES -->
<Message ID="ADMB0022E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMB0022E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMB0022E=ADMB0022E: The server {0}/{1} specified for the target configuration is not an application server.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The importApplicationsFromWasprofile only supports application import on an applicaiton server.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify an application server as a target server for the importApplicationsFromWasprofile command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMB0025E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMB0025E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMB0025E=ADMB0025E: Application {0} is already installed in the target cell.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The application cannot be imported because it is already installed in the target cell.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Remove or rename the application either in the target cell or in the configuration archive file.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMB0028E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMB0028E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMB0028E=ADMB0028E: A server cluster named {0} does not exist in the configuration archive file.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The server cluster chosen as the source server cluster does not exist in the configuration archive file.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a valid server name for the source server.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMB0018E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMB0018E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMB0018E=ADMB0018E: Either targetNodeName or targetServerName is missing or targetClusterName is missing for the importApplicationFromWasprofile command.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The importApplicationsFromWasprofile command requires either both targetNode and targetServerName parameters or only targetClusterName parameter.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify both targetNodeName and targetServerName parameters or targetClusterName parameter for the importApplicationsFromWasprofile command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMB0008I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMB0008I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMB0008I=ADMB0008I: The importWasprofile command overwrites the current configuration of the wsprofile profile.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMB0005E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMB0005E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMB0005E=ADMB0005E: Server {1} on Node {0} does not exist.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified node name or server name are not valid.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a valid node name and server name.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMB0021E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMB0021E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMB0021E=ADMB0021E: The server {0}/{1} specified for the target configuration is a cluster member server.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The importApplicationsFromWasprofile does not support application import on a cluster member server.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Do not specify a cluster member server as a target server for the importApplicationsFromWasprofile command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMB0024E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMB0024E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMB0024E=ADMB0024E: The server {0} specified for the source server is not an application server.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The importApplicationsFromWasprofile only supports application import from an applicaiton server.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify an application server as a source server for the importApplicationsFromWasprofile command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMB0027E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMB0027E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMB0027E=ADMB0027E: Target cluster {1} does not exist.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The cluster specified with targetClusterName does not exist in the specified node of the target configuration.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a valid target cluster name.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMB0017E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMB0017E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMB0017E=ADMB0017E: Either the server names in the configuration archive do not match the server names in the system configuration or the server types in the configuration archive do not match the server types in the system configuration. The product only supports importWasprofile for profiles with the same amount of servers with the same server names and types.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The importWasprofile command requires that the names and the types of servers in the configuration archive to match the names and the types of servers in the system configuration.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Only use this command when the names and the types of all the servers are the same between the configuration archive and the system configuration.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMB0001E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMB0001E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMB0001E=ADMB0001E: The system configuration contains more than one node. The product supports a single node only for the importWasprofile and exportWasprofile commands.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This is a restriction of the product.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Do not use this command when there are more than one node in the system configuration.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMB0007E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMB0007E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMB0007E=ADMB0007E: Server {0} already exists on node {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The importServer command creates a new server based on the server configuration from the archive.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a different server name.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMB0020E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMB0020E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMB0020E=ADMB0020E: Target server {1} on target node {0} does not exist.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The server specified with targetServerName does not exist in the specified node of the target configuration.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a valid target node name and server name.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMB0023E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMB0023E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMB0023E=ADMB0023E: An application server named {0} does not exist in the configuration archive file.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The application server chosen as the source server does not exist in the configuration archive file.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a valid server name for the source server.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMB0026E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMB0026E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMB0026E=ADMB0026E: TargetClusterName parameter cannot be used with TargetNodeName and TargetServerName parameters.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Applications can be deployed either to an application server or to a cluster server, but not to both.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Use both targetNodeName and targetServerName parameters or targetClusterName parameter as a target server which applications are deployed to.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMB0010E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMB0010E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMB0010E=ADMB0010E: The deployed application {1} in systemapps.xml in configuration archive does not contain prefix of {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The systemapps.xml file in the configuration archive does not contain the specified variable prefix for the application.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that &lt;deployedApplications&gt; entries in systemapps.xml start with ${WAS_INSTALL_ROOT}.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMB0016E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMB0016E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMB0016E=ADMB0016E: The number of servers in the configuration archive does not match the number of servers in the system configuration. The product only supports importWasprofile for profiles with the same number of servers.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The importWasprofile command requires that the number of servers in the configuration archive and the system configuration match.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Only use this command when both system configuration and configuration archive contains the same number of the servers, except for the case that the system configuration contains no server.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMB0019E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMB0019E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMB0019E=ADMB0019E: Target node {0} does not exist.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The node specified with targetNodeName does not exist in the target configuration.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a valid target node name.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMB0003E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMB0003E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMB0003E=ADMB0003E: The configuration archive contains more than one node. The product supports single node for importWasprofile and exportWasprofile command.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This is a restriction of the product.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Do not use this command where there is more than one node in the configuration archive.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMB0009E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMB0009E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMB0009E=ADMB0009E: The specified node {0} does not exist.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified node name does not match any node that is defined in the configuration.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check the spelling of the node name.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<!-- END MESSAGES -->
</TMSSource>
