<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/css" href="../../resources/stylesheets/wasmsgxml.css"?>
<TMSSource name="TivoliMessages" tmsVersion="1.0" xml:lang="en">
<!-- CMVC MSG File Name = /com.ibm.ws.eba.app.utils/src/com/ibm/ws/eba/utils/messages/APPUTILSmessages.nlsprops -->
<!-- DO NOT EDIT THIS FILE - This file was generated by the XML/Html & Property emitter -->
<!-- BEGIN MESSAGES -->
<Message ID="CWSAN0036E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="UNABLE_TO_EXPAND_BUNDLE_DUE_TO_EXCEPTION" varFormat="Java">
    UNABLE_TO_EXPAND_BUNDLE_DUE_TO_EXCEPTION=CWSAN0036E: Could not expand bundle {0} for application {2}. Exception {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The bundle needs to be expanded so that it can be used by another bundle that is referring to it by reference.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Either change the application so that it does not refer to the bundle, or investigate the cause of the exception.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAN0023W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="UNREADABLE_WAR_MANIFEST_APPUTILS0023W" varFormat="Java">
    UNREADABLE_WAR_MANIFEST_APPUTILS0023W=CWSAN0023W: Cannot read the manifest of the bundle {0} in the EBA {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The bundle manifest, MANIFEST.MF, for a bundle in the enterprise bundle archive (EBA) file cannot be read. This bundle cannot serve web content and might not operate correctly.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that the bundle file contains a valid manifest file.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAN0037E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="UNABLE_TO_INSTALL_BUNDLE" varFormat="Java">
    UNABLE_TO_INSTALL_BUNDLE=CWSAN0037E: An internal error occurred. Could not install bundle {0} for application root {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    CMSG0001
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    CMSG0002
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAN0035E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="UNABLE_TO_EXPAND_BUNDLE" varFormat="Java">
    UNABLE_TO_EXPAND_BUNDLE=CWSAN0035E: An internal error occurred. Could not expand bundle {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    CMSG0001
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    CMSG0002
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAN0005E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="APPUTILS0005E" varFormat="Java">
    APPUTILS0005E=CWSAN0005E: The deployment content value is not valid, because it does not contain the deployed-version attribute: {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A deployment manifest, DEPLOYMENT.MF file, must contain a valid deployed-version header.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If you provided the DEPLOYMENT.MF file, check that it contains a valid deployed-version header.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAN0014W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="APPUTILS0014W" varFormat="Java">
    APPUTILS0014W=CWSAN0014W: Cannot parse an Export-Service entry {0} in application {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An entry in the Export-Service header of the application manifest, APPLICATION.MF, is not valid.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Locate and correct the relevant header.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAN0034E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="UNABLE_TO_EXPAND_UNEXPECTED_BUNDLE" varFormat="Java">
    UNABLE_TO_EXPAND_UNEXPECTED_BUNDLE=CWSAN0034E: An internal error occurred. Could not expand bundle {0} because it is not in the expected location.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    CMSG0001
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    CMSG0002
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAN0044E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="BAD_DEPLOYED_SERVICE_IMPORT_HEADER" varFormat="Java">
    BAD_DEPLOYED_SERVICE_IMPORT_HEADER=CWSAN0044E: The service import {0} in the deployment for application {1} at version {2} does not conform to the correct syntax.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The deployment manifest for the application contains an incorrectly formatted service import.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check that the application correctly specifies the services that it imports, then try again to deploy the application.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAN0024E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="APPUTILS0024E" varFormat="Java">
    APPUTILS0024E=CWSAN0024E: DeployedService-Import header is not valid: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The DeployedService-Import header in a deployment manifest, DEPLOYMENT.MF, is not valid.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If you provided the deployment manifest, correct the contents of the DeployedService-Import header.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAN0040E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_IBR_ROOT_DIR" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_IBR_ROOT_DIR=CWSAN0040E: An internal error occurred. Could not locate the global bundle cache.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    CMSG0001
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    CMSG0002
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAN0042E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ARIES_CONTEXT_EXCEPTION" varFormat="Java">
    ARIES_CONTEXT_EXCEPTION=CWSAN0042E: An error occurred attempting to install a bundle with URL {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Apache Aries container could not install the bundle.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check previous Apache Aries messages for details of the failure.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAN0004E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="APPUTILS0004E" varFormat="Java">
    APPUTILS0004E=CWSAN0004E: Cannot create ContentImpl object based on content: {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The application content is ambiguous or not valid.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check and correct the source of the content, if possible.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAN0013W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="APPUTILS0013W" varFormat="Java">
    APPUTILS0013W=CWSAN0013W: Cannot parse an Import-Service entry {0} in application {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An entry in the Import-Service header of the application manifest, APPLICATION.MF, is not valid.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Locate and correct the relevant header.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAN0022E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WAB_FILTER_ERROR_APPUTILS0022E" varFormat="Java">
    WAB_FILTER_ERROR_APPUTILS0022E=CWSAN0022E: An internal error has occurred. There was an error searching for bundles in EBA {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    CMSG0001
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    CMSG0002
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAN0045E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="UNEXPANDED_BUNDLE" varFormat="Java">
    UNEXPANDED_BUNDLE=CWSAN0045E: An internal error occurred. By reference bundle {0} is not expanded at location {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    CMSG0001
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    CMSG0002
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAN0019E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="APPUTILS0019E" varFormat="Java">
    APPUTILS0019E=CWSAN0019E: Invalid header split: {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Provision-Bundle header in the deployment manifest, DEPLOYMENT.MF is not valid.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If you provided this file, correct the contents of the Provision-Bundle header.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAN0009E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="APPUTILS0009E" varFormat="Java">
    APPUTILS0009E=CWSAN0009E: Cannot parse the version {0} because it does not comply with the OSGi version specification.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A manifest header cannot be parsed because it contains a version attribute that is not valid.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Locate and correct the version according to the OSGi version specification.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAN0032E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="APPUTILS0032E" varFormat="Java">
    APPUTILS0032E=CWSAN0032E: The Application-SymbolicName {0} and Application-Version {1} in the DEPLOYMENT.MF do not match the Application-SymbolicName {2} and Application-Version {3} in APPLICATION.MF.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Application-SymbolicName and Application-Version in the application manifest, APPLICATION.MF, and deployment manifest, DEPLOYMENT.MF, do not match.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check that the correct file is provided, and ensure the values of Application-SymbolicName and Application-Version in the APPLICATION.MF and DEPLOYMENT.MF are the same.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAN0025E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="APPLICATION_CONTENT_MISMATCH" varFormat="Java">
    APPLICATION_CONTENT_MISMATCH=CWSAN0025E: The Deployed-Content {0} in the DEPLOYMENT.MF file does not match the Application-Content {1} in the APPLICATION.MF file of the enterprise bundle archive (EBA).
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The bundles listed in the Deployed-Content header in the DEPLOYMENT.MF file must match the bundles listed in the Application-Content header in the APPLICATION.MF file. The bundle version in the Deployed-Content header in the DEPLOYMENT.MF file must be within the version range for the corresponding bundle in the Application-Content header in the APPLICATION.MF file.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If you provided the deployment manifest, correct the contents of the Deployed-Content header in the DEPLOYMENT.MF file. Ensure that each bundle is listed in both the Deployed-Content header in the DEPLOYMENT.MF file and the Application-Content header in the APPLICATION.MF file, and that the bundle version in the Deployed-Content header in the DEPLOYMENT.MF file is within the version range for the corresponding bundle in the Application-Content header in the APPLICATION.MF file.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAN0039E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="APPUTILS0038E" varFormat="Java">
    APPUTILS0038E=CWSAN0039E: An internal error occurred. Could not create new Directory Mapping file {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    CMSG0001
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    CMSG0002
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAN0026E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="USE_BUNDLE_MISMATCH" varFormat="Java">
    USE_BUNDLE_MISMATCH=CWSAN0026E: The Deployed-Use-Bundle {0} in the DEPLOYMENT.MF file does not match the Use-Bundle {1} in the APPLICATION.MF file of the enterprise bundle archive (EBA).
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The bundles listed in the Deployed-Use-Bundle header in the DEPLOYMENT.MF file must also be listed in the Use-Bundle header in the APPLICATION.MF file. The bundle version in the Deployed-Use-Bundle header in the DEPLOYMENT.MF file must be within the version range for the corresponding bundle in the Use-Bundle header in the APPLICATION.MF file. The Use-Bundle header in the APPLICATION.MF file can list additional bundles that are not listed in the Deployed-Use-Bundle header of the DEPLOYMENT.MF file.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If you provided the deployment manifest, correct the contents of the Deployed-Use-Bundle header in the DEPLOYMENT.MF file. Ensure that each bundle listed in the Deployed-Use-Bundle header in the DEPLOYMENT.MF file is also listed in the Application-Content header of the APPLICATION.MF file, and that the bundle version in the Deployed-Use-Bundle header of the DEPLOYMENT.MF file is within the version range for the corresponding bundle in the Use-Bundle header in the APPLICATION.MF file.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAN0012E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="APPUTILS0012E" varFormat="Java">
    APPUTILS0012E=CWSAN0012E: Cannot create temporary output directory for file {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The product needs to create a temporary directory but cannot.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check that storage space exists, and that the product has the necessary permissions to create the directory.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAN0033E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="UNABLE_TO_PROCESS_APP" varFormat="Java">
    UNABLE_TO_PROCESS_APP=CWSAN0033E: An internal error occurred. Could not process application {0}. The byValue expansion directory is missing.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    CMSG0001
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    CMSG0002
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAN0018E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="APPUTILS0018E" varFormat="Java">
    APPUTILS0018E=CWSAN0018E: Invalid header split: {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Deployed-Use-Bundle header in the deployment manifest, DEPLOYMENT.MF is not valid.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If you provided this file, correct the contents of the Use-Bundle header.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAN0002E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="APPUTILS0002E" varFormat="Java">
    APPUTILS0002E=CWSAN0002E: Invalid header split: {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Deployed-Content header in the deployment manifest, DEPLOYMENT.MF, is not valid.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If you provided this file, correct the contents of the Deployed-Content header.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAN0021W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MISSING_WAR_MANIFEST_APPUTILS0021W" varFormat="Java">
    MISSING_WAR_MANIFEST_APPUTILS0021W=CWSAN0021W: A bundle {0} in the EBA {1} has no bundle manifest.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A bundle file in the enterprise bundle archive (EBA) file has no bundle manifest, MANIFEST.MF. This bundle cannot serve web content and might not operate correctly.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that the bundle file contains a valid bundle manifest file.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAN0008E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="APPUTILS0008E" varFormat="Java">
    APPUTILS0008E=CWSAN0008E: Cannot parse the string because a quotation mark (&quot;) is missing: {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A bundle manifest cannot be processed because at least one element does not contain a required quotation mark.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Locate and correct the specified bundle manifest.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAN0017W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="APPUTILS0017W" varFormat="Java">
    APPUTILS0017W=CWSAN0017W: An internal error occurred. Unable to create new security file {0} in the workspace.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    CMSG0001
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    CMSG0002
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAN0031E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="APPUTILS0031E" varFormat="Java">
    APPUTILS0031E=CWSAN0031E: The Application-Version {0} in the DEPLOYMENT.MF does not match the Application-Version {1} in APPLICATION.MF.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Application-Version in the application manifest, APPLICATION.MF, and deployment manifest, DEPLOYMENT.MF, do not match.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check that the correct file is provided, and ensure the values of Application-Version in the APPLICATION.MF and DEPLOYMENT.MF are the same.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAN0038E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="APPUTILS0037E" varFormat="Java">
    APPUTILS0037E=CWSAN0038E: An internal error occurred. Could not create new security file {0} in the workspace.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    CMSG0001
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    CMSG0002
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAN0027E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="APPUTILS0021E" varFormat="Java">
    APPUTILS0021E=CWSAN0027E: Invalid header split: {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The WAS-Feature-Required header in the deployment manifest, DEPLOYMENT.MF, is not valid.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If you provided the deployment manifest, correct the contents of the WAS-Feature-Required header.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAN0011E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="APPUTILS0011E" varFormat="Java">
    APPUTILS0011E=CWSAN0011E: Cannot parse {0} for the exact version.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A file that must contain exact versions only, such as a deployment manifest, DEPLOYMENT.MF, contains a range of versions.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Locate and correct the relevant header.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAN0001E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="APPUTILS0001E" varFormat="Java">
    APPUTILS0001E=CWSAN0001E: Cannot create ApplicationMetadataImpl object from the application manifest {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An application manifest, APPLICATION.MF, must contain both Application-SymbolicName and Application-Version headers.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Edit the APPLICATION.MF file to add the missing header or headers.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAN0043E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MANIFEST_PARSE_EXCEPTION" varFormat="Java">
    MANIFEST_PARSE_EXCEPTION=CWSAN0043E: An error occurred attempting to install a bundle with URL {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The deployment manifest for the bundle could not be parsed.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check that the deployment manifest is correctly formatted.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAN0007E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="APPUTILS0007E" varFormat="Java">
    APPUTILS0007E=CWSAN0007E: The path {0} is not the location of a valid file or directory.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A bundle manifest cannot be extracted because the location is not a valid file or directory.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If you provided this location, check that it is valid and that it exists.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAN0041E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="GLOBAL_CACHE_FILE_NOT_A_BUNDLE" varFormat="Java">
    GLOBAL_CACHE_FILE_NOT_A_BUNDLE=CWSAN0041E: An internal error occurred. The file for bundle {0} at version {1} in the bundle cache does not appear to be a valid bundle.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The internal bundle cache found a file for the bundle, but could not verify the bundle manifest in the file.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Delete the failing bundle from the bundle cache and download it again. If the problem persists then check whether the bundle in the bundle repository is valid.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAN0016W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="APPUTILS0016W" varFormat="Java">
    APPUTILS0016W=CWSAN0016W: An internal error occurred. Unable to create new security file {0} in the workspace.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    CMSG0001
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    CMSG0002
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAN0030E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="APPUTILS0030E" varFormat="Java">
    APPUTILS0030E=CWSAN0030E: The Application-SymbolicName {0} in the DEPLOYMENT.MF does not match the Application-SymbolicName {1} in APPLICATION.MF.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Application-SymbolicName in the application manifest, APPLICATION.MF, and deployment manifest, DEPLOYMENT.MF, do not match.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check that the correct file is provided, and ensure the values of Application-SymbolicName in the APPLICATION.MF and DEPLOYMENT.MF are the same.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAN0020E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="APPUTILS0020E" varFormat="Java">
    APPUTILS0020E=CWSAN0020E: Duplicate bundle content was found in EBA {0} for WAB {1} at locations {2} and {3}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Two web application bundle (WAB) files in the enterprise bundle archive (EBA) file have the same bundle symbolic name, version, and Web-ContextPath.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that the EBA file contains the correct WAB files.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAN0010E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="APPUTILS0010E" varFormat="Java">
    APPUTILS0010E=CWSAN0010E: Cannot parse the version because the version attribute is empty.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A manifest header cannot be parsed because it contains an empty version attribute.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Locate and correct the relevant header.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAN0006E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="APPUTILS0006E" varFormat="Java">
    APPUTILS0006E=CWSAN0006E: Cannot create filter for {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A service has been declared with a filter expression that is not valid.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Locate and correct the filter expression.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAN0015W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="APPUTILS0015W" varFormat="Java">
    APPUTILS0015W=CWSAN0015W: Cannot parse an Application-Roles entry {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An entry in the Application-Roles header of the application manifest, APPLICATION.MF, is not valid.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Locate and correct the relevant header.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAN0046E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="TOO_MANY_MANIFESTS" varFormat="Java">
    TOO_MANY_MANIFESTS=CWSAN0046E: An internal error occurred. Multiple copies of the manifest file {0} were found using case-insensitive matching for the archive {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Manifest files in an EBA are case-insensitive. On case-sensitive systems this means that there can be multiple copies of the manifest, which is an error.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Change any artefacts so that they do not contain multiple copies of the manifest file.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<!-- END MESSAGES -->
</TMSSource>
