<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/css" href="../../resources/stylesheets/wasmsgxml.css"?>
<TMSSource name="TivoliMessages" tmsVersion="1.0" xml:lang="en">
<!-- CMVC MSG File Name = ws/code/admin.jmx.thinclient/src/com/ibm/ws/management/resources/adminsdk.nlsprops -->
<!-- DO NOT EDIT THIS FILE - This file was generated by the XML/Html & Property emitter -->
<!-- BEGIN MESSAGES -->
<Message ID="CWLCA0009E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWLCA0009E" varFormat="Java">
    CWLCA0009E=CWLCA0009E: The node {0} does not exist
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Possibly incorrect node name
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check if the node name is entered correctly
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWLCA0032E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWLCA0032E" varFormat="Java">
    CWLCA0032E=CWLCA0032E: The JavaVirtualMachine preset with the name {0} does not exist
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The preset named does not exist or it exists at a cell or node scope other than what was specified
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check that the node name and node or cell scope are entered correctly
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWLCA0012E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWLCA0012E" varFormat="Java">
    CWLCA0012E=CWLCA0012E: The sdk {0} is not available on node {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Possibly incorrect SDK name, or the given SDK is not istalled on the node
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Select an SDK that&apos;s available on the node. If the SDK you select is installed on a managed node, ensure that the node agent on that managed node has been restarted at least once since the SDK was installed. The deployment manager is not aware of a newly installed SDK until after the node agent is restarted
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWLCA0002E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWLCA0002E" varFormat="Java">
    CWLCA0002E=CWLCA0002E: Either the cluster parameter, or the node, or the node and server, must be specified
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Parameters cluster, node, and server cannot all be missing for this particular command
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Either specify the cluster, or the node, or the node and server
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWLCA0008E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWLCA0008E" varFormat="Java">
    CWLCA0008E=CWLCA0008E: The cluster {0} is not found
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Possibly incorrect cluster name
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check if the cluster name is entered correctly, or if the cluster exists at all
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWLCA0031E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWLCA0031E" varFormat="Java">
    CWLCA0031E=CWLCA0031E: The javahome is not a valid value
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    the javahome value must be a valid location for a java install path
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a valid java install file path
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWLCA0011E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWLCA0011E" varFormat="Java">
    CWLCA0011E=CWLCA0011E: The javahome {0} does not represent a valid Java installation path on node {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Possibly incorrect javahome
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Query availabe SDKs for the node first, and choose the right javahome from there
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWLCA0001E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWLCA0001E" varFormat="Java">
    CWLCA0001E=CWLCA0001E: The server entity specification is inconsistent
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The valid server entity specifications for this command are: cluster only, node only, node and server only, or none of these
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Use the valid parameter combinations: cluster only, node only, or node and server only, or none of these
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWLCA0007E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWLCA0007E" varFormat="Java">
    CWLCA0007E=CWLCA0007E: The sdk parameter and the javahome cannot both be specified
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Only one (or none) or the parameters jdk and javahome can be specified
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify either the sdk parameter or the javahome, or none of them
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWLCA0010E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWLCA0010E" varFormat="Java">
    CWLCA0010E=CWLCA0010E: The server {0} does not exist
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Possibly incorrect server name
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check if the server name is entered correctly
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWLCA0006E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWLCA0006E" varFormat="Java">
    CWLCA0006E=CWLCA0006E: Must specify either the sdk parameter or the javahome (but not both)
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Either the sdk parameter or the javahome must be specified for this command
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify either the sdk parameter or the javahome
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWLCA0005E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWLCA0005E" varFormat="Java">
    CWLCA0005E=CWLCA0005E: For server entity (or entities), either specify the cluster only, or the server along with its parent node only
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The valid server parameter combinations for this command are: cluster only, or server and node only
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Either specify the cluster parameter only, or the node and server parameters only
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWLCA0004E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWLCA0004E" varFormat="Java">
    CWLCA0004E=CWLCA0004E: The parameter(s) must be specified with valid (non-empty) value(s)
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The parameter(s) cannot be null or empty string(s) for the given command
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specifify the required parameter(s) with valid value(s)
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWLCA0033E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWLCA0033E" varFormat="Java">
    CWLCA0033E=CWLCA0033E: Could not get a handle to the configuration service.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The configuration service, a required internal service was not properly initialized.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Restart the server or local process if running in local mode.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWLCA0013E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWLCA0013E" varFormat="Java">
    CWLCA0013E=CWLCA0013E: The node name/server name combination of {0}/{1} is invalid
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Either node name, or server name, or both, is incorrect
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Use correct node name/server name combination
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWLCA0003E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWLCA0003E" varFormat="Java">
    CWLCA0003E=CWLCA0003E: The server parameter must be specified along with its parent node
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    To uniquely identify a server, its parent node name is required
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specifify the server name along with the parent node name
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<!-- END MESSAGES -->
</TMSSource>
