<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/css" href="../../resources/stylesheets/wasmsgxml.css"?>
<TMSSource name="TivoliMessages" tmsVersion="1.0" xml:lang="en">
<!-- CMVC MSG File Name = ws/code/runtime/src/com/ibm/ejs/jms/messaging.nlsprops -->
<!-- DO NOT EDIT THIS FILE - This file was generated by the XML/Html & Property emitter -->
<!-- BEGIN MESSAGES -->
<Message ID="WMSG0006E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MDBListenerCreateException" varFormat="Java">
    MDBListenerCreateException=WMSG0006E: Error creating MDBListener for JMS Listener {0}, JMSDestination {1} : {2}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An exception was received while trying to create the MDBListener instance for the given JMS Listener.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Determine from the given exception the reason that the MDBListener was not created. Examine your JMS Listener configuration file to ensure the definition is correct, and ensure that all the necessary JMS resources are bound into the WebSphere JNDI name space. Also, ensure that the necessary JMS provider classes are in the application server class path.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0003E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="JMSListenerInitializeMDBException" varFormat="Java">
    JMSListenerInitializeMDBException=WMSG0003E: Error initializing JMSListenerStub: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An exception was received while trying to initialize the JMS Listener.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Determine from the given exception the reason that the JMS Listener has not initialized.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG3010E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INCORRECT_ACT_SEPC_TYPE_WMSG3010" varFormat="Java">
    INCORRECT_ACT_SEPC_TYPE_WMSG3010=WMSG3010E: The activate endpoint method was called with an activation specification of type {1} when a type of {0} is expected.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An incorrect activation specification class was passed to the endpointActivation method of the resource adapter wrapper.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    When using the resource adapter wrapper, ensure that the correct activation specification class is passed to the endpointActivation method
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0318E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PCFCommandServerInvalidSettingTypeReturned" varFormat="Java">
    PCFCommandServerInvalidSettingTypeReturned=WMSG0318E: The Command Server has returned some attributes of the incorrect type.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    While unpacking the response from the queue manager an incorrect type was found.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Try again later.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0022E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MDBListenerDuplicate" varFormat="Java">
    MDBListenerDuplicate=WMSG0022E: Duplicate MDBListener definition for {0}, JMSDestination {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An attempt has been made to define a duplicate JMS Listener in the configuration file.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the JMS Listener configuration file to remove the duplicate entry, then restart the EJB Server to re-initialize the JMS Listener.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG1626W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MQ_INSTALL_ROOT_VERSION_HAS_CHANGED_WMSG1626" varFormat="Java">
    MQ_INSTALL_ROOT_VERSION_HAS_CHANGED_WMSG1626=WMSG1626W: The WebSphere MQ messaging provider installed at {0} has been updated from version {1} to version {2}. A server restart may be required to properly register this update.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Service has been applied to the WebSphere MQ messaging provider which has changed its version number.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    The application server may need to be restarted in order to properly register the new WebSphere MQ messaging provider code with the application server.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG1624E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="JMS_REGISTRATION_UNSUPPORTED_VERSION_WMSG1624" varFormat="Java">
    JMS_REGISTRATION_UNSUPPORTED_VERSION_WMSG1624=WMSG1624E: It was not possible to use the specified WebSphere MQ messaging provider at path {0} because it is at version {1}. The minimum supported version is {2}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The WebSphere MQ messaging provider code installed at the specified path is at a level that is lower than the minimum level supported and so can not be used.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Modify the configuration of the WebSphere MQ messaging provider in the application server so it points to a supported level of the WebSphere MQ messaging provider. This will involve either changing the contents or install directory of the WebSphere MQ resource adapter or changing the value of the MQ_INSTALL_ROOT variable. Then restart your application server.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0319E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PCFCommandServerQueueNameNotValid" varFormat="Java">
    PCFCommandServerQueueNameNotValid=WMSG0319E: The Queue name you have specified is invalid.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The queue name specified is not valid.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the name of the queue.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0031E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="JMSSessionRunException" varFormat="Java">
    JMSSessionRunException=WMSG0031E: Exception processing JMS Message for MDB {0}, JMSDestination {1} : {2}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    During the processing of a JMS message an unexpected exception was received.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the exception for reasons for the problem. After correction restart the MDB EJB JAR module from the administrative console.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0120I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MQQueueDefinerClusterNameTooLong" varFormat="Java">
    MQQueueDefinerClusterNameTooLong=WMSG0120I: Cluster name is over 48 characters long. reason = {0}, parameter = {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The cluster name specified is longer than 48 characters.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that the cluster name contains less than 48 characters.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0019E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MDBListenerStartException" varFormat="Java">
    MDBListenerStartException=WMSG0019E: Unable to start MDB Listener {0}, JMSDestination {1} : {2}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An exception has occurred during the start of the given MDB Listener.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the exception for reasons for the problem, then restart the MDB EJB JAR module from the administrative console.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0012E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="JMSConfigParseErrors" varFormat="Java">
    JMSConfigParseErrors=WMSG0012E: Errors parsing JMS Listener config file: {0}, {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An error was issued trying to parse the given JMS Listener configuration file.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the problem in the JMS Listener configuration file, then restart the EJB Server.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0041E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="JMSListenerFailedToStart" varFormat="Java">
    JMSListenerFailedToStart=WMSG0041E: JMS Listener failed to start
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The JMS Listener service was unable to start because of some initialization errors.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the error logs to determine the cause of the problem,correct any errors then restart the server.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG1613W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MQ_INSTALL_ROOT_VERSION_HAS_CHANGED_WMSG1613" varFormat="Java">
    MQ_INSTALL_ROOT_VERSION_HAS_CHANGED_WMSG1613=WMSG1613W: The WebSphere MQ installed at {0} has been updated from version {1} to version {2}. A server restart may be required to properly register this update.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Service has been applied to the WebSphere MQ install used by WebSphere Application Server.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    The application server may need to be restarted in order to properly register the new client with the application server.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG1604E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="JMS_REGISTRATION_UNSUPPORTED_VERSION_WMSG1604" varFormat="Java">
    JMS_REGISTRATION_UNSUPPORTED_VERSION_WMSG1604=WMSG1604E: It was not possible to use the specified WebSphere MQ JMS client at path {0} because it is at version {1}, the minimum supported version is {2}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The MQ_INSTALL_ROOT variable has been configured to refer to a level of the WebSphere MQ JMS client that is not supported.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Modify the MQ_INSTALL_ROOT variable to reference a supported level of the WebSphere MQ JMS client.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0320E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PCFCommandServerConnectionError" varFormat="Java">
    PCFCommandServerConnectionError=WMSG0320E: Internal Queue Manager error.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An internal exception has been created in the queue manager.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Try again later.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0109I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MQQueueDefinerInvalidBackoutQueueName" varFormat="Java">
    MQQueueDefinerInvalidBackoutQueueName=WMSG0109I: Invalid backout Queue name specified. reason = {0}, parameter = {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The backout queue name specified is not valid.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that the backout queue name contains a valid value.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0311E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PCFCommandServerSelectorError" varFormat="Java">
    PCFCommandServerSelectorError=WMSG0311E: There has been a selector error.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    There was an error in a selector.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Try again later.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0108I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MQQueueDefinerInvalidClusterNameList" varFormat="Java">
    MQQueueDefinerInvalidClusterNameList=WMSG0108I: Invalid Cluster name list specified. reason = {0}, parameter = {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The cluster name list specified is not valid.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that the cluster name list contains a valid value.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG1301E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="EXCEPTION_BUILDING_REFERENCE_WMSG1301" varFormat="Java">
    EXCEPTION_BUILDING_REFERENCE_WMSG1301=WMSG1301E: An exception occurred building the reference for JNDI deployment of {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This exception is unexpected. The cause is not immediately known.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0011W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="JMSConfigParseWarnings" varFormat="Java">
    JMSConfigParseWarnings=WMSG0011W: Warnings parsing JMS Listener config file: {0}, {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A warning was issued trying to parse the given JMS Listener configuration file.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the problem in the JMS Listener configuration file, then restart the EJB Server.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0029E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="LoginException" varFormat="Java">
    LoginException=WMSG0029E: Error during JMSListener server login for MDB {0}, JMSDestination {1} : {2}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    During the login processing on a secure application server an unexpected exception was received.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the exception for reasons for the security problem. After correction restart the MDB EJB JAR module from the administrative console.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0013E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="JMSConfigParseFatals" varFormat="Java">
    JMSConfigParseFatals=WMSG0013E: Errors parsing JMS Listener config file: {0}, {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An error was issued trying to parse the given JMS Listener configuration file.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the problem in the JMS Listener configuration file, then restart the EJB Server.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0018E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="JMSConnectionException" varFormat="Java">
    JMSConnectionException=WMSG0018E: Error on JMSConnection for MDB {0}, JMSDestination {1} : {2}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An exception has been reported by the JMS provider on a JMSConnection.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the exception for reasons for the problem, then restart the MDB EJB JAR module from the administrative console.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0340E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PCFQueueDataValueLessThanZero" varFormat="Java">
    PCFQueueDataValueLessThanZero=WMSG0340E: The value specified was less than zero
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A value was specified that is outside the valid range.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a number greater than or equal to zero.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0327E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PCFCommandQueueDepthNotANumber" varFormat="Java">
    PCFCommandQueueDepthNotANumber=WMSG0327E: The Queue Depth specified was not a valid number.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The queue depth specified is not a valid number.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Enter a valid number for the queue depth then try again.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG1720I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WMQ_DISABLED_WMSG1720" varFormat="Java">
    WMQ_DISABLED_WMSG1720=WMSG1720I: All WebSphere MQ functionality on this server has been disabled.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    All WebSphere MQ functionality has been disabled on this server as a result of the &apos;disable WebSphere MQ functionality&apos; check box being selected on a WebSphere MQ messaging provider panel at an appropriate scope. Alternatively the manageWMQ administrative command may have been used to disable WebSphere MQ functionality. As a result of this all WebSphere MQ messaging provider, WebSphere MQ link, WebSphere MQ client link and MQ server functionality has been disabled.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    None unless WebSphere MQ functionality is required, in which case clear the &apos;disable WebSphere MQ functionality&apos; check box on the relevant WebSphere MQ messaging provider panel or make use of the manageWMQ administrative command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0324E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PCFCommandServerQueueManagerQuiescing" varFormat="Java">
    PCFCommandServerQueueManagerQuiescing=WMSG0324E: The Queue Manager is inactive.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The queue manager is inactive. Perhaps it is waiting to be restarted.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Wait for the queue manager to be restarted then try again.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG1300E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ERROR_BUILDING_REFERENCE_WMSG1300" varFormat="Java">
    ERROR_BUILDING_REFERENCE_WMSG1300=WMSG1300E: An error occurred building the reference for JNDI deployment of {0}. Error code {1} was returned from MQ with the error messages [{2}] and [{3}]
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An exception was created while building a reference object for JNDI deployment. This indicates that there is an inconsistency in the resource definition.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check the XML definition of the resource.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0300E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PCFCommandServerInvalidSetting" varFormat="Java">
    PCFCommandServerInvalidSetting=WMSG0300E: The {0} setting was not a valid value.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    One of the settings has a value that is not valid.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Change the setting so it is valid.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0304E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PCFCommandServerInvaidQueueName" varFormat="Java">
    PCFCommandServerInvaidQueueName=WMSG0304E: The Queue name you specified contained invalid characters.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The queue name specified was not valid.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Change the queue name so it is a valid name.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG1152E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="QUEUE_NAME_TOO_LONG_WMSG1152" varFormat="Java">
    QUEUE_NAME_TOO_LONG_WMSG1152=WMSG1152E: Unable to define JMS Destination {0} as the Queue name is too long - maximum length is {1} characters
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The name of the queue is too long.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Reduce the length of the queue name to the maximum number of characters allowed or less.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0007E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="JMSListenerStubStartMDBException" varFormat="Java">
    JMSListenerStubStartMDBException=WMSG0007E: Error starting JMSListenerStub: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An exception was received while trying to start the JMS Listener.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Determine from the given exception the reason why the JMS Listener did not start.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0111I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MQQueueDefinerInvalidRemoteQueueName" varFormat="Java">
    MQQueueDefinerInvalidRemoteQueueName=WMSG0111I: Invalid remote Queue name specified. reason = {0}, parameter = {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The remote queue name specified is not valid.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that the remote queue name contains a valid value.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG3080E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CREATE_ENDPOINT_UNAVAILABLE_WMSG3080" varFormat="Java">
    CREATE_ENDPOINT_UNAVAILABLE_WMSG3080=WMSG3080E: The system called an unexpected method. The createEndpoint method was called on a message endpoint factory in the Control Region Adjunct on z/OS.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This exception is unexpected. The cause is not immediately known.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0322E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PCFCommandServerQueueManagerNameError" varFormat="Java">
    PCFCommandServerQueueManagerNameError=WMSG0322E: The Queue Manager name was either invalid or not known.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The name specified for queue manager is either not valid or not known.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check that the queue manager name is valid and that the queue manager exists.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0034E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="JMSSessionRollbackException" varFormat="Java">
    JMSSessionRollbackException=WMSG0034E: Exception rollingback JMS Session for MDB {0}, JMSDestination {1} : {2}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    During the rollback of a JMS message an unexpected exception was received.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the exception for reasons for the problem and resolve the transaction using the administrative console. After correction restart the MDB EJB JAR module from the administrative console.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0020E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MDBListenerStopException" varFormat="Java">
    MDBListenerStopException=WMSG0020E: Unable to stop MDB Listener {0}, JMSDestination {1} : {2}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An exception has occurred when attempting to stop the given MDB Listener.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the exception for reasons for the problem, then try stopping the MDB EJB JAR module again from the administrative console.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0049E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MDBListenerStartFailed" varFormat="Java">
    MDBListenerStartFailed=WMSG0049E: Failed to start MDB {0} against listener port {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The MDB Listener did not start, while being bound to the given listener port.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the exception details to determine the reason for the problem, then restart the given listener port.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG1610E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CANNOT_CREATE_CF_WMSG1610" varFormat="Java">
    CANNOT_CREATE_CF_WMSG1610=WMSG1610E: An exception occurred instantiating a WebSphere MQ JCA RA type connection factory.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A WebSphere MQ JCA RA connection factory could not be created, and will not be bound into the WebSphere Application Server JNDI.  It will not be available to applications.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the linked exception to determine why the connection factory could not be created.  Correct the problem, if possible.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0123I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MQQueueDefinerUnrecognisedErrorTooLong" varFormat="Java">
    MQQueueDefinerUnrecognisedErrorTooLong=WMSG0123I: An error occurred that is not recognised. reason = {0}, parameter = {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An exception was created for a problem that has not been recognized.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Use the WebSphere MQ information center to identify the problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0302E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PCFCommandServerCommandFailed" varFormat="Java">
    PCFCommandServerCommandFailed=WMSG0302E: The action you tried did not complete. Check the other errors to determine the cause.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The command did not complete successfully. There should be other error messages that describe the cause of the problem.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Inspect the other error messages.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0014E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SAXParseException" varFormat="Java">
    SAXParseException=WMSG0014E: Error parsing JMSListener config file: {0}, line: {1}, column: {2}, message: {3}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An exception was received while trying to parse the given JMS Listener configuration file.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the problem in the JMS Listener configuration file, then restart the EJB Server.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0112I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MQQueueDefinerInvalidTransmissionQueueName" varFormat="Java">
    MQQueueDefinerInvalidTransmissionQueueName=WMSG0112I: Invalid transmission Queue name specified. reason = {0}, parameter = {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The transmission queue name specified is not valid.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that the transmission queue name contains a valid value.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0326E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PCFCommandServerPortNotANumber" varFormat="Java">
    PCFCommandServerPortNotANumber=WMSG0326E: The Port number specifed was not a valid number.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Port number specified is not a valid number.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Enter a valid number for the port then try again.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0043I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MDBListenerStopped" varFormat="Java">
    MDBListenerStopped=WMSG0043I: MDB Listener {0} stopped for JMSDestination {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The given MDB Listener has stopped.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the Listener has stopped unexpectedly, examine the application server logs for preceding error messages.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0330E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PCFCommandServerPriorityNotANumber" varFormat="Java">
    PCFCommandServerPriorityNotANumber=WMSG0330E: The specified priority was not a number.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The default priority specified was not valid number.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that the default priority attribute contains a number.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0303E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PCFCommandServerQueueExists" varFormat="Java">
    PCFCommandServerQueueExists=WMSG0303E: The Queue you tried to create already existed.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The queue already existed.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    The queue was created elsewhere. Click OK again to modify the queue.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0301E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PCFCommandServerClusterSettingNotValid" varFormat="Java">
    PCFCommandServerClusterSettingNotValid=WMSG0301E: The settings you chose would have made the Queue a cluster Queue and a transmission Queue.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The queue is a transmission queue and cannot also be defined as a cluster queue.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Remove the cluster name or cluster name list settings so the queue is not a member of a cluster queue.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0028E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ServerSessionCreateException" varFormat="Java">
    ServerSessionCreateException=WMSG0028E: Exception creating JMS ServerSession for MDB {0}, JMSDestination {1} : {2}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    During the creation of a JMS ServerSession for a new MDB Listener an unexpected exception was received.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the exception for reasons for the problem. After correction restart the MDB EJB JAR module from the administrative console.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0056W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SessionPoolMaxConnectionsTooSmall" varFormat="Java">
    SessionPoolMaxConnectionsTooSmall=WMSG0056W: MDB Listener Port {0} maximum sessions size of {1} is greater than its JMS Connection Factory {2} Session Pool size of {3}, setting maximum sessions to {3}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A message-driven bean is being started against the given listener port. This port has a maximum sessions value larger than the size of the JMS Connection Factory Session Pool that it is configured to use. The MDB Listener will start using the Session Pool size.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Increase the JMS Connection Factory Session Pool size, or decrease the listener port maximum sessions.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0341E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PCFCommandServerInvaidClusterName" varFormat="Java">
    PCFCommandServerInvaidClusterName=WMSG0341E: The Cluster name you specified contained invalid characters.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The cluster name specified is not valid.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Change the cluster name so it is a valid name.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0045E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="JMSListenerInitializeFailed" varFormat="Java">
    JMSListenerInitializeFailed=WMSG0045E: JMS Listener initialization failed
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The JMS Listener service could not initialize because of some previous errors.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the previous error messages to determine the cause of the problem,correct any errors then restart the server.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG1627I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MQ_NATIVEPATH_WMSG1627" varFormat="Java">
    MQ_NATIVEPATH_WMSG1627=WMSG1627I: Native libraries for the WebSphere MQ messaging provider will be loaded from the following directory: {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The WebSphere MQ messaging provider has determined that the specified directory will contain any native libraries that it needs. This message will be output even if no native libraries are available.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0346E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PCFQueueDataValueTooLong" varFormat="Java">
    PCFQueueDataValueTooLong=WMSG0346E: A value that was too long was specified.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A specified string value is too long.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a value that is not too long.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0064E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ResourceAdapterListenerPortNotValid" varFormat="Java">
    ResourceAdapterListenerPortNotValid=WMSG0064E: Unable to start message-driven bean (MDB) {0} against listener port {1}. It is not valid to specify a Java Message Service (JMS) resource adapter resource for a listener port; either use a different JMS resource with a listener port or use a default messaging JMS resource with an activation specification.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A message-driven bean is starting. This bean is bound to a listener port that specifies Java Naming Directory (JNDI) names for a JMS resource adapter. JMS resource adapters cannot be used by a listener port because they support activation specifications only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Either redeploy the message-driven bean against a default messaging JMS activation specification or redeploy the message-driven bean against a different JMS resource that supports listener ports.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0004E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="JMSListenerInitializeException" varFormat="Java">
    JMSListenerInitializeException=WMSG0004E: Error initializing JMSListenerStub: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An exception was received while trying to initialize the JMS Listener.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Determine from the given exception the reason that the JMS Listener has not initialized.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0037E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="JMSServerSessionStartException" varFormat="Java">
    JMSServerSessionStartException=WMSG0037E: Exception starting JMS ServerSession for MDB {0}, JMSDestination {1} : {2}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    During the starting of a JMS ServerSession an unexpected exception was received.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the exception for reasons for the problem. After correction restart the MDB EJB JAR module from the administrative console.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0315E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PCFCommandServerUnexpectedIOError" varFormat="Java">
    PCFCommandServerUnexpectedIOError=WMSG0315E: Unexpected IO error occurred.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    While sending a message an IO exception was created.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Try again later.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0032E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="RollbackException" varFormat="Java">
    RollbackException=WMSG0032E: Unable to rollback JMS ServerSession transaction for MDB {0}, JMSDestination {1} : {2}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    During the rollback of a JMS message an unexpected exception was received.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the exception for reasons for the problem and resolve the transaction using the administrative console. After correction restart the MDB EJB JAR module from the administrative console.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0063E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DefaultMessagingListenerPortNotValid" varFormat="Java">
    DefaultMessagingListenerPortNotValid=WMSG0063E: Unable to start message-driven bean (MDB) {0} against listener port {1}. It is not valid to specify a default messaging Java Message Service (JMS) resource for a listener port; either use a different JMS resource with a listener port or use a default messaging JMS resource with an activation specification.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A message-driven bean is starting. This bean is bound to a listener port that specifies Java Naming Directory (JNDI) names for a default messaging JMS resource. Default messaging cannot be used by a listener port because it is a JMS resource adapter that supports activation specifications only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Either redeploy the message-driven bean against a default messaging JMS activation specification or redeploy the message-driven bean against a different JMS resource that supports listener ports.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0118I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MQQueueDefinerBackoutQueueNameTooLong" varFormat="Java">
    MQQueueDefinerBackoutQueueNameTooLong=WMSG0118I: Backout Queue name is over 48 characters long. reason = {0}, parameter = {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The backout queue name specified is longer than 48 characters.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that the backout queue name contains less than 48 characters.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0001I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="JMSListenerStarted" varFormat="Java">
    JMSListenerStarted=WMSG0001I: JMS Listener started successfully
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The JMS Listener service has started successfully.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG1602I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MESSAGING_CLIENT_ONLY_WMSG1602" varFormat="Java">
    MESSAGING_CLIENT_ONLY_WMSG1602=WMSG1602I: WebSphere MQ JMS Client only has been installed
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    WebSphere MQ JMS Server has not been installed on this node so will not be available.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If a JMS server is to be started on this node, WebSphere MQ JMS Server must be installed.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG1609E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="BAD_CF_TYPE2_WMSG1609" varFormat="Java">
    BAD_CF_TYPE2_WMSG1609=WMSG1609E: An internal error occurred.  Unexpected object type {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This exception is unexpected. The cause is not immediately known.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0027E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MDBInvocationException" varFormat="Java">
    MDBInvocationException=WMSG0027E: Exception invoking MessageDrivenBean.onMessage() for MDB {0} : {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    During the invocation of the MessageDrivenBean.onMessage() method an unexpected exception was received.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the exception for reasons for the problem. After correction restart the MDB EJB JAR module from the administrative console.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0122I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MQQueueDefinerUnknownParameterTooLong" varFormat="Java">
    MQQueueDefinerUnknownParameterTooLong=WMSG0122I: Unknown Parameter is too long. reason = {0}, parameter = {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The PCF response message claims a parameter was too long, but the parameter was not expected.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check that the correct parameter is being used. Reference the WebSphere MQ information center if necessary.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0105I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MQQueueDefinerInvalidQueueName" varFormat="Java">
    MQQueueDefinerInvalidQueueName=WMSG0105I: Invalid Queue name specified. reason = {0}, parameter = {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The queue name specified is not valid.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that the queue name attribute contains a valid value.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0321E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PCFCommandServerOpenFailed" varFormat="Java">
    PCFCommandServerOpenFailed=WMSG0321E: Internal Queue Manager error.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An internal exception has been created in the queue manager.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Try again later.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0050E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CheckDurableSubscriptionException" varFormat="Java">
    CheckDurableSubscriptionException=WMSG0050E: Exception checking JMS durable subscriptions {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The message listener service checks that the current set of durable subscriptions are still valid and do not need unsubscribing. An exception was received during this check.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the exception details to determine the reason for the problem, then restart the server.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0038E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MDBPooledThreadMDBException" varFormat="Java">
    MDBPooledThreadMDBException=WMSG0038E: Exception in MDBPooledThread: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    During the processing of a JMS message on a server thread an unexpected exception was received.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the exception for reasons for the problem. After correction restart the MDB EJB JAR module from the administrative console.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0025E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MDBSecurityNotConfigured" varFormat="Java">
    MDBSecurityNotConfigured=WMSG0025E: MessageDrivenBean does not have any security permissions configured
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    During the creation of an MDB Listener on a secure application server an exception was received that indicated the given message-driven bean did not have its security permissions set.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Configure the MessageDrivenBean.onMessage() method access permissions for access by anyone or by the Server security ID.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0336E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PCFQueueDataValueNull" varFormat="Java">
    PCFQueueDataValueNull=WMSG0336E: You specified a null value where a String was required.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A null was specified for one of the queue data values.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a value that is not null.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0328E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PCFCommandServerMaximumMessageLengthNotANumber" varFormat="Java">
    PCFCommandServerMaximumMessageLengthNotANumber=WMSG0328E: The Maximum Message Length specified was not a valid number.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The maximum message length specified was not a valid number.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Enter a valid number for the maximum message length then try again.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0026E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MDBOnMessageException" varFormat="Java">
    MDBOnMessageException=WMSG0026E: Exception invoking MessageDrivenBean.onMessage() for MDB {0} : {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    During the invocation of the MessageDrivenBean.onMessage() method an unexpected exception was received.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the exception for reasons for the problem. After correction restart the MDB EJB JAR module from the administrative console.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0106I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MQQueueDefinerInvalidQueueDescription" varFormat="Java">
    MQQueueDefinerInvalidQueueDescription=WMSG0106I: Invalid Queue description specified. reason = {0}, parameter = {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The queue description specified is not valid.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that the queue description attribute contains a valid value.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0332E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PCFCommandServerMQQueueNameNotSpecified" varFormat="Java">
    PCFCommandServerMQQueueNameNotSpecified=WMSG0332E: The Name of the MQ Queue is required by the WMQQueueDefiner MBean
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The WMQQueueDefiner MBean was not supplied with a queue name.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify the name of the MQ queue.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0059E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MDBListenerRetryLimitReached" varFormat="Java">
    MDBListenerRetryLimitReached=WMSG0059E: Maximum restart retry count of {0} reached for Listener Port {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The given listener port has reached its retry limit for starting.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the reason for the problem. After correction restart the listener port from the administrative console.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0115I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MQQueueDefinerQueueDescriptionTooLong" varFormat="Java">
    MQQueueDefinerQueueDescriptionTooLong=WMSG0115I: Queue description is over 64 characters long. reason = {0}, parameter = {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The queue description specified is longer than 64 characters.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that the queue description contains less than 64 characters.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0061W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MDBUnknownProperty" varFormat="Java">
    MDBUnknownProperty=WMSG0061W: An Internal error has occured. The activation config expected a param of type {2} but got a {1} in MDB {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This exception is unexpected. The cause is not immediately known.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0119I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MQQueueDefinerRemoteQMGRNameTooLong" varFormat="Java">
    MQQueueDefinerRemoteQMGRNameTooLong=WMSG0119I: Remote Queue Manager name is over 48 characters long. reason = {0}, parameter = {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The remote queue manager name specified is longer than 48 characters.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that the remote queue manager name contains less than 48 characters.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0010E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="JMSConfigParseException" varFormat="Java">
    JMSConfigParseException=WMSG0010E: Error parsing JMSListener config file: {0}, {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An exception was received while trying to parse the given JMS Listener configuration file.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the problem in the JMS Listener configuration file, then restart the EJB Server.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0310E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PCFCommandServerQueueNotEmpty" varFormat="Java">
    PCFCommandServerQueueNotEmpty=WMSG0310E: Deletion of the Queue failed as it contains some messages that could not be removed.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    There were some messages on the queue that could not be purged.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Try again later.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0329E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PCFCommandServerBackoutThresholdNotANumber" varFormat="Java">
    PCFCommandServerBackoutThresholdNotANumber=WMSG0329E: The Backout Threshold specified was not a valid number.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The backout threshold specified is not a valid number.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Enter a valid number for the backout threshold then try again.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0055E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ReadRequestLogException" varFormat="Java">
    ReadRequestLogException=WMSG0055E: Exception reading the Late Response Message Consumer Log {0}, {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The late response message consumer was unable to read the given log file, because of an exception.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the exception details to determine why the log file could not be read.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0052E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CleanupDurableSubscriptionException" varFormat="Java">
    CleanupDurableSubscriptionException=WMSG0052E: Exception unsubscribing JMS durable subscription {0} : {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    When attempting to unsubscribe a durable subscription an exception was received.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the exception details to determine the reason for the problem, then restart the server.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0306E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PCFCommandServerUnexpectedPCFError" varFormat="Java">
    PCFCommandServerUnexpectedPCFError=WMSG0306E: Unexpected error occurred. PCF reason code {0}, please check the WebSphere MQ documentation for a description of the error.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This exception is unexpected. The cause is not immediately known.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0036E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="JMSRetryLimitReached" varFormat="Java">
    JMSRetryLimitReached=WMSG0036E: Maximum message delivery retry count of {0} reached for MDB {1}, JMSDestination {2}, MDBListener stopped
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The given JMS Destination has reached its retry limit for attempting to process a JMS message.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the reason for the problem. After correction restart the MDB EJB JAR module from the administrative console.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0317E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PCFCommandServerInvalidQueueSettingsReturned" varFormat="Java">
    PCFCommandServerInvalidQueueSettingsReturned=WMSG0317E: The Command Server has returned some invalid Queue settings.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    While unpacking the response from the queue manager an incorrect queue setting was found.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Try again later.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0335E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PCFCommandServerInternalException" varFormat="Java">
    PCFCommandServerInternalException=WMSG0335E: The Host name that the Queue Manager is running on is required by the WMQQueueDefiner MBean.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The WMQQueueDefiner MBean was not supplied with a host name.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Contact your IBM service representative.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0902E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MQBindersDisabled" varFormat="Java">
    MQBindersDisabled=WMSG0902E: The WebSphere MQ JMS Binders have been disabled as either the WebSphere MQ Client has not been installed, or the MQ_INSTALL_ROOT variable has not been set.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The WebSphere MQ JMS client has not been installed.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Install the WebSphere MQ JMS client and set the MQ_INSTALL_ROOT variable.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0323E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PCFCommandServerQueueManagerNotAvailable" varFormat="Java">
    PCFCommandServerQueueManagerNotAvailable=WMSG0323E: The Queue Manager is not available.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The queue manager is not available. Perhaps it is not running.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check that the queue manager is running then try again.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG1607E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="BAD_CF_TYPE1_WMSG1607" varFormat="Java">
    BAD_CF_TYPE1_WMSG1607=WMSG1607E: An internal error occurred.  Unexpected object type {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This exception is unexpected. The cause is not immediately known.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0060W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MDBUnknownActivationSpecParam" varFormat="Java">
    MDBUnknownActivationSpecParam=WMSG0060W: Unknown activation config property {1} specified for binding MDB {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The activation configuration property is not a known property. This will be ignored and a warning message logged.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure the property name is correct and is spelt correctly.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0009W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="JMSListenerStubTerminateException" varFormat="Java">
    JMSListenerStubTerminateException=WMSG0009W: Error terminating JMSListenerStub : {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An exception was received while trying to terminate the JMS Listener.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the exception indicates a serious problem, examine the reason for the problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0331E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PCFCommandServerMQClientNotPresent" varFormat="Java">
    PCFCommandServerMQClientNotPresent=WMSG0331E: The MQ Client is required for this functionality, but it is not installed.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The MQ Client was not installed and this is required to configure WebSphere MQ.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Install the MQ Client.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0033E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PostInvokeException" varFormat="Java">
    PostInvokeException=WMSG0033E: Exception committing JMS ServerSession transaction for MDB {0}, JMSDestination {1} : {2}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    During the committing of a JMS message an unexpected exception was received.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the exception for reasons for the problem. After correction restart the MDB EJB JAR module from the administrative console.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0035E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="JMSSessionCommitException" varFormat="Java">
    JMSSessionCommitException=WMSG0035E: Exception committing JMS Session for MDB {0}, JMSDestination {1} : {2}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    During the committing of a JMS message an unexpected exception was received.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the exception for reasons for the problem. After correction restart the MDB EJB JAR module from the administrative console.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0030E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PreInvokeException" varFormat="Java">
    PreInvokeException=WMSG0030E: Exception beginning JMS ServerSession transaction for MDB {0}, JMSDestination {1} : {2}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    During the processing of a JMS message the JMS Listener was unable to begin a transaction.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the exception for reasons for the problem. After correction restart the MDB EJB JAR module from the administrative console.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0344E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PCFCommandServerInvaidQueueDescription" varFormat="Java">
    PCFCommandServerInvaidQueueDescription=WMSG0344E: The Queue Description you specified contained invalid characters.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified queue description contains characters that are not valid.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Change the queue description so it contains only valid characters.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG1625E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="JMS_REGISTRATION_MQ_JAVA_NOT_FOUND_WMSG1625" varFormat="Java">
    JMS_REGISTRATION_MQ_JAVA_NOT_FOUND_WMSG1625=WMSG1625E: It was not possible to detect the WebSphere MQ messaging provider code at the specified path {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The WebSphere MQ messaging provider code is not installed at the specified path.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Modify the configuration of the WebSphere MQ messaging provider in the application server so that it points to the correct path of the WebSphere MQ messaging provider. This will involve either changing the native path or install directory of the WebSphere MQ resource adapter or changing the value of the MQ_INSTALL_ROOT variable. Then restart your application server.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG1622E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MQ_INSTALL_ROOT_UPDATED_PLEASE_RESTART_WMSG1622" varFormat="Java">
    MQ_INSTALL_ROOT_UPDATED_PLEASE_RESTART_WMSG1622=WMSG1622E: The installation directory of the WebSphere MQ messaging provider has been updated from {0} to {1}. The WebSphere MQ messaging provider has been disabled. A server restart is required to re-enable this function.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An update has been made to the installation directory of the WebSphere MQ messaging provider.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    The application server must be restarted in order to use the client installed at the updated path.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0325E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PCFCommandServerQueueManagerStopping" varFormat="Java">
    PCFCommandServerQueueManagerStopping=WMSG0325E: The Queue Manager is stopping.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The queue manager is stopping.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Wait for the queue manager to be restarted then try again.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0900W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ResourceBinderDisabled" varFormat="Java">
    ResourceBinderDisabled=WMSG0900W: JMS resource binder for resource type {0} is disabled
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The JMS resource binder for the given type of resource is disabled because the binder cannot resolve the necessary classes for this JMS resource type.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If this resource type is required to be supported, check that the necessary JMS messaging components are installed then restart the application server.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0024W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MDBListenerTerminateException" varFormat="Java">
    MDBListenerTerminateException=WMSG0024W: Exception terminating MDBListener {0}, JMSDestination {1} : {2}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    During the stop of an MDB Listener, the terminating of the listener caused the given exception.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the exception indicates a serious problem, examine the reason for the problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0313E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PCFCommandServerQueueDoesNotExist" varFormat="Java">
    PCFCommandServerQueueDoesNotExist=WMSG0313E: The Queue you tried to modify does not exist.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An attempt to modify a queue was made, but the queue does not exist.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    The queue might have been deleted while you were editing its settings. Click OK to create the queue.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0345E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PCFCommandServerInvaidParameter" varFormat="Java">
    PCFCommandServerInvaidParameter=WMSG0345E: An unknown Parameter contained invalid characters.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    One of the parameters contains characters that are not valid, and is not a parameter that the system was expecting.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Contact your IBM Service Representative.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG1612E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MQ_INSTALL_ROOT_UPDATED_PLEASE_RESTART_WMSG1612" varFormat="Java">
    MQ_INSTALL_ROOT_UPDATED_PLEASE_RESTART_WMSG1612=WMSG1612E: The MQ_INSTALL_ROOT has been updated from {0} to {1}. The WebSphere MQ Messaging Provider has been disabled. A server restart is required to re-enable the function.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An update has been made to the MQ_INSTALL_ROOT variable.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    The application server must be restarted in order to use the client installed at the updated path.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0314E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PCFCommandServerUnexpectedMQError" varFormat="Java">
    PCFCommandServerUnexpectedMQError=WMSG0314E: Unexpected error occurred. MQ reason code {0}, please check the WebSphere MQ Information Center for a description of the error.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    While creating a queue an unexpected exception was received.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Refer to the WebSphere MQ information center to find a description of the error.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0048W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ListenerPortMBeanActivateException" varFormat="Java">
    ListenerPortMBeanActivateException=WMSG0048W: Exception activating JMX MBean {0}, exception {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    While activating a ListenerPort JMX MBean an exception was received.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the exception details to determine the reason for the problem, then restart the application server.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0339E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PCFQueueDataValueInvalid" varFormat="Java">
    PCFQueueDataValueInvalid=WMSG0339E: The value specified was not one of the valid value
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The value specified has a limited number of options, none of which were specified.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a valid value.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG1605E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="JMS_REGISTRATION_MQ_JAVA_NOT_FOUND_WMSG1605" varFormat="Java">
    JMS_REGISTRATION_MQ_JAVA_NOT_FOUND_WMSG1605=WMSG1605E: It was not possible to detect the MQ JMS client at the specified path {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The MQ_INSTALL_ROOT variable has been configured to refer to a file system location that does not appear to contain the WebSphere MQ JMS client.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Modify the MQ_INSTALL_ROOT variable to reference the location of the WebSphere MQ JMS client.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0113I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MQQueueDefinerUnknownInvalidParameter" varFormat="Java">
    MQQueueDefinerUnknownInvalidParameter=WMSG0113I: Unrecognised parameter is invalid. reason = {0}, parameter = {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The PCF response message is reporting that a parameter has caused an error, but the program does not know how to handle it.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Look up the parameter in the WebSphere MQ information center and fix the problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0305E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PCFCommandServerQueueOpen" varFormat="Java">
    PCFCommandServerQueueOpen=WMSG0305E: Unable to perform the action as the Queue was open.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The queue was open and the force option was not set.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Try again later when the queue is not being used.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG3001E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_PROPERTIES_WMSG3001" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_PROPERTIES_WMSG3001=WMSG3001E: The mandatory property ID is not set on the activation specification {0} of the resource adapter wrapper.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The ID property is a required property for the resource adapter wrapper, but it is not set.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the configuration and restart the application.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG3000E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_PROPERTIES_WMSG3000" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_PROPERTIES_WMSG3000=WMSG3000E: The mandatory property JmsActSpecJndiName is not set on the activation specification {0} of the resource adapter wrapper.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The JmsActSpecJndiName property is a required property for the resource adapter wrapper, but it is not set.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the configuration and restart the application.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0121I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MQQueueDefinerTransmissionQueueNameTooLong" varFormat="Java">
    MQQueueDefinerTransmissionQueueNameTooLong=WMSG0121I: Transmission Queue name is over 48 characters long. reason = {0}, parameter = {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The transmission queue name specified is longer than 48 characters.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that the transmission queue name contains less than 48 characters.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0114I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MQQueueDefinerQueueNameTooLong" varFormat="Java">
    MQQueueDefinerQueueNameTooLong=WMSG0114I: Queue name is over 48 characters long. reason = {0}, parameter = {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The queue name specified is longer than 48 characters.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that the queue name contains less than 48 characters.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0309E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PCFCommandServerNotAuthorized" varFormat="Java">
    PCFCommandServerNotAuthorized=WMSG0309E: You are not authorized to perform these actions.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Either credentials were not specified or they were not valid.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Provide valid credentials to perform the action.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG3013E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DEACTIVATE_FAILED_WMSG3013" varFormat="Java">
    DEACTIVATE_FAILED_WMSG3013=WMSG3013E: The endpoint that the resource adapter wrapper {1} wraps for endpoint {0} is not activated.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    There was an attempt to deactivate an endpoint, but the endpoint is not activated.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that endpoint is activated before you deactivate it.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG3011E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DEACTIVATE_FAILED_WMSG3011" varFormat="Java">
    DEACTIVATE_FAILED_WMSG3011=WMSG3011E: During deactivation, the endpoint created the following exception: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    There was an exception during the deactivation of an endpoint.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the exception for further information.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0333E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PCFCommandServerMQQueueManagerNameNotSpecified" varFormat="Java">
    PCFCommandServerMQQueueManagerNameNotSpecified=WMSG0333E: The Name of the MQ Queue Manager is required by the WMQQueueDefiner MBean.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The WMQQueueDefiner MBean was not supplied with a queue manager name.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify the name of the MQ queue manager.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0002I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="JMSListenerStopped" varFormat="Java">
    JMSListenerStopped=WMSG0002I: JMS Listener stopped successfully
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The JMS Listener service has stopped successfully.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0016E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MDBPostInvokeException" varFormat="Java">
    MDBPostInvokeException=WMSG0016E: postInvoke exception for MDB {0} listening upon JMSDestination {1}, exception: {2}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An exception was received during postInvoke transaction completion processing, after calling the MDB.onMessage() method.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the exception for reasons for the problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0342E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PCFCommandServerInvaidClusterNameList" varFormat="Java">
    PCFCommandServerInvaidClusterNameList=WMSG0342E: The Cluster Namelist you specified contained invalid characters.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The name specified for the cluster name list is not valid.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a valid name for the cluster name list.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0337E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PCFQueueDataValueTooShort" varFormat="Java">
    PCFQueueDataValueTooShort=WMSG0337E: A value that was too short was specified.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A string value was specified that is too short.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a value that is long enough.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0124E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PCFInternalQueueDefinerException" varFormat="Java">
    PCFInternalQueueDefinerException=WMSG0124E: An internal MQ queue definer MBean error has occurred.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An internal problem has occurred that relates to the MQ queue definer message-driven bean.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See the additional error messages associated with this message for further information.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG1719I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MBEAN_INFO_WMSG1719" varFormat="Java">
    MBEAN_INFO_WMSG1719=WMSG1719I: Implementation info is {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Output by WMQInfo MBean
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    None
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0058I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MDBListenerRestartScheduled" varFormat="Java">
    MDBListenerRestartScheduled=WMSG0058I: Listener Port {0} will attempt to restart in {1} seconds
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The listener port has stopped due to a problem. Because the the max.recovery.retries and recovery.timeout.interval custom properties are set, the application server will attempt to restart it.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG1718I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MBEAN_INFO_WMSG1718" varFormat="Java">
    MBEAN_INFO_WMSG1718=WMSG1718I: Version is {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Output by WMQInfo MBean
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    None
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG1717I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MBEAN_INFO_WMSG1717" varFormat="Java">
    MBEAN_INFO_WMSG1717=WMSG1717I: Type is {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Output by WMQInfo MBean
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    None
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG1716I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MBEAN_INFO_WMSG1716" varFormat="Java">
    MBEAN_INFO_WMSG1716=WMSG1716I: Title is {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Output by WMQInfo MBean
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    None
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG1715I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MBEAN_INFO_WMSG1715" varFormat="Java">
    MBEAN_INFO_WMSG1715=WMSG1715I: Name is {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Output by WMQInfo MBean
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    None
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG1714I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MBEAN_INFO_WMSG1714" varFormat="Java">
    MBEAN_INFO_WMSG1714=WMSG1714I: Native Libraries {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Output by WMQInfo MBean
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    None
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG1713I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MBEAN_INFO_WMSG1713" varFormat="Java">
    MBEAN_INFO_WMSG1713=WMSG1713I: Jar Files: {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Output by WMQInfo MBean
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    None
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG1712I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MBEAN_INFO_WMSG1712" varFormat="Java">
    MBEAN_INFO_WMSG1712=WMSG1712I: Version is {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Output by WMQInfo MBean
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    None
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG1711I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MBEAN_INFO_WMSG1711" varFormat="Java">
    MBEAN_INFO_WMSG1711=WMSG1711I: Native File Directory is {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Output by WMQInfo MBean
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    None
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG1710I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MBEAN_INFO_WMSG1710" varFormat="Java">
    MBEAN_INFO_WMSG1710=WMSG1710I: Install Directory is {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Output by WMQInfo MBean
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    None
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0008E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="JMSListenerStubStartException" varFormat="Java">
    JMSListenerStubStartException=WMSG0008E: Error starting JMSListenerStub: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An exception was received while trying to start the JMS Listener.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Determine from the given exception the reason why the JMS Listener did not start.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG3012E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ACTIVATE_FAILED_WMSG3012" varFormat="Java">
    ACTIVATE_FAILED_WMSG3012=WMSG3012E: The endpoint that the resource adapter wrapper {1} wraps for endpoint {0} is already activated.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The endpointActivation method of the resource adapter wrapper was called when the endpoint is already activated. An endpoint can be activated only once.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that endpoint is not activated multiple times.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG1603E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="JMS_REGISTRATION_OSGI_FAILURE_WMSG1603" varFormat="Java">
    JMS_REGISTRATION_OSGI_FAILURE_WMSG1603=WMSG1603E: An internal error occurred. It was not possible to register the WebSphere MQ JMS client with the application server due to exception {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An exception was created while registering the WebSphere MQ JMS client with the server.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0316E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PCFCommandServerQueueNotLocal" varFormat="Java">
    PCFCommandServerQueueNotLocal=WMSG0316E: You tried to view a Queue that was not a local Queue. Only administration of local Queues is supported.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    You tried to view a queue that is not a local queue.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify the name of a queue that is a local queue.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG1709I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MBEAN_INFO_WMSG1709" varFormat="Java">
    MBEAN_INFO_WMSG1709=WMSG1709I: WebSphere MQ messaging provider is not configured
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Output by WMQInfo MBean
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    None
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG1708I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MBEAN_INFO_WMSG1708" varFormat="Java">
    MBEAN_INFO_WMSG1708=WMSG1708I: WebSphere MQ messaging provider configuration is not valid
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Output by WMQInfo MBean
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    None
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG1707I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MBEAN_INFO_WMSG1707" varFormat="Java">
    MBEAN_INFO_WMSG1707=WMSG1707I: Unable to obtain any version information from WebSphere MQ messaging provider because of exception: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Output by WMQInfo MBean
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    None
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG1705I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MBEAN_INFO_WMSG1705" varFormat="Java">
    MBEAN_INFO_WMSG1705=WMSG1705I: Information from WebSphere MQ messaging provider follows:
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Output by WMQInfo MBean
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    None
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG1703I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MBEAN_INFO_WMSG1703" varFormat="Java">
    MBEAN_INFO_WMSG1703=WMSG1703I: RAR implementation version {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Output by WMQInfo MBean
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    None
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG1702I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MBEAN_INFO_WMSG1702" varFormat="Java">
    MBEAN_INFO_WMSG1702=WMSG1702I: Using the WebSphere MQ Resource Adapter
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Output by WMQInfo MBean
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    None
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG1701I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MBEAN_INFO_WMSG1701" varFormat="Java">
    MBEAN_INFO_WMSG1701=WMSG1701I: Using the WebSphere MQ messaging provider
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Output by WMQInfo MBean
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    None
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG1700I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MBEAN_INFO_WMSG1700" varFormat="Java">
    MBEAN_INFO_WMSG1700=WMSG1700I: Currently active WebSphere MQ messaging provider configuration in WebSphere Application Server {0}, report at {1});
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Output by WMQInfo MBean
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    None
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0102I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MQQueueDefinerInvalidQueueDepth" varFormat="Java">
    MQQueueDefinerInvalidQueueDepth=WMSG0102I: Invalid maximum Queue depth specified. reason = {0}, parameter = {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The queue depth specified was not in the range 0-640000.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that the queue depth contains a valid value.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0107I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MQQueueDefinerInvalidClusterName" varFormat="Java">
    MQQueueDefinerInvalidClusterName=WMSG0107I: Invalid Cluster name specified. reason = {0}, parameter = {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The cluster name specified is not valid.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that the cluster name attribute contains a valid value.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0110I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MQQueueDefinerInvalidRemoteQMGRName" varFormat="Java">
    MQQueueDefinerInvalidRemoteQMGRName=WMSG0110I: Invalid remote Queue Manager name specified. reason = {0}, parameter = {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The remote queue manager name specified is not valid.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that the remote queue manager name contains a valid value.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0023W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MDBListenerCloseException" varFormat="Java">
    MDBListenerCloseException=WMSG0023W: Exception closing MDBListener {0}, JMSDestination {1} : {2}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Closing the specified MDB Listener created the given exception.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the exception indicates a serious problem, examine the reason for the problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0005E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MDBListenerCreateMDBException" varFormat="Java">
    MDBListenerCreateMDBException=WMSG0005E: Error creating MDBListener for JMS Listener {0}, JMSDestination {1} : {2}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An exception was received while trying to create the MDBListener instance for the given JMS Listener.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Determine from the given exception the reason that the MDBListener was not created. Examine your JMS Listener configuration file to ensure the definition is correct, and ensure that all the necessary JMS resources are bound into the WebSphere JNDI name space. Also, ensure that the necessary JMS provider classes are in the application server class path.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0501E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_SESSION_TYPE_WMSG0501E" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_SESSION_TYPE_WMSG0501E=WMSG0501E: An internal error occurred. The javax.jms.MessageConsumer implementation {0} is invalid for use with the {1} com.ibm.wsspi.JmsMessageListenerSupport.MessageListenerSetter.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This exception is unexpected. The cause is not immediately known.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0047E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="NoMDBBinding" varFormat="Java">
    NoMDBBinding=WMSG0047E: MessageDrivenBeanBinding does not exist for MDB {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified message-driven bean does not have a message-driven bean binding in its binding configuration.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure the given message-driven bean has being assembled and installed correctly, then reinstall the bean.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0500E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="UNKNOWN_SESSION_TYPE_WMSG0500E" varFormat="Java">
    UNKNOWN_SESSION_TYPE_WMSG0500E=WMSG0500E: It is not possible to set a javax.jms.MessageListener on a javax.jms.MessageConsumer of the type {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A com.ibm.wsspi.JmsMessageListenerSupport.MessageListenerSetter has not been registered to set a message listener on the supplied javax.jms.MessageConsumer implementation.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0044W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MDBListenerNotStarted" varFormat="Java">
    MDBListenerNotStarted=WMSG0044W: MDB Listener listening on JMSDestination {1} has not started as the EJB {0} is not installed
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The given MDB Listener has not being started because the message-driven bean with the given JNDI home name is not installed and started.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the JMSListenerConfig.xml file specifies an incorrect EJB JNDI home name, correct the entry then restart the server.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG1600E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="VARMAP_EXCEPTION_WMSG1600" varFormat="Java">
    VARMAP_EXCEPTION_WMSG1600=WMSG1600E: An exception occurred determining the WebSphere MQ JMS paths: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    WebSphere MQ JMS messaging is not usable.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0103I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MQQueueDefinerInvalidMessageLength" varFormat="Java">
    MQQueueDefinerInvalidMessageLength=WMSG0103I: Invalid maximum message length specified. reason = {0}, parameter = {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The message length specified was not within range.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that the message length attribute contains a valid value.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG1611I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PROVIDER_LEVEL_WMSG1611" varFormat="Java">
    PROVIDER_LEVEL_WMSG1611=WMSG1611I: The installed level of the WebSphere MQ messaging provider is {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This is an informational message indicating the level of the installed WebSphere MQ messaging provider.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG1623E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MQ_INSTALL_ROOT_CONTENT_CHANGED_WMSG1623" varFormat="Java">
    MQ_INSTALL_ROOT_CONTENT_CHANGED_WMSG1623=WMSG1623E: The WebSphere MQ messaging provider installed at {0} has been updated and an application server restart is required to pick up this update. The WebSphere MQ messaging provider has been disabled.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An update has been applied to the WebSphere MQ messaging provider used by the application server. The nature of the update is such that the application server needs a restart for the WebSphere MQ messaging provider to work.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    The application server needs to be restarted in order to register the updated WebSphere MQ messaging provider.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG3104E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVOKE_FAILURE_WMSG3104" varFormat="Java">
    INVOKE_FAILURE_WMSG3104=WMSG3104E: An error occurred because the method {0} is not expected to be called for application {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This exception is unexpected. The cause is not immediately known.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG3103E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVOKE_FAILURE_WMSG3103" varFormat="Java">
    INVOKE_FAILURE_WMSG3103=WMSG3103E: An error occurred because the method {0} is not expected to be called for application {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This exception is unexpected. The cause is not immediately known.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG3102E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVOKE_FAILURE_WMSG3102" varFormat="Java">
    INVOKE_FAILURE_WMSG3102=WMSG3102E: An error occurred because the method {0} is not expected to be called for application {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This exception is unexpected. The cause is not immediately known.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG1608E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="NO_WMQ_JCA_RA2_WMSG1608" varFormat="Java">
    NO_WMQ_JCA_RA2_WMSG1608=WMSG1608E: An internal error occurred.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This exception is unexpected. The cause is not immediately known.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0057E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="JMSConnectionLinkedException" varFormat="Java">
    JMSConnectionLinkedException=WMSG0057E: Error on JMSConnection for MDB {0}, JMSDestination {1}, JMS Linked Exception : {2}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An exception has been reported by the JMS provider on a JMSConnection.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the exception for reasons for the problem, then restart the MDB EJB JAR module from the administrative console.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG1614E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MQ_INSTALL_ROOT_CONTENT_CHANGED_WMSG1614" varFormat="Java">
    MQ_INSTALL_ROOT_CONTENT_CHANGED_WMSG1614=WMSG1614E: The WebSphere MQ installed at {0} has been updated and a server restart is required for the the WebSphere MQ Messaging Provider to work with this update. The WebSphere MQ Messaging Provider has been disabled.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An update has been applied to the WebSphere MQ installed used by the application server. The nature of the update is such that the application server needs a restart for the WebSphere MQ Messaging Provider to work.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    The application server needs to be restarted in order to register the updated client with the application server.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0901E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASBindersDisabled" varFormat="Java">
    WASBindersDisabled=WMSG0901E: The WebSphere MQ JMS Binders have been disabled as the WebSphere MQ JMS Client has not been installed.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The WebSphere MQ JMS client has not been installed.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Install the WebSphere MQ JMS client.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0051E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SetCurrentSubscriptionsForAppException" varFormat="Java">
    SetCurrentSubscriptionsForAppException=WMSG0051E: Exception updating the JMS durable subscriptions log {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    When an application is started that contains JMS durable subscriptions, the subscriptions are logged to ensure that they get cleaned up if the application is subsquently removed. An exception has occurred during this update.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the exception details to determine the reason for the problem, then restart the server.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0343E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PCFCommandServerInvaidBackoutReQueueName" varFormat="Java">
    PCFCommandServerInvaidBackoutReQueueName=WMSG0343E: The Backout Re-Queue Queue Name you specified contained invalid characters.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The name specified for the backout re-queue queue is not valid.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a valid name for the backout re-queue queue.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0307E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PCFCommandServerUnableToConnectToQueueManager" varFormat="Java">
    PCFCommandServerUnableToConnectToQueueManager=WMSG0307E: Unable to connect to the Queue Manager.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Unable to connect to the queue manager.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check that the queue manager and command server are running and that the settings you specified are correct.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0054E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WriteRequestLogException" varFormat="Java">
    WriteRequestLogException=WMSG0054E: Exception writing to the Late Response Message Consumer Log {0}, {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The late response message consumer could not write to the given log file.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the exception details to determine why the message consumer could not write to the log file.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG3101E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="AFTER_DELIVERY_FAILURE_WMSG3101" varFormat="Java">
    AFTER_DELIVERY_FAILURE_WMSG3101=WMSG3101E: An error occurred during after-delivery processing. See the linked exception for more information: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This exception is unexpected. The cause is not immediately known.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0015E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ParseException" varFormat="Java">
    ParseException=WMSG0015E: Error parsing JMSListener config file: {0}, message: {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An exception was received while trying to parse the given JMS Listener configuration file.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the problem in the JMS Listener configuration file, then restart the EJB Server.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0053I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CleanedUpDurableSubscription" varFormat="Java">
    CleanedUpDurableSubscription=WMSG0053I: Redundent JMS durable subscription {0} has been unsubscribed
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The durable subscription manager has determined the given subscription is now redundant, perhaps because the application has been removed. The subscription has been unsubscribed.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0334E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PCFCommandServerHostNameNotSpecified" varFormat="Java">
    PCFCommandServerHostNameNotSpecified=WMSG0334E: The Host name that the Queue Manager is running on is required by the WMQQueueDefiner MBean.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The WMQQueueDefiner MBean was not supplied with a host name.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify the name of the host on which the queue manager is running.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0017E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="JNDILookupException" varFormat="Java">
    JNDILookupException=WMSG0017E: Unable to lookup JMS resources, JNDI lookup exception: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An exception was received performing a JNDI lookup of a JMS resource.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the exception for reasons for the problem. This might be because the given JMS resource has not being defined to the WebSphere JNDI namespace, or perhaps because the necessary JMS provider classes are not in the application server class path.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0104I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MQQueueDefinerInvalidBackoutThreshold" varFormat="Java">
    MQQueueDefinerInvalidBackoutThreshold=WMSG0104I: Invalid backout threshold specified. reason = {0}, parameter = {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The backout threshold specified is not in the range 0-999999999
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that the backout threshold attribute contains a valid value.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0062W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MDBDestinationJndiNameError" varFormat="Java">
    MDBDestinationJndiNameError=WMSG0062W: The JNDI specified in the listener port ({1}) is not the same as that specifed in the bindings {2} for MDB {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The JNDI name for the destination in the listener port must match the destination JNDI name in the bindings.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that the JNDI name for the destination is the same in both the listenerPort definition and the message-driven bean bindings.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0042I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MDBListenerStarted" varFormat="Java">
    MDBListenerStarted=WMSG0042I: MDB Listener {0} started successfully for JMSDestination {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The given MDB Listener has started successfully.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG3100E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="BEFORE_DELIVERY_FAILURE_WMSG3100" varFormat="Java">
    BEFORE_DELIVERY_FAILURE_WMSG3100=WMSG3100E: An error occurred during before delivery processing, see linked exception for more information: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This exception is unexpected. The cause is not immediately known.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0312E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PCFCommandServerNotEnoughStorage" varFormat="Java">
    PCFCommandServerNotEnoughStorage=WMSG0312E: There is not enough main storage to perform the action.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    There is not enough space available in main storage to perform the action.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Consult the WebSphere MQ information center to correct the problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0046E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MDBListenerPortNotFound" varFormat="Java">
    MDBListenerPortNotFound=WMSG0046E: Unable to find Listener Port {1} for binding MDB {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The binding of the specified message-driven bean to the specified listener port was unsuccessful because the listener port could not be found.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure the given listener port exists in the Message Listener Service for the given application server.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0039E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MDBPooledThreadException" varFormat="Java">
    MDBPooledThreadException=WMSG0039E: Exception in MDBPooledThread: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    During the processing of a JMS message on a server thread an unexpected exception was received.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the exception for reasons for the problem. After correction restart the MDB EJB JAR module from the administrative console.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0338E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PCFQueueDataQueueNameSet" varFormat="Java">
    PCFQueueDataQueueNameSet=WMSG0338E: The Queue Name was set twice.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A queue name cannot be set twice.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Do not specify the queue name twice.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0101I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MQQueueDefinerInvalidPriority" varFormat="Java">
    MQQueueDefinerInvalidPriority=WMSG0101I: Invalid default priority specified. reason = {0}, parameter = {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The priority specified was not in the range 0-9.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that the priority contains a valid value.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG1303E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="IBM_JMS_NOT_AVAILABLE_WMSG1303" varFormat="Java">
    IBM_JMS_NOT_AVAILABLE_WMSG1303=WMSG1303E: Unable to define JMS Destination {0} as neither WebSphere Embedded Messaging nor WebSphere MQ JMS is available
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    When attempting to define a JMS Destination to WebSphere Embedded Messaging, the required classes could not be found on this node.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Install WebSphere Embedded Messaging or WebSphere MQ JMS on this node.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0117I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MQQueueDefinerClusterNameListTooLong" varFormat="Java">
    MQQueueDefinerClusterNameListTooLong=WMSG0117I: Cluster name list is over 48 characters long. reason = {0}, parameter = {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The cluster name list specified is longer than 48 characters.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that the cluster name list contains less than 48 characters.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG1601I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MESSAGING_NOT_INSTALLED_WMSG1601" varFormat="Java">
    MESSAGING_NOT_INSTALLED_WMSG1601=WMSG1601I: WebSphere MQ JMS has not been installed
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    WebSphere MQ JMS has not been installed on this node so will not be available.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If WebSphere MQ JMS is to be used on this node it must be installed.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG1606E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="NO_WMQ_JCA_RA1_WMSG1606" varFormat="Java">
    NO_WMQ_JCA_RA1_WMSG1606=WMSG1606E: An internal error occurred.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This exception is unexpected. The cause is not immediately known.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0100E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MQQueueDefinerAuthorizationException" varFormat="Java">
    MQQueueDefinerAuthorizationException=WMSG0100E: User is not authorised to access Command Queue
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The user name and password are either not known or do not have the required access privileges.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check that the user name and password are correct.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0308E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PCFCommandServerMessageTooBigForQueue" varFormat="Java">
    PCFCommandServerMessageTooBigForQueue=WMSG0308E: The message was too big for the Queue.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The message was bigger than the maximum message length setting for the queue.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Use WebSphere MQ tooling to increase the maximum message length of the SYSTEM.ADMIN.COMMAND.QUEUE.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0021E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MDBListenerCreateError" varFormat="Java">
    MDBListenerCreateError=WMSG0021E: Exception constructing MDBListenerImpl {0}, JMSDestination {1} : {2}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An exception has occurred during the creation of an MDB Listener.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the exception for reasons for the problem, then restart the EJB Server to re-initialize the JMS Listener.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WMSG0040W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="JMSListenerStartedWithWarnings" varFormat="Java">
    JMSListenerStartedWithWarnings=WMSG0040W: JMS Listener started with warnings
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The JMS Listener service has started, however some warnings were issued during initialization.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the warnings for any problems that might need correcting.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<!-- END MESSAGES -->
</TMSSource>
