<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/css" href="../../resources/stylesheets/wasmsgxml.css"?>
<TMSSource name="TivoliMessages" tmsVersion="1.0" xml:lang="en">
<!-- CMVC MSG File Name = WSERV1/ws/code/policyset/src/com/ibm/ws/policyset/admin/resources/policySetAdmin.nlsprops --> 
<!-- DO NOT EDIT THIS FILE - This file was generated by the XML/Html & Property emitter -->
<!-- BEGIN MESSAGES -->
<Message ID="CWPST0102E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0102E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0102E=CWPST0102E: The {0} zip file contains more than one policy set.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The compressed file contains multiple policy sets. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Import only one policy set from a compressed file. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0138E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0138E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0138E=CWPST0138E: A duplicate {0} file was found in application: {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The control file that has been specified exists. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0073E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0073E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0073E=CWPST0073E: The {0} resource already exists in the attachment.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The resource that has been specified already exists in the attachment. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the resource was specified correctly.  If it is correct, no user action is required. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0181E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0181E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0181E=CWPST0181E: The {0} parameter is not valid when the {1} parameter is set to true.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A policy set name cannot be specified when the service reference is set to inherit the policy set attachment of the service. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Remove the policySet parameter or modify the inheritFromService parameter. Retry the request after making the required change. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0029E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0029E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0029E=CWPST0029E: The {1} parameter cannot be used if the {0} parameter is specified.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The command can only process the policySet parameter or the bindingLocation parameter.  Both parameters cannot be used simultaneously. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a value for the binding location or the policy set name and retry the command. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0101E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0101E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0101E=CWPST0101E: The {0} zip file contains the {1} policyset that exists on this system.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The compressed file contains a policy set that is already defined. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Import a policy set that is not already defined on your system. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0137E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0137E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0137E=CWPST0137E: The {0} control file could not be found for application: {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The application specified did not have a WSPolicy control file. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check the application name and verify it is correct. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0072E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0072E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0072E=CWPST0072E: More than one attachment was found with the following id: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Duplicate attachment IDs were found for the application and attachment type that have been specified. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0180E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0180E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0180E=CWPST0180E: The {0} parameter is only valid when a service reference resource is specified.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified parameter cannot be used unless a service reference resource is specified. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Remove the specified parameter or modify the resource to include a service reference. Retry the request after making the required change. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0028E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0028E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0028E=CWPST0028E: The system could not validate a policy type within a policy set: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The system created an unexpected error and could not access the implementation class for the policy type. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0100E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0100E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0100E=CWPST0100E: The {0} zip file contains directory entries that are not valid.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The compressed file does not contain the expected directory entries. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the compressed file was created with the exportPolicySet or exportBinding command. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0136E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0136E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0136E=CWPST0136E: Either httpGet or wsMex must be specified.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Either httpGet or wsMex must be specified. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Retry the command with either httpGet or wsMex. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0071E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0071E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0071E=CWPST0071E: The attachments were not found.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    No attachments were found for the application and attachment type that have been specified. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the application name and attachment type are specified correctly. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0027E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0027E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0027E=CWPST0027E: The system is unable to initialize the PolicySetManager MBean: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The system created an unexpected error and could not initialize PolicySetManager MBean. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0135E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0135E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0135E=CWPST0135E: The {0} binding cannot be deleted because it is the default binding for the following servers: {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A binding cannot be deleted if it is a default binding. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Change the default binding for the specified servers before attempting to delete the binding. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0070E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0070E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0070E=CWPST0070E: The {0} attachment ID is not found.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The attachment ID that has been specified could not be found. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the application name, attachment ID, and attachment type are specified correctly. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0026E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0026E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0026E=CWPST0026E: The {0} policy set name contains characters that are not valid.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A character in the policy set name is not valid. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify valid characters in the policy set name, including alphanumeric characters or a space, hyphen ( - ), or underscore ( _ ) character. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0134E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0134E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0134E=CWPST0134E: The {0} binding cannot be deleted because it is the default binding for the following domains: {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A binding cannot be deleted if it is a default binding. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Change the default binding for the specified domains before attempting to delete the binding. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0025E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0025E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0025E=CWPST0025E: The following list of policy types are not valid: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The attributes of the policy types that are listed are not valid and must be corrected. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the contents and attributes of the policy types that are listed. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0133E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0133E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0133E=CWPST0133E: The {0} binding cannot be deleted because it is still referenced by attachments for the following applications: {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A binding cannot be deleted if it is referenced by an attachment. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Remove the binding from all attachments before attempting to delete the binding. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0169E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0169E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0169E=CWPST0169E: The system could not find the asset name in the file path.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The asset name could not be determined from the file path for the attachment file. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the asset directory exists and is valid. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0024E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0024E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0024E=CWPST0024E: The {0} output file name does not contain any file separator slashes.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The output file name does not contain any file separator slashes. It must contain at least one. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify at least one file separator slash in the output file name. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0132E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0132E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0132E=CWPST0132E: The default bindings cannot be removed for the global security domain.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The default bindings for provider or client cannot be set to the empty string for the global security domain. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a valid value for the provider or client default binding and retry the command. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0168E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0168E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0168E=CWPST0168E: The policy attachment file is not found for the {0} asset.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The system could not find the policy attachment files for the asset. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the asset name was specified correctly. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0023E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0023E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0023E=CWPST0023E: The {0} output file name is a directory.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The output file name does not specify a file in the directory path. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify an output file name that does not contain a directory name in the last part of the directory path. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0059E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0059E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0059E=CWPST0059E: The following duplicate policy type is found: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A policy type with the name that has been specified already exists. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a new policy type name. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0131E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0131E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0131E=CWPST0131E: The {1} parameter cannot be used if the {0} parameter is specified.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The command can only process the domainName parameter or the bindingLocation parameter.  Both parameters cannot be used simultaneously. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a value for the binding location or the domain name and retry the command. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0167E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0167E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0167E=CWPST0167E: The servicesIndex.xml file could not be located for the {0} asset.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The system could not find the servicesIndex.xml file for the asset name that has been provided. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the asset name is specified correctly to ensure that the correct resources are found. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0022E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0022E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0022E=CWPST0022E: The {0} output file name exists in the configuration.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The output file name exists and could not be overwritten. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a new output file name with a valid directory path. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0058E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0058E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0058E=CWPST0058E: The following duplicate policy set is found: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A policy set with the name that has been specified already exists. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a new policy set name. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0130E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0130E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0130E=CWPST0130E: A duplicate defaultBindings.xml file already exists.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The default bindings file that has been specified already exists. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0166E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0166E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0166E=CWPST0166E: The {1} parameter cannot be used if the {0} parameter is specified.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The command can only process one of the specified parameters.  Both parameters cannot be used simultaneously. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a value for one of the parameters and retry the command. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0021E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0021E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0021E=CWPST0021E: The following policy set directory does not contain any files: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The policy set directory that has been specified does not contain any sub-directories or files. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Create the policy set or verify that the policy set directory contains files and directories. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0057E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0057E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0057E=CWPST0057E: The {0} default policy type is not found.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The default policy type could not be found. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the correct policy type name has been specified. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0165E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0165E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0165E=CWPST0165E: The following resources are already attached to the asset: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Resources cannot be attached to an asset if they are already attached. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify resources that are not attached to this asset. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0020E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0020E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0020E=CWPST0020E: The following directory path does not exist: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The path name that has been specified does not exist. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the path name exists and is spelled correctly. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0056E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0056E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0056E=CWPST0056E: The {0} policy type is not found.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The policy type could not be found. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the correct policy type name has been specified. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0164E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0164E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0164E=CWPST0164E: The {0} composition unit is not found.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The composition unit could not be found. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the correct composition unit name has been specified. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0055E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0055E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0055E=CWPST0055E: The {0} policy set is not found.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The policy set could not be found. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the correct policy set name has been specified. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0163E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0163E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0163E=CWPST0163E: The bindings for the specified application cannot be upgraded because the application is installed on a server at version {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The bindings for the application cannot be upgraded if the application is installed on a server that is not at the latest version. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the application name is correct. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0119E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0119E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0119E=CWPST0119E: The configuration service cannot be initialized.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The configuration service cannot be initialized. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0054E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0054E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0054E=CWPST0054E: The binding reference has been removed from the attachment file, but the binding file could not be found: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The binding reference was removed from the attachment file. The binding file could not be found. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the correct binding name has been specified and that the attachment references a valid binding. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0162E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0162E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0162E=CWPST0162E: The {0} domain name is not valid for the attachment resource.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The domain of the binding is different than the domain of the attachment resource. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a valid value for the domain name and retry the command invocation. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0118E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0118E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0118E=CWPST0118E: The {0} bus is not found.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The bus could not be found. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the correct bus name has been specified. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0053E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0053E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0053E=CWPST0053E: The {0} binding was not found.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The binding could not be found. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the correct binding name has been specified and that the specified attachment references a valid binding. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0089E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0089E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0089E=CWPST0089E: The system created an error because of an unterminated variable reference.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The ending parenthesis or brace could not be found. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the variable definition syntax is correct and delimited by the percentage (%) character. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0161E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0161E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0161E=CWPST0161E: A duplicate bindingDefinition.xml file already exists: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The binding definition file for the binding that has been specified exists for the asset. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the binding name is correct. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0009E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0009E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0009E=CWPST0009E: Multiple cell repository contexts are found.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The cell contains multiple repository contexts. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0117E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0117E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0117E=CWPST0117E: WSN service client attachments are not valid at an endpoint or operation layer.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A policy set attachment for a WSN service client is not valid at an endpoint or operation layer within a web service. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Attach the policy set for a WSN service client at a higher level within the web service. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0052E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0052E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0052E=CWPST0052E: The system could not set the binding attributes for the {0} policy type.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An error was created and the binding attributes for the specified policy type were not set. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check the log file for additional information. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0088E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0088E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0088E=CWPST0088E: The {0} system policy set type was not recognized.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The policy set type is not a known system type. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify the contents of the policy set files. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0160E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0160E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0160E=CWPST0160E: The {0} policy type is not valid for WSMex.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Only WSSecurity and WSAddressing are valid policy types for WSMex. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a policy set with valid policy types and retry the command invocation. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0008E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0008E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0008E=CWPST0008E: The cell repository context cannot be found.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    There is no repository context for the cell. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0116E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0116E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0116E=CWPST0116E: A policy set that contains WSReliableMessaging cannot be attached to an endpoint or operation.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    WSReliableMessaging cannot be attached to an endpoint or operation within a web service. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Either attach the policy set at a higher level, or remove WSReliableMessaging from the policy set and retry the command invocation. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0051E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0051E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0051E=CWPST0051E: A binding was not found for the {0} attachment ID.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The attachment ID that has been specified does not reference a custom binding. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the correct attachment ID is specified. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0087E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0087E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0087E=CWPST0087E: A duplicate system/trust policyAttachments.xml file is found.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The system/trust policy attachment file exists in your configuration. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0007E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0007E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0007E=CWPST0007E: The command created an exception: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The command could not be processed because of an error. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the command name and parameters are valid and spelled correctly. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0115E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0115E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0115E=CWPST0115E: The resource cannot contain a module name if the attachment is for a WSN service client.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    WSN service client attachments cannot contain module names in the resource. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Remove the module name from the resource and retry the command invocation. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0050E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0050E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0050E=CWPST0050E: A policy type name must be specified to remove the server-level binding.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The policy type must be specified to remove a server-level binding. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify the policy type name and retry the command invocation. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0086E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0086E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0086E=CWPST0086E: The {0} binding file is not found for the {1} policy type.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The binding file could not be found. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the correct binding name has been specified. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0194E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0194E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0194E=CWPST0194E: Provider bindings are not supported for the {0} policy type.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The system only supports client bindings for the specified policy type. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the correct policy type is specified, and modify the request to specify the client attachment type. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0006E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0006E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0006E=CWPST0006E: The command could not be validated.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An unexpected exception occurred. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the wrapped exception to determine the cause of the exception. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0114E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0114E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0114E=CWPST0114E: The {0} parameter did not contain valid values.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified parameter must contain valid values. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the parameter contains values accepted by the command. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0085E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0085E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0085E=CWPST0085E: A duplicate bindings.xml file already exists: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The binding configuration file that has been specified exists for the asset. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the binding name is correct. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0193E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0193E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0193E=CWPST0193E: The {0} policy type cannot be added to the {1} policy set because the policy set is attached to an asset that is installed on a server at version {2}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified policy set is attached to an asset that is installed on a server that does not support the specified policy type. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Create a new policy set containing the specified policy type, or detach this policy set from resources deployed on older nodes. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0005E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0005E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0005E=CWPST0005E: The {0} policy set cannot be deleted.  It is attached to the following applications: {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A policy set cannot be deleted if it is attached to an application. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Transfer the attachments for this policy set to another policy set or detach this policy set from all applications. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0113E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0113E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0113E=CWPST0113E: The system could not find the WSN service in the file path.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The WSN service could not be determined from the file path for the attachment file. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the WSN service directory exists and is valid. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0149E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0149E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0149E=CWPST0149E: An error occurred configuring {0} in WebSphere Application Server repository: {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Prior messages detail the cause of this failure.  Typically, the error conditions include wrong server and node names that are specified as module targets during installation. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Read the error messages and rectify the problem. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0084E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0084E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0084E=CWPST0084E: The system created an exception: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The command created an unexpected exception. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the wrapped exception to determine the cause of the problem. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0148W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0148W" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0148W=CWPST0148W: The policyset of {0} is not defined in server. You may need to manually import or define this policyset to make your application work properly.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The policyset found within attachment file of application is not defined on the server yet. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Define the policyset on the server then redeploy the application. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0192E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0192E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0192E=CWPST0192E: An attachment to a policy set that contains the {0} policy type is not supported on an application that is installed on a server at version {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The version of the server where the application is installed does not support the specified policy type. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Select a different policy set for the resource. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0004E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0004E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0004E=CWPST0004E: The {0} default policy set cannot be edited.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The system does not allow you to edit the default policy sets. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0112E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0112E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0112E=CWPST0112E: The following resources are already attached to the WSN service: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Resources cannot be attached to a WSN service if they are already attached. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify resources that are not attached to this WSN service. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0083E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0083E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0083E=CWPST0083E: The required {0} attribute was not found in the {1} policy set.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A required policy set attribute is missing from the policy set file. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the policy set file has not been corrupted.  If the policy set file has been corrupted, you might need to recreate the file. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0191E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0191E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0191E=CWPST0191E: The command cannot complete successfully because the following resource is a service reference that is configured to inherit the policy set attachment of the service: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The command is attempting to modify the policy set attachment of a service reference that is configured to inherit the policy set attachment of the service. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Configure the service reference resource to override the policy set attachment of the service. Retry the request after making the required change. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0003E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0003E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0003E=CWPST0003E: The command created an exception: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The system could not find the command that has been requested. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the command name is valid and spelled correctly. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0039E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0039E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0039E=CWPST0039E: The system could not retrieve the policy set ID. 
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The policy set attachment could not be created.  The system created an error and could not retrieve the policy set ID. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the hard disk is not full and that the application directory exists. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0111E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0111E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0111E=CWPST0111E: The {0} and {1} properties must be specified when the attachment is for a WSN service client.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The bus name and WSN service name must be specified. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a value for the bus name and WSN service name and retry the command invocation. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0147E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0147E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0147E=CWPST0147E: The {0} property does not contain a valid value.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The property value that has been specified is not valid. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a valid value for the property and retry the command invocation. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0082E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0082E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0082E=CWPST0082E: The {0} policy type exists in the policy set.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The policy type exists in the policy set that has been specified. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the policy set name and the policy type name are correct.  If they are correct, then no user action is required. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0190E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0190E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0190E=CWPST0190E: Unable to configure the {0} application because it contains configuration for WSPolicy that requires version {1} or later of the WebSphere Application Server.  The application is installed on a node at version {2}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The application is configured on a node that does not support the requested configuration. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Uninstall the application from the node that does not comply with the required minimum version of the application server, or install the specified minimum version of the application server on the target node. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0002E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0002E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0002E=CWPST0002E: The system created an exception: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An IOException exception occurred. The system could not write to the policy set configuration file. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the hard disk is not full. If you are writing to a new file, verify that directory that has been specified exists. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0038E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0038E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0038E=CWPST0038E: The policy set attachment file could not be created.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The policy set attachment file could not be created in your configuration. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the hard disk is not full and that the application directory exists. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0110E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0110E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0110E=CWPST0110E: The client attachment type is required when {0} and {1} are specified for the {2} parameter.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The bus name and WSN service name can only be specified for the client attachment type. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the value for the attachmentType parameter and retry the command invocation. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0146E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0146E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0146E=CWPST0146E: The application or provider attachment type is required when the systemType property in the {0} parameter is: {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The application or provider attachment type must must be specified when the systemType property is specified. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the value for the attachmentType parameter and retry the command invocation. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0081E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0081E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0081E=CWPST0081E: The {0} policy type is not found.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The policy type could not be found in the policy set. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the policy set name and the policy type name are correct. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0001E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0001E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0001E=CWPST0001E: The system created an exception: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An IOException or a FileNotFoundException exception occurred.  The policy set configuration file was not found or could not be read. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the policy set configuration file exists and is not corrupted. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0037E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0037E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0037E=CWPST0037E: The binding reference was not found for the {0} attachment ID.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The attachment ID that has been specified does not contain a custom binding reference. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the application name, attachment ID, and attachment type were specified correctly. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0145E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0145E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0145E=CWPST0145E: Unable to add nor replace resources when provider policy set is enabled.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Adding multiple resources as well as replacing resources is not valid when provider policy set is enabled. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Disable provider policy set to perform this action. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0080E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0080E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0080E=CWPST0080E: The following file name is not valid: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The policy set file name is not valid. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the policy set name is valid, and check the log file for additional information. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0036E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0036E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0036E=CWPST0036E: The dynamicClient parameter is only allowed when the client attachment type is specified.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The dynamicClient parameter cannot be specified as true unless the attachment type is client. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify the client value for the attachment type with the dynamic client set to true, or set the value for the dynamic client as false. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0144E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0144E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0144E=CWPST0144E: Multiple resources are not valid when provider policy set is enabled.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Multiple resources cannot be specified or used when provider policy set is enabled. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a different resource or disable provider policy set. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0143W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0143W" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0143W=CWPST0143W: The bindingLocation properties of node and server are deprecated.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The ability to get and set bindings by specifying the node and server properties in the bindingLocation parameter is deprecated. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify the bindingName parameter and an empty bindingLocation parameter and retry the command. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0035E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0035E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0035E=CWPST0035E: The {0} attachment type is not valid.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The attachment type that has been specified is not valid. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a valid attachment type. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0179E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0179E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0179E=CWPST0179E: A service and a service reference cannot be specified in the same attachment.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A service and a service reference, or their endpoints or operations, cannot be specified in the same attachment. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a different resource or create separate attachments for the service and service reference resources. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0034E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0034E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0034E=CWPST0034E: The application name is required when attachment type is {0} and the attachmentProperties parameter is not specified.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The application name must be specified. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a value for the application name and retry the command invocation. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0142E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0142E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0142E=CWPST0142E: The imported policy set type of {0} does not match the specified policy set type of {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The imported policy set is not of the same type as verified in the command. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Retry the command specifying a policy set of the correct type. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0178E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0178E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0178E=CWPST0178E: The {0} parameter is only valid when the client attachment type is specified.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified parameter cannot be used unless the attachment type is client. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify the client value for the attachment type or remove the specified parameter and retry the request. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0033E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0033E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0033E=CWPST0033E: The system/trust policy attachment file is not found.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The system/trust policy attachment file could not be found. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the attachment type was specified correctly and that the attachment file exists and is not corrupted. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0069E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0069E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0069E=CWPST0069E: The {0} input parameter is missing or not valid.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A required parameter is null or empty. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify the command syntax and retry the command invocation. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0141E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0141E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0141E=CWPST0141E: The following resource does not contain any WSPolicy settings: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The resource does not contain any WSPolicy settings. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Retry the command specifying a different resource. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0177E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0177E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0177E=CWPST0177E: The {0} parameter must specify the name of a service when the {1} parameter is specified.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The expandResources parameter must specify the name of a service when the serviceRef parameter is specified. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a service name for the expandResources parameter or remove the serviceRef parameter, and retry the command. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0032E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0032E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0032E=CWPST0032E: The client policy attachment file was not found: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The client policy attachment file could not be found for the application that has been specified. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the application name and attachment type were specified correctly. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0068E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0068E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0068E=CWPST0068E: An input parameter that has been specified is not valid.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A required parameter is null or empty. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify the command syntax and retry the command invocation. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0140E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0140E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0140E=CWPST0140E: The following resource must have a policy set attachment before sharing policy: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Policy sharing requires a policy set attachment to share. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    First attach a policy set then retry the command. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0176E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0176E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0176E=CWPST0176E: The {0} policy type is not valid for an HTTP GET request.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The command specifies an HTTP GET request, but the associated policy set does not contain valid policy types. Only HTTP transport and SSL transport are valid policy types for an HTTP GET request. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that the command specifies a policy set with valid policy types. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0031E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0031E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0031E=CWPST0031E: The {0} policy attachment file was not found.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The policy attachment file could not be found for the application that has been specified. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the application name and attachment type were specified correctly. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0067E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0067E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0067E=CWPST0067E: The file name that has been specified is not valid.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The policy set or policy attachment file name is null or empty. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a valid file name. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0175E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0175E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0175E=CWPST0175E: The {0} property requires the {1} property.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A property specified for the command has a prerequisite property, but this property is missing. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Either specify a value for the prerequisite property, or omit the dependent property for this command. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0030E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0030E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0030E=CWPST0030E: The {0} input argument must also be specified with the {1} input argument.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This command requires that both input arguments are specified. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify values for both of the input arguments for this command. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0066E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0066E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0066E=CWPST0066E: Cannot find the bindings.xml file.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The bindings.xml file could not be found. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the correct application name and policy type have been specified. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0174E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0174E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0174E=CWPST0174E: The list of policy types in the {0} policy set file does not match the list of policy type files in the directory.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The list of policy types contained in the policy set file must match the list of existing policy type files. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the policy set, and check the log file for additional information. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0065E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0065E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0065E=CWPST0065E: The {0} default server-level binding file is not found.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The default server-level binding file could not be found. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the correct policy type, node, and server have been specified. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0173E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0173E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0173E=CWPST0173E: The {0} policy set name does not match the name that is found in the policy set file.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The policy set name must match the policy set name contained in the policy set file. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the policy set name, and check the log file for additional information. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0129E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0129E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0129E=CWPST0129E: The {0} compressed file contains the {1} binding that exists on this system.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The compressed file contains a binding that is already defined. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Import a binding that is not already defined on your system. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0064E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0064E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0064E=CWPST0064E: The {0} default cell-level binding file is not found.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The default cell-level binding file could not be found. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the correct policy type has been specified. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0172E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0172E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0172E=CWPST0172E: The {0} policy set contains the following list of policy types that are not valid: {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The attributes of the policy types that are listed are not valid and must be corrected. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the contents and attributes of the policy types that are listed. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0128E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0128E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0128E=CWPST0128E: The {0} compressed file contains more than one binding.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The compressed file contains multiple bindings. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Import only one binding from a compressed file. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0063E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0063E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0063E=CWPST0063E: The {0} binding file is not found.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The binding file could not be found. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the correct binding name has been specified. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0099E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0099E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0099E=CWPST0099E: The {0} zip file contains entries that have no directory path information.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The compressed file specified must contain directory path information. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the compressed file was created with the exportPolicySet command. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0171E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0171E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0171E=CWPST0171E: The {0} binding name contains characters that are not valid.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A character in the binding name is not valid. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify valid characters in the binding name, including alphanumeric characters or a space, hyphen ( - ), or underscore ( _ ) character. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0019E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0019E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0019E=CWPST0019E: The following directory path is not a directory: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The path name that has been specified is not a valid directory path. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the path name is a valid directory structure. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0127E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0127E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0127E=CWPST0127E: The {0} compressed file does not contain a binding.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The compressed file does not contain a binding. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the compressed file was created with the exportBinding command. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0062E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0062E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0062E=CWPST0062E: The {0} application is not found.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The application could not be found. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the correct application name has been specified. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0098E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0098E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0098E=CWPST0098E: The {0} zip file does not contain any files.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The compressed file specified must contain files. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the correct compressed file was specified and that it contains files. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0170E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0170E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0170E=CWPST0170E: The resource cannot contain a module name if the {0} parameter is specified.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Attachments for the specified asset cannot contain module names in the resource. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Remove the module name from the resource and retry the command invocation. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0018E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0018E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0018E=CWPST0018E: Policy set {0} cannot be deleted because it is still attached
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A policy set cannot be deleted if it is attached to a resource. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Transfer the attachments for this policy set to another policy set or detach this policy set from all resources. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0126E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0126E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0126E=CWPST0126E: The following duplicate binding is found: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A binding with the name that has been specified already exists. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a new binding name. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0061E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0061E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0061E=CWPST0061E: The following duplicate clientPolicyAttachments.xml is found: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The client policy attachment file already exists. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0097E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0097E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0097E=CWPST0097E: The {0} application file is not found.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The application file that has been specified could not be found. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the application has been installed correctly. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0017E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0017E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0017E=CWPST0017E: The {0} path name did not contain the {1} string.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The path name might not be valid or might not contain the correct syntax. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the path that has been specified in the message exists on the file system and is readable. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0125E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0125E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0125E=CWPST0125E: The following binding directory does not contain any files: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The binding directory that has been specified does not contain any sub-directories or files. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Create the binding or verify that the binding directory contains files and directories. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0060E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0060E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0060E=CWPST0060E: The following duplicate policyAttachments.xml file is found: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The policy attachment file that has been specified already exists. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0096E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0096E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0096E=CWPST0096E: The {0} server is not found.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The server could not be found. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the correct server name has been specified. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0016E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0016E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0016E=CWPST0016E: The following directory path is not writable: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The command is not allowed to write to the specified directory path. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the directory path has write permission. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0124E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0124E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0124E=CWPST0124E: The {0} binding is not valid for the specified type.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The binding that has been specified does not match the attachment type or the binding type. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a different binding name or a different attachment or binding type. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0095E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0095E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0095E=CWPST0095E: The {0} node is not found.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The node could not be found. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the correct node name has been specified. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0015E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0015E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0015E=CWPST0015E: A resource was specified as empty or null.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A resource must have a valid value. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Replace the empty or null value with a valid resource value. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0123E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0123E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0123E=CWPST0123E: The templates repository context was not found.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The system could not locate the templates repository context. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the templates context exists. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0159E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0159E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0159E=CWPST0159E: The {0} binding type is not valid.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The binding type that has been specified is not a valid value. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a valid value for the binding type for the command invocation. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0094E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0094E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0094E=CWPST0094E: The PolicyTypeProvider class could not be loaded: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified implementation class could not be loaded. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    This is an internal error, but processing continues with the remaining policy type implementation classes. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0014E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0014E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0014E=CWPST0014E: The servicesIndex.xml file could not be located for the {0} application and module.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The system could not find the servicesIndex.xml file for the application name and module name that has been provided. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the application name and module name are specified correctly to ensure that the correct resources are found. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0122E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0122E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0122E=CWPST0122E: Either {0} or {1} must be specified, but not both.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Only one of the parameters can be specified. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Retry the command with the correct parameters. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0158E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0158E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0158E=CWPST0158E: The imported binding type of {0} does not match the specified binding type of {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The imported binding is not of the same type as verified in the command. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Retry the command specifying a binding of the correct type. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0093E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0093E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0093E=CWPST0093E: The variable map cannot be initialized.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The variable map cannot be initialized. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0013E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0013E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0013E=CWPST0013E: The following resources are already attached to the application: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Resources cannot be attached to an application if they are already attached. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify resources that are not attached to this application. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0049E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0049E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0049E=CWPST0049E: The system does not allow the cell-level binding to be removed.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The cell level binding cannot be removed. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0121E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0121E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0121E=CWPST0121E: Unable to find cell name.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The cell name cannot be found. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0157E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0157E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0157E=CWPST0157E: A general binding cannot be assigned to an application with version {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The version of the application does not allow general bindings. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Use a custom binding for the application attachment. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0092E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0092E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0092E=CWPST0092E: The repository cannot be initialized.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The repository cannot be initialized. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0048E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0048E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0048E=CWPST0048E: The application name is required when attachment type is {0} and the binding does not reference a WSN service client or system attachment.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The application name is required with this attachment type. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify an application name and retry the command invocation. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0120E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0120E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0120E=CWPST0120E: Access denied for resource {0}, {1} authority required.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The current user role does not have access to the resource. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Retry the command with a higher level user. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0156E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0156E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0156E=CWPST0156E: The {0} version is not valid for the specified application.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The version that has been specified is not valid. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a valid value for the version and retry the command invocation. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0091E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0091E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0091E=CWPST0091E: The following variable is not defined: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified variable is not defined. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the variables in the variable definition are correct. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0011E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0011E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0011E=CWPST0011E: The following resources are not valid: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The resources that have been specified are not valid web service resources. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the resources are specified correctly and ensure that the resources are valid web service resources. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0047E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0047E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0047E=CWPST0047E: A required property was not found for the bindingLocation parameter.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The bindingLocation parameter is missing a required property. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that you have included the correct bindingLocation properties and that the properties are spelled correctly. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0155E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0155E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0155E=CWPST0155E: Unable to create or assign application specific bindings when provider policy set is enabled.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Provider policy set must be used with general bindings. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Either remove the provider policy set from the attachment, or assign general bindings. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0090E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0090E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0090E=CWPST0090E: The following recursive variable appears: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified variable occurs recursively. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the variables in the variable definition are correct. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0046E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0046E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0046E=CWPST0046E: The bindings for the {0} policy type could not be updated.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The system created an error and could not create or update the binding file. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check the log file for additional information. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0154E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0154E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0154E=CWPST0154E: The security domain of the selected binding does not match the security domain of the attachment resource.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The domain of the binding is different than the domain of the attachment resource. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a different binding for the attachment and retry the command invocation. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0045E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0045E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0045E=CWPST0045E: The binding reference for the {0} attachment ID could not be created.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The system created an error and could not edit the custom binding reference for the attachment. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check the log file for additional error messages. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0153E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0153E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0153E=CWPST0153E: The {0} parameter cannot be specified at application level.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The parameter is not valid at the application level of a Web Service. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a lower level within the Web Service and retry the command invocation. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0189E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0189E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0189E=CWPST0189E: Attributes are not supported for the {0} policy type.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The system does not support attributes for the specified policy type. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the correct policy type is specified, or set the attributes in the binding. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0109E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0109E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0109E=CWPST0109E: The servicesIndex.xml file could not be located for bus: {0} WSN service: {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The system could not find the servicesIndex.xml file for the bus name and WSN service name that has been provided. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the bus name and WSN service name are specified correctly to ensure that the correct resources are found. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0044E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0044E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0044E=CWPST0044E: The attributes could not be set for the {0} policy type.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The system created an error and could not edit the attributes for the policy type. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check the log file for additional information, and verify that the attributes are valid. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0152E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0152E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0152E=CWPST0152E: The {0} domain name is not valid.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The domain name value that has been specified is not valid. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a valid value for the domain name and retry the command invocation. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0188E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0188E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0188E=CWPST0188E: An attachment for a service reference cannot be updated with an application or service attachment.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An attachment for a service reference cannot be replaced with an application or service attachment. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a different resource or create separate attachments for the service and service reference resources. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0108E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0108E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0108E=CWPST0108E: The client policy attachment file is not found for bus: {0} WSN service: {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The system could not find the client policy attachment file for the bus and WSN service. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the bus name and WSN service name were specified correctly. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0043E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0043E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0043E=CWPST0043E: Attributes are required unless you are removing or switching a binding.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    If the bindingName parameter or the remove parameter is not specified, then you must specify a value for the attributes parameter. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a value for either the bindingName or remove parameter, or specify a value for the attributes parameter. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0079E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0079E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0079E=CWPST0079E: The policy type cannot be modified.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The policy type cannot be modified when updating policy type attributes. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the attributes on the command invocation. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0151E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0151E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0151E=CWPST0151E: The {0} attribute cannot be modified.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified attribute cannot be modified. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the attributes on the command invocation. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0187E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0187E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0187E=CWPST0187E: An attachment for an application or service cannot be updated with a service reference attachment.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An attachment for an application or service cannot be replaced with a service reference attachment. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a different resource or create separate attachments for the service and service reference resources. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0107E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0107E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0107E=CWPST0107E: The {0} binding cannot be deleted because it is still referenced by an attachment.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A binding cannot be deleted if it is referenced by an attachment. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Remove the binding from all attachments before attempting to delete the binding. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0042E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0042E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0042E=CWPST0042E: The PolicyTypeProvider class was not found for the {0} policy type.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An implementation class was not found for the policy type that has been specified. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the policy type was specified correctly. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0078E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0078E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0078E=CWPST0078E: The policy set name cannot be modified.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The policy set name cannot be modified when updating a policy set. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the attributes on the command invocation. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0150E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0150E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0150E=CWPST0150E: An error occurred creating the configuration documents in the repository.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An unexpected error occurred when saving the configuration documents of the application to the WebSphere repository during application installation.  This message is preceded by a more detailed message regarding the failure. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Refer to the previous messages in the log file for a failure description. If no messages are displayed, see the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0186E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0186E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0186E=CWPST0186E: The format of the resource is not supported on an application that is installed on a server at version {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The version of the server where the application is installed does not support a resource to be specified in name-value pair format. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the format of the resource, and retry the request. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0106E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0106E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0106E=CWPST0106E: The bindingName and remove parameters are required when you specify the attachment ID as an asterisk (*).
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    If you specify an asterisk (*) for the value of the attachment ID, then you must specify values for the bindingName and remove parameters.  This command deletes the custom binding or removes the policy type from the custom binding specified by the bindingName parameter. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a value for the bindingName parameter and set the remove parameter as true to delete the custom binding.  If you do not want to delete the custom binding or the policy type from the custom binding, specify a different value for the attachment ID. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0041E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0041E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0041E=CWPST0041E: The policy attachment file is not found for the {0} application.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The system could not find the policy attachment files for the application. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the application name was specified correctly. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0077E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0077E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0077E=CWPST0077E: The {0} attribute is not valid.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The attribute that has been specified is not a supported attribute for a policy set. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a supported attribute for the command invocation. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0185E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0185E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0185E=CWPST0185E: A service reference attachment is not supported on an application that is installed on a server at version {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The version of the server where the application is installed does not support service reference attachments. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Attach the policy set to the service client resource. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0105E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0105E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0105E=CWPST0105E: The {0} zip file does not contain a policy set.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The compressed file does not contain a policy set. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the compressed file was created with the exportPolicySet command. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0040E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0040E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0040E=CWPST0040E: The system could not find the application name in the file path.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The application name could not be determined from the file path for the attachment file. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the application directory exists and is valid. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0076E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0076E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0076E=CWPST0076E: The {0} policy set type is not valid.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The policy set type that has been specified is not a valid value. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a valid value for the policy set type for the command invocation. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0184E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0184E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0184E=CWPST0184E: The resources for the {0} attachment cannot be updated since the attachment does not contain a policy set.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A policy set attachment for a service reference with no policy set cannot be updated. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Create a separate attachment for the specified resources. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0104E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0104E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0104E=CWPST0104E: The {0} file name is a directory.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The file name does not specify a file in the directory path. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that a file name is specified in the last section of the directory path. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0075E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0075E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0075E=CWPST0075E: The system cannot write to this read only instance.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The system cannot write to the policy set or policy set attachment because it is read only. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0183E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0183E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0183E=CWPST0183E: An endpoint or an operation is not valid if the {0} parameter is not specified.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A policy set attachment for a service reference is not valid at an endpoint or operation layer when the policy set is not specified. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Modify the resource to specify a service reference, and retry the request. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0103E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0103E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0103E=CWPST0103E: The {0} zip file contains a {1} policy that is not valid on this system.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The compressed file contains a policy which is not defined on this system. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Use the policyType parameter with the addPolicyType command to create the missing policy on this system. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0139E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0139E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0139E=CWPST0139E: Specifying a resource at the endpoint or operation layer is not valid for WSPolicy.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    You can only configure WSPolicy support at the application or service layer within a web service, not at a lower level such as endpoint or operation layer. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify the resource at a higher level within the web service such as application or service layer, and retry the command. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0074E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0074E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0074E=CWPST0074E: The {0} resource was not found in the attachment.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The resource does not exist in the attachment that has been specified. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the resource and the attachment ID were specified correctly. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPST0182E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWPST0182E" varFormat="Java">
    CWPST0182E=CWPST0182E: Only one resource is valid if the {0} parameter is not specified.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Multiple resources cannot be specified when the policy set is not specified. 
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Modify the resources parameter or specify the policySet parameter. Retry the request after making the required change. 
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<!-- END MESSAGES -->
</TMSSource>
