<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/css" href="../../resources/stylesheets/wasmsgxml.css"?>
<TMSSource name="TivoliMessages" tmsVersion="1.0" xml:lang="en">
<!-- CMVC MSG File Name = SIB/ws/code/sib.zwlmclassifier.impl/src/com/ibm/ws/sib/zwlmclassifier/CWSJWMessages.nlsprops, -->
<!-- DO NOT EDIT THIS FILE - This file was generated by the XML/Html & Property emitter -->
<!-- BEGIN MESSAGES -->
<Message ID="CWSJW0002W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PARSER_CLASS_INVOKE_ERROR_CWSJW0002" varFormat="Java">
    PARSER_CLASS_INVOKE_ERROR_CWSJW0002=CWSJW0002W: An exception prevented the retrieval of classification rules from the classification XML parser class {0} and therefore the default transaction class {1} will be applied to all work.  {2}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The classification XML parser class reads an XML document that defines rules for assigning a Workload Management transaction class to various types of work within the Application Server.  An exception occurred when the classification XML parser class was invoked to retrieve the rules.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check the server logs for related errors. For further information on resolving this error, see the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJW0004W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DISCRIMINATOR_SYNTAX_ERROR_CWSJW0004" varFormat="Java">
    DISCRIMINATOR_SYNTAX_ERROR_CWSJW0004=CWSJW0004W: The following WLM classification rule has a syntax error in the discriminator attribute.  The rule will be ignored.  Type={0}, {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The value of the discriminator attribute is not a valid XPath expression.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the rule in the WLM classification XML file and restart the server.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJW0001I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PARSER_CLASS_NOT_FOUND_CWSJW0001" varFormat="Java">
    PARSER_CLASS_NOT_FOUND_CWSJW0001=CWSJW0001I: The classification XML parser class {0} was not found and therefore the default transaction class {1} will be applied to all work.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The classification XML parser class reads an XML document that defines rules for assigning a Workload Management transaction class to various types of work within the Application Server.  The classification XML parser class is not expected to be present on all platforms.  On platforms where it is expected (currently only z/OS) its absence could indicate an error in the installation of the Application Server.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the platform is z/OS, check the installation and server logs for related errors.  If the platform is not z/OS, ignore this message.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJW0005E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="EXCP_DURING_INIT_CWSJW0005" varFormat="Java">
    EXCP_DURING_INIT_CWSJW0005=CWSJW0005E: Creation of the WlmClassifierHandlerFactory object failed with exception: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A problem occurred while creating the WlmClassifierHandlerFactory object.  The accompanying error messages contain information about the problem.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See See the accompanying error messages for more information about the problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJW0003W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SELECTOR_SYNTAX_ERROR_CWSJW0003" varFormat="Java">
    SELECTOR_SYNTAX_ERROR_CWSJW0003=CWSJW0003W: The following WLM classification rule has a syntax error in the selector attribute.  The rule will be ignored.  Type={0}, {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The value of the selector attribute is not a valid message selector according to the JMS 1.1 Specification.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the rule in the WLM classification XML file and restart the server.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSJW9999E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="TEMPORARY_CWSJW9999" varFormat="Java">
    TEMPORARY_CWSJW9999=CWSJW9999E: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    If the message does not give sufficient information, see the accompanying error messages for further information.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    For further information on resolving this error, see the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<!-- END MESSAGES -->
</TMSSource>
