<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/css" href="../../resources/stylesheets/wasmsgxml.css"?>
<TMSSource name="TivoliMessages" tmsVersion="1.0" xml:lang="en">
<!-- CMVC MSG File Name = SERV1/ws/code/dpmanager/src/com/ibm/datapower/dmi/amp/websphereProvider/resources/messages.nlsprops -->
<!-- DO NOT EDIT THIS FILE - This file was generated by the XML/Html & Property emitter -->
<!-- BEGIN MESSAGES -->
<Message ID="CWPOW0560E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="AMPEventChannel.startExOccured" varFormat="Java">
    AMPEventChannel.startExOccured=CWPOW0560E: An exception occurred when the DataPower appliance manager attempted to start the channel chains for the {0} channel.  The DataPower appliance manger cannot start until this exception is resolved.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The DataPower appliance manager attempted to start the channel chain as part of its initialization process.  The DataPower appliance manager cannot receive events from the appliances it manages until the channel chain is started. On z/OS operating systems, it is common to secure ports so that the ports cannot be opened unauthorized users. If the distribution manager process is not running under a user that is authorized to open the port for the DataPower appliance manager, this exception also occurs.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    To use the DataPower appliance manager, ensure that the channel chains which contain the channel, are properly configured and enabled.  The endpoint might be disabled or its port cannot be opened.  After the problem is corrected, restart the DataPower appliance manager.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWPOW0561E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="AMPEventChannel.stopExOccured" varFormat="Java">
    AMPEventChannel.stopExOccured=CWPOW0561E: An exception occurred when the DataPower appliance manager attempted to stop the channel chains for the {0} channel.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The DataPower appliance manager encountered an error when it was shutting down. It will continue its shutdown process.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Look for previous errors in the log that might explain why the error occurred.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<!-- END MESSAGES -->
</TMSSource>
