<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/css" href="../../resources/stylesheets/wasmsgxml.css"?>
<TMSSource name="TivoliMessages" tmsVersion="1.0" xml:lang="en">
<!-- CMVC MSG File Name = ws/code/admin.jmx.thinclient/src/com/ibm/ws/management/resources/nodeutils.nlsprops -->
<!-- DO NOT EDIT THIS FILE - This file was generated by the XML/Html & Property emitter -->
<!-- BEGIN MESSAGES -->
<Message ID="ADMU0514E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0514E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0514E=ADMU0514E: Unsupported JMX Connector: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A Java Management Extensions (JMX) connector type was requested that is not supported.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Request a connector type that is supported.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU3200I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU3200I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU3200I=ADMU3200I: Server launched. Waiting for initialization status.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The server process launched. The product is waiting for initialization status.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0124I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0124I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0124I=ADMU0124I: The system clock of the new node ({0}) is not synchronized with that of the deployment manager ({1}).
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    To add a node, the system clock of the node to be added must be fairly close to that of the deployment manager.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Change the new node system clock to be the same as that of the deployment manager.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU7770I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU7770I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU7770I=ADMU7770I: Generic Server: {0} STARTED successfully.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The generic server started successfully.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU3019E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU3019E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU3019E=ADMU3019E: Exception waiting for server stop {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An exception was issued while the server was in the process of stopping.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the log files for the server to see why the stop function issued an exception.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0015I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0015I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0015I=ADMU0015I: Backing up the original cell repository.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The original configuration files are saved before the utility program changes them.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU8044I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU8044I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU8044I=ADMU8044I: The administrative agent is destroying the administrative subsystem for the deregistered node.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU1502E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU1502E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU1502E=ADMU1502E: If you specify &quot;-serviceUserName&quot; or &quot;-servicePassword&quot; then you must specify both of these as well as &quot;-registerService&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    You must specify &quot;-serviceUserName&quot; and &quot;-servicePassword&quot; together.  You must also specify &quot;-registerService&quot;
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Obtain values for the above and resubmit request.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0123E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0123E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0123E=ADMU0123E: Could not find text for message ID {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified message ID could not be found in the message file.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU2029E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU2029E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU2029E=ADMU2029E: Exception {0} caught in creating EAR Object from {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The enterprise archive (EAR) file could not be obtained from the specified location. The EAR file will not be expanded to the specified destination.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Run the EARExpander tool to expand the EAR file to its appropriate locations.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU1501W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU1501W" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU1501W=ADMU1501W: Exception caught while de-registering node agent as Windows service - please check addNode.log for details
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    There was a problem found while de-registering node agent as Windows service.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check addNode.log for additional information.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0014I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0014I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0014I=ADMU0014I: Adding node {0} configuration to cell: {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Configuration files from the node are being uploaded to the cell repository that the deployment manager manages.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0512I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0512I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0512I=ADMU0512I: Server {0} cannot be reached. It appears to be stopped.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The server cannot be reached and seems to be stopped.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU8043I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU8043I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU8043I=ADMU8043I: The administrative agent is stopping the administrative subsystem for the deregistered node.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0122E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0122E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0122E=ADMU0122E: Exception {0} copying application files from {1} to {2}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Unexpected exception in file copy.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Manually copy files.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU2028E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU2028E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU2028E=ADMU2028E: Exception {0} caught in expanding ear at {1} to {2}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The enterprise archive (EAR) file could not be expanded to the destination.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Run the EARExpander tool to expand the EAR file to its appropriate locations.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU1500W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU1500W" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU1500W=ADMU1500W: Exception caught while registering node agent as Windows service - please check addNode.log for details
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The node agent could not be registered as a Windows service.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check the addNode.log file for additional information.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0403E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0403E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0403E=ADMU0403E: The syncNode command may only be run when the node agent is stopped.  Either stop the node agent or use the administrative console or wsadmin to synchronize the node.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The syncNode command is a recovery tool that performs an offline synchronization operation. To avoid interference, the node agent must be stopped prior to running the syncNode command.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Stop the node agent before running the syncNode command, or use the normal synchronization facility in the administrative console or the NodeSync MBean in wsadmin.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0013I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0013I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0013I=ADMU0013I: A document already exists at the cell level: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified document exists at the cell level.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU8042I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU8042I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU8042I=ADMU8042I: Node has been successfully registered.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The node has been registered with an adminagent.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU3060E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU3060E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU3060E=ADMU3060E: Timed out waiting for server shutdown.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The amount of time taken for server shutdown exceeded the -timeout value requested.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Use a larger value for the -timeout option or perform problem determination on the server to investigate possible errors.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0121E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0121E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0121E=ADMU0121E: Unexpected exception {0} while checking existence of {1} in the target repository.  {1} will not be uploaded.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The check, to determine if the application already exists in the repository to which the node is being added, failed. The application will not be uploaded as a part of the addNode command even if the -includeapps option is specified.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    After the addNode command finishes, install the application using either the administrative console or the wsadmin tool.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU7009E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU7009E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU7009E=ADMU7009E: There is an unexpected exception in expandArchive. The archive file {0} will not be extracted in following paths {1}. Exception: {2}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The disk might be full, or the directory might not have write permission.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Use EARExpander command to extract the archive file.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU2027E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU2027E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU2027E=ADMU2027E: Exception {0} caught in creating varmap for scope {1}, {2}, {3}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The variable map could not be created. Applications might not be restored or deleted from their binary Web address.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Run the EARExpander tool to expand the application enterprise archive (EAR) files to their appropriate locations.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0402I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0402I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0402I=ADMU0402I: The configuration for node {0} has been synchronized with Deployment Manager {1}: {2}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified node was successfully synchronized with the deployment manager.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0012I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0012I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0012I=ADMU0012I: Creating Node Agent configuration for node: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The addNode command created the configuration files for the node agent for the new node.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0510I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0510I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0510I=ADMU0510I: Server {0} is now {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The state of the specified server is given.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU8041I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU8041I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU8041I=ADMU8041I: The administrative agent is starting the administrative subsystem for the registered node.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU4113E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU4113E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU4113E=ADMU4113E: Verify that username and password information is correct.  If running tool from the command line, pass in the correct -username and -password.  Alternatively, update the &lt;conntype&gt;.client.props file.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The tool could not contact the remote server because of a credentials problem.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Pass in the correct user name and password. If you are using a command, pass in -username &amp; -password, or update the soap/sas.client.props file.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0120I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0120I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0120I=ADMU0120I: {0} will not be uploaded since it already exists in the target repository.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    File already exists.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU7008E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU7008E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU7008E=ADMU7008E: Unexpected exception in expandEar. The ear file {0} will not be extracted in following paths {1}. Exception: {2}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The disk might be full, or the directory might not have write permission.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Use EARExpander command to extract the enterprise archive (EAR) file.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU2026E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU2026E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU2026E=ADMU2026E: Node {0} is not incorporated into any cell.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An attempt was made to remove a node that has never been added in the first place.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Run the addNode command before attempting to run the removeNode command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0401I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0401I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0401I=ADMU0401I: Begin syncNode operation for node {0} with Deployment Manager {1}: {2}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified node is being synchronized with the deployment manager.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU2025W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU2025W" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU2025W=ADMU2025W: Removal of node {0} is complete, but there were errors.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This node was removed from the cell, but problems occurred during the removal.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the previous errors to determine what occurred. You might need to run the cleanupNode utility to remove this node from the deployment manager configuration.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0011E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0011E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0011E=ADMU0011E: Error creating configuration in the cell repository {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Configuration files for the new node could not be uploaded to the deployment manager for creation in the cell repository.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that the deployment manager is running and that the FileTransfer application is running in the deployment manager. Record the exception information from this message for further problem determination. If the Java(TM) virtual machine (JVM) OutOfMemoryError error is in the stack trace in the addNode.log file, the heap size for the addNode command or the deployment manager might need to be increased. For the addNode command, add the -Xmx(size) parameter to the addNode command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU4112I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU4112I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU4112I=ADMU4112I: Error details may be seen in the file: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This is an informational message indicating where to look for further information.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Look in the file for more information.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU8040I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU8040I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU8040I=ADMU8040I: The administrative agent is initializing the administrative subsystem for the registered node.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU3014W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU3014W" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU3014W=ADMU3014W: Server recovery complete, problems occurred during recovery. Server log files should contain failure information.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The server had problems during recovery and has stopped.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the log files to see what failure messages were recorded there.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU8076E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU8076E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU8076E=ADMU8076E: The node was not removed from the cell configuration because the node has a different product version than the local node
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The difference in node product versions likely resulted from attempting to remove an old node that was migrated to a higher product level, while the migrated deployment manager is running.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Stop the migrated deployment manager and try removing the node again
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU8075W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU8075W" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU8075W=ADMU8075W: Application {0} is not imported because conflicting object {1} already exists.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Cannot import application because business-level application or composition unit already exists.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU7006W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU7006W" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU7006W=ADMU7006W: The cell name contained in the backup file is not the same as the current cell name of your configuration which is &quot;{0}&quot;.  Since you specified the &quot;-force&quot; option, the backup file will be restored but you will need to manually correct the resulting problems.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This backup file was created from a system with a different cell name.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    After the restore operation has completed, correct any resulting problems and confirm proper system function before starting production applications.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0010E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0010E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0010E=ADMU0010E: Error obtaining repository client {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A client connection for the Cell configuration repository could not be obtained.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Record the exception information from this message for further problem determination.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU4111E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU4111E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU4111E=ADMU4111E: Program exiting with error: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An error occurred during program execution.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Perform problem determination to investigate possible causes.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU2024I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU2024I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU2024I=ADMU2024I: Removal of node {0} is complete.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified node has been successfully removed.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU3013I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU3013I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU3013I=ADMU3013I: Server recovery complete.  Server stopped.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The server has completed recovery and has stopped.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU8074E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU8074E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU8074E=ADMU8074E: The administrative agent port number specified for {0} connector is invalid, deregisterNode cannot continue.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Failed to deregister the node because the port number specified is invalid.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check your administrative agent serverindex.xml and find the correct port number of the connector.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU3402E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU3402E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU3402E=ADMU3402E: Server name not specified; must supply the name of a server.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This tool requires that a server name be provided.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a server name.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU7005E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU7005E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU7005E=ADMU7005E: The cell name contained in the backup file is not the same as the current cell name of your configuration which is &quot;{0}&quot;.  You may ignore this condition by specifying &quot;-force&quot; as a command line option.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This backup file was created from a system with a different cell name.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Either use the &quot;-force&quot; option on the restoreConfig command and manually correct the problems, or restore the cell using a backup file that used the same cell name as the current system.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU2023E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU2023E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU2023E=ADMU2023E: Exception removing servers from clusters {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A problem occurred attempting to remove the servers from the clusters.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the exception to determine the specific problem. To force the node to be removed, specify the -force option.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU3012E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU3012E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU3012E=ADMU3012E: Exception attempting to get free port for status socket {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A free port could not be allocated to communicate server status.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the log file for the utility to perform further problem determination. Attempt to run the utility again.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0044E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0044E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0044E=ADMU0044E: It is not valid to run syncNode on the same node as the Deployment Manager: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The syncNode program only applies to app server nodes, not the ND deployment manager node itself.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Do not attempt to run syncNode on the Deployment Manager node itself.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU8073E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU8073E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU8073E=ADMU8073E: Application Server nodes with profilePath {0} failed to deregister from the administrative agent.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    One or more Application Server nodes failed to deregister.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Review the associated error in deregisterNode.log or turn on trace to diagnose the problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU3401I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU3401I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU3401I=ADMU3401I: Server stop request issued. No stop status requested.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A stop server request was issued without a stop status request.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU2022I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU2022I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU2022I=ADMU2022I: Removing cluster member {0} from cluster {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified cluster member is being removed from the specified cluster.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU7004E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU7004E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU7004E=ADMU7004E: Unexpected exception while building cache entry for {0} and {1}.  Exception is: {2}. All the related binaries may not be deleted/updated.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The exception message may detail probable cause.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If an application ear file is not expanded to the destination specified during installation then use EARExpander tool to expand the ear.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU3011E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU3011E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU3011E=ADMU3011E: Server launched but failed initialization. Server logs, startServer.log, and other log files under {0} should contain failure information.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The server process failed to start.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the log files to see what failure messages were recorded there.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU8029E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU8029E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU8029E=ADMU8029E: Error running deregisterNode on non supported environment.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An attempt was made, using the deregisterNode operation, to remove a profile from the registry in an unsupported environment. A node can be deregistered only when it runs on the same machine as the administrative agent. The administrative agent is the AdminAgent MBean.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Remove a node from the registry when the node is located on the same machine as the administrative agent.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU4000I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU4000I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU4000I=ADMU4000I: Server {0} stop completed.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The stopServer command completed successfully.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0043E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0043E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0043E=ADMU0043E: Error trying to federate a node that is still registered to an AdminAgent.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The node you are trying to federate still registered to an AdminAgent.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    You need to unregister the node from an AdminAgent before being able to federate to DeploymentManager.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU8072E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU8072E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU8072E=ADMU8072E: Application Server nodes with profilePath {0} failed to register with the administrative agent.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    One or more Application Server nodes failed to register.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Review the associated error in registerNode.log or turn on trace to diagnose the problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU3400I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU3400I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU3400I=ADMU3400I: Server launched. No initialization status. Process id is: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The -nowait option was used for the startServer command, so no initialization status is available for the launched process.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU2021I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU2021I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU2021I=ADMU2021I: Removing all servers on this node from all clusters in the cell.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This is an informational message marking the progress of the program.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU8028E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU8028E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU8028E=ADMU8028E: An error occurred during node deregistration; rolling back to original configuration.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The node could not be removed from the registry. The configuration is rolled back to the original configuration.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Review the associated messages in deregisterNode.log to determine the specific problem and retry the deregisterNode command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0042E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0042E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0042E=ADMU0042E: The addNode/removeNode operation lock could not be released at the Deployment Manager.  You may need to invoke AdminOperations.forceNodeFederationOrRemovalTokenReset operation to manually complete this final step of addNode or removeNode.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The lock used to prevent concurrent addNode and removeNode operations could not be reset.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If you can not run an addNode or removeNode operation after receiving this message, you can clear the lock by invoking the AdminOperations.forceNodeFederationOrRemovalTokenReset operation.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU8071I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU8071I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU8071I=ADMU8071I: All Application Server nodes have been successfully deregistered.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Deregistration of all specified nodes successfully completed.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU2020E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU2020E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU2020E=ADMU2020E: Exception removing applications {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A problem occurred attempting to remove the applications from this node.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the exception to determine the specific problem. To force the node to be removed, specify the -force option.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU7709E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU7709E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU7709E=ADMU7709E: Unexpected exception while processing server: {0}; exception = {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An unexpected exception has been detected.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the product installation is correct.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU8027E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU8027E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU8027E=ADMU8027E: An error occurred when invoking destroyProfile operation on AdminAgent mbean; rolling back to original configuration.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The profile could not be deleted. The destroyProfile operation on the AdminAgent MBean failed. The configuration is rolled back to the original configuration.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Review the associated error in deregisterNode.log or turn on trace to diagnose the problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0041E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0041E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0041E=ADMU0041E: Another addNode or removeNode operation is currently in progress. Please attempt this operation later.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Concurrent addNode and removeNode operations are not allowed.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Wait until the first addNode or removeNode operation completes, and then retry this operation.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU8070I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU8070I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU8070I=ADMU8070I: All Application Server nodes have been successfully registered.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Registration of all specified nodes successfully completed.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU6012I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU6012I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU6012I=ADMU6012I: Exception in run {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    NONE
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU7708E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU7708E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU7708E=ADMU7708E: Failed while trying to determine the Windows Service log file name for server: {0}; 
probable error executing WASService.exe: {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The log file for the Windows service associated with this server could not be found.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the product installation is correct.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU8026E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU8026E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU8026E=ADMU8026E: An error occurred when invoking stopProfile operation on AdminAgent mbean; rolling back to original configuration.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The profile could not be stopped. The stopProfile operation on AdminAgent MBean failed. The configuration is rolled back to the original configuration.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Review the associated error in deregisterNode.log or turn on trace to diagnose the problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0040E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0040E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0040E=ADMU0040E: Exception on MBean invocation {0} {1} {2}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An MBean call failed.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Record and save the exception information from this message for further problem determination.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU7707E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU7707E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU7707E=ADMU7707E: Failed while trying to determine the Windows Service name for server: {0}; 
probable error executing WASService.exe: {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Windows service associated with this server could not be found.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that a Windows service associated with the specified server exists.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU8025E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU8025E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU8025E=ADMU8025E: An error occurred when calling deregisterWithAdminAgent command; rolling back to original configuration.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Failed running deregisterWithAdminAgent command.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Review the associated error in deregisterNode.log or turn on trace to diagnose the problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU7750E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU7750E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU7750E=ADMU7750E: The {0} command has failed because another process has temporarily requested exclusive access to {1}.  Please wait a few minutes and try again.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Another command is running and might conflict with this one.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Wait a few minutes and try the command again.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0183E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0183E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0183E=ADMU0183E: Duplicate Entry Exception: An exception occurred while checking existence of node agent short name {0} in the Deployment Manager cell. The node agent short name already exists in the distributed cell.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The node agent short name already exists in the distributed cell to which this node is being added.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that the node agent short name is unique across all the nodes in the distributed cell before running the addNode command. Make the node agent short name unique in the deployment manager cell. Then run the addNode command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0529E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0529E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0529E=ADMU0529E: Unexpected exception {0} thrown while restoring application binaries from the base configuration.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    When the removeNode command runs, the applications from the original configuration are put back in place. Something caused the command to fail. Manual recovery is necessary.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Use the EARExpander command to expand the application enterprise archive (EAR) file to the location specified on the binariesURL attribute. The attribute is in the corresponding deployment.xml configuration file.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU7706E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU7706E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU7706E=ADMU7706E: Failed while trying to deregister the Windows Service {0}; 
probable error executing WASService.exe: {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Windows service associated with this server could not be removed from the registry.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the error message and make correction accordingly.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU8024E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU8024E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU8024E=ADMU8024E: An error occurred when invoking startProfile operation on AdminAgent mbean; rolling back to original configuration.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The profile failed to start. The startProfile operation on the  AdminAgent MBean failed. The configuration is rolled back to the original configuration.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Review the associated error in registerProfile.log or turn on trace to diagnose the problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0211I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0211I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0211I=ADMU0211I: Error details may be seen in the file: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This is an informational message indicating that additional information is available in the log file.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Look in the file for additional information.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0182E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0182E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0182E=ADMU0182E: Duplicate Entry Exception: An exception occurred while checking existence of node short name {0} in the Deployment Manager cell. The node short name already exists in the distributed cell.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The node short name already exists in the distributed cell to which this node is being added.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that the node short name is unique across all the nodes in the distributed cell before running the addNode command. Make the node short name unique in the deployment manager cell. Then run the addNode command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0528I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0528I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0528I=ADMU0528I: Details of Queue Manager deletion may be seen in the file: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    You can see the details of the deletion of the queue manager in the specified file.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Look in the file for more information.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU7705E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU7705E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU7705E=ADMU7705E: Failed while trying to stop the Windows Service associated with server: {0}; 
probable error executing WASService.exe: {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Windows Service associated with this server failed to stop.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check return code and correct the problem then retry the operation.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU8023E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU8023E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU8023E=ADMU8023E: An error occurred when invoking initializeProfile operation on AdminAgent mbean; rolling back to original configuration.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The profile failed to initialize. The initializeProfile operation on the AdminAgent MBean failed. The configuration is rolled back to the original configuration.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Review the associated error in registerProfile.log or turn on trace to diagnose the problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU8059E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU8059E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU8059E=ADMU8059E: An error occurred when trying to get the managed node name.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An error occurred when trying to get the managed node name.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Review the associated error in registerNode.log or turn on trace to diagnose the problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0181E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0181E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0181E=ADMU0181E: Duplicate Entry Exception: An exception occurred while checking existence of cluster transition name {0}, node {1} in the Deployment Manager cell. The cluster transition name already exists in the distributed cell.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The cluster transition name already exists in the distributed cell to which this node is being added.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that the cluster transition name is unique across all the servers in the distributed cell before running the addNode command. Make the cluster transition name unique in the deployment manager cell. Then run the addNode command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0527I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0527I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0527I=ADMU0527I: WebSphere Embedded Messaging support not installed; Queue Manager not deleted from server {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Embedded messaging support is not installed. The queue manager cannot be deleted from the specified server.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0029E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0029E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0029E=ADMU0029E: An error occurred during node removal: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The node could not be removed.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the exception to determine the specific problem and take corrective action.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU7704E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU7704E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU7704E=ADMU7704E: Failed while trying to start the Windows Service associated with server: {0}; 
probable error executing WASService.exe: {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Windows service associated with this server failed to start.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check the return code and correct the problem. Then retry the operation.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU8022E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU8022E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU8022E=ADMU8022E: An error occurred when calling registerWithAdminAgent command; rolling back to original configuration.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Failed running registerWithAdminAgent command of the profile to be registered.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Review the associated error in registerNode.log or turn on trace to diagnose the problem and look for trace information in the trace log.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU3040E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU3040E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU3040E=ADMU3040E: Timed out waiting for server initialization: {0} seconds
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The server initialization process has exceeded the timeout limit.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Perform problem determination on the server to check for possible errors.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU8058E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU8058E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU8058E=ADMU8058E: An error occurred when trying to set the admin preferred authorization mechanism to {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An error occurred when trying to set the admin preferred authorization mechanism
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Review the associated error in registerNode.log or turn on trace to diagnose the problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0180E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0180E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0180E=ADMU0180E: Duplicate Entry Exception: An exception occurred while checking existence of server short name {0}, node {1} in the Deployment Manager cell. The server short name already exists in the distributed cell.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The server short name already exists in the distributed cell to which this node is being added.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that the short name is unique across all the servers in the distributed cell before running the addNode command. Make the server short name in the deployment manager cell unique. Then run the addNode command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0028I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0028I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0028I=ADMU0028I: Log generated.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A log was generated.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0526I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0526I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0526I=ADMU0526I: Deleting Queue Manager for node {0} on server {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The queue manager is being deleted on the specified node and the specified server.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU7703I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU7703I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU7703I=ADMU7703I: The Windows Service {0} associated with {1} is now being deregistered.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    When a server is removed, the corresponding Windows service is removed from the registry.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU8021I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU8021I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU8021I=ADMU8021I: Backing up the original config directory of the profile to be deregistered.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The original configuration files for the profile are being saved before they are removed from the registry.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU8057E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU8057E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU8057E=ADMU8057E: An error occurred during node deregistration; rolling back to original configuration.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    If an error occurs during the deregisterNode command process and it cannot complete, an attempt is made to restore the configuration to its original state, though this might also fail to complete.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Review the associated messages in the deregisterNode.log file to determine the specific problem. Retry the deregisterNode.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0071E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0071E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0071E=ADMU0071E: Exception occurred during security authentication.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An exception occurred during the password encryption/decryption.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify the user name and password are correct and retry the operation.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0525I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0525I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0525I=ADMU0525I: Details of Queue Manager creation may be seen in the file: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The details of the queue manager creation cannot be seen in the specified file.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Look in the file for more information on the queue manager creation.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU7702I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU7702I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU7702I=ADMU7702I: Because {0} is registered to run as a Windows Service, the request to stop this server will be completed by stopping the associated Windows Service.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    When a server is registered to run as a Windows Service, the Windows Service is used to stop the server.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0070W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0070W" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0070W=ADMU0070W: Retrieving signer certificates from dmgr failed - this may cause node federation to fail.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The signer certificates could not be retrieved from the deployment manager. The user name, password, or both might be incorrect.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the user name and password are correct. Alternatively, use the retrieveSigners script to download the signer certificates from the deployment manager.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0027E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0027E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0027E=ADMU0027E: An error occurred during federation {0}; rolling back to original configuration.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    If the addNode process cannot complete, an attempt is made to restore the configuration to its original state. However, the restoration might also fail to complete.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Review the associated messages in the addNode.log file to determine the specific problem, and retry the addNode command. You might need to run the cleanupNode command before retrying the addNode command, if the rollback did not complete as expected.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU8020E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU8020E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU8020E=ADMU8020E: Error running registerNode on non supported environment.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The node could not be registered using the registerNode because no connection was made to the administrative agent during node registration. The administrative agent is the AdminAgent MBean.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that a connection is made to the correct port of the administrative agent.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU8056E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU8056E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU8056E=ADMU8056E: Error removing the managed node from an adminagent.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An error occurred during managed node removal from an adminagent.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Review the associated error or turn on trace to diagnose the problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0308I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0308I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0308I=ADMU0308I: The node {0} and associated applications were successfully added to the {1} cell.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified node and its associated applications were successfully added to the specified cell.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0026I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0026I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0026I=ADMU0026I: An error occurred during federation; rolling back to original configuration.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    If the addNode process cannot complete, an attempt is made to restore the configuration to its original state. However, the restoration might also fail to complete.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Review the associated messages in the addNode.log file to determine the specific problem, and retry the addNode command. You might need to run the cleanupNode command before retrying the addNode command, if the rollback did not complete as expected.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU5506I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU5506I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU5506I=ADMU5506I: {0} files successfully restored
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified number of files were successfully restored.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0524I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0524I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0524I=ADMU0524I: WebSphere Embedded Messaging support not installed; Queue Manager not created
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Embedded messaging was not installed. The queue manager was not created.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU7701I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU7701I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU7701I=ADMU7701I: Because {0} is registered to run as a Windows Service, the request to start this server will be completed by starting the associated Windows Service.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    When a server is registered to run as a Windows Service, the Windows Service is used to start the server.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU8055E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU8055E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU8055E=ADMU8055E: An error occurred when trying to create the managed node.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An error occurred when trying to create managed node.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Review the associated error in registerNode.log or turn on trace to diagnose the problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0307I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0307I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0307I=ADMU0307I: You might want to:
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message suggests that you do the actions associated with the messages that immediately follow this message.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU2004E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU2004E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU2004E=ADMU2004E: An exception occurred
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An exception occurred.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Record the exception data and perform further problem determination.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU3029I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU3029I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU3029I=ADMU3029I: Conflict detected on port {0} for endpoint {2} of the server {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The port for the specified endpoint of this server is already in use by this or another server.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Do not attempt to use a port that is already in use.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU3101I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU3101I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU3101I=ADMU3101I: Using explicit host and port {0}:{1} for server: {2}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified hot and the specified port were used.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU4018E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU4018E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU4018E=ADMU4018E: &quot;-script&quot; option is not supported on zOS platform.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An error occurred when the program ran.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Remove the &quot;-script&quot; option and rerun the command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU5505I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU5505I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU5505I=ADMU5505I: Restoring file {0} to location {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified file is being restored to the specified location.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0523I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0523I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0523I=ADMU0523I: Creating Queue Manager for node {0} on server {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The queue manager is being created for the specified node on the specified server.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0025E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0025E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0025E=ADMU0025E: Given host and port do not point to a Deployment Manager.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The connected process does not have a DeploymentManager MBean. The most common cause is that the specified host or port is not for the deployment manager.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the host and port passed to the tool are correct.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU8054E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU8054E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU8054E=ADMU8054E: Failed to create managed node with name {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The node name being used to create a new managed node already exist.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    The node name being used to create a new managed node already exist. Specify different name.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0306I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0306I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0306I=ADMU0306I: Note:
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message indicates that at least one message immediately follows this message and that you should read any messages that immediately follow this one.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU2003E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU2003E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU2003E=ADMU2003E: No setupCmdLine file found to modify: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The file was not located.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check that a setupCmdLine file exists in the installation.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU3028I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU3028I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU3028I=ADMU3028I: Conflict detected on port {0}.  Likely causes: a) An instance of the server {1} is already running  b) some other process is using port {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A port required by this server is already in use by this or another server.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Do not attempt use a port that is already in use.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU3100I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU3100I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU3100I=ADMU3100I: Reading configuration for server: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The server configuration is being read.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0024I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0024I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0024I=ADMU0024I: Deleting the old backup directory.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The original configuration files are saved before they the utility program changes them.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU5504I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU5504I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU5504I=ADMU5504I: Restore location successfully renamed
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified location has been renamed.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU8053I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU8053I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU8053I=ADMU8053I: Successfully connected to AdminAgent Server: {0}:{1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This is an informational message indicating that the program has established communications with the AdminAgent.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0522E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0522E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0522E=ADMU0522E: No server by this name in the configuration: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    No server was located in the configuration repository by the specified name.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check the spelling of the server name. Check the integrity of the configuration files.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0305I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0305I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0305I=ADMU0305I: Install applications onto the {0} cell using wsadmin $AdminApp or the Administrative Console.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    None
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU8009I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU8009I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU8009I=ADMU8009I: Begin deregistration of Application Server with path {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The node will be deregistered with an adminagent.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU3027E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU3027E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU3027E=ADMU3027E: An instance of the server may already be running: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An attempt has been made to start a server that is already running.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Do not attempt to start a server that is already running.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU2037W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU2037W" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU2037W=ADMU2037W: The {0} node host name that the product is federating does not match the {1} deployment manager host name. The local operating system registry is usually only supported when the cell is configured on a single machine.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The host names for the deployment manager and for the node being federated do not match. This mismatch might be an indication of an unsupported configuration. The local operating system registry will not work across multiple machines, except in special cases. These special cases include having a cell reside exclusively on the z/OS operating system, or be part of a Microsoft Windows domain controller.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the node being federated is the intended node, and that the active user registry is supported. For more information, refer to the information center documentation on the supported configurations that can be used with the local operating system registry. If the registry is not supported, change the active user registry to a registry that is supported either through the administrative console or scripting.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0059I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0059I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0059I=ADMU0059I: Adding node {0} to node group {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The configuration files for the node are being uploaded to the cell repository that the deployment manager manages because the specified node is being added to the specified node group.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0023E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0023E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0023E=ADMU0023E: Exception waiting for server initialization {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An IOException was issued while the program was waiting for input on the server status port.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Record and save the exception information from this message for further problem determination. Examine the log file for the utility and rerun the program with the -trace option.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU8052I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU8052I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU8052I=ADMU8052I: Removing signers exchanged during node registration.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Removing security signers that were exchanged during node registration.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU5503E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU5503E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU5503E=ADMU5503E: The restore location could not be renamed - another process may be using this subdirectory
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The location of the restored configuration could not be renamed.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Use the -location option on the restoreConfig command to specify a location which does not exist, or which can be renamed.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0521E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0521E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0521E=ADMU0521E: 
No node named &quot;{0}&quot; is found in this cell.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    No node was located in the configuration repository with the specified name.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check the spelling of the node name. Check the integrity of the configuration files.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU2001I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU2001I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU2001I=ADMU2001I: Begin removal of node: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Removal of the node has started.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0304I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0304I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0304I=ADMU0304I: Because -includeapps was not specified, applications installed on the standalone node were not installed on the new cell.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Because the -includeapps option of the addNode command was not specified, applications installed on the stand-alone node were not installed on the new cell.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU8008I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU8008I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU8008I=ADMU8008I: Restoring all original pre-registered files of the profile after deregistration.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The original configuration files are being restored after the profile was removed from the registry.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0022I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0022I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0022I=ADMU0022I: Node Agent launched. Waiting for initialization status.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The node agent launched and is waiting for initialization status.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0058I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0058I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0058I=ADMU0058I: Removing node {0} from all node groups.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The configuration files for the node are being uploaded to the cell repository that the deployment manager manages because the specified node is being removed from all the node groups.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU5502I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU5502I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU5502I=ADMU5502I: The directory {0} already exists; renaming to {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified directory for the restored configuration already exists and is being renamed to the specified directory.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU8051I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU8051I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU8051I=ADMU8051I: Removed signers successfully.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Removed security signers that were exchanged during node registration successfully.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU4123E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU4123E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU4123E=ADMU4123E: Ensure that the Deployment Manager is running on the specified host and port.  Also ensure that the security configuration in ssl.client.props on the node is compatible with the Deployment Manager.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A connection could not be made to the deployment manager.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that the deployment manager is running. Ensure that the proper host name and port are used when attempting to connect to the process.  Also ensure that the security configuration in ssl.client.props on the node is compatible with the Deployment Manager.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU2036I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU2036I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU2036I=ADMU2036I: To continue removal of this node manually, you may use manageprofiles utility to delete the profile for this node and run cleanupNode utility on Deployment Manager.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The node can be removed manually if error messages or warning messages resulted from running the removeNode command.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Use the manageprofiles command to delete the profile for this node. Run the cleanupNode command on the deployment manager.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0303I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0303I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0303I=ADMU0303I: Update the configuration on the {0} Deployment Manager with values from the old cell-level documents.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The configuration on the specified deployment manager was updated.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0057W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0057W" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0057W=ADMU0057W: {0} WARNING(S) occurred while removing node {1} from all node groups. {2}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    One or more warnings occurred while removing the node from all the node groups.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required..
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU8007I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU8007I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU8007I=ADMU8007I: Exchanged signers successfully.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Exchanged security signers successfully.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU2035W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU2035W" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU2035W=ADMU2035W: WARNING! Node removal utility is unable to remove this node since it was created during Cell Profile creation.  Your current node has not been modified.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The removeNode tool could not remove the node because the node was created during cell profile creation.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Use the manageprofiles command to delete the node. Run the cleanupNode command on the deployment manager.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0021E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0021E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0021E=ADMU0021E: Error occurred stopping server {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An attempt was made to stop the specified server, but the server did not stop.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the log files for the server to see why the server is not stopped.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU5501E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU5501E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU5501E=ADMU5501E: The backup file specified {0} does not exist.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The file specified containing the backed up configuration documents cannot be found.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the file given to the restoreConfig command exists and can be read.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU4122E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU4122E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU4122E=ADMU4122E: The specified server may not be running, or no appropriate username and password are provided if the specified server runs in secure mode
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A connection to the server could not be established.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that the targeted process is running. Ensure that the proper user name and password are used when attempting to connect to the process in secure mode.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU8050E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU8050E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU8050E=ADMU8050E: An error occurred during signers removal.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An error occurred when adminagent tried to remove signers that were exchanged during node registration.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Review the associated error in deregsiterNode.log or turn on trace to diagnose the problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0302I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0302I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0302I=ADMU0302I: Any cell-level documents from the standalone {0} configuration have not been migrated to the new cell.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    None
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0056W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0056W" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0056W=ADMU0056W: {0} WARNING(S) occurred while adding node {1} to node group {2}. {3}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    One or more warnings occurred while adding the node to the node group.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required..
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU8006E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU8006E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU8006E=ADMU8006E: An error occurred when calling deregisterNode command.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The profile could not be removed from the registry.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Review the associated error in deregisterNode.log or turn on trace to diagnose the problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU3522E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU3522E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU3522E=ADMU3522E: No server by this name in the configuration: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified server name cannot be located within the configuration for this node.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check that the specified name is spelled correctly and that a directory by that name does exist under the servers directory in the configuration.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU5002I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU5002I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU5002I=ADMU5002I: {0} files successfully backed up
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified number of files were backed up.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0020I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0020I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0020I=ADMU0020I: Reading configuration for Node Agent process: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The configuration for the specified node agent process is being read.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU2034I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU2034I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU2034I=ADMU2034I: Use wsadmin or the Administrative Console to uninstall any such buses from the Deployment Manager.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    You can use the wsadmin tool or the administrative console to uninstall any buses from the deployment manager.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0055W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0055W" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0055W=ADMU0055W: {0} WARNING(S) occurred while converting node group {2} to sysplex node group for node {1}. {3}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    One or more warnings occurred while converting the node group to a sysplex node group.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required..  ADMU0060W is issued for each warning message encountered.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU8005I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU8005I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU8005I=ADMU8005I: Admin preferred authorization mechanism is set to {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Security admin preferred authorization mechanism is set to RSAToken.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU5001I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU5001I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU5001I=ADMU5001I: Backing up config directory {0} to file {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified configuration directory is being backed up to the specified file.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU2033I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU2033I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU2033I=ADMU2033I: Any buses that were uploaded to the {0} cell configuration during addNode using the -includebuses option are not uninstalled by removeNode.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    If the addNode command, with the -includebuses option specified, previously uploaded any buses to the specified cell, the removeNode command did not uninstall any of those buses.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0300I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0300I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0300I=ADMU0300I: The node {0} was successfully added to the {1} cell.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified node was successfully added to the specified cell.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0509I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0509I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0509I=ADMU0509I: The {0} &quot;{1}&quot; cannot be reached. It appears to be stopped.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The server cannot be reached and seems to be stopped.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0054W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0054W" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0054W=ADMU0054W: {0} WARNING(S) occurred while checking if node {1} can join node group {2}. {3}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    One or more warnings occurred while checking whether the node can join the node group.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required..
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU8004I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU8004I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU8004I=ADMU8004I: Backing up the original config directory of the node to be registered.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The original configuration files are being saved before the utility program changes them.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0119E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0119E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0119E=ADMU0119E: Unexpected exception {0} in rolling back application binaries.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Expansion of the application enterprise archive (EAR) files to appropriate locations failed because the addNode command failed.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Use the EARExpander tool to expand the application EAR files to their appropriate destination. The destination is specified in the binariesURL attribute of the deployment.xml file in the repository.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU2032I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU2032I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU2032I=ADMU2032I: Use wsadmin or the Administrative Console to uninstall any such applications from the Deployment Manager.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    You can use the wsadmin tool or the administrative console to uninstall applications from the deployment manager.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0508I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0508I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0508I=ADMU0508I: The {0} &quot;{1}&quot; is {2}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The state of the specified server is given.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU8003E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU8003E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU8003E=ADMU8003E: An error occurred when calling registerNode command; rolling back to original configuration.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The registerNode command failed. The configuration is being rolled back to the original configuration.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Review the associated error in registerNode.log or turn on trace to diagnose the problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU8039E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU8039E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU8039E=ADMU8039E: Required option type is expected if you try to register a WebSphere plug-in type.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The node could not be registered because the node is not a stand-alone node.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify the node type and the plug-in type to register the plug-in type.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0118E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0118E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0118E=ADMU0118E: The log file cannot be written to location {0}; please specify a different location with -logfile
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The log file could not be written to the specified location. Permissions or a security issue might be a cause of the problem.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Use the -logfile option to specify a new location for the logfile.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0053E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0053E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0053E=ADMU0053E: Exception occurred while removing node {1} from all node groups. {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Removal of the specified node from all node groups failed.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Record the exception information from this message and perform problem determination using that exception data.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0089E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0089E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0089E=ADMU0089E: Exception caught during rollback of application binaries {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The rollback of the application binaries failed.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Consult the addNode.log file for additional information.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU2031I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU2031I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU2031I=ADMU2031I: Any applications that were uploaded to the {0} cell configuration during addNode using the -includeapps option are not uninstalled by removeNode.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    If the addNode command, with the -includeapps option specified, previously uploaded any applications to the specified cell, the removeNode command did not uninstall any of those applications.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0009I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0009I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0009I=ADMU0009I: Successfully connected to Deployment Manager Server: {0}:{1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This is an informational message indicating that the program has established communications with the Deployment Manager.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0507I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0507I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0507I=ADMU0507I: No servers found in configuration under: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The servers directory is empty in the configuration.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check the integrity of the configuration files.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU8002I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU8002I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU8002I=ADMU8002I: Exchanging signers between adminagent and node with path {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Exchanging signers between adminagent and node to be registered.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU8038I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU8038I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU8038I=ADMU8038I: Deregistering the node with an adminagent.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The node will be deregistered with an adminagent.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU9994W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU9994W" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU9994W=ADMU9994W: Options username or password is not needed to start a server and it will be ignored.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The given option is not needed to start a server and it is ignored.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0117E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0117E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0117E=ADMU0117E: The application {0} on this node cannot be merged with the Cell. The application binaries URL conflicts with what is already in the Cell.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The application already exists in the cell configuration repository and uses a different URL for the location of its binaries. The application cannot be merged with the cell configuration and will be ignored.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Install the application on the deployment manager if it is to be used in servers for this cell.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0052E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0052E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0052E=ADMU0052E: Exception occurred while adding node {1} to node group {2}. {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified node could not be added to the specified node group.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Record the exception information from this message and perform problem determination using that exception data.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0088E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0088E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0088E=ADMU0088E: No Server MBean named {0} in this process {1}:{2}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The server name does not match the process attributes.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check that the name is spelled correctly.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0506I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0506I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0506I=ADMU0506I: Server name: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The server name is displayed.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU2030E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU2030E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU2030E=ADMU2030E: Exception {0} caught in getting binariesURL from {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified deployment.xml file could not be loaded to obtain the value of the binariesURL attribute. The enterprise archive (EAR) file will not be expanded or deleted from that location.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Run the EARExpander tool to expand the EAR file to its appropriate location. Alternatively, delete the directory of the EAR file that was supposed to be deleted.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0008E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0008E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0008E=ADMU0008E: Error obtaining MBean by name {0}: {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A query to locate an MBean failed.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Record the exception information in this message for further investigation.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU8037I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU8037I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU8037I=ADMU8037I: Backing up the original wsadmin.properties file of the node to be registered.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The wsadmin.properties file is being saved before it is changed.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU8001E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU8001E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU8001E=ADMU8001E: An error occurred during node registration; rolling back to original configuration.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    If an error occurs during the registerNode command process and it cannot complete, an attempt is made to restore the configuration to its original state, though this might also fail to complete.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Review the associated messages in the registerNode.log file to determine the specific problem. Retry the registerNode command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU3055E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU3055E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU3055E=ADMU3055E: Error obtaining MBean by name {0}: {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A query to locate an MBean failed.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check that the server process is still running. Examine the log files for the program to perform further problem determination.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0116I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0116I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0116I=ADMU0116I: Tool information is being logged in file {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Tool information is being logged to the specified file.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU3300I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU3300I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU3300I=ADMU3300I: Launch script for server created: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The server launch script has been successfully created.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0051E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0051E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0051E=ADMU0051E: Exception occurred while converting node group {2} to sysplex node group for node {1}. {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified node group could not be converted to a sysplex node group for the specified node.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Record the exception information from this message and perform problem determination using that exception data.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU9993E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU9993E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU9993E=ADMU9993E: Invalid parameter {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The parameter that is provided is not valid for the given option.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Provide a different parameter.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0505I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0505I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0505I=ADMU0505I: Servers found in configuration:
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This is an informational message printed before a list of servers.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0007E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0007E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0007E=ADMU0007E: Error while copying {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The program was not able to copy a file. There may not be enough disk space or there may be a problem reading the file.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check the available disk space on the system. Check that the file does exist and is readable.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU8036I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU8036I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU8036I=ADMU8036I: Registering the node with an AdminAgent.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The node is being registered with an adminagent.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU3054E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU3054E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU3054E=ADMU3054E: No Server MBean named {0} in this process {1}:{2}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The MBean of type Server appears to be missing from the process.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check that the named server is actually running on the host and port specified.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0115I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0115I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0115I=ADMU0115I: Trace mode is on.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Trace has been enabled.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0050E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0050E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0050E=ADMU0050E: Exception encountered while checking if node {1} can join node group {2}. {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Whether the specified node could join the specified node group could not be determined.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Record the exception information from this message and perform problem determination using that exception data.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU9992E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU9992E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU9992E=ADMU9992E: Parameter required for option: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A parameter is required for the displayed option, but one was not provided.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Provide a parameter for this option.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0006E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0006E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0006E=ADMU0006E: Exception creating Deployment Manager connection: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The client utility program was not able to establish a connection to the Deployment Manager using the information provided.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check that the Deployment Manager host and port are reachable from the system on which the utility is being executed.  One method to check connectivity is to use the TCP/IP &quot;ping&quot; command.  If security is enabled, ensure the user and password are specified correctly.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU8035E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU8035E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU8035E=ADMU8035E: Ensure that the AdminAgent is running on the specified port.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A connection cannot be made to the administrative agent. The administrative agent is the AdminAgent MBean.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that the administrative agent is running. Ensure that the proper port is used when attempting to connect to the process.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0114E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0114E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0114E=ADMU0114E: Exception launching Node Agent process: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The node agent process for the new node failed to launch.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Record and save the exception information from this message and perform further problem determination to investigate why the process failed to launch.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0222I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0222I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0222I=ADMU0222I: Exception accessing the plugin-cfg.xml file.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The code that attempts to upload the plugin-cfg.xml configuration file failed and issued an exception.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Record and save the exception information from this message and perform further problem determination to investigate why the file cannot be accessed.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU3009E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU3009E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU3009E=ADMU3009E: Exception waiting for server initialization {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An exception occurred while the program was listening to the status socket for the server. The server process failed to start.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Record and save the exception information in this message for further problem determination.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU1211I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU1211I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU1211I=ADMU1211I: To obtain a full trace of the failure, use the -trace option.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    You can use the trace option to gather additional information.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Consider using the -trace option on the command line.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU9991E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU9991E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU9991E=ADMU9991E: Unknown option: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The option specified is not a known option.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the usage statement and specify a known option.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0503I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0503I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0503I=ADMU0503I: Retrieving server status for all servers
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The server status is being retrieved for all servers.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0005E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0005E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0005E=ADMU0005E: Error synchronizing repositories {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An error occurred during configuration synchronization. If the error was encountered during addNode, the configuration will be rolled back to the base configuration. If this error was encountered during syncNode, node and cell repositories may be out of synchronization with each other.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the log files for additional problem determination information.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU8034E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU8034E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU8034E=ADMU8034E: The profile path {0} does not exist locally on the Administrative Agent system.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Make sure the profile path you specify is correct and the profile path exists locally on the Administrative Agent system.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Review the associated error to diagnose the problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU2019I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU2019I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU2019I=ADMU2019I: Removing installed applications from node {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The installed applications are being removed from the specified node.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0113E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0113E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0113E=ADMU0113E: Program exiting with error: {0}, resulting from: {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The program did not finish because of the specified error.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Record the exception information from this message and perform problem determination using that exception data.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0004E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0004E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0004E=ADMU0004E: Exception attempting to get result from configuration synchronization {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An exception occurred during configuration synchronization while waiting for an asynchronous operation on the Deployment Manager.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Record the exception information from this message for further investigation.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU8033E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU8033E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU8033E=ADMU8033E: Error trying to register a node that has been registered already.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The node could not be registered because it has already been registered.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that the node has not been previously registered before attempting to register it.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU8069E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU8069E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU8069E=ADMU8069E: If you specify the conntype, you must also specify the port.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    You must specify port option if you specified conntype option.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Review the associated error to diagnose the problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU2018I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU2018I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU2018I=ADMU2018I: Node {0} has been removed from the Deployment Manager configuration.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified node has been removed from the deployment manager configuration.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0112E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0112E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0112E=ADMU0112E: Exception writing serverindex.xml file: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The code that attempts to update the serverindex.xml configuration file failed and issued an exception.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Record and save the exception information from this message and perform further problem determination to investigate why the file cannot be written to.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU3007E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU3007E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU3007E=ADMU3007E: Exception {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Some general exception condition has been discovered.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Combine this information with additional exception messages in order to perform additional problem determination.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0003I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0003I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0003I=ADMU0003I: Node {0} has been successfully federated.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This is an informational message indicating that the addNode program has successfully completed.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU7714I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU7714I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU7714I=ADMU7714I: WASService command for server {0} completed successfully.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The WASService command completed successfully.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0039E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0039E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0039E=ADMU0039E: There is already a node named {0} in the cell.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    You cannot run the addNode command to add a node to a cell which already contains a node of the same name.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Do not attempt to run the addNode command to add a node to a cell already containing a node of the same name.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0501E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0501E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0501E=ADMU0501E: Server name not specified; must supply the name of a server or -all for all servers.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Neither the server name nor the -all argument was specified on the serverStatus command.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Either specify the server name or the -all argument on the serverStatus command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU8032E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU8032E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU8032E=ADMU8032E: Failed getting AdminAgent mbean, deregisterNode cannot continue.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The AdminAgent MBean, which is the administrative agent, could not be gotten during the removal of the node from the registry. The node removal was attempted using the deregisterNode operation.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Review the associated error in deregisterNode.log or turn on trace to diagnose the problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU8068E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU8068E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU8068E=ADMU8068E: If you specify the port, you must also specify the conntype.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    You must specify conntype option if you specified port option.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Review the associated error to diagnose the problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU2017I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU2017I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU2017I=ADMU2017I: The local original configuration has been restored.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The local configuration file has been restored.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0111E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0111E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0111E=ADMU0111E: Program exiting with error: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The program did not finish because of the specified error.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the program is in the current working directory, verify that the directory is on the PATH or prefix the command invocation with the current working directory.  Otherwise, record the exception information from this message and perform problem determination using that exception data.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU2096I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU2096I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU2096I=ADMU2096I: Any security domains that are no longer required can be removed using the deleteSecurityDomain task using the force option. They can also be manually removed.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    You can use the deleteSecurityDomain task with the force option to remove any unused security domains. You can also manually delete the security domains that are not required any more.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0500I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0500I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0500I=ADMU0500I: Retrieving server status for {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The status of the specified service is being retrieved.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0002E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0002E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0002E=ADMU0002E: Exception attempting to process server {0}: {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An exception occurred while attempting to attach to the server and obtain its state.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Record the exception information from this message for further investigation.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0038E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0038E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0038E=ADMU0038E: The Deployment Manager&apos;&apos;s IP address resolves as 127.0.0.1, but the Deployment Manager is not on the local machine.  The Deployment Manager&apos;&apos;s host name configuration or DNS is configured incorrectly.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The deployment manager host name is not resolving correctly.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the host name is configured properly at the deployment manager.  For Linux systems, modify either the /etc/hosts file or the /etc/nsswitch.conf file to search the domain name server (DNS) before files.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU6009I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU6009I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU6009I=ADMU6009I: Processing complete.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Processing complete.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU7713E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU7713E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU7713E=ADMU7713E: WASService command for server {0} failed. Unexpected exit code {1} from running {2}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The WASService command returned a non-zero exit code.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the product installation and environment configuration are correct. Then, run the WASService command manually.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU8031E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU8031E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU8031E=ADMU8031E: Failed getting AdminAgent mbean, registerNode cannot continue.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The node could not be registered because the AdminAgent MBean could not be gotten.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Review the associated error in registerNode.log or turn on trace to diagnose the problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU8067E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU8067E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU8067E=ADMU8067E: Parameter {0} was specified twice.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    You cannot specify the same parameter more than once.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Review the associated error in registerNode.log or turn on adminagent trace to diagnose the problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU4211I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU4211I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU4211I=ADMU4211I: To obtain a full trace of the failure, use the -trace option.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The trace option can be used to obtain a full trace of the failure.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU2016E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU2016E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU2016E=ADMU2016E: Node {0} has not been removed from the Deployment Manager configuration.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The node configuration files remain in the cell configuration repository.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the -force option is used, run the cleanupNode utility on the deployment manager to remove the configuration files for this node.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0254I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0254I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0254I=ADMU0254I: Update the node configuration for {0} on the Deployment Manager.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The particular node configuration is updated.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0001I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0001I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0001I=ADMU0001I: Begin federation of node {0} with Deployment Manager at {1}:{2}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This is an informational message indicating that the addNode program has started.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU2095I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU2095I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU2095I=ADMU2095I: Any security domains that were uploaded to the {0} cell configuration during addNode are not removed by removeNode.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    If the addNode command uploaded any security domains to the specified cell, the removeNode command did not remove these security domains.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0037E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0037E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0037E=ADMU0037E: The node cannot lookup the Deployment Manager using host name {0}. The host name in the Deployment Manager configuration may need to be fully qualified.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The local node cannot look up the deployment manager host name that is specified in the deployment manager configuration.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Do one of the following actions:
 - Add the deployment manager host name to the DNS.
 - Fully qualify the deployment manger host name in the deployment manager server index configuration.
 -Add the DNS of the domain to the TCP/IP configuration of the node.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU7712E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU7712E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU7712E=ADMU7712E: Failed while trying to determine the Windows Service status for service: {0}; 
probable error executing WASService.exe: {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The status for the Windows service could not be obtained.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the product installation is correct.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU8030E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU8030E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU8030E=ADMU8030E: Failed finding backup files so unregister node cannot continue.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Before removing the node from the registry, the configuration must be backed up. However, the configuration files to back up could not be found.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that the node was previously registered, and that the backup files exist in your environment.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU8066E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU8066E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU8066E=ADMU8066E: You specified a non supported parameter {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    You cannot use non supported parameters.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Review the associated error in registerNode.log or turn on adminagent trace to diagnose the problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU2015I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU2015I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU2015I=ADMU2015I: This exception can be ignored by specifying -force.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This is an informational message explaining that the -force option can be used to eliminate the message.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU2094W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU2094W" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU2094W=ADMU2094W: The node product extension is {0} which does not match the Deployment Manager product extension which is {1}.  Some operations and configurations may not be valid on this node.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The operation will continue even though the product extensions do not match.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure the necessary product extensions are installed on the node to support any subsequent operations and configurations applied to it.  Additional product extensions may need to be installed.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0036E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0036E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0036E=ADMU0036E: The Deployment Manager cannot lookup by name host {0} at address {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The local host can look up the deployment manager host, but the deployment manager cannot look up the new node. The situation can occur if the Dynamic Host Configuration Protocol (DHCP) does not interact with domain name servers (DNS).
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Try using a static IP address if the DHCP does not interact with the DNS. If the host name is not fully qualified, try updating the host name. To update the host name, specify the -nodeName parameter and the -hostName parameter on the changeHostName command of the AdminTask object.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU7711E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU7711E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU7711E=ADMU7711E: Unexpected exception associated with WASService.exe: {0} during processing of server with name: {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An unexpected exception has been detected.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the product installation is correct.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU3220I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU3220I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU3220I=ADMU3220I: Base server runtime initialized. Waiting for application initialization.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The server initialized. The product is waiting for application initialization.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU8065E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU8065E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU8065E=ADMU8065E: You did not specify all required parameters. Required parameters you did not specify are {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    You need to specify all required parameters.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Review the associated error in registerNode.log or turn on adminagent trace to diagnose the problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU2014I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU2014I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU2014I=ADMU2014I: Restoring original configuration.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The original product configuration is being restored.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU3111E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU3111E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU3111E=ADMU3111E: Server stop requested but failed to complete.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The stop request failed. Additional information is supplied in other messages.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Record the failure information from the other messages and perform problem determination on the server to investigate why it failed to stop.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU2093E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU2093E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU2093E=ADMU2093E: Custom property {0} has no value.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified custom property was found, but has no value.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the configuration to be certain a value is specified for the custom property.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0035E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0035E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0035E=ADMU0035E: WebSphere Express nodes are not supported in a Network Deployment cell.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Express node could not be added to a Network Deployment cell because an Express node is not supported in a Network Deployment environment.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Do not attempt to add the node.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU7710E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU7710E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU7710E=ADMU7710E: Unexpected exit code {1} from WASService.exe while executing {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An unexpected exit code was returned from WASService.exe
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify WebSphere installation and Windows environment; try running command manually; contact IBM support.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU8064E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU8064E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU8064E=ADMU8064E: If you specify the nodepassword, you must also specify the nodeusername.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    You must specify the nodeusername when you specify the nodepassword.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Review the associated error in registerNode.log or turn on adminagent trace to diagnose the problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0251I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0251I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0251I=ADMU0251I: Begin changing node name for {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The process of renaming the node has started.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU3002E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU3002E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU3002E=ADMU3002E: Exception attempting to process server {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A more detailed exception has occurred while attempting to start or stop the named server. This message is always paired with a second message that displays the detailed exception.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Record and save the exception information in the follow-on message for further problem determination.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU2092E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU2092E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU2092E=ADMU2092E: The node and Deployment Manager must have the same product extensions, but they do not match.  The node product extension is {0} and the Deployment Manager product extension is {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The operation cannot be completed because the product extensions do not match between the node and the deployment manager.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check the product extensions installed on both the node and the deployment manager. Additional product extensions might need to be installed.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0034E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0034E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0034E=ADMU0034E: The node/cell name of the node being federated with addNode must have a different name than the cell name of the Network Deployment manager node: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The cell name of the Network Deployment manager node must be unique within the cell.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that the cell name of the deployment manager is unique within the cell.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU8063E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU8063E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU8063E=ADMU8063E: If you specify the nodeusername, you must also specify the nodepassword.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    You must specify the nodepassword when you specify the nodeusername.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Review the associated error in registerNode.log or turn on adminagent trace to diagnose the problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU2012I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU2012I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU2012I=ADMU2012I: Backing up Network Deployment configuration.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The product configuration is being backed up.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU3001I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU3001I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU3001I=ADMU3001I: Server {0} open for recovery; process id is {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified server is recovering.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0250I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0250I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0250I=ADMU0250I: Node {0} has been successfully renamed to {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified node has been successfully renamed.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU8019E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU8019E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU8019E=ADMU8019E: Error trying to register an unsupported profile. You can only register a stand-alone application server node with an administrative agent.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The node you are trying to register is not a stand-alone server node. You can only register a stand-alone application server node.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that the node you are trying to register to an administrative agent is a stand-alone application server node.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU2091E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU2091E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU2091E=ADMU2091E: Exception {0} caught checking product extensions on the node or the Deployment Manager.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The product extensions installed on the node or the deployment manager could not be determined.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the exception to determine the specific problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0033E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0033E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0033E=ADMU0033E: The node {0} already has been added to the cell.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    You cannot run the addNode command on a node that has already been added to a cell.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Do not attempt to run addNode twice on the same node.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU8062E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU8062E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU8062E=ADMU8062E: If you specify the password, you must also specify the user name.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    You must specify the user name when you specify the password.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Review the associated error in registerNode.log or turn on adminagent trace to diagnose the problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU3000I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU3000I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU3000I=ADMU3000I: Server {0} open for e-business; process id is {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified server has started. The process id indicates the PID for Distributed platforms while on z/OS it represents the Server token(stoken).
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU8018E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU8018E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU8018E=ADMU8018E: Error running registerNode on non supported environment.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An attempt was made to register a node in an unsupported environment. A node can be registered only when it runs on the same machine as the administrative agent, which is the AminAgent MBean.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Register a node, using the registerNode operation, when the node is located on the same machine as the administrative agent. The administrative agent is the AdminAgent MBean.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0032E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0032E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0032E=ADMU0032E: It is not valid to run addNode on the same node as the Deployment Manager: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The addNode program only applies to base app server nodes, not the Network Deployment deployment manager node itself.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Do not attempt to run addNode on the Deployment Manager node itself.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU8061E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU8061E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU8061E=ADMU8061E: If you specify the user name, you must also specify the password.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    You must specify the password when you specify the user name.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Review the associated error in registerNode.log or turn on adminagent trace to diagnose the problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU2010I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU2010I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU2010I=ADMU2010I: Stopping all server processes for node {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    All server processes are being stopped for the specified node.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU8017I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU8017I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU8017I=ADMU8017I: The administrative subsystem for deregistered node has been successfully destroyed.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0031E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0031E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0031E=ADMU0031E: Node Agent launched but failed initialization. Process id was: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The node agent process returned an unsuccessful status value.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the log files for the node agent to perform additional problem determination.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU6002I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU6002I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU6002I=ADMU6002I: Begin Asset Preparation -
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Preparation of assets has begun.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU8060E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU8060E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU8060E=ADMU8060E: An error occurred when trying to get the profile key.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An error occurred when trying to get the profile key.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Review the associated error in registerNode.log or turn on trace to diagnose the problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU8016I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU8016I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU8016I=ADMU8016I: The administrative subsystem for the deregistered node has been successfully stopped.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0030I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0030I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0030I=ADMU0030I: Node Agent initialization completed successfully. Process id is: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This is an informational message indicating that the node agent process started without errors.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU6001I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU6001I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU6001I=ADMU6001I: Begin App Preparation -
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Preparation of applications has begun.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU8015I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU8015I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU8015I=ADMU8015I: The administrative subsystem for the registered node has been successfully started.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU8014I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU8014I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU8014I=ADMU8014I: The administrative subsystem for the registered node has been successfully initialized.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0129E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0129E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0129E=ADMU0129E: The deployment manager is of an older version or has less feature packs installed than this node; the node has not been added
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The deployment manager version is earlier than that of the node.  The product requires that the deployment manager version be at the same version as the node, or at a later version.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Upgrade the deployment manager to the same version as the node, or a later version than the node.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0064E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0064E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0064E=ADMU0064E: addNode can only be run from a base (application server) profile
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The addNode command did not run because the profile from which it was begun is not a base (application server) profile.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Run the command from a base (application server) profile, such as AppSrv01.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU8013I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU8013I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU8013I=ADMU8013I: Application Server with path {0} has been successfully deregistered.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The node was successfully deregistered with an adminagent.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU8049E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU8049E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU8049E=ADMU8049E: An error occurred when adminagent tried to exchange signers with the node.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An error occurred when adminagent tried to exchange signers with the node that you tried to register.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Review the associated error in registerNode.log or turn on trace to diagnose the problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0128I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0128I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0128I=ADMU0128I: Starting tool with the {0} profile
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    If -profileName is passed, that specified profile will be used. If run from a profile&apos;&apos;s bin directory, that profile will be used. Otherwise the default profile is used. This message just clarifies the profile used.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    You may want to verify that the profile listed in this message is the desired profile.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0063E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0063E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0063E=ADMU0063E: The {0} node does not exist in the cell so the -asExistingNode option cannot be used.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    You cannot use the -asExistingNode option unless the node already exists in the cell.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Use the command with a node that already exists in the cell or do not use the -asExistingNode option.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU8012I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU8012I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU8012I=ADMU8012I: Application Server with path {0} has been successfully registered.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Registration of the specified profile successfully completed.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0019E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0019E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0019E=ADMU0019E: Error occurred reading from an input stream {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The read method of an I/O stream issued an exception.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Record and save the exception information in this message for further problem determination. Examine the log file for the utility and rerun the program with the -trace option.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU8048E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU8048E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU8048E=ADMU8048E: Error trying to unregister node that has not been registered.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Failed to unregister the node, the node may have not been registered yet or the node may have been registered to different AdminAgent.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check if the node you are trying to unregister was registered or make sure you try to unregister the node from the correct AdminAgent.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0127E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0127E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0127E=ADMU0127E: The version of the Deployment Manager ({0}) is earlier than that of this node ({1}).
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The deployment manager version is earlier than that of the specified node. The product requires that the deployment manager version be at the same version as the node, or at a later version.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Upgrade the deployment manager to the same version as the node, or a later version than the node.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0062E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0062E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0062E=ADMU0062E: The -asExistingNode option cannot be used with any of the following options: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The -asExistingNode option is incompatible with these options.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Retry the command and omit either the -asExistingNode option or all of the incompatible options.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU7773E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU7773E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU7773E=ADMU7773E: Generic Server: {0} is not RUNNING
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An attempt was made to stop a generic server that is not running.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that the generic server is running before attempting to stop it.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0018I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0018I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0018I=ADMU0018I: Launching Node Agent process for node: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The node agent process is starting.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0061W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0061W" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0061W=ADMU0061W: The -nodeagentshortname option is used in a z/OS environment only.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The -nodeagentshortname option is ignored on operating systems other than the z/OS operating system.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Use the option on the z/OS operating system only.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU8047E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU8047E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU8047E=ADMU8047E: An error occurred when invoking listProfiles operation on AdminAgent mbean; rolling back to original configuration.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Failed invoking listProfiles operation on AdminAgent mbean.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Review the associated error in registerNode.log or turn on trace to diagnose the problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0126E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0126E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0126E=ADMU0126E: The version of the Deployment Manager ({0}) is earlier than that of this node ({1}); the node has not been added.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The deployment manager version is earlier than that of the specified node. The product requires that the deployment manager version be at the same version as the node, or at a later version. The node has not been added to the cell.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Upgrade the deployment manager to the same version as the node, or a later version than the node.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU7772I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU7772I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU7772I=ADMU7772I: Generic Server: {0} STOPPED successfully.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The generic server successfully stopped.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0060W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0060W" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0060W=ADMU0060W: The -portprops option overrides the -startingport option.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The options are mutually exclusive.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify the correct option.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU8010I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU8010I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU8010I=ADMU8010I: Begin registration of Application Server with path {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Registration of the profile has begun.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0017E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0017E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0017E=ADMU0017E: Error occurred closing an input/output stream {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The close method of an I/O stream object issued an exception. This probably is a secondary exception that came after an earlier I/O failure.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Record and save the exception information in this message for further problem determination. Examine the log file for the utility and rerun the program with the -trace option.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU3201I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU3201I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU3201I=ADMU3201I: Server stop request issued. Waiting for stop status.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A request to stop the server was made. The product is waiting for server status.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU8046E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU8046E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU8046E=ADMU8046E: The administrative agent port number specified for {0} connector is invalid, registerNode cannot continue.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Failed to register the node because the port number specified is invalid.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check your administrative agent serverindex.xml and find the correct port number of the connector.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0125E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0125E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0125E=ADMU0125E: Change the clock of the new node to be within {0} minutes of the clock of the deployment manager.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The addNode command failed because the clock of the new node is out of synchronization with the deployment manager.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Change the clock of the new node to be within the specified minutes of the clock of the deployment manager.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU7771E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU7771E" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU7771E=ADMU7771E: Generic Server: {0} already running - use the &quot;-forceGenericServerStart&quot; to force server start!
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An attempt was made to start a generic server that has already been started.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Use &quot;stopServer.(bat|sh)&quot; to stop the generic server,
 then retry the startServer command or use the &quot;-forceGenericServerStart&quot; option to try to force the start of the generic server.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU0016I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU0016I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU0016I=ADMU0016I: Synchronizing configuration between node and cell.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Configuration synchronization is occurring between a node and a cell.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ADMU8045I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMU8045I" varFormat="Java">
    ADMU8045I=ADMU8045I: Node has been successfully deregistered.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The node has been deregistered from an adminagent.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<!-- END MESSAGES -->
</TMSSource>
