<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/css" href="../../resources/stylesheets/wasmsgxml.css"?>
<TMSSource name="TivoliMessages" tmsVersion="1.0" xml:lang="en">
<!-- CMVC MSG File Name = ws/code/process.impl/src/com/ibm/ws/process/processmessages.nlsprops -->
<!-- DO NOT EDIT THIS FILE - This file was generated by the XML/Html & Property emitter -->
<!-- BEGIN MESSAGES -->
<Message ID="PROC0024E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PROC0024E" varFormat="Java">
    PROC0024E=PROC0024E: Java thread dump has failed.  Failure reason was the virtual machine was unable to call the method [{3}] on the Java dump class: [{0}].  The error was a NullPointerException.  Java Virtual Machine version is: [{1}].  Java Virtual Machine Vendor is: [{2}].
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A request to create a Java thread dump, also referred to as a Java core dump, was not processed because a NullPointerException exception occurred, and the internal diagnostic class and method to generate the Java thread dump could not be executed.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check the documentation for the JVM that is running on this system to make sure that the creation of a Java thread dump is supported on that JVM version.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="PROC0014E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PROC0014E" varFormat="Java">
    PROC0014E=PROC0014E: Process termination failed.  The process identified by [{0}] did not terminate in a timely manner.  It still appears to be active on the system.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified process was not terminated.  See the description of the error code for more information.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Use the operating system mechanisms to manually stop the process.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="PROC0004E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PROC0004E" varFormat="Java">
    PROC0004E=PROC0004E: Executable: [{0}] does not appear to be a valid executable.  Process could not be created.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The process has not been created because either the specified file does not exist, or the current user does not have permission to run this file.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check the name of the specified file and its permissions. Verify that the current user has permission to run this file.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="PROC0023E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PROC0023E" varFormat="Java">
    PROC0023E=PROC0023E: Java thread dump has failed.  Failure reason was the virtual machine was unable to call the method [{3}] on the Java dump class: [{0}].  The error was a NoSuchMethodException.  Java Virtual Machine version is: [{1}].  Java Virtual Machine Vendor is: [{2}].
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A request to create a Java thread dump, also referred to as a Java core dump, was not processed because a NoSuchMethodException exception occurred, and the internal diagnostic class and method to generate the Java thread dump could not be executed.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check the documentation for the JVM that is running on this system to make sure that the creation of a Java thread dump is supported on that JVM version.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="PROC0029E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PROC0029E" varFormat="Java">
    PROC0029E=PROC0029E: Java thread dump has failed.  Failure reason was the virtual machine was unable to call the method [{3}] on the Java dump class: [{0}].  The error was an InvokationTargetException.  Java Virtual Machine version is: [{1}].  Java Virtual Machine Vendor is: [{2}].
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A request to create a Java thread dump, also referred to as a Java core dump, was not processed because an InvokationTargetException exception occurred, and the internal diagnostic class and method to generate the Java thread dump could not be executed.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check the documentation for the JVM that is running on this system to make sure that the creation of a Java thread dump is supported on that JVM version.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="PROC0013E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PROC0013E" varFormat="Java">
    PROC0013E=PROC0013E: Process termination failed.  The error returned from native was: {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified process was not terminated.  See the description of the error code for more information.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Use the operating system mechanisms to manually stop the process.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="PROC0019E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PROC0019E" varFormat="Java">
    PROC0019E=PROC0019E: Java thread dump has failed.  Failure reason was the virtual machine was unable to load Java dump class: [{0}].  Java Virtual Machine version is: [{1}].  Java Virtual Machine Vendor is: [{2}].
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A request to create a Java thread dump, also referred to as a Java core dump, was not processed because the internal diagnostic class could not be loaded.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check the documentation for the Java Virtual Machine (JVM) that is running on this system to make sure that the creation of a Java thread dump is supported on that JVM version.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="PROC0003E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PROC0003E" varFormat="Java">
    PROC0003E=PROC0003E: Working Directory: [{0}] does not appear to be valid, or accessible by the process.  Process could not be created.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The process was not created because the specified working directory does not exist on the system or the user ID that is being used to run the process does not have access to the specified directory.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify the name of a working directory that exists on the system, and make sure that the user ID that is being used to run the process has permission to access that directory.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="PROC0009E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PROC0009E" varFormat="Java">
    PROC0009E=PROC0009E: The operating system reported not enough free memory to create the process.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The process was not created because there is not enough memory available on this system to contain the new process.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Reduce the current memory usage on this system.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="PROC0022E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PROC0022E" varFormat="Java">
    PROC0022E=PROC0022E: Java thread dump has failed.  Failure reason was the virtual machine was unable to call the method [{3}] on the Java dump class: [{0}].  The error was an IllegalAccessException.  Java Virtual Machine version is: [{1}].  Java Virtual Machine Vendor is: [{2}].
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A request to create a Java thread dump, also referred to as a Java core dump, was not processed because an IllegalAccessException exception occurred, and the internal diagnostic class and method to generate the Java thread dump could not be executed.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check the documentation for the JVM that is running on this system to make sure that the creation of a Java thread dump is supported on that JVM version.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="PROC0028E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PROC0028E" varFormat="Java">
    PROC0028E=PROC0028E: Java thread dump has failed.  Failure reason was the virtual machine was unable to call the method [{3}] on the Java dump class: [{0}].  The error was an IllegalArgumentException.  Java Virtual Machine version is: [{1}].  Java Virtual Machine Vendor is: [{2}].
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A request to create a Java thread dump, also referred to as a Java core dump, was not processed because an IllegalArgumentException exception occurred, and the internal diagnostic class and method to generate the Java thread dump could not be executed.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check the documentation for the JVM that is running on this system to make sure that the creation of a Java thread dump is supported on that JVM version.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="PROC0012E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PROC0012E" varFormat="Java">
    PROC0012E=PROC0012E: The parameters passed in to terminate appear to be invalid or null.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The process was not terminated because the parameters specified in the termination request are either not valid, or null.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="PROC0018E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PROC0018E" varFormat="Java">
    PROC0018E=PROC0018E: The process bind failed.  The PID [{0}] could not be bound to.  The operating system reported the binding process does not have sufficient authority.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The process represented by the PID cannot be monitored because the current process does not have the authority needed to complete the binding request.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="PROC0002E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PROC0002E" varFormat="Java">
    PROC0002E=PROC0002E: Group: [{0}] does not appear to be valid on this system.  Process could not be created.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The process was not created because the specified group name is not defined for this system.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a group name that is defined for this system.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="PROC0008E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PROC0008E" varFormat="Java">
    PROC0008E=PROC0008E: The operating system reported too many file handles are already open.  Process could not be created.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The process was not created because the maximum number of file handles that the operating system allows are already open.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Increase the maximum number of file handles that the operating system allows, or reduce the number of processes that are currently active.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="PROC0031E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PROC0031E" varFormat="Java">
    PROC0031E=PROC0031E: The process creation failed.  The process creation for program [{0}] with priority [{1}] timed out.  This can occur if the system activity is too high for a process to be created within a specific time limit of two minutes.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This situation might occur if high system activity prevents the creation of process within within the specified time limit.  The general time limit for the process to initialize is two minutes.  This is because generally if a process cannot initialize within the time limit then there is not enough system resources to adequately run the new process.  When the time limit is exceeded, a CreateProcessTimeoutException is issued and the process creation is canceled.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check the CPU, memory, and overall system load characteristics for processes which are monopolizing machine resources.  Also check the system limit settings for values that may be affecting the number of processes that can be running at the same time, limits on CPU usage, and memory being allocated to each process.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="PROC0021E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PROC0021E" varFormat="Java">
    PROC0021E=PROC0021E: Java thread dump has failed.  Failure reason was the virtual machine was unable to link the Java dump class: [{0}] into the virtual machine.  Java Virtual Machine version is: [{1}].  Java Virtual Machine Vendor is: [{2}].
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A request to create a Java thread dump, also referred to as a Java core dump, was not processed because the internal diagnostic class could not be linked into the Java Virtual Machine (JVM).
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check the documentation for the JVM that is running on this system to make sure that the creation of a Java thread dump is supported on that JVM version.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="PROC0027E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PROC0027E" varFormat="Java">
    PROC0027E=PROC0027E: Java thread dump has failed.  Failure reason was the virtual machine was unable to call the method [{3}] on the Java dump class: [{0}].  The error was an IllegalAccessException.  Java Virtual Machine version is: [{1}].  Java Virtual Machine Vendor is: [{2}].
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A request to create a Java thread dump, also referred to as a Java core dump, was not processed because an IllegalAccessException exception occurred, and the internal diagnostic class and method to generate the Java thread dump could not be executed.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check the documentation for the JVM that is running on this system to make sure that the creation of a Java thread dump is supported on that JVM version.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="PROC0011E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PROC0011E" varFormat="Java">
    PROC0011E=PROC0011E: Process termination failed.  The current effective UID attempting to terminate the process [{0}] does not have authority to terminate it.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified process was not terminated because the user ID that was used to issue the termination request does not have the authority to terminate this process.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Log onto the system using an ID that has the authority to terminate this process, and manually stop the process.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="PROC0017E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PROC0017E" varFormat="Java">
    PROC0017E=PROC0017E: The process bind failed.  The PID [{0}] is invalid.  It contains non-numeric charcaters.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The binding request could not be completed because the specified process ID (PID) contained non-numeric characters.  A PID must contain all numberic characters.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="PROC0001E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PROC0001E" varFormat="Java">
    PROC0001E=PROC0001E: User: [{0}] does not appear to be valid on this system.  Process could not be created.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The process was not created because the specified user name is not defined for this system.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a user name that is defined for this system.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="PROC0007E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PROC0007E" varFormat="Java">
    PROC0007E=PROC0007E: Some files required by the process or the process definition were inaccessible.  Please check the standard in, out, and error file redirects and directories.  Process could not be created.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The process cannot access some of the files that it requires.  These files might be standard out or error redirection files, and the user ID being used to run the process might not have read or write access to the files or the directories in which these log files reside.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check the standard out and error redirection log files and their directories.  Make sure that the user ID being used to run the process has read and write access to the log files, and the directories in which these log files reside.  If the profile containing the server is maintained for use by a non-root user, or the server is configured to run as a non-root user, then ensure the user ID being used to run the process owns the entire profile directory.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="PROC0030E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PROC0030E" varFormat="Java">
    PROC0030E=PROC0030E: Java thread dump has failed.  Method for generating java thread dumps for Java Virtual Machine version: [{0}] from vendor: [{1}] is unknown.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A request to create a Java thread dump, also referred to as a Java core dump, was not processed because it is unknown how to create the Java thread dump on the installed Java Virtual Machine (JVM).
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check the documentation for the JVM that is running on this system to make sure that the creation of a Java thread dump is supported on that JVM version.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="PROC0020E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PROC0020E" varFormat="Java">
    PROC0020E=PROC0020E: Java thread dump has failed.  Failure reason was the virtual machine was unable to initialize the Java dump class: [{0}].  Java Virtual Machine version is: [{1}].  Java Virtual Machine Vendor is: [{2}].
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A request to create a Java thread dump, also referred to as a Java core dump, was not processed because the internal diagnostic class could not be initialized.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check the documentation for the Java Virtual Machine (JVM) that is running on this system to make sure that the creation of a Java thread dump is supported on that JVM version.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="PROC0026E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PROC0026E" varFormat="Java">
    PROC0026E=PROC0026E: Java thread dump has failed.  Failure reason was the virtual machine was unable to initialize the Java dump class method: [{0}].  Java Virtual Machine version is: [{1}].  Java Virtual Machine Vendor is: [{2}].
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A request to create a Java thread dump, also referred to as a Java core dump, was not processed because the internal diagnostic class dump method could not be initialized.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check the documentation for the JVM that is running on this system to make sure that the creation of a Java thread dump is supported on that JVM version.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="PROC0010E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PROC0010E" varFormat="Java">
    PROC0010E=PROC0010E: Process: [{0}] is not on the system.  It could not be bound to.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The binding request could not be completed because the specified process ID (PID) is not valid for this system.  Therefore, the process cannot be monitored.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that the PID value being passed to the binding request is a valid PID for this system.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="PROC0016E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PROC0016E" varFormat="Java">
    PROC0016E=PROC0016E: The process creation failed.  Some files that are required by the process or the process definition are inaccessible, such as standard in, out, and error redirects.  Verify that the current user has read and write access to the following items:  Working directory: [{1}].  Standard input: [{2}].  Standard output: [{3}].  Standard error: [{4}].  Empty [] indicates that the value is not set and the operating system defaults are used.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The process was not able to access some of the files that it expected.  The files that cannot be accessed are probably log files.  These files might be standard out or error redirection files, and the user ID being used to run the process might not have read or write access to the files or the directories in which these log files reside.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check the standard out and error redirection files and their directories.  Ensure that the user ID being used to run the process has read and write access to the log files, and the directories in which these log files reside.  If the profile containing the server is maintained for use by a non-root user, or the server is configured to run as a non-root user, then ensure the user ID being used to run the process owns the entire profile directory.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="PROC0006E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PROC0006E" varFormat="Java">
    PROC0006E=PROC0006E: Process Group: [{0}] is not valid.  Process could not be created.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The process was not created because the specified process is not valid.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a valid process group.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="PROC0025E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PROC0025E" varFormat="Java">
    PROC0025E=PROC0025E: Java thread dump has failed.  Failure reason was the virtual machine was unable to call the method [{3}] on the Java dump class: [{0}].  The error was a SecurityException.  Java Virtual Machine version is: [{1}].  Java Virtual Machine Vendor is: [{2}].
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A request to create a Java thread dump, also referred to as a Java core dump, was not processed because a SecurityException exception occurred, and the internal diagnostic class and method to generate the Java thread dump could not be executed.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check the documentation for the JVM that is running on this system to make sure that the creation of a Java thread dump is supported on that JVM version.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="PROC0015E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PROC0015E" varFormat="Java">
    PROC0015E=PROC0015E: The process creation failed.  Some files that are required by the process or the process definition are inaccessible, such as standard in, out, and error redirects.  Verify that user [{0}] has read and write access to the following items:  Working directory: [{1}].  Standard input: [{2}].  Standard output: [{3}].  Standard error: [{4}].  Empty [] indicates the value is not set and the operating system defaults are used.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The process was not able to access some of the files that it expected.  The files that cannot be accessed are probably log files.  These files might be standard out or error redirection files, and the user ID being used to run the process might not have read or write access to the files or the directories in which these log files reside.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check the standard out and error redirection files and their directories.  Ensure that the user ID being used to run the process has read and write access to the log files, and the directories in which these log files reside.  If the profile containing the server is maintained for use by a non-root user, or the server is configured to run as a non-root user, then ensure the user ID being used to run the process owns the entire profile directory.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="PROC0005E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PROC0005E" varFormat="Java">
    PROC0005E=PROC0005E: Priority: [{0}] does not appear to be a valid value for this system or could not be set.  Process could not be created.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The process was not created because a priority was specified that is not valid.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a valid process priority.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<!-- END MESSAGES -->
</TMSSource>
