<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/css" href="../../resources/stylesheets/wasmsgxml.css"?>
<TMSSource name="TivoliMessages" tmsVersion="1.0" xml:lang="en">
<!-- CMVC MSG File Name = ws/code/orbext/src/com/ibm/ws/orbimpl/WSORBMessages.nlsprops -->
<!-- DO NOT EDIT THIS FILE - This file was generated by the XML/Html & Property emitter -->
<!-- BEGIN MESSAGES -->
<Message ID="ORBX0320E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="IIOPTunnelServlet.Exception" varFormat="Java">
    IIOPTunnelServlet.Exception=ORBX0320E: {0}: Exception ={1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An exception occurred while attempting to connect to the server from the IIOPTunnelServlet program.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See the description of the exception for more information.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ORBX0090I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="LocationServant.RegisteredServer" varFormat="Java">
    LocationServant.RegisteredServer=ORBX0090I: Server registered: ServerUUID={0}   HostName={1}   Port={2}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The indicated server has been registered with the Location Service Daemon.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ORBX0300E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="IIOPTunnelServlet.parsingPort" varFormat="Java">
    IIOPTunnelServlet.parsingPort=ORBX0300E: service(): An exception occurred while parsing port number. Query string={0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The IIOPTunnelServlet program cannot parse the port number that was received from the client.  The port number was taken from the IOR of the object that the server is servicing.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that the port number is correct for the server.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ORBX0060E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="LocationServiceDaemon.portInUse" varFormat="Java">
    LocationServiceDaemon.portInUse=ORBX0060E: Port {0} is in use. Specify a different port number.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Location Service Daemon is attempting to start listening on a port that another process is already using.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a different port number for the Location Service Daemon, or end the process that is using the port. Then restart the Location Service Daemon.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ORBX0310E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="IIOPTunnelServlet.IOException" varFormat="Java">
    IIOPTunnelServlet.IOException=ORBX0310E: service(): IOException occurred while setting up client/server sockets. Exception={0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An I/O Exception occurred while attempting to connect to the server from the IIOPTunnelServlet program.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that the server is active and is accepting requests.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ORBX0100I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="LocationServant.UnregisteredServer" varFormat="Java">
    LocationServant.UnregisteredServer=ORBX0100I: Server unregistered: ServerUUID={0}   HostName={1}   Port={2}&quot;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The indicated server has been unregistered with the Location Service Daemon.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ORBX0040E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="LocationServiceDaemon.failedOnWait" varFormat="Java">
    LocationServiceDaemon.failedOnWait=ORBX0040E: Location Service Daemon failed on waiting for requests.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Location Service Daemon is not ready to accept requests. It cannot enter into a wait state.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Restart the Location Service Daemon.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ORBX0350E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="Redirector.RequestIOException" varFormat="Java">
    Redirector.RequestIOException=ORBX0350E: handleRequest(): IOException occurred while redirecting the client request packet to the server. Exception={0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An I/O exception has occurred. This exception is the result of a failed or interrupted I/O operation.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure the server is active and is accepting requests. You can also try to ping the target machine that you are trying to reach to make sure that the network is functioning properly.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ORBX0220E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="JNIReaderManager.noNonFullNativeReaders" varFormat="Java">
    JNIReaderManager.noNonFullNativeReaders=ORBX0220E: None of the native code&apos;s reader threads has room in its queue for a new Socket to watch, a COMM_FAILURE was thrown.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    None of the native code&apos;s reader threads have room in thrie queue for a new Socket to watch.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Use the Object Request Broker (ORB) com.ibm.CORBA.numJNIReaders custom property to add more reader threads.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ORBX0210I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="JNIReaderThread.fdConnectionMap.get" varFormat="Java">
    JNIReaderThread.fdConnectionMap.get=ORBX0210I: after calling fdConnectionMap.get() with Filedescriptor {0} the returned GIOPConnection was {1}. The fdConnectionMap contains {2}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message does not indicate an error. It provides configuration information for problem determination.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ORBX0050E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="LocationServiceDaemon.exception" varFormat="Java">
    LocationServiceDaemon.exception=ORBX0050E: ERROR: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Location Service Daemon received an unexpected exception.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the exception for a possible user error.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ORBX0340I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="IIOPTunnelServlet.servletInfo" varFormat="Java">
    IIOPTunnelServlet.servletInfo=ORBX0340I: The servlet used to tunnel IIOP packets through an HTTP Server.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message states the return value for the standard servlet method getServletInfo.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ORBX0010E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="LocationServiceClient.portNotSetException" varFormat="Java">
    LocationServiceClient.portNotSetException=ORBX0010E: Persistent IOR port number is not provided. Object references will be transient.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The com.ibm.CORBA.LSDPort property was not set when the Object Request Broker (ORB) was initialized.  This situation causes transient object references.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If persistent object references are required, when initializing the ORB, set the com.ibm.CORBA.LSDPort property to a value that will remain persistent on that host machine.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ORBX0170I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ServerActivator.StoringActiveServerList" varFormat="Java">
    ServerActivator.StoringActiveServerList=ORBX0170I: Location Service Daemon is storing the active server list to {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The active server list is being stored in the indicated file.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ORBX0360E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="Redirector.ReplyIOException" varFormat="Java">
    Redirector.ReplyIOException=ORBX0360E: handleReply(): IOException occurred while redirecting the server reply packet back to the client. Exception={0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An I/O exception has occurred. This exception is the result of a failed or interrupted I/O operation.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure the server is active and is accepting requests. You can also try to ping the target machine that you are trying to reach to make sure that the network is functioning properly.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ORBX0030I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="LocationServiceDaemon.waitForRequests" varFormat="Java">
    LocationServiceDaemon.waitForRequests=ORBX0030I: Location Service Daemon is listening with server ID = {0} on port = {1} ...
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Location Service Daemon is ready to accept requests on the indicated port.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ORBX0150I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ServerActivator.RestoreServerList" varFormat="Java">
    ServerActivator.RestoreServerList=ORBX0150I: Location Service Daemon is initializing the list of active servers from {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Location Service Daemon has been configured to persistently store the list of active servers that are registered. During startup, the Location Service Daemon uses the specified stored file to restore the list of active servers.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ORBX0160I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ServerActivator.StartServer" varFormat="Java">
    ServerActivator.StartServer=ORBX0160I: Location Service Daemon is starting server {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified server is starting.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ORBX0380E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="Redirector.Exception" varFormat="Java">
    Redirector.Exception=ORBX0380E: Redirector(.): Exception occurred while calling GlobalORBFactory init method. Exception={0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Object Request Broker (ORB) failed to initialize in response to a call to the GlobalORBFactory.init method. See the description of the exception for more information.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure the server is active and is accepting requests.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ORBX0400E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="JNIReaderManager.ClassCastError" varFormat="Java">
    JNIReaderManager.ClassCastError=ORBX0400E:  A ClassCastException was encountered while attempting to add a connection to a JNI Reader thread.  The input stream of the connection type being passed to the reader thread could not be cast to a FileInputStream.  This is most likely because the JSSE2 security provider has been configured in conjunction with JNIReaderThreads.  JNIReaderThreads and the JSSE2 security provider cannot be used together; if this is the case, either unconfigure JNIReaderThreads, or change the JSSE2 security provider to JSSE.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Object Request Broker (ORB) service could not complete a connection to a JNI reader thread. See the descripiton of the exception more information.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Resolve the error reported in the exception and restart the ORB service.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ORBX0190I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WS.IBMCopyright" varFormat="Java">
    WS.IBMCopyright=ORBX0190I: 5639-D57, (C) COPYRIGHT International Business Machines Corp., 2001 All Rights Reserved Licensed Materials - Property of IBM US Government Users Restricted Rights - Use, duplication or disclosure restricted by GSA ADP Schedule Contract with IBM Corp.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The software you are running is copyrighted property of the International Business Machines (IBM) Corporation and all use, duplication or disclosure by U.S. government users is restricted to the GSA ADP Schedule Contract between the U.S. government and the IBM Corporation.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ORBX0020E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="LocationServiceClient.UUIDNotSetException" varFormat="Java">
    LocationServiceClient.UUIDNotSetException=ORBX0020E: Unique server ID (UUID) is not set.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The com.ibm.CORBA.ServerUUID property was not set when the Object Request Broker (ORB) was initialized. The Location Service Daemon requires this property to uniquely identify a server.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    When initializing the ORB, set the com.ibm.CORBA.ServerUUID property to the UUID (Universally Unique Identifier) that was assigned to the server.  The system administrator usually assigns the UUID to a server.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ORBX0180I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="JNIReaderManager.invalidNumberOfReaders" varFormat="Java">
    JNIReaderManager.invalidNumberOfReaders=ORBX0180I: The property {0} has a value of {1}.  This is not a valid value. The number of JNIReaderThreads is set to the default value of {2}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message does not indicate an error. It provides configuration information for problem determination.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ORBX0080I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="LocationServant.FirewallPlugin" varFormat="Java">
    LocationServant.FirewallPlugin=ORBX0080I: Location Service Daemon has registered a firewall plugin.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Location Service Daemon will be interacting with a firewall. The Location Service Daemon will authorize the server&apos;s port when the server registers with the Location Service Daemon.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ORBX0290E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="IIOPTunnelServlet.parsingHost" varFormat="Java">
    IIOPTunnelServlet.parsingHost=ORBX0290E: service(): An exception occurred while parsing the host name. Query string={0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The IIOPTunnelServlet program cannot parse the host name that was received from the client.  The host name was taken from the IOR of the object that the server is servicing.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure that the host name is correct for the server.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ORBX0370E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="Redirector.Throwable" varFormat="Java">
    Redirector.Throwable=ORBX0370E: A throwable exception occurred while redirecting the IIOP packets. Exception={0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An underlying transport level problem has occurred.  See the description of the exception for more information.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure the server is active and is accepting requests. You can also try to ping the target machine that you are trying to reach to make sure that the network is functioning properly.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ORBX0120I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ServerActivator.SSLEnabled" varFormat="Java">
    ServerActivator.SSLEnabled=ORBX0120I: Registered servers started by the Location Service Daemon will need to be SSL enabled.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Location Service has been configured to listen on an SSL enabled port. Servers that are started by the Location Service Daemon are notified that they need to listen on an SSL enabled port.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ORBX0110I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ServerActivator.StartServers" varFormat="Java">
    ServerActivator.StartServers=ORBX0110I: Location Service Daemon will start the registered servers.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A server is considered registered if there is an entry for the server in the IBMLSDServerRegistry.properties file.  The Location Service Daemon has been configured to start a registered server if a request comes in for that server and the server is not registered with the Location Service Daemon as an active server.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ORBX0140I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ServerActivator.StoreServerList" varFormat="Java">
    ServerActivator.StoreServerList=ORBX0140I: Location Service Daemon will persistently store the list of active servers to {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Location Service Daemon has been configured to persistently store the list of active servers that are registered.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ORBX0200I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="JNIReaderThread.showfdConnectionMap" varFormat="Java">
    JNIReaderThread.showfdConnectionMap=ORBX0200I: Before calling the native method addConnection0, the contents of the fdConnectionMap are {0}, and the fileDescriptor for the connection being added is {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message does not indicate an error. It provides configuration information for problem determination.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ORBX0330E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="IIOPTunnelServlet.unsupported" varFormat="Java">
    IIOPTunnelServlet.unsupported=ORBX0330E: service(): HTTP method type &quot;{0}&quot; is not supported; only &quot;POST&quot; method type is supported.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The IIOPTunnelServer program only supports the HTTP POST method.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure your Web server and the servlet engine supports the POST method.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ORBX0390E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="Transport.Exception" varFormat="Java">
    Transport.Exception=ORBX0390E: Cannot create listener thread. Exception=[ {0} ].
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Object Request Broker (ORB) service could not create a listener thread. See the descripiton of the exception for more information.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Resolve the error reported in the exception and restart the ORB service.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="ORBX0130I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ServerActivator.ServerTimeOut" varFormat="Java">
    ServerActivator.ServerTimeOut=ORBX0130I: Registered Servers will have {0} milliseconds to start.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Location Service Daemon has been configured to start servers. When a server is started, the Location Service Daemon uses the indicated timeout value when waiting for a server to start.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<!-- END MESSAGES -->
</TMSSource>
