<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/css" href="../../resources/stylesheets/wasmsgxml.css"?>
<TMSSource name="TivoliMessages" tmsVersion="1.0" xml:lang="en">
<!-- CMVC MSG File Name = ws/code/admin.scripting/src/com/ibm/ws/scripting/resources/wscpMessage.nlsprops -->
<!-- DO NOT EDIT THIS FILE - This file was generated by the XML/Html & Property emitter -->
<!-- BEGIN MESSAGES -->
<Message ID="WASX8025W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX8025W" varFormat="Java">
    WASX8025W=WASX8025W: AdminConfig object is not available.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The AdminConfig command cannot be run because the configuration service is not available.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a server with a running configuration service and reissue the wsadmin command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7345E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7345E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7345E=WASX7345E: Cannot find node &quot;{0}&quot; in configuration data.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The wsadmin tool cannot run the AdminControl startServer command because there is no node of the specified name in the configuration.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the node name is spelled correctly.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7211I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINCONFIG_HELP_LISTTEMPLATES" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINCONFIG_HELP_LISTTEMPLATES=WASX7211I: Method: listTemplates

	Arguments: type

	Description: Returns a list of the templates available for the given
	type.  These templates may be used in invocations of 
	createUsingTemplate.

	Method: listTemplates

	Arguments: type, match

	Description: Returns a list of the templates with display names
	that contain the string specified by &quot;match&quot; available for the given
	type.  These templates may be used in invocations of 
	createUsingTemplate.

	Method: listTemplates

	Arguments: type, pattern

	Description: Returns a list of the templates with display names
	that contain the string matching with the wildcard &quot;pattern&quot; for the 
	given type.  These templates may be used in invocations of 
	createUsingTemplate.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7344E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7344E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7344E=WASX7344E: Node name is required when the client is connected to process type &quot;{0}&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The wsadmin tool cannot run the AdminControl startServer command because the node name is not specified.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify the node name to locate the server in the startServer command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7005E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PORT_REQUIRES_ARG" varFormat="Java">
    PORT_REQUIRES_ARG=WASX7005E: The &quot;-port&quot; option requires a port number.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The wsadmin launcher has been invoked with the -port option, but no port number argument was found.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a port number for the -port option and reissue the wsadmin command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX8024I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX8024I" varFormat="Java">
    WASX8024I=WASX8024I: Cannot find the command or command group pattern: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The command pattern specified is not found, try different pattern.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that the searching pattern correctly.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7343E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7343E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7343E=WASX7343E: The specified node name &quot;{0}&quot; is not the same as the node &quot;{1}&quot; this client is currently connected to.&quot;,
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The wsadmin tool cannot run the AdminControl startServer command because the node name that has been specified is not the same as the node name that is currently connected to by the node agent.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the node name is spelled correctly.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX8023E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX8023E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX8023E=WASX8023E: The upload file &quot;{0}&quot; does not exist for installation.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The file is not uploaded for installation.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that this file exists and is readable.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7487E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7487E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7487E=WASX7487E: Failed to import script libraries modules: {0}; {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An error occured during importing script libraries modules.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the script libraries modules, then restart the wsadmin tool.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7486W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7486W" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7486W=WASX7486W: This -clientMode option will be ignored because the -enableClientModule option is not specified.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The -clientMode option has been specified, but the -enabledClientModule option has not been specified.  The -clientMode option will be ignored.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify the -enableClientModule option with the AdminApp install command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7341W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7341W" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7341W=WASX7341W: No &quot;save&quot; was performed before the interactive scripting session exited; configuration changes will not be saved.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An interactive scripting session concluded without saving configuration changes.  No configuration changes were saved.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Invoke the AdminConfig &quot;save&quot; command to save your configuration changes.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7377W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7377W" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7377W=WASX7377W: &lt;typeClass&gt; element with the same class name, {0}, found in {1} at line {2}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A type handler registerd to handle the same type class is included in the extension xml more than once.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Remove the duplicate type handler in the extension xml file.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7223I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINAPP_HELP_PRECOMPILEJSPS" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINAPP_HELP_PRECOMPILEJSPS=WASX7223I: &quot;preCompileJSPs&quot; option; use this option to specify that JSPs are to be precompiled.  The default is nopreCompileJSPs.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7318E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="EXCEPTION_DECLARING_BEAN" varFormat="Java">
    EXCEPTION_DECLARING_BEAN=WASX7318E: Received exception while declaring {0}; exception information: {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An error has occurred during the initialization of the objects used by wsadmin.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    This exception is unexpected. The cause is not immediately known.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7452I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINAPP_HELP_ALLOWSERVICEREMOTEINCLUDE" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINAPP_HELP_ALLOWSERVICEREMOTEINCLUDE=WASX7452I: &quot;allowServiceRemoteInclude&quot; option; Enables an enterprise application to service 
an include request from an enterprise application with -allowDispatchRemoteInclude set to true.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX8021E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX8021E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX8021E=WASX8021E: The wsadmin with version &quot;{0}&quot; connected to an incompatible server or deployment manager with node version &quot;{1}&quot;, which is not supported. &quot;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The wsadmin tool is connecting to an incompatible version of the server or deployment manager node.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the server or deployment manager node has same or higher version as the wsadmin tool. Connect to a compatible server or deployment manager node.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7447E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="APPEND_TRACE_REQUIRES_ARG" varFormat="Java">
    APPEND_TRACE_REQUIRES_ARG=WASX7447E: &quot;-appendtrace&quot; option must be followed by a &apos;true&apos; or &apos;false&apos;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The wsadmin launcher did not run because no argument was found for the -appendtrace option.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a string value for the -appendtrace option and reissue the wsadmin command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7272I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HELP_HELP_NOTIFICATIONS" varFormat="Java">
    HELP_HELP_NOTIFICATIONS=WASX7272I: Method: notifications

	Arguments: MBean

	Description: Display information about the notifications sent by
	the specified MBean.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7432I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINAPP_HELP_VALIDATEINSTALL" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINAPP_HELP_VALIDATEINSTALL=WASX7432I: &quot;validateinstall&quot; option; specifies desired level of application install validation. Valid option values are:
	off: no application deployment validation
	warn: perform application deployment validation and 
		continue with the application deployment process 
		even when there are reported warning or error 
		messages.
	fail: perform application deployment validation and 
		not to continue with the application deployment 
		process when there are reported warning or 
		error messages.
The default is off.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7123E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7123E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7123E=WASX7123E: Unexpected &quot;{0}&quot; found. {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The wsadmin tool found the specified character in an unexpected location in the input stream.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct and reissue the command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7002E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DASH_C_NEEDS_FOLLOWING_COMMAND" varFormat="Java">
    DASH_C_NEEDS_FOLLOWING_COMMAND=WASX7002E: &quot;-c&quot; option must be followed by a command.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The wsadmin launcher has been invoked with the &quot;-c&quot; option. This option requires that a string be supplied to be interpreted as a wsadmin command.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Reissue the wsadmin command with a command string following the -c option.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7420I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINAPP_HELP_UPDATEINTERACTIVE" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINAPP_HELP_UPDATEINTERACTIVE=WASX7420I: Method: updateInteractive

	Arguments: application name, content type, options

	Description: updates the application specified by &quot;application
	name&quot; using update type specified by &quot;content type&quot; with
	options specified by &quot;options&quot;. If content type is app or
	file, user is prompted for information about each relevant task.

	Valid update content type values are 
		app - entire application
		file - a single file
		modulefile - a module
		partialapp - partial application

	All valid options for install command are valid for the
	update command. Additional update options are 
		-operation - operation to be performed. Valid values are
			add - adds new contents
			addupdate - performs add or updates based on
				existence of contents in the application
			delete - deletes contents
			update - update existing contents
		  This option is required if content type is file
		  or modulefile. This option must have &quot;update&quot; as
		  the value if content type is app. This option is
		  ignored if content type is partialapp.
		-contents - file containing the contents to be added or
		  updated. The specified file has to be local to the
		  scripting client. This option is required except for
		  delete operation.
		-contenturi - URI of the file to be added, updated, or
		  removed from the application. This option is required if 
		  content type is file or modulefile. This option 
		  is ignored if content type is app or partialapp.

	The AdminApp &quot;options&quot; command may be used to get a list of all 
	possible options for a given ear file.  The AdminApp &quot;help&quot; command
	may be used to get more information about each particular option.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7157I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINAPP_HELP_DEPL.EXTENSION.REG" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINAPP_HELP_DEPL.EXTENSION.REG=WASX7157I: &quot;depl.extension.reg&quot; option; specifies location of properties file for deployment extensions.
This option is deprecated. There is no replacement for this option.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7376E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7376E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7376E=WASX7376E: Invalid element end-tag: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The reported element tag in the extension xml file is not supported.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Remove the unsupported element tag in the extension xml file.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX8020E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX8020E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX8020E=WASX8020E: An argument is required for parameter &quot;{0}.&quot;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified parameter requires an accompanying argument.  For example, if you specify &quot;-node&quot; you need to follow &quot;-node&quot; with the name of a node: &quot;-node mynode.&quot;
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Supply an argument for the indicated parameter.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7100I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINAPP_HELP_LIST" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINAPP_HELP_LIST=WASX7100I: Method: list

	Arguments: none

	Description: Lists all installed applications

	Method: list

	Arguments: target scope

	Description: List installed applications on a given &quot;target scope&quot; 
	For example, WebSphere:cell=myCell,node=myNode,server=myServer or 
	WebSphere:cell=myCell,cluster=myCluster.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7122E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7122E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7122E=WASX7122E: Expected &quot;{0}&quot;  not found. {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The wsadmin tool did not find the specified string in the expected location in the input stream.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct and reissue the command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7375E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7375E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7375E=WASX7375E: Element type {0} is already defined.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The same element type is used more than once in the extension xml file.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Remove the extra element type in the extension xml file.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7266I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7266I" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7266I=WASX7266I: A was.policy file exists for this application; would you like to display it?
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7027I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINCONTROL_GENERAL_HELP" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINCONTROL_GENERAL_HELP=WASX7027I: The AdminControl object enables the manipulation of MBeans running
	in a WebSphere server process.  The number and type of MBeans available
	to the scripting client depends on the server to which the client is
	connected.  If the client is connected to a Deployment Manager, then
	all the MBeans running in the Deployment Manager are visible as are all
	the MBeans running in the Node Agents connected to this Deployment
	Manager, and all the MBeans running in the application servers on those
	nodes.

	The following commands are supported by AdminControl; more detailed
	information about each of these commands is available by using the
	&quot;help&quot; command of AdminControl and supplying the name of the command
	as an argument.

	Note that many of these commands support two different sets of
	signatures: one that accepts and returns strings, and one low-level
	set that works with JMX objects like ObjectName and AttributeList.
	In most situations, the string signatures are likely to be more useful,
	but JMX-object signature versions are supplied as well.  Each of these
	JMX-object signature commands has &quot;_jmx&quot; appended to the command name.
	Hence there is an &quot;invoke&quot; command, as well as a &quot;invoke_jmx&quot; command.

completeObjectName
		Returns a String version of an object name given a template
		name
getAttribute_jmx
		Given ObjectName and name of attribute, returns value of
		attribute
getAttribute	Given String version of ObjectName and name of attribute,
		returns value of attribute
getAttributes_jmx
		Given ObjectName and array of attribute names, returns 
		AttributeList.
getAttributes	Given String version of ObjectName and attribute names,
		returns String of name value pairs. Given String version
		of ObjectName, returns String of all name value pairs.
getCell		Returns the cell name of the connected server 
getConfigId	Given String version of ObjectName, return a configuration
		ID for the corresponding configuration object, if any
getDefaultDomain
		Returns &quot;WebSphere&quot;
getDomainName	Returns &quot;WebSphere&quot;
getHost		Returns String representation of connected host
getMBeanCount	Returns number of registered beans
getMBeanInfo_jmx
		Given ObjectName, returns MBeanInfo structure for MBean
getNode		Returns the node name of the connected server 
getObjectInstance
		Given String version of ObjectName, returns ObjectInstance
		object that match.
getPort		Returns String representation of port in use
getType		Returns String representation of connection type in use
help		Shows help information
invoke_jmx	Given ObjectName, name of method, array of parameters and
		signature, invokes method on MBean specified
invoke		Invokes a method on the specified MBean
isRegistered_jmx
		Returns true if supplied ObjectName is registered
isRegistered	Returns true if supplied String version of ObjectName is
		registered
makeObjectName	Returns an ObjectName built with the given string
queryNames_jmx	Given ObjectName and QueryExp, retrieves set of ObjectNames
		that match.
queryNames	Given String version of ObjectName, retrieves String of
		ObjectNames that match
queryMBeans	Given String version of ObjectName, returns a set of
		ObjectInstances object that match
reconnect	Reconnects with server
setAttribute_jmx
		Given ObjectName and Attribute object, sets attribute for MBean
		specified
setAttribute	Given String version of ObjectName, attribute name and
		attribute value, sets attribute for MBean specified
setAttributes_jmx
		Given ObjectName and AttributeList object, sets attributes for
		the MBean specified
setAttributes	Given String version of ObjectName, attribute name
		and value pairs, sets attributes for the MBean specified
startServer	Given the name of a server, starts that server
stopServer	Given the name of a server, stops that server
testConnection	Tests the connection to a DataSource object
trace		Sets the wsadmin trace specification
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7374W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7374W" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7374W=WASX7374W: Missing element type {0} in {1} at line {2}. Ignoring this {3} element type.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The extension xml file contains an element type reported in this warning message with required element type missing.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Add the missing element type reported in this message to the extension xml file.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7003E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="OPTION_NEEDS_FOLLOWING_FILENAME" varFormat="Java">
    OPTION_NEEDS_FOLLOWING_FILENAME=WASX7003E: &quot;{0}&quot; option must be followed by a file name.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The wsadmin launcher has been invoked with an option that requires the name of a file, but no such argument was found.  These options are -f, -p, and -profile.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Reissue the wsadmin command with a file name following the option.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7483E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7483E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7483E=WASX7483E: Application edit of {0} failed: see previous messages for details.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An AdminApp edit command did not run.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See previous messages for details.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7121E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7121E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7121E=WASX7121E: &quot;{0}&quot; found instead of expected &apos;{&apos;. {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The wsadmin tool found the specified string when &apos;{&apos; was expected in the input stream.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct and reissue the command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7265W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7265W" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7265W=WASX7265W: Stop not completed for server &quot;{0}&quot; on node &quot;{1}&quot;.  The stop process may have timed out.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified server process cannot stop.  The request has timed out.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the server is stopped.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7482W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7482W" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7482W=WASX7482W: The duplicate properties are specified. The latter property value will be set.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The duplicate properties are specified in the command. The latter property value will be set to the property.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Respecify the property name and value.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7126I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINCONFIG_HELP_HASCHANGES" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINCONFIG_HELP_HASCHANGES=WASX7126I: Method: hasChanges

	Arguments: none

	Description: Returns true if unsaved configuration changes exist
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7373W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7373W" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7373W=WASX7373W: Duplicate implementation class entry, {0}, found in {1} at line {2}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The same implementation class is included in the extension xml file more than once.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Remove the duplicate implementation class from the extension xml file.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7120E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7120E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7120E=WASX7120E: Diagnostic information from exception with text &quot;{0}&quot; follows:

 {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The wsadmin tool created an exception.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the exception information in the log file to determine the source of the problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7264I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7264I" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7264I=WASX7264I: Stop completed for server &quot;{0}&quot; on node &quot;{1}&quot;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified server is stopped on the specified node.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7051I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINCONTROL_HELP_HELP" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINCONTROL_HELP_HELP=WASX7051I: Method: help

	Arguments: none

	Description: Displays general help for AdminControl.

	Method: help

	Arguments: command

	Description: Displays help for the AdminControl command specified by 
	&quot;command.&quot;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7024E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_IPC_CONN_TYPE" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_IPC_CONN_TYPE=WASX7024E: Error creating &quot;{0}&quot; connection to host &quot;{1}&quot;; ensure that the correct IPC host is specified in the wsadmin.properties file or with &quot;-ipchost&quot; on the command line; exception information: {2}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The connector did not establish a connection to the host.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the accompanying exception information and the information in the wsadmin.traceout file to determine the cause of the error.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7263W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7263W" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7263W=WASX7263W: Start not completed for server &quot;{0}&quot; on node &quot;{1}&quot;.  The server launching process may have timed out.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified server process cannot start. The request has timed out.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the server is started.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7372E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7372E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7372E=WASX7372E: Error instantiating the class for {0} provided in extension: {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The system cannot instantiate the implementation class provided in the extension xml file.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the exception in the trace log and correct the problem accordingly. Verify that the class provides a constructor with no argument.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7339I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINCONFIG_HELP_HELP" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINCONFIG_HELP_HELP=WASX7339I: Method: help

	Arguments: none

	Description: Displays general help for AdminConfig.

	Method: help

	Arguments: method name

	Description: Displays help for the AdminConfig method specified by
	&quot;method name.&quot;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7480E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7480E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7480E=WASX7480E: &quot;{0}&quot; found instead of expected &apos;[&apos;. {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The wsadmin tool found the specified string when &apos;[&apos; was expected in the input stream.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct and reissue the command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7004E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HOST_REQUIRES_ARG" varFormat="Java">
    HOST_REQUIRES_ARG=WASX7004E: The &quot;-host&quot; option requires a host name.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The wsadmin launcher has been invoked with the -host option, but no host name argument was found.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a host name for the -host option and reissue the wsadmin command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7371E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7371E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7371E=WASX7371E: Error locating the class for {0} provided in extension: {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The system cannot find the implementation class provided in the extension xml file.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the implementation class in the extension xml file is correct and that the class is in the class path.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7262I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7262I" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7262I=WASX7262I: Start completed for server &quot;{0}&quot; on node &quot;{1}&quot;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified server is started on the specified node.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7276I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HELP_HELP_ADMINAPP" varFormat="Java">
    HELP_HELP_ADMINAPP=WASX7276I: Method: AdminApp

	Arguments: none

	Description: Display general help information for the
	AdminApp object provided by wsadmin.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7298E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7298E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7298E=WASX7298E: Cannot invoke &quot;{0}&quot; command because this client is not connected to a Network Deployment Manager server.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The AdminConfig command requires a connection to a deployment manager server.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Connect to a deployment manager server or do not invoke this AdminConfig command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7189I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7189I" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7189I=WASX7189I: Validation level set to {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An informational message issued in response to invoking the AdminConfig setValidationLevel.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7445E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="JOB_ID_REQUIRES_ARG" varFormat="Java">
    JOB_ID_REQUIRES_ARG=WASX7445E: &quot;-jobid&quot; option must be followed by a jobID string.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The wsadmin launcher did not run because no jobid argument was found for the -jobid option.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a value for the -jobid option and reissue the wsadmin command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7172I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINAPP_HELP_DEPLOYEJB.DBTYPE" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINAPP_HELP_DEPLOYEJB.DBTYPE=WASX7172I: &quot;deployejb.dbtype&quot; option; specifies the database type for EJBDeploy; valid values are {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7360I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINCONFIG_HELP_REQUIRED" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINCONFIG_HELP_REQUIRED=WASX7360I: Method: required

	Arguments: type

	Description: Displays the required attributes contained by an object
	of type &quot;type&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7163I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINAPP_HELP_DEFAULTBINDING.CF.JNDI" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINAPP_HELP_DEFAULTBINDING.CF.JNDI=WASX7163I: &quot;defaultbinding.cf.jndi&quot; option; specifies the JNDI name for the default connection factory
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7370E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7370E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7370E=WASX7370E: Error registering bean {0} provided in extension: {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The system cannot register the bean provider specified in the extension xml file with the BSF.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the exception in the trace log and correct the problem accordingly. CMSG0002.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7043I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINCONTROL_HELP_GETATTRIBUTE" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINCONTROL_HELP_GETATTRIBUTE=WASX7043I: Method: getAttribute

	Arguments: object name, attribute

	Description: Returns value of &quot;attribute&quot; for the MBean described by 
	&quot;object name.&quot;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7333I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINAPP_HELP_REDEPLOY" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINAPP_HELP_REDEPLOY=WASX7333I: This option is deprecated. Use the &quot;update&quot; option instead.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7297E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7297E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7297E=WASX7297E: Cannot write to file &quot;{0}&quot;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The AdminConfig extract command did not write document data to the specified file.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the wsadmin.traceout log file to determine the problem.  Verify that there is enough space in the file system and that there are no file permission problems.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7188I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7188I" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7188I=WASX7188I: Cross-document validation enablement set to {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An informational message issued in response to invoking the AdminConfig setCrossDocumentValidationEnabled.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7068I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINCONFIG_HELP_TYPES" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINCONFIG_HELP_TYPES=WASX7068I: Method: types

	Arguments: none

	Description: Displays all the possible top-level configuration 
	object types.

	Method: types

	Arguments: pattern

	Description: Displays all the possible top-level configuration 
	object types matching with the wildcard &quot;pattern&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7029I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="JACL_WELCOME_HELP" varFormat="Java">
    JACL_WELCOME_HELP=WASX7029I: For help, enter: &quot;$Help help&quot;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7079E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7079E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7079E=WASX7079E: Unable to determine attribute information for type &quot;{0}&quot;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The wsadmin tool cannot process an attribute that has been specified on an AdminConfig command.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    This exception is unexpected. The cause is not immediately known.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7296E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7296E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7296E=WASX7296E: The name specified is not the name of a file &quot;{0}&quot;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The AdminConfig extract command did not run because the specified filename describes an existing file system entity that is not a file.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the specified name is not a directory name.  Specify a valid file name and reissue the command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7204I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINCONFIG_HELP_GETOBJECTNAME" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINCONFIG_HELP_GETOBJECTNAME=WASX7204I: Method: getObjectName; 

	Arguments: config id

	Description: Returns a string version of the ObjectName for the MBean
	that corresponds to this configuration ID. If there is no such
	running MBean this returns an empty string.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7025E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MALFORMED_OBJECT_NAME" varFormat="Java">
    MALFORMED_OBJECT_NAME=WASX7025E: Error found in String &quot;{0}&quot;; cannot create ObjectName.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The wsadmin tool did not create the ObjectName object because a string was incorrectly formatted.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the string is not empty and that it is correctly formatted for an ObjectName string.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7489E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="EXT_DIR_REQUIRES_ARG" varFormat="Java">
    EXT_DIR_REQUIRES_ARG=WASX7489E: &quot;-extdir&quot; option must be followed by a path to set to ws.ext.dirs.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The wsadmin launcher did not run because no argument was found for the -extdir option.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a path for the -extdir option and reissue the wsadmin command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7187E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7187E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7187E=WASX7187E: Invalid value &quot;{0}&quot; -- possible valid values are &quot;{1}&quot;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A value that has been specified for an AdminConfig command is not valid.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a valid value for the AdminConfig command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7381I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINAPP_HELP_NODEPLOYWS" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINAPP_HELP_NODEPLOYWS=WASX7381I: &quot;nodeployws&quot; option; specifies to not deploy WebService during install; this is the default setting.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7037I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINCONTROL_HELP_GETMBEANCOUNT" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINCONTROL_HELP_GETMBEANCOUNT=WASX7037I: Method: getMBeanCount

	Arguments: none

	Description: Returns number of registered beans
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7321I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINCONFIG_HELP_CREATEDOCUMENT" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINCONFIG_HELP_CREATEDOCUMENT=WASX7321I: Method: createDocument

	Arguments: documentURI, filename

	Description: Creates a new document in the configuration repository.
	The &quot;documentURI&quot; is the name of the document to be created in the 
	repository which is relative to the root of the configuration 
	repository such as &quot;cells/MyCell/myfile.xml&quot;, and the &quot;filename&quot; 
	is the name of the file to create which must be a valid local file 
	name such as &quot;c:/myfile&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7078E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7078E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7078E=WASX7078E: Missing config id: no id found in &quot;{0}&quot;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The wsadmin tool did not recognize the configuration ID that has been specified for an AdminConfig command.  No opening parenthesis was found.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a valid configuration ID using one of two forms: name(uri) or (uri).
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7478I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINAPP_HELP_NOUSEAUTOLINK" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINAPP_HELP_NOUSEAUTOLINK=WASX7478I: &quot;nouseAutoLink&quot; option; the EJB reference targets do not resolve automatically. The default setting is &quot;nouseAutoLink&quot;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purpose only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7077E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7077E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7077E=WASX7077E: Incomplete config id: need closing parenthesis in &quot;{0}&quot;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The wsadmin tool did not recognize the configuration ID that has been specified for an AdminConfig command. No closing parenthesis was found.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a valid configuration ID using one of two forms: name(uri) or (uri).
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7001I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="GENERAL_HELP" varFormat="Java">
    GENERAL_HELP=WASX7001I: wsadmin is the executable for WebSphere scripting. 
Syntax: 

wsadmin 
	[ -h(elp)  ] 
	[ -?  ]  
	[ -c &lt;command&gt; ] 
	[ -p &lt;properties_file_name&gt;] 
	[ -profile &lt;profile_script_name&gt;] 
	[ -f &lt;script_file_name&gt;] 
	[ -javaoption java_option] 
	[ -lang  language]  
	[ -wsadmin_classpath  class path]  
	[ -profileName profile]  
	[ -conntype  
		SOAP
			[-host host_name]
			[-port port_number]
			[-user userid]
			[-password password] | 
		RMI
			[-host host_name]
			[-port port_number]
			[-user userid]
			[-password password] | 
		JSR160RMI
			[-host host_name]
			[-port port_number]
			[-user userid]
			[-password password] | 
		IPC
			[-ipchost host_name]
			[-port port_number]
			[-user userid]
			[-password password] | 
		NONE 
	]
	[ -jobid &lt;jobid_string&gt;] 
	[ -tracefile &lt;trace_file&gt;] 
	[ -appendtrace &lt;true/false&gt;] 
	[ script parameters ]

Where 	&quot;command&quot; is a command to be passed to the script processor; 
	&quot;properties_file_name&quot; is a java properties file to be used; 
	&quot;profile_script_name&quot; is a script file to be run before the 
		main command or file; 
	&quot;script_file_name&quot; is a command to be passed to the script processor; 
	&quot;java_option&quot; is a java standard or non-standard option to be passed 
		to the java program; 
	&quot;language&quot; is the language to be used to interpret scripts; 
		supported values are &quot;jacl&quot; and &quot;jython&quot;. 
	&quot;classpath&quot; is a class path to be appended to built-in one;
	&quot;-conntype&quot;  specifies the type of connection to be used; 
		the default argument is &quot;SOAP&quot; 
		a conntype of &quot;NONE&quot; means that no server connection is made
		and certain operations will be performed in local mode;
	&quot;host_name&quot;  is the host used for the SOAP or RMI connection; 
		the default is the local host; 
	&quot;port_number&quot;  is the port used for the SOAP or RMI connection; 
	&quot;userid&quot;  is the userid required when the server is running in
		secure mode;
	&quot;password&quot;  is the password required when the server is running in
		secure mode;
	&quot;script parameters&quot;  is anything else on the command line.  These 
		are passed to the script in the argv variable; the number of
		parameters is available in the argc variable.
	&quot;jobid_string&quot; is a jobID string to be used to audit each invocation 
		of wsadmin;
	&quot;trace_file&quot; is the log file name and location where wsadmin trace 
		output is directed;

If no command or script is specified, an interpreter shell is 
created for interactive use. To leave an interactive scripting session,
use the &quot;quit&quot; or &quot;exit&quot; commands.

Several commands, properties files, and profiles may be specified 
on a single command line.  They are processed and run in 
order of their specification.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7039I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINCONTROL_HELP_GETDEFAULTDOMAIN" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINCONTROL_HELP_GETDEFAULTDOMAIN=WASX7039I: Method: getDefaultDomain

	Arguments: none

	Description: returns &quot;WebSphere&quot;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7245I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINAPP_HELP_UPDATEACCESSIDS" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINAPP_HELP_UPDATEACCESSIDS=WASX7245I: Method: updateAccessIDs

	Arguments: application name, boolean:bAll

	Description: Updates the application binding file for an installed 
	application with access IDs for all the users and groups.  Specifying 
	true for bAll updates all the users/groups even if there are access
	IDs already present in the bindings.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7449I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINAPP_HELP_TARGET" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINAPP_HELP_TARGET=WASX7449I: &quot;target&quot; option; specifies the target for AdminApp install functions.
Example of target option value is WebSphere:cell=mycell,node=mynode,server=myserver
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7009E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CONN_REQUIRES_PORT" varFormat="Java">
    CONN_REQUIRES_PORT=WASX7009E: The &quot;{0}&quot; connection type requires that a port be specified in a properties file or with &quot;-port&quot; on the command line.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The wsadmin launcher cannot determine what port number should be used when a connector is created.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a -port option on the wsadmin command line or a com.ws.scripting.port property in the wsadmin.properties file.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7181I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINAPP_HELP_NODEPLOYEJB.PRECOMPILEJSPS" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINAPP_HELP_NODEPLOYEJB.PRECOMPILEJSPS=WASX7181I: &quot;nodeployejb.preCompileJSPs&quot; option; specifies that EJBDeploy should not pre-compile JSPs; this is the default setting.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7464I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINAPP_HELP_DEPLOYEJB.SQLJCLASSPATH" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINAPP_HELP_DEPLOYEJB.SQLJCLASSPATH=WASX7464I: &quot;deployejb.sqljclasspath&quot; option; specifies the SQLJ classpath for EJBDeploy
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7230I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINAPP_HELP_WAS.INSTALL.ROOT" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINAPP_HELP_WAS.INSTALL.ROOT=WASX7230I: &quot;was.install.root&quot; option; this option is obsolete
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7062I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINAPP_HELP_HELP" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINAPP_HELP_HELP=WASX7062I: Method: help

	Arguments: none

	Description: Display general help for AdminApp.

	Method: help

	Arguments: method or option

	Description: Display help for the AdminApp method or option specified 
	by String.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7477I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINAPP_HELP_BLANAME" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINAPP_HELP_BLANAME=WASX7477I: &quot;blaname&quot; option; use this option to specify the name of the business level application.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purpose only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7031I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="JYTHON_WELCOME_HELP" varFormat="Java">
    JYTHON_WELCOME_HELP=WASX7031I: For help, enter: &quot;print Help.help()&quot;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7034I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINCONTROL_HELP_RECONNECT" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINCONTROL_HELP_RECONNECT=WASX7034I: Method: reconnect

	Arguments: none

	Description: Reconnects with the server
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7243I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINAPP_HELP_RAR.DESC" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINAPP_HELP_RAR.DESC=WASX7243I: &quot;rar.desc&quot; option; this option is a description of the J2CResourceAdapter.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7404I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINAPP_HELP_VIEW" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINAPP_HELP_VIEW=WASX7404I: Method: view

	Arguments: name, taskname option

	Description: View the task specified by the &quot;taskname option&quot;
	parameter for the application or module specified by the &quot;name&quot;
	parameter. Use &quot;-tasknames&quot; as the option to get a list of valid
	task names for the application. Otherwise, specify one or more
	task names as the option.

	Method: view

	Arguments: name

	Description: View the application or module specified by
	the &quot;name&quot; parameter.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7293I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINCONFIG_HELP_CONVERTTOCLUSTER" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINCONFIG_HELP_CONVERTTOCLUSTER=WASX7293I: Method: convertToCluster

	Arguments: server id, cluster name

	Description: Creates a new ServerCluster object with the name 
	specified by &quot;cluster name,&quot; and makes the server specified by 
	&quot;server id&quot; the first member of this cluster.  Applications loaded
	on this server are now configured on the new cluster.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7007E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DASH_CONNTYPE_NEEDS_FOLLOWING_CONN" varFormat="Java">
    DASH_CONNTYPE_NEEDS_FOLLOWING_CONN=WASX7007E: &quot;-conntype&quot; option must be followed by connection type information.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The wsadmin launcher has been invoked with the -conntype option, but no connection type argument was found.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a connection type for the -conntype option and reissue the wsadmin command.  For example, the SOAP, RMI, or NONE connection types are valid values for the -conntype option.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7288I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINCONTROL_HELP_GETATTRIBUTE_JMX" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINCONTROL_HELP_GETATTRIBUTE_JMX=WASX7288I: Method: getAttribute_jmx

	Arguments: object name (type ObjectName), attribute (String)

	Description: Returns value of &quot;attribute&quot; for the MBean described by 
	&quot;object name.&quot;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7183I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINAPP_HELP_NODISTRIBUTEAPP" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINAPP_HELP_NODISTRIBUTEAPP=WASX7183I: &quot;nodistributeApp&quot; option; specifies that the application management component should not distribute application binaries.  The default setting is &quot;distributeApp&quot;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7098I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINAPP_HELP_OPTIONS" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINAPP_HELP_OPTIONS=WASX7098I: Method: options

	Arguments: none

	Description: Displays the general options available for every 
	application to be installed.

	Method: options

	Arguments: filename

	Description: Displays all the options available for installing the 
	application in the file specified by &quot;filename&quot;.

	Method: options

	Arguments: appname

	Description: Displays all the options available for editing the 
	application specified by &quot;appname&quot;.

	Method: options

	Arguments: modulename

	Description: Displays all the options available for editing the 
	application module specified by &quot;modulename&quot;.

	Method: options

	Arguments: filename, operation

	Description: Displays all the options available for the 
	file specified by &quot;filename&quot; using the specified operation.
	Valid operations are &quot;installapp&quot;, &quot;updateapp&quot;, &quot;addmodule&quot;, 
	and &quot;updatemodule&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7309W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7309W" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7309W=WASX7309W: No &quot;save&quot; was performed before the script &quot;{0}&quot; exited; configuration changes will not be saved.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The changes invoked by a script concluded were not saved.  No configuration changes were saved.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the script uses the AdminConfig save command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7418E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7418E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7418E=WASX7418E: Application update for {0} failed: see previous messages for details.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The wsadmin tool did not run the AdminApp update command.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7033I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINCONTROL_HELP_GETPORT" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINCONTROL_HELP_GETPORT=WASX7033I: Method: getPort

	Arguments: none

	Description: Returns the port used for scripting connection.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7424I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINAPP_HELP_CREATEMBEANSFORRESOURCES" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINAPP_HELP_CREATEMBEANSFORRESOURCES=WASX7424I: &quot;createMBeansForResources&quot; option: this option specifies that MBeans are created for all the resources such as servlets, jsps, EJBs, defined in an application when the application is started on a deployment target; the default is nocreateMBeansForResources.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7417E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7417E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7417E=WASX7417E: {0} option is required when {1} content type and {2} operation are specified.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The missing option is a required option if the specified content type and operation are provided in the update command.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify the missing option and reissue the update command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7416E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7416E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7416E=WASX7416E: {0} option is required when {1} content type is specified.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The missing option is required when the specified content type is provided in the update command.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify the missing option and reissue the update command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7015E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="EXCEPTION_RUNNING_COMMAND" varFormat="Java">
    EXCEPTION_RUNNING_COMMAND=WASX7015E: Exception running command: &quot;{0}&quot;; exception information:
{1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The wsadmin tool cannot run interactive mode for the specified command.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the accompanying exception information to determine the appropriate action.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7267I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HELP_HELP_HELP" varFormat="Java">
    HELP_HELP_HELP=WASX7267I: Method: help

	Arguments: none

	Description: Display general help for Help.

	Method: help

	Arguments: method

	Description: Display help for the Help method specified 
	by String.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7289I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINCONTROL_HELP_GETATTRIBUTES_JMX" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINCONTROL_HELP_GETATTRIBUTES_JMX=WASX7289I: Method: getAttributes_jmx

	Arguments: object name (type ObjectName), attributes (String[])

	Description: Returns an AttributeList object containing the values
	of the attributes named in &quot;attributes&quot; for the object named by 
	&quot;object name.&quot;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7307E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7307E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7307E=WASX7307E: Cannot create object of type &quot;{0}&quot; on a Network Deployment Manager node.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The AdminConfig create command cannot create this type of object.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Modify the create command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7415W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7415W" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7415W=WASX7415W: Ignoring {0} option when {1} operation is specified.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The option specified in the message is not required if the specified operation is provided in the update command.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7249E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="USER_REQUIRES_ARG" varFormat="Java">
    USER_REQUIRES_ARG=WASX7249E: The &quot;-user&quot; option requires a user name.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The wsadmin launcher has been invoked with the -user option, but no user name argument was found.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a user name for the -user option and reissue the wsadmin command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7306E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7306E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7306E=WASX7306E: Cannot complete testConnection function because the node for Data Source &quot;{0}&quot; cannot be determined.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The wsadmin tool cannot determine the node for the specified DataSource that was specified by the AdminControl testConnection command.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the DataSource is correctly configured.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7414W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7414W" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7414W=WASX7414W: Ignoring {0} option when {1} content type is specified.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The option specified in this message is not required if the specified content type is provided in the update command.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7085I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINCONFIG_HELP_GETID" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINCONFIG_HELP_GETID=WASX7085I: Method: getid

	Arguments: containment path

	Description: Returns the configuration ID for an object described by the
	given containment path -- for example, /Node:myNode/Server:s1/JDBCProvider:jdbc1/
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7379E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="LANGUAGE_NOT_SUPPORTED" varFormat="Java">
    LANGUAGE_NOT_SUPPORTED=WASX7379E: Language &quot;{0}&quot; is not supported. Supported languages are jacl and jython.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An unsupported scripting language was specified.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a supported scripting language with the -lang option or com.ibm.ws.scripting.defaultLang option.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7305I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7305I" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7305I=WASX7305I: Client is connected to a server of type &quot;{0}&quot;.  The server &quot;{1}&quot; will be started on node &quot;{2}&quot; without attempting to synchronize the configuration.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The wsadmin tool cannot synchronize the configuration before startup because a node agent process is starting.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WSCP0140E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WSCP_EXC_OPENING_BRACE" varFormat="Java">
    WSCP_EXC_OPENING_BRACE=WSCP0140E: &quot;{0}&quot; found instead of expected &apos;{&apos;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    There is a syntax error in a string provided in an attribute list
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the attribute list syntax.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7413E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7413E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7413E=WASX7413E: Invalid operation value: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The value for the operation option is not valid. Valid values for this parameter are app, file, modulefile, and partialapp.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Reissue the update command with the correct operation value.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7472I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINCONFIG_HELP_RESETATTRIBUTES" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINCONFIG_HELP_RESETATTRIBUTES=WASX7472I: Method: resetAttributes

	Arguments: config id, attributes

	Description: Use the resetAttributes command to reset the specific attributes for a
	configuration object.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7059I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINCONTROL_HELP_GETCONFIGID" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINCONTROL_HELP_GETCONFIGID=WASX7059I: Method: getConfigId

	Arguments: object name

	Description: Returns a configuration ID for the configuration object that
	corresponds to the MBean named by &quot;object name.&quot;  This function
	communicates with the configuration service to look up a configuration ID that
	can be used by AdminConfig.  If no configuration object exists that
	corresponds to the supplied object name string, getConfigId returns an
	empty string.

	The object name string supplied as input to this function may be a
	wildcard -- for example:
		&quot;type=Server,*&quot;
	In this case, getConfigId returns the configuration ID of the first matching
	object found.  Message WASX7026W is also displayed as a warning.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7030I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="JAVASCRIPT_WELCOME_HELP" varFormat="Java">
    JAVASCRIPT_WELCOME_HELP=WASX7030I: For help, enter: &quot;Help.help()&quot;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7412E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7412E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7412E=WASX7412E: Invalid content type value: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The value for the content type parameter is not valid.  Valid values for this parameter are add, addupdate, delete, and update.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Reissue the update command with the correct content type value.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7160I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINAPP_HELP_DEFAULTBINDING.DATASOURCE.JNDI" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINAPP_HELP_DEFAULTBINDING.DATASOURCE.JNDI=WASX7160I: &quot;defaultbinding.datasource.jndi&quot; option; specifies the JNDI name for the default datasource
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7303I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7303I" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7303I=WASX7303I: The following options are passed to the scripting environment and are available as arguments that are stored in the argv variable: &quot;{0}&quot;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The wsadmin tool did not recognize some arguments as command line parameters.  The wsadmin tool stores these arguments in the argv variable and are available to the script.  The argc variable contains the number of arguments available in the argv variable.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the unrecognized arguments are arguments for scripts or commands to use.  Correct or delete unrecognized options if necessary.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7411W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7411W" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7411W=WASX7411W: Ignoring the following provided option: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The wsadmin tool cannot recognize some options specified in the AdminApp command.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that options provided in the message are correct.  Reissue the AdminApp command if necessary. Otherwise, no action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7166I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINAPP_HELP_DEFAULTBINDING.VIRTUAL_HOST" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINAPP_HELP_DEFAULTBINDING.VIRTUAL_HOST=WASX7166I: &quot;defaultbinding.virtual.host&quot; option; specifies the default virtual host name.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7268I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HELP_HELP_ATTRIBUTES" varFormat="Java">
    HELP_HELP_ATTRIBUTES=WASX7268I: Method: attributes

	Arguments: MBean

	Description: Display information about the attributes of the 
	specified MBean.

	Method: attributes

	Arguments: MBean, attribute name

	Description: Display information about the specified attribute on 
	the specified MBean.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX8019E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX8019E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX8019E=WASX8019E: Incorrect number of key fields specified for step {0}: {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The option values provided to the specified step are not complete.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify the correct number of key fields for the step and reissue the AdminTask command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7302E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7302E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7302E=WASX7302E: Cannot get tasks using file {0}. Ensure that this file exists and is readable.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The AdminApp options command did not obtain task options from the specified ear file.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that this file exists and is readable.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7367I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINAPP_HELP_UPDATE.IGNORE.OLD" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINAPP_HELP_UPDATE.IGNORE.OLD=WASX7367I: &quot;update.ignore.old&quot; option; this option specifies that when an application is updated, the bindings from the old version are ignored during the reinstall operation.  This option only has meaning if the &quot;update&quot; option is specified; otherwise it is ignored.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7338E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7338E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7338E=WASX7338E: Caught exception stopping server &quot;{0}.&quot;  Exception information:
{1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The AdminControl stopServer command did not run.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the wsadmin.traceout file and the server log files to determine the source of the problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7099I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINAPP_HELP_TASKINFO" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINAPP_HELP_TASKINFO=WASX7099I: Method: taskInfo

	Arguments: filename, taskname

	Description: Runs default bindings for the application specified 
	by &quot;filename&quot; and displays detailed information about the install task 
	specified by &quot;taskname&quot;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7300I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINCONFIG_HELP_GETVALIDATIONSEVERITYRESULT" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINCONFIG_HELP_GETVALIDATIONSEVERITYRESULT=WASX7300I: Method: getValidationSeverityResult

	Arguments: severity

	Description: Returns the number of validation messages with the given 
	severity from the most recent validation.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX8018E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX8018E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX8018E=WASX8018E: Cannot find a match for option value {0} for step {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The option values for the specified step do not match the existing data.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify the correct option values for the step and reissue the AdminTask command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7337I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7337I" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7337I=WASX7337I: Invoked stop for server &quot;{0}&quot; on node &quot;{1}&quot;; Waiting for stop completion.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A request has been made to stop the specified server process.  The scripting process will wait until the stop is complete or the action times out.  In the first case, WASX7264I should be issued; in the second case, WASX7265W should be issued.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7301E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7301E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7301E=WASX7301E: Cannot get the task info for {0} using file {1}. Ensure that this file exists and is readable.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The AdminApp taskInfo command did not obtain task information from the specified ear file.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the file exists and is readable, and that the task name is spelled correctly.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7473I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINAPP_HELP_EXPORTTOLOCAL" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINAPP_HELP_EXPORTTOLOCAL=WASX7473I: &quot;exportToLocal&quot; option; specifies the option for AdminApp export function to export application to the client local machine.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX8017E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX8017E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX8017E=WASX8017E: Command provider error: step {0} does not contain any key
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The AdminTask command contains an internal error.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Retry with scripting trace on and take a look wsadmin.traceout. CMSG0002.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7225I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINAPP_HELP_VALIDATEAPP" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINAPP_HELP_VALIDATEAPP=WASX7225I: &quot;validateApp&quot; option; this option is obsolete
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7119E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7119E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7119E=WASX7119E: Invalid option &quot;{0}.&quot;  Valid options are &quot;overwriteOnConflict,&quot; and &quot;rollbackOnConflict.&quot;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The mode that has been specified with the AdminConfig setSaveMode command is not valid.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a valid save mode. The valid options are &quot;overwriteOnConflict&quot; and &quot;rollbackOnConflict&quot;.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7227W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7227W" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7227W=WASX7227W: Profile {0} is in the wrong language and will not be executed; language used is {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The wsadmin tool cannot run the profile that has been specified is not in the same scripting language as the scripting session.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Remove the profile from the wsadmin.properties file or the wsadmin command line options.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7049I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINCONTROL_HELP_COMPLETEOBJECTNAME" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINCONTROL_HELP_COMPLETEOBJECTNAME=WASX7049I: Method: completeObjectName

	Arguments: object name, template

	Description: Returns a String version of an object name that matches
	the &quot;template.&quot;  For example, the template might be &quot;type=Server,*&quot;
	If there are several MBeans that match the template, the first match
	is returned.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7336E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7336E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7336E=WASX7336E: The &quot;{0}&quot; option is required if &quot;{1}&quot; is specified.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A required option is missing for the AdminApp install command.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify each required option and reinvoke the command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7052I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINCONTROL_HELP_GETTYPE" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINCONTROL_HELP_GETTYPE=WASX7052I: Method: getType

	Arguments: none

	Description: Returns connection type used for scripting connection.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX8016E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX8016E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX8016E=WASX8016E: Command provider error: null object type
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The AdminTask command contains an internal error.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Retry with scripting trace on and take a look wsadmin.traceout. CMSG0002.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7118I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7118I" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7118I=WASX7118I: Changes have been made to the configuration, but these changes have not been saved.
Enter &quot;quit&quot; or &quot;exit&quot; if you want to terminate this session without saving your changes.
To save the changes, invoke the &quot;save&quot; command on the AdminConfig object.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The user requested to terminate an interactive scripting session, but configuration changes have not yet been saved.  Commit the unsaved changes.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    To exit the scripting session without saving your changes, respond with &quot;quit&quot; or &quot;exit.&quot;  Any other response keeps the session active.  Use the AdminConfig save command to commit any unsaved changes.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7444E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7444E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7444E=WASX7444E: Invalid parameter value &quot;{0}&quot; for parameter &quot;{1}&quot; on command &quot;{2}&quot;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A parameter value is not valid. Do not specify parameter values as null or empty strings.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Reissue the AdminConfig command with the correct parameter value.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7175I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINAPP_HELP_DEPLOYEJB.RMIC" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINAPP_HELP_DEPLOYEJB.RMIC=WASX7175I: &quot;deployejb.rmic&quot; option; specifies extra RMIC options to be used for EJBDeploy
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7454I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINAPP_HELP_NOALLOWDISPATCHREMOTEINCLUDE" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINAPP_HELP_NOALLOWDISPATCHREMOTEINCLUDE=WASX7454I: &quot;noallowDispatchRemoteInclude&quot; option; Disables an enterprise application to dispatch 
includes to resources across web modules in different JVMs in a managed node environment via the standard RequestDispatcher mechanism.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7273I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HELP_HELP_CLASSNAME" varFormat="Java">
    HELP_HELP_CLASSNAME=WASX7273I: Method: classname

	Arguments: MBean

	Description: Display information about the classname of the 
	specified MBean.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX8015E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX8015E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX8015E=WASX8015E: Invalid option value for step {0}: {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Option value provided to the specified step is not valid.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Reissue the AdminTask command with the correct option value for step.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7443I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7443I" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7443I=WASX7443I: Server &quot;{0}&quot; on node &quot;{1}&quot; is not being monitored. Please verify that the server has stopped before continuing.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The wsadmin tool issued a request to stop the specified server process. The scripting process will not wait until the request succeeds.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the server stopped before continuing.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7438I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINAPP_HELP_NOPROCESSEMBEDDEDCONFIG" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINAPP_HELP_NOPROCESSEMBEDDEDCONFIG=WASX7438I: &quot;noprocessEmbeddedConfig&quot; option; Use this option to ignore the embedded configuration data that is included in the application. The default setting is &quot;processEmbeddedConfig&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7423I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINAPP_HELP_OPERATION" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINAPP_HELP_OPERATION=WASX7423I: &quot;operation&quot; option: this option is used in the update or updateInteractive command to specify the operation to be performed. Valid values are
	add - adds new content
	addupdate - performs add or update based on existence
	   of contents in the application
	delete - deletes contents
	update - update existing contents
This option is required if content type is file or modulefile.
This option must have &quot;update&quot; as the value if content type
is app. This option is ignored for other content type values.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX8014E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX8014E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX8014E=WASX8014E: Step {0} is not a table.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    More than one set of data values was specified for the step and is not a table.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Provide one set of data values to the step indicated in this error message and reissue the AdminTask command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7442E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7442E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7442E=WASX7442E: &quot;{0}&quot; action not supported when node name is not provided.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Specify the node name as one of the arguments.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Include the node name for the server in your arguments.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7116E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7116E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7116E=WASX7116E: Cannot copy file &quot;{0}&quot; to file &quot;{1}&quot;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The wsadmin tool cannot copy the ear file to a temporary location for AdminApp processing.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the wsadmin.traceout log file to determine the problem. Verify that there is enough space in the file system and that there are no file permission problems.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7170I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINAPP_HELP_NODEPLOYEJB" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINAPP_HELP_NODEPLOYEJB=WASX7170I: &quot;nodeployejb&quot; option; specifies that EJBDeploy should not be run during install; this is the default setting.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7330I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINAPP_HELP_CLUSTER" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINAPP_HELP_CLUSTER=WASX7330I: &quot;cluster&quot; option; specifies the cluster name for AdminApp install functions.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX8013I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX8013I" varFormat="Java">
    WASX8013I=WASX8013I: Detailed help for step: {0}

Description: {1}

Collection: {2}

Arguments:
{3}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7053I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINCONFIG_GENERAL_HELP" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINCONFIG_GENERAL_HELP=WASX7053I: The AdminConfig object communicates with the Config Service in a
	WebSphere server to manipulate configuration data for a WebSphere
	installation.  AdminConfig has commands to list, create, remove,
	display, and modify configuration data, as well as commands to display
	information about configuration data types.

	Most of the commands supported by AdminConfig operate in two modes:
	the default mode is one in which AdminConfig communicates with the
	WebSphere server to accomplish its tasks.  A local mode is also
	possible, in which no server communication takes place.  The local
	mode of operation is invoked by bringing up the scripting client with
	no server connected using the command line &quot;-conntype NONE&quot; option
	or setting the &quot;com.ibm.ws.scripting.connectionType=NONE&quot; property in
	the wsadmin.properties.

	The following commands are supported by AdminConfig; more detailed
	information about each of these commands is available by using the
	&quot;help&quot; command of AdminConfig and supplying the name of the command
	as an argument.

attributes	Shows the attributes for a given type
checkin		Checks a file into the configuration repository
convertToCluster
		Converts a server to be the first member of a new ServerCluster
create		Creates a configuration object, given a type, a parent, and
		a list of attributes, and optionally an attribute name for the
		new object
createClusterMember
		Creates a new server that is a member of an existing cluster
createDocument	Creates a new document in the configuration repository
createUsingTemplate
		Creates an object using a particular template type
defaults	Displays the default values for attributes of a given type
deleteDocument	Deletes a document from the configuration repository
existsDocument	Tests for the existence of a document in the configuration
		repository
extract		Extracts a file from the configuration repository
getCrossDocumentValidationEnabled
		Returns true if cross-document validation is enabled
getid		Shows the configuration ID of an object, given a string version
		of its containment
getObjectName	Given a configuration ID, returns a string version of the
		ObjectName for the corresponding running MBean, if any
getObjectType	Given a configuration ID, returns a string version of the
		object type
getSaveMode	Returns the mode used when &quot;save&quot; is invoked
getValidationLevel
		Returns the validation used when files are extracted from the
		repository.
getValidationSeverityResult
		Returns the number of messages of a given severity from the
		most recent validation
hasChanges	Returns true if unsaved configuration changes exist
help		Shows help information
installResourceAdapter
		Installs a J2C resource adapter with the given rar file name
		and an option string in the node
list		Lists all configuration objects of a given type
listTemplates	Lists all available configuration templates of a given type
modify		Changes specified attributes of a given configuration object
parents		Shows the objects which contain a given type
queryChanges	Returns a list of unsaved files
remove		Removes the specified configuration object
required	Displays the required attributes of a given type.
reset		Discards unsaved configuration changes
resetAttributes	Resets value of the specified attributes.
save		Commits unsaved changes to the configuration repository
setCrossDocumentValidationEnabled
		Sets the cross-document validation enabled mode.
setSaveMode	Changes the mode used when &quot;save&quot; is invoked
setValidationLevel
		Sets the validation used when files are extracted from the
		repository.
show		Shows the attributes of a given configuration object
showall		Recursively shows the attributes of a given configuration
		object, and all the objects contained within each attribute.
showAttribute	Displays only the value for the single attribute specified.
types		Shows the possible types for configuration
uninstallResourceAdapter
		Uninstalls a J2C resource adapter with the given resource
		adapter configuration ID.
unsetAttributes	Unsets value of the specified attributes.
validate	Invokes validation
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7441E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7441E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7441E=WASX7441E: &quot;{0}&quot; action not supported when process type of server being stopped is &quot;{1}&quot;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Use the terminate flag only to stop servers of the managed process type.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the server to stop is a managed process.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7115E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7115E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7115E=WASX7115E: Cannot read input file &quot;{0}&quot;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The wsadmin tool cannot read the ear file when preparing to copy it to a temporary location for AdminApp processing.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the wsadmin.traceout log file to determine the problem. Verify that the file path is correct and that there are no file permission problems.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX8012E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX8012E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX8012E=WASX8012E: Step {0} is not enabled.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The wsadmin tool cannot modify the data in the specified step.  It is not enabled for the task.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Reissue the AdminTask command without the step option indicated in this error message.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7114E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7114E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7114E=WASX7114E: Cannot create temporary file in directory &quot;{0}&quot;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The wsadmin tool cannot copy the ear file to a temporary location for AdminApp processing.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the wsadmin.traceout log file to determine the problem. Verify that there is enough space in the file system, and that there are no file permission problems.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7331I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7331I" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7331I=WASX7331I: Unexpected exception received when querying for changes in this session: 	{0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The wsadmin tool created an exception because it could not determine if configuration changes have been made during the session.  The connection to the server process might have broken before the scripting session was stopped.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX8011W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX8011W" varFormat="Java">
    WASX8011W=WASX8011W: AdminTask object is not available.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The wsadmin tool cannot connect to a server.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Reissue the wsadmin command to create a server connection.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7203I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINCONFIG_HELP_GETCROSSDOCUMENTVALIDATIONENABLED" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINCONFIG_HELP_GETCROSSDOCUMENTVALIDATIONENABLED=WASX7203I: Method: getCrossDocumentValidationEnabled

	Arguments: none

	Description: Returns a message giving the current cross-document
	enablement setting.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7475E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7475E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7475E=WASX7475E: The {0} output file already exists. Specify another output file name.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A file, which has the same name as the specified output file name in exportFile command, exists in the local directory.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Rerun the exportFile command and specify a non-existent output file name.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7113E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7113E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7113E=WASX7113E: Task &quot;{0}&quot; not valid; valid tasks are &quot;{1}&quot;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The task name is not valid for the AdminApp taskInfo command that has been invoked.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a valid task name as described in the WAS7113E message output.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7103I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINAPP_HELP_EDITINTERACTIVE" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINAPP_HELP_EDITINTERACTIVE=WASX7103I: Method: editInteractive

	Arguments: application name, options

	Description: Edits the application specified by &quot;application name&quot; 
	using the options specified by &quot;options&quot;. The user is prompted for 
	information about each relevant task.

	Method: editInteractive

	Arguments: application name

	Description: Edits the application specified by &quot;application name.&quot;
	The user is prompted for information about each relevant task.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7257E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7257E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7257E=WASX7257E: Cannot locate NodeAgent object on node &quot;{0}&quot;.  Unable to start server &quot;{1}&quot; on that node.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The AdminControl startServer command did not run because the NodeAgent on the server&apos;s node is not running.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Start the NodeAgent on the appropriate machine.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX8010E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX8010E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX8010E=WASX8010E: Invalid scripting language: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified language is not supported.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a supported scripting language.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7294I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINCONFIG_HELP_EXTRACT" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINCONFIG_HELP_EXTRACT=WASX7294I: Method: extract

	Arguments: documentURI, filename

	Description: Extracts a configuration repository document that 
	is described by the &quot;documentURI&quot; and places it in the file named 
	by the &quot;filename&quot;.  The &quot;documentURI&quot; describes a document that 
	must exist in the repository and is relative to the root of 
	repository such as &quot;cells/MyCell/myfile.xml&quot;, and the &quot;filename&quot; 
	must be a valid local file name to extract the document to such as 
	&quot;c:/myfile&quot;. This method returns an opaque &quot;digest&quot; object which 
	should be used to check the file back in the repository using the 
	checkin command.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7259I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINCONTROL_HELP_STOPSERVER" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINCONTROL_HELP_STOPSERVER=WASX7259I: Method: stopServer

	Arguments: server name

	Description: Stops a server.

	Method: stopServer

	Arguments: server name, immediate flag

	Description: Stops a server.  If the &quot;immediate flag&quot; is set to
	&quot;immediate&quot; then a stopImmediate is performed for the specified
	server.  Otherwise, a normal stop is performed.

	Method: stopServer

	Arguments: server name, node name

	Description: Stops a server in the specified node.

	Method: stopServer

	Arguments: server name, node name, immediate flag

	Description: Stops a server in the specified node.  If the
	&quot;immediate flag&quot; is set to &quot;immediate&quot; then a stopImmediate
	is performed for the specified server.  Otherwise, a normal
	stop is performed.

	Method: stopServer

	Arguments: server name, node name, terminate flag

	Description: Stops a server on the specified node. If the 
	&quot;terminate flag&quot; is set to &quot;terminate&quot; then a terminate
	is performed for the specified server. Otherwise, a normal stop
	is performed.
	This operation can only be performed on a Managed Process.
	The node name is a required argument.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7112I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7112I" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7112I=WASX7112I: The following options are valid for &quot;{0}&quot;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This informational message displays in response to an AdminApp options command.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7256W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7256W" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7256W=WASX7256W: Cannot locate NodeSync object on node &quot;{0}&quot;.  Unable to synchronize configurations before starting server &quot;{1}&quot;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The AdminControl startServer invocation did not run because the wsadmin tool cannot locate the NodeSync object on the specified node.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the logs on the node if the NodeSync object is not running.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7365I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7365I" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7365I=WASX7365I: Explanation: {0}
 User action: {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7232I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINAPP_HELP_APPNAME" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINAPP_HELP_APPNAME=WASX7232I: &quot;appname&quot; option; use this option to specify the name of the application.  The default is to use the display name of the application.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7220E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7220E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7220E=WASX7220E: This operation was invoked with the &quot;-local&quot; option, but the scripting client is connected to process &quot;{0}&quot; on node &quot;{1}.&quot; Local operations can not be performed when a connection exists to a server.  You can either re-run the command without the &quot;-local&quot; option, or invoke the scripting client without servers running.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The &quot;-local&quot; option is not permitted for AdminApp functions when the scripting client is connected to a server.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Remove the &quot;-local&quot; option, or use the &quot;-conntype NONE&quot; option to avoid connecting to a server.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7165I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINAPP_HELP_DEFAULTBINDING.EJBJNDI.PREFIX" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINAPP_HELP_DEFAULTBINDING.EJBJNDI.PREFIX=WASX7165I: &quot;defaultbinding.ejbjndi.prefix&quot; option; specifies the prefix for the JNDI name of EJBs.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7205I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINAPP_HELP_LISTMODULES" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINAPP_HELP_LISTMODULES=WASX7205I: Method: listModules

	Arguments: application name, options

	Description: List the modules in the application specified by 
	&quot;application name using the options specified by &quot;options&quot;.  The valid 
	option is &quot;-server&quot;.  If &quot;-server&quot; is specified, then the
	return value will include the server information on each module.

	Method: listModules

	Arguments: application name

	Description: List the modules in the application specified by 
	&quot;application name&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7111E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7111E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7111E=WASX7111E: Cannot find a match for supplied option: &quot;{0}&quot; for task &quot;{1}&quot;. The supplied option must match with the existing task data in the application and the existing task data are: &quot;{2}&quot;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    =The data is not valid for an AdminApp install command for the specified task.  The task consists of some number of items, some of which cannot be changed.  The unchangeable items are a key for the data must exactly match the information included in an install command for this task.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Invoke the AdminApp taskInfo command for this file and task name to determine what information is needed for the task.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7466I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINCONFIG_HELP_GETOBJECTTYPE" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINCONFIG_HELP_GETOBJECTTYPE=WASX7466I: Method: getObjectType

	Arguments: config id

	Description: Displays the configuration object type by &quot;config id.&quot;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7224I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINAPP_HELP_NOPRECOMPILEJSPS" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINAPP_HELP_NOPRECOMPILEJSPS=WASX7224I: &quot;nopreCompileJSPs&quot; option; use this option to specify that JSPs are not to be precompiled.  This is the default.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7471I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINCONFIG_HELP_UNSETATTRIBUTES" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINCONFIG_HELP_UNSETATTRIBUTES=WASX7471I: Method: unsetAttributes

	Arguments: config id, attributes

	Description: Use the unsetAttributes command to reset the specific attributes for a
	configuration object to the default values.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7364E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7364E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7364E=WASX7364E: Error getting help information for message id {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The directory containing the help information does not exist.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    This exception is unexpected. The cause is not immediately known.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7169I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINAPP_HELP_DEPLOYEJB" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINAPP_HELP_DEPLOYEJB=WASX7169I: &quot;deployejb&quot; option; specifies that EJBDeploy should be run during install; the default is &quot;nodeployejb&quot;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7255E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7255E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7255E=WASX7255E: Cannot find server &quot;{0}&quot; in configuration data.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The AdminControl startServer command did not run because the server that has been specified does not exist.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the server name is spelled correctly.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7202I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINCONFIG_HELP_SETCROSSDOCUMENTVALIDATIONENABLED" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINCONFIG_HELP_SETCROSSDOCUMENTVALIDATIONENABLED=WASX7202I: Method: setCrossDocumentValidationEnabled

	Arguments: flag

	Description: Sets the cross-document validation enabled flag to
	true or false.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7287I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINCONTROL_HELP_ISREGISTERED_JMX" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINCONTROL_HELP_ISREGISTERED_JMX=WASX7287I: Method: isRegistered_jmx

	Arguments: object name (type ObjectName)

	Description: Returns true if supplied &quot;object name&quot; is registered.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7146I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7146I" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7146I=WASX7146I: The following configuration files contain unsaved changes:
 {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The wsadmin tool displays this informational message in response to the AdminConfig queryChanges command.  The command lists the files that have been updated by the scripting client since the last save or reset command.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7110E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7110E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7110E=WASX7110E: Incorrect number of elements in option: &quot;{0}&quot; for task: &quot;{1};&quot; number of elements should be {2}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The data is not valid for an AdminApp install command for the specified task.  The task consists of some number of items, but a different number has been supplied.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Invoke the AdminApp taskInfo command for this file and task name to determine what information is needed for the task.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7284I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINCONFIG_HELP_CREATECLUSTERMEMBER" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINCONFIG_HELP_CREATECLUSTERMEMBER=WASX7284I: Method: createClusterMember

	Arguments: cluster id, node id, member attributes

	Description: Creates a new Server object on the node specified 
	by &quot;node id.&quot;  This Server is created as a new member of the existing
	cluster specified by &quot;cluster id,&quot; and has attributes specified in
	&quot;member attributes.&quot;  One attribute is required: &quot;memberName.&quot;
	The Server is created using the default template for
	Server objects, and has the name and specified by the 
	&quot;memberName&quot; attribute.

	Method: createClusterMember

	Arguments: cluster id, node id, member attributes, template id

	Description: Creates a new Server object on the node specified 
	by &quot;node id.&quot;  This Server is created as a new member of the existing
	cluster specified by &quot;cluster id,&quot; and has attributes specified in
	&quot;member attributes.&quot;  One attribute is required: &quot;memberName.&quot;
	The Server is created using the Server template
	specified by &quot;template id,&quot; and has the name specified by
	the &quot;memberName&quot; attribute.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7402W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SECURITY_NONFIPS_PROVIDER" varFormat="Java">
    SECURITY_NONFIPS_PROVIDER=WASX7402W: &quot;Use FIPS&quot; is enabled, but the SSL provider is not IBMJSSEFIPS. FIPS approved cryptographic algorithms may not be used.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    You cannot use FIPS approved cryptographic algorithms if SSL provider is not IBMJSSEFIPS.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the exception in the trace log and correct the problem accordingly.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7363E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7363E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7363E=WASX7363E: No help available for message id {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Help message command cannot locate any message information for the specified message id.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the specified message id is correct.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7399E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7399E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7399E=WASX7399E: List of J2CResourceAdapter objects still using the specified Resource Adapter:
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    J2CResourceAdapter objects currently use the resource adapter specified in the uninstallResourceAdapter command.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Uninstall the resource adapters listed in this error message before attempting to uninstall the specified resource adapter. To force this uninstall action without uninstalling the other resource adapters first, use the -force option with uninstallResourceAdapter command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7254E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7254E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7254E=WASX7254E: &quot;{0}&quot; action not supported when process type is &quot;{1}&quot;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The wsadmin tool is connected to the wrong type of process.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the wsadmin tool is connected to the correct process.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7012E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="EXCEPTION_LOADING_PROPERTIES_FILE" varFormat="Java">
    EXCEPTION_LOADING_PROPERTIES_FILE=WASX7012E: Exception received while loading properties file {0}; exception information: &quot;{1}&quot;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    During wsadmin initialization, a properties file could not be loaded.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the wsadmin.traceout log file to determine the problem. Verify that there is enough space in the file system and that there are no file permission problems.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7021E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CANNOT_FIND_LANG_FOR_COMMANDS" varFormat="Java">
    CANNOT_FIND_LANG_FOR_COMMANDS=WASX7021E: Cannot determine scripting language for command invocation -- please specify &quot;-lang&quot; option on the command line.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The wsadmin tool cannot determine which scripting language to use with the -c option.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a supported scripting language with the -lang option on the wsadmin command line, or com.ibm.ws.scripting.defaultLang property in the wsadmin.properties file.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7398E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7398E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7398E=WASX7398E: List of applications still using the specified Resource Adapter:
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Applications currently use the resource adapter specified in the uninstallResourceAdapter command.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Uninstall the applications listed in this error message before uninstalling the resource adapter. To force this uninstall action without uninstalling applications first, specify the -force option with uninstallResourceAdapter command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7236I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINAPP_HELP_REMOTEDIR" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINAPP_HELP_REMOTEDIR=WASX7236I: &quot;remotedir&quot; option; this option is obsolete
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7470E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7470E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7470E=WASX7470E: One or more attributes name must be specified for unsetAttributes; received: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The attribute name will be unset is not specified.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Supply the attribute name to be unset.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7057I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINCONFIG_HELP_SHOW" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINCONFIG_HELP_SHOW=WASX7057I: Method: show

	Arguments: config id

	Description: Displays all the attributes for the configuration object
	named by &quot;config id.&quot;

	Method: show

	Arguments: config id, attribute list

	Description: Displays the attributes specified in &quot;attribute list&quot;
	for the configuration object named by &quot;config id.&quot;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7361I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7361I" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7361I=WASX7361I: No required attribute found for type &quot;{0}&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    No required attributes were found for the specified type.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7397I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7397I" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7397I=WASX7397I: The following J2CResourceAdapter objects are removed: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7252E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7252E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7252E=WASX7252E: Unable to locate running server &quot;{0}&quot; on node &quot;{1}&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The AdminControl stopServer command did not run because a running server of the specified name was not found.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the server name is spelled correctly.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7143E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7143E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7143E=WASX7143E: The object with id &quot;{0}&quot; does not exist.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The wsadmin tool did not process the AdminConfig command because a configuration ID that has been specified does not correspond to an existing configuration object.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the id is spelled correctly.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7234I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINAPP_HELP_CONTEXTROOT" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINAPP_HELP_CONTEXTROOT=WASX7234I: &quot;contextroot&quot; option; use this option to specify the context root to be used when installing a stand-alone war file.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7070E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CONFIG_NOT_AVAILABLE" varFormat="Java">
    CONFIG_NOT_AVAILABLE=WASX7070E: The configuration service is not available.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The AdminConfig command did not start because the wsadmin process is not connected to a server with a running config service.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a server with a running configuration services and reissue the wsadmin command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7322I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINCONFIG_HELP_DELETEDOCUMENT" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINCONFIG_HELP_DELETEDOCUMENT=WASX7322I: Method: deleteDocument

	Arguments: documentURI

	Description: Deletes a document from the configuration repository.
	The &quot;documentURI&quot; is the name of the document to be deleted from the 
	repository which is relative to the root of configuration repository 
	such as &quot;cells/MyCell/myfile.xml&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7250E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PASSWORD_REQUIRES_ARG" varFormat="Java">
    PASSWORD_REQUIRES_ARG=WASX7250E: The &quot;-password&quot; option requires a password.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The wsadmin launcher has been invoked with the -password option, but no password argument was found.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a password for the -password option and reissue the wsadmin command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7395E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7395E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7395E=WASX7395E: The specified values for -lang and -internalLang options are not the same. Use one or the other option but not both.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The -lang and -internalLang options are specified. However, the values for the two options are not the same.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify either the -lang or -internalLang option.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7419I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINAPP_HELP_UPDATE" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINAPP_HELP_UPDATE=WASX7419I: Method: update

	Arguments: application name, content type, options

	Description: updates the application specified by &quot;application
	name&quot; using update type specified by &quot;content type&quot; with
	options specified by &quot;options&quot;.

	Valid update content type values are 
		app - entire application
		file - a single file
		modulefile - a module
		partialapp - partial application

	All valid options for install command are valid for the
	update command. Additional update options are 
		-operation - operation to be performed. Valid values are
			add - adds new contents
			addupdate - performs add or updates based on
				existence of contents in the application
			delete - deletes contents
			update - update existing contents
		  This option is required if content type is file
		  and modulefile. This option must have &quot;update&quot; as
		  the value if content type is app. This option is
		  ignored if content type is partialapp.
		-contents - file containing the contents to be added or
		  updated. The specified file has to be local to the
		  scripting client. This option is required except for
		  delete operation.
		-contenturi - URI of the file to be added, updated, or
		  removed from the application. This option is required if 
		  content type is file or modulefile. This option 
		  is ignored if content type is app or partialapp.

	The AdminApp &quot;options&quot; command may be used to get a list of all 
	possible options for a given ear file.  The AdminApp &quot;help&quot; command
	may be used to get more information about each particular option.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7050I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINCONTROL_HELP_TRACE" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINCONTROL_HELP_TRACE=WASX7050I: Method: trace

	Arguments: trace specification

	Description: Turns on the trace specified by &quot;trace specification&quot;
	in the scripting process.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7141E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7141E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7141E=WASX7141E: Incorrect trace string supplied: &quot;{0}&quot;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The trace string that has been specified for an AdminControl trace command is not valid.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the trace string is spelled correctly.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7275I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HELP_HELP_ADMINCONFIG" varFormat="Java">
    HELP_HELP_ADMINCONFIG=WASX7275I: Method: AdminConfig

	Arguments: none

	Description: Display general help information for the
	AdminConfig object provided by wsadmin.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7456I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINCONTROL_HELP_QUERYMBEANS" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINCONTROL_HELP_QUERYMBEANS=WASX7456I: Method: queryMBeans

	Arguments: object name 

	Description: Returns a Set containing ObjectInstances object
	that match the input object name.

	Method: queryMBeans

	Arguments: object name (type ObjectName), query (type QueryExp)

	Description: Returns a Set containing ObjectInstances object
	that match the input object name and query.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7019E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="NO_CONN_TYPE" varFormat="Java">
    NO_CONN_TYPE=WASX7019E: No connection type specified; use &quot;-conntype&quot; on the command line.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The wsadmin tool requires connection type information. Specify the connection type with the -conntype command line option or the com.ibm.ws.scripting.connectionType property in wsadmin.properties.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a valid connection type with the -conntype command line option or the com.ibm.ws.scripting.connectionType property in wsadmin.properties.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7140E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7140E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7140E=WASX7140E: Length mismatch: {0} parameters were specified, but {1} signatures were supplied. The same number must be specified for both.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A different number of parameters and signature elements have been specified for an AdminControl invoke command.  There must be exactly one signature element for every parameter.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify exactly one signature element for every parameter and reissue the invoke command. Alternatively, reissue the command with no signature elements.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7162I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINAPP_HELP_DEFAULTBINDING.DATASOURCE.PASSWORD" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINAPP_HELP_DEFAULTBINDING.DATASOURCE.PASSWORD=WASX7162I: &quot;defaultbinding.datasource.password&quot; option; specifies the password for the default datasource
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7380I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7380" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7380=WASX7380I: Invalid file name specified: {0}. File name must end with the following file extensions: ear, jar, rar, or war
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7173I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINAPP_HELP_DEPLOYEJB.DBSCHEMA" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINAPP_HELP_DEPLOYEJB.DBSCHEMA=WASX7173I: &quot;deployejb.dbschema&quot; option; specifies the database schema for EJBDeploy
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7392W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7392W" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7392W=WASX7392W: Your application contains policy permissions that are in the filter policy. These permissions are security sensitive and can compromise the integrity of the system. Continuing with the application deployment process ...
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The application server attempts to prevent applications from performing security-sensitive operations such as: calling the System.exit() method, replacing the java 2 Security manager, and replacing the java 2 Security policy. If the application is granted the all permission (java.security.AllPermission), the java 2 Security permission checks are disabled.  This compromises the integrity of the system.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Review the application policy that is located in the EAR/META-INF/was.policy file. Remove the security-sensitive permissions and grant the application only the permissions that are required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7283E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7283E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7283E=WASX7283E: This command requires an object of type &quot;{0}&quot;, but the specified object &quot;{1}&quot; has type: &quot;{2}&quot;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An AdminConfig command did not run because a required object must be a specific type.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify an object of the correct type and reinvoke the command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7391W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7391W" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7391W=WASX7391W: Your application contains policy permissions that are in the filter policy. These permissions are security sensitive and can compromise the integrity of the system. Do you want to continue with the application deployment process?
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The application server attempts to prevent applications from performing security-sensitive operations such as: calling the System.exit() method, replacing the java 2 Security manager, and replacing the java 2 Security policy. If the application is granted the all permission (java.security.AllPermission), the java 2 Security permission checks are disabled. This compromises the integrity of the system.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Review the application policy that is located in the EAR/META-INF/was.policy file. Remove the security-sensitive permissions and grant the application only the permissions that are required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7479I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINAPP_HELP_ASYNCREQUESTDISPATCHTYPE" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINAPP_HELP_ASYNCREQUESTDISPATCHTYPE=WASX7479I: &quot;asyncRequestDispatchType&quot; option; specifies the asynchronous request dispatch type for web container for each application.  The default setting is &quot;DISABLED&quot;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7040I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINCONTROL_HELP_GETMBEANINFO_JMX" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINCONTROL_HELP_GETMBEANINFO_JMX=WASX7040I: Method: getMBeanInfo_jmx

	Arguments: object name (type ObjectName)

	Description: Returns the MBeanInfo structure for the MBean described 
	by the object name.  An easier way to get this information is to use
	the &quot;Help&quot; object -- for example, the &quot;operations&quot; command of the Help
	object returns information about all the operations supported by the
	specified MBean.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7282E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7282E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7282E=WASX7282E: No editing tasks are available for application &quot;{0}&quot;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The AdminApp edit or editInteractive command did not run because specified application has no valid tasks to edit.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7292I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINCONTROL_HELP_INVOKE_JMX" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINCONTROL_HELP_INVOKE_JMX=WASX7292I: Method: invoke_jmx

	Arguments: object name (type ObjectName), operation (type String),
	arguments (type Object[]), signature (type String[])

	Description: Invoke the operation named by &quot;operation&quot; on the MBean
	described by &quot;object name,&quot; using the arguments given in &quot;arguments&quot; and
	the signature in &quot;signature.&quot;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7390E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7390E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7390E=WASX7390E: Operation not supported - testConnection command with config id and properties arguments is not supported. Use testConnection command with config id argument only.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The wsadmin tool does not support this command.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Do not use this command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7484I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINAPP_HELP_VALIDATESCHEMA" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINAPP_HELP_VALIDATESCHEMA=WASX7484I: &quot;validateSchema&quot; option; Use this option to specify that the schema is to be validated.  The default is &quot;novalidateSchema&quot;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7281E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7281E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7281E=WASX7281E: Cannot install application using file &quot;{0}&quot;. Ensure that this file exists and is readable.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The AdminApp command did not run because specified file cannot be used.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that this file exists and is readable.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7023E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_CONN_TYPE" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_CONN_TYPE=WASX7023E: Error creating &quot;{0}&quot; connection to host &quot;{1}&quot;; exception information: {2}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The connector did not establish a connection to the host.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the accompanying exception information and the information in the wsadmin.traceout file to determine the cause of the error.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7242I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINAPP_HELP_RAR.NAME" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINAPP_HELP_RAR.NAME=WASX7242I: &quot;rar.name&quot; option; The &quot;rar.name&quot; option is the name for the J2CResourceAdapter.  If it is not specified, then the display name in the RAR&apos;s deployment descriptor is used.  If that is not specified, then the RAR file name is used.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7014E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CANNOT_FIND_LANG_INTERACTIVE" varFormat="Java">
    CANNOT_FIND_LANG_INTERACTIVE=WASX7014E: Cannot determine scripting language to use in interactive mode -- please specify &quot;-lang&quot; option on the command line.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The wsadmin tool cannot determine which scripting language to use for an interactive session.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a value for the -lang option on the wsadmin command line, or com.ibm.ws.scripting.defaultLang property in the wsadmin.properties file.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7280E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7280E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7280E=WASX7280E: An application with name &quot;{0}&quot; does not exist.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The AdminApp command did not run because the specified application does not exist.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the application name is spelled correctly.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WSCP0138E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WSCP_EXC_CLOSING_BRACE" varFormat="Java">
    WSCP_EXC_CLOSING_BRACE=WSCP0138E: Expected &apos;}&apos; not found
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    There is a syntax error in a string provided in an attribute list
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the attribute list syntax.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7186I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINAPP_HELP_DDLPREFIX" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINAPP_HELP_DDLPREFIX=WASX7186I: &quot;ddlprefix&quot; option; specifies DDL prefix to use when invoking exportDDL.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7332I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINCONTROL_HELP_GETCELL" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINCONTROL_HELP_GETCELL=WASX7332I: Method: getCell

	Arguments: none

	Description: Returns the cell to which the scripting process is
	connected.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7054I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINCONFIG_HELP_CREATE" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINCONFIG_HELP_CREATE=WASX7054I: Method: create

	Arguments: type, parent, attributes

	Description: Create a configuration object of the type named by
	&quot;type,&quot; the parent named by &quot;parent,&quot; using the attributes supplied by
	&quot;attributes.&quot;

	Method: create

	Arguments: type, parent, attributes, parent attribute name, 

	Description: Create a configuration object of the type named by
	&quot;type,&quot; the parent named by &quot;parent,&quot; using the attributes supplied
	by &quot;attributes&quot; and the attribute name in the parent given by
	&quot;parent attribute name&quot;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7201I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINCONFIG_HELP_GETVALIDATIONLEVEL" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINCONFIG_HELP_GETVALIDATIONLEVEL=WASX7201I: Method: getValidationLevel

	Arguments: none

	Description: Returns a message giving the current validation level.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7274I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HELP_HELP_ALL" varFormat="Java">
    HELP_HELP_ALL=WASX7274I: Method: classname

	Arguments: MBean

	Description: Display information about the attributes,
	operations, constructors, description, notifications, 
	and classname of the specified MBean.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7408I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7408I" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7408I=WASX7408I: The specified node configuration is successfully removed from the workspace. If you decide to commit this change to the master cell repository, you may need to perform manual steps to complete the removal steps include restoring the original application server cell configuration as the active configuration and updating the cell value in setupCmdLine.bat. If there are still running application servers for this node, you have to manually stop those servers.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Removal of the node from the configuration requires some manual steps. This operation is not recommended.  Alternatively, use the removeNode utility script.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If you did not commit the change, run the AdminConfig reset command to restore the configuration to its initial state.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7393I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINAPP_HELP_ALLOWPERMINFILTERPOLICY" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINAPP_HELP_ALLOWPERMINFILTERPOLICY=WASX7393I: &quot;allowPermInFilterPolicy&quot; option; specifies to continue with the application deployment process even when the application contains policy permissions that are in the filter policy
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7422I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINAPP_HELP_CONTENTURI" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINAPP_HELP_CONTENTURI=WASX7422I: &quot;contenturi&quot; option: this option is used in the update or updateInteractive command to specify the URI of the file to be added, updated, or removed from the application. This option is required if content type is file or modulefile. This option is ignored for other content type values.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7407I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7407I" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7407I=WASX7407I: The specified node configuration is successfully removed from the workspace. If you decide to commit this change to the master repository, your configuration may become invalid. To revert this operation and remove any unsaved configuration changes in the workspace, perform &quot;AdminConfig reset&quot; command.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Removal of the node from the configuration will corrupt your configuration.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If you did not commit the change, run the AdminConfig reset command to restore the configuration to its initial state.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7095I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7095I" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7095I=WASX7095I: The AdminApp object allows application objects to be manipulated
	-- this includes installing, uninstalling, editing, and listing. Most
	of the commands supported by AdminApp operate in two modes: the default
	mode is one in which AdminApp communicates with the WebSphere server to
	accomplish its tasks.  A local mode is also possible, in which no
	server communication takes place.  The local mode operation is invoked
	by bringing up the scripting client with no server connected using the
	command line &quot;-conntype NONE&quot; option tor setting the
	&quot;com.ibm.ws.scripting.connectionType=NONE&quot; property in the
	wsadmin.properties.

	The following commands are supported by AdminApp; more detailed
	information about each of these commands is available by using the
	&quot;help&quot; command of AdminApp and supplying the name of the command
	as an argument.

deleteUserAndGroupEntries 
		Deletes all the user/group information for all the roles and
		all the user name/password information for RunAs roles for a
		given application
edit		Edits the properties of an application
editInteractive	Edits the properties of an application interactively
export		Exports application to a file
exportDDL	Exports DDL from application to a directory
exportFile	Exports content of a single file from an application to a file
getDeployStatus	Returns the combined Deployment status of the application
help		Shows help information
install		Installs an application, given a file name and an option string
installInteractive
		Installs an application in interactive mode, given a file name
		and an option string
isAppReady	Checks whether the application is ready to be run
list		Lists all installed applications
listModules	Lists the modules in a specified application
options		Shows the options available, for a given file, application,
		or in general
renameApplication	Rename a given application
publishWSDL	Publishs WSDL files for a given application
searchJNDIReferences
		Lists application that refers to the given JNDIName on a given
		node
taskInfo	Shows detailed information pertaining to a given install task
		for a given file
uninstall	Uninstalls an application, given an application name and
		an option string
update		Updates an installed application
updateAccessIDs	Updates the user/group binding information with accessID
		from user registry for a given application
updateInteractive	Updates an installed application interactively
view		Views an application or module, given an application or
		module name
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7124I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINCONFIG_HELP_SAVE" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINCONFIG_HELP_SAVE=WASX7124I: Method: save

	Arguments: none

	Description: Commits unsaved changes to the configuration repository
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7406E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7406E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7406E=WASX7406E: Cannot find task name {0} in the application {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The AdminApp view command did not run because the application viewable tasks are not valid.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify the correct task with the correct spelling. To list the valid task names, use the -tasknames option.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7481I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINAPP_HELP_DEPLOYEJB.COMPLIANCELEVEL" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINAPP_HELP_DEPLOYEJB.COMPLIANCELEVEL=WASX7481I: &quot;deployejb.complianceLevel&quot; option; specifies the JDK level for compiler compliance for EJBDeploy; default is 1.4.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7044I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINCONTROL_HELP_GETATTRIBUTES" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINCONTROL_HELP_GETATTRIBUTES=WASX7044I: Method: getAttributes

	Arguments: object name, attributes
	Returns a string listing the values of the attributes named in 
	&quot;attributes&quot; for the object named by &quot;object name&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7312I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINCONFIG_HELP_DEFAULTS" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINCONFIG_HELP_DEFAULTS=WASX7312I: Method: defaults

	Arguments: type

	Description: Displays all the possible attributes contained by an 
	object of type &quot;type,&quot; along with the type and default value of each
	attribute, if the attribute has a default value.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7405E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7405E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7405E=WASX7405E: No viewable tasks are available for application &quot;{0}&quot;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The AdminApp view command did not run because the application has no valid tasks to view.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    This application is not editable.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7026W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WARNING_MULTIPLE_MATCHES" varFormat="Java">
    WARNING_MULTIPLE_MATCHES=WASX7026W: String &quot;{0}&quot; corresponds to {1} different MBeans; returning first one.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The AdminControl getConfigId or completeObjectName command cannot run because the ObjectName template that has been specified matches two or more running MBeans.  This informational message indicates that the first matching MBean will be used.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that first matching MBean is correct.  Otherwise, specify the desired MBean and reissue the command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7093I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7093I" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7093I=WASX7093I: Issuing message: &quot;{0}&quot;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This informational message is logged when the subject message is displayed to the user.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7425I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINAPP_HELP_NOCREATEMBEANSFORRESOURCES" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINAPP_HELP_NOCREATEMBEANSFORRESOURCES=WASX7425I: &quot;nocreateMBeansForResources&quot; option: this option specifies that MBeans are not created for all the resources such as servlets, jsps, EJBs, defined in an application when the application is started on a deployment target; this is the default setting.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7410I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINAPP_HELP_UPDATEACCESSIDS_ZOS" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINAPP_HELP_UPDATEACCESSIDS_ZOS=WASX7410I: Method: updateAccessIDs

	Arguments: application name, boolean:bAll

	Description: Updates the application binding file for an installed 
	application with access IDs for all the users and groups.  Specifying 
	true for bAll updates all the users/groups even if there are access
	IDs already present in the bindings.

	Method: updateAccessIDs

	Arguments: application name, boolean:bApp

	Description: Updates the application binding file for an installed 
	application with access IDs for all the users and groups.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7097I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINAPP_HELP_INSTALLINTERACTIVE" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINAPP_HELP_INSTALLINTERACTIVE=WASX7097I: Method: installInteractive

	Arguments: filename, options

	Description: Installs the application in the file specified by 
	&quot;filename&quot; using the options specified by &quot;options&quot;. The user is 
	prompted for information about each relevant task.

	The AdminApp &quot;options&quot; command may be used to get a list of all 
	possible options for a given ear file.  The AdminApp &quot;help&quot; command
	may be used to get more information about each particular option.

	Method: installInteractive

	Arguments: filename

	Description: Installs the application specified by &quot;filename&quot; using 
	default options. The user is prompted for information about each 
	relevant task.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7229I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINAPP_HELP_INSTALLDIR" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINAPP_HELP_INSTALLDIR=WASX7229I: &quot;installdir&quot; option; specifies the directory into which the application binaries should be placed.
This option is deprecated. It is replaced by installed.ear.destination option.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7092I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7092I" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7092I=WASX7092I: Command not logged; contains a password.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This informational message is logged instead of WASX7090I if the command appears to contain a password.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7394I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINAPP_HELP_NOALLOWPERMINFILTERPOLICY" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINAPP_HELP_NOALLOWPERMINFILTERPOLICY=WASX7394I: &quot;noallowPermInFilterPolicy&quot; option; specifies to not continue with the application deployment process when the application contains policy permission that are in the filter policy. This is the default setting.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7091I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7091I" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7091I=WASX7091I: Executing script: &quot;{0}&quot;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This is an informational message logging that this script was invoked.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7036I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINCONTROL_HELP_QUERYNAMES" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINCONTROL_HELP_QUERYNAMES=WASX7036I: Method: queryNames

	Arguments: object name 

	Description: Returns a String containing the ObjectNames that match 
	the input object name, which may be a wild card.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7431I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINAPP_HELP_INSTALLED.EAR.DESTINATION" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINAPP_HELP_INSTALLED.EAR.DESTINATION=WASX7431I: &quot;installed.ear.destination&quot; option; specifies the directory into which the application binaries should be placed.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7476I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINAPP_HELP_USEAUTOLINK" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINAPP_HELP_USEAUTOLINK=WASX7476I: &quot;useAutoLink&quot; option; allow the EJB reference targets to resolve automatically. 

The application must contain an EJB 3.0 module and all modules must share one common target to enable the autolink support.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purpose only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7164I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINAPP_HELP_DEFAULTBINDING.CF.RESAUTH" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINAPP_HELP_DEFAULTBINDING.CF.RESAUTH=WASX7164I: &quot;defaultbinding.cf.resauth&quot; option; specifies the RESAUTH for the connection factory.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7334I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINAPP_HELP_REDEPLOY.IGNORE.OLD" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINAPP_HELP_REDEPLOY.IGNORE.OLD=WASX7334I: This option is deprecated. Use the &quot;update.ignore.old&quot; option instead.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7090I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7090I" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7090I=WASX7090I: Executing command: &quot;{0}&quot;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This is an informational message logging that this command was invoked.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX8009E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX8009E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX8009E=WASX8009E: Invalid parameter: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The command does not contain the specified parameter.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that parameter name is spelled correctly or use help command to view detailed help for the command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7151I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINAPP_HELP_EXPORT" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINAPP_HELP_EXPORT=WASX7151I: Method: export

	Arguments: application name, filename, options

	Description: Exports the application specified by &quot;application name&quot; 
	to the file specified by &quot;filename&quot; using the options specified by 
	&quot;options&quot;.

	Method: export

	Arguments: application name, filename

	Description: Exports the application specified by &quot;application name&quot; 
	to the file specified by &quot;filename.&quot;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7013E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CANNOT_FIND_LANG" varFormat="Java">
    CANNOT_FIND_LANG=WASX7013E: Cannot determine scripting language for file: &quot;{0}&quot; -- please specify &quot;-lang&quot; option on the command line.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The wsadmin tool cannot determine which scripting language to use for the specified file.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a value for the -lang option on the wsadmin command line, or com.ibm.ws.scripting.defaultLang property in the wsadmin.properties file.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7328E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7328E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7328E=WASX7328E: A single attribute name must be specified for showAttribute; received: &quot;{0}&quot;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The AdminConfig showAttribute command only displays the value of a single attribute, but multiple attribute names were supplied.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a single attribute name.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7436W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7436W" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7436W=WASX7436W: At least one default binding option has been specified, but usedefaultbindings option has not been specified.  The default binding option(s) will be ignored.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    To use any default binding option, specify the usedefaultbindings option.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify the usedefaultbindings option in the option string with the AdminApp install, installInteractive, update, or updateInteractive command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7286I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINCONTROL_HELP_ISINSTANCEOF_JMX" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINCONTROL_HELP_ISINSTANCEOF_JMX=WASX7286I: Method: isInstanceOf_jmx

	Arguments: object name (type ObjectName), classname (String)

	Description: Returns true if the MBean described by &quot;object name&quot; is of
	the class given by &quot;classname.&quot;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7219E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7219E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7219E=WASX7219E: The {0} attribute must be specified if the {1} attribute has the value &quot;{2}&quot;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    There is a constraint on the specified attribute.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify the missing attribute.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX8008E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX8008E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX8008E=WASX8008E: Command {0} does not contain any step.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The command does not contain any step.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that step name is spelled correctly or use help command to view detailed help for the command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7429I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINAPP_HELP_SEARCHJNDIREFERENCES" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINAPP_HELP_SEARCHJNDIREFERENCES=WASX7429I: Method: searchJNDIReferences

	Arguments: node or nodes config id, options

	Description: List all applications that refer to the specified
	JNDIName option on the specified node or nodes.

	The valid options are -JNDIName which is a required option
	and -verbose which is an optional option that does not take any value.
	The JNDIName option takes a value of a JNDI name.
	The verbose option will show more information.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7369I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINAPP_HELP_EXPORTDDL" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINAPP_HELP_EXPORTDDL=WASX7369I: Method: exportDDL

	Arguments: application name, directory name, options

	Description: Exports DDL from the application specified by 
	&quot;application name&quot; to the directory specified by &quot;directory name&quot; using
	the options specified by &quot;options&quot;.

	Method: exportDDL

	Arguments: application name, directory name

	Description: Exports DDL from the application specified by 
	&quot;application name&quot; to the directory specified by &quot;directory name.&quot;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7231I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINAPP_HELP_CONFIGROOT" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINAPP_HELP_CONFIGROOT=WASX7231I: &quot;configroot&quot; option; this option is obsolete
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7474I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINAPP_HELP_EXPORTFILE" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINAPP_HELP_EXPORTFILE=WASX7474I: Method: exportFile

	Arguments: application name, uri, filename

	Description: This command exports the contents of a single file 
	which is specified by the uri argument, from the application, 
	which is specified by the application name argument, to the file, 
	which is specified by the file argument.

	Specify the uri argument within the context of an application. 
	For example: META-INF/application.xml. For files within a module, 
	start the uri with a module uri.  For example: myapp.war/WEB-INF/web.xml.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7327I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7327I" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7327I=WASX7327I: Contents of was.policy file:
 {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The list displays the was.policy security policy file associated with this application.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7435W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7435W" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7435W=WASX7435W: Value {0} is converted to a boolean value of false.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A string value representing a boolean is not entered as true or false.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the string value is correct and reissue the command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX8007I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX8007I" varFormat="Java">
    WASX8007I=WASX8007I: Detailed help for command group: {0}

Description: {1}

Commands:
{2}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7109E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7109E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7109E=WASX7109E: Insufficient data for install task &quot;{0}&quot;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The data is not complete for an AdminApp install command for the specified task.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Invoke the AdminApp taskInfo command for this file and task name to determine what information is needed for the task.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7326I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7326I" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7326I=WASX7326I: Loaded properties file &quot;{0}&quot;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    During the initialization of a scripting process, several properties files might load.  Use this message to determine which properties files that are in use.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7384I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINAPP_HELP_DEPLOYWS" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINAPP_HELP_DEPLOYWS=WASX7384I: &quot;deployws&quot; option; specifies to deploy WebServices during install; the default is &quot;nodeployws&quot;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7060I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINCONFIG_HELP_CONTENTS" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINCONFIG_HELP_CONTENTS=WASX7060I: Method: contents

	Arguments: type

	Description: Displays the object types that can be contained in &quot;type.&quot;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7434W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7434W" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7434W=WASX7434W: Found the following deprecated option: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The options listed in this message are deprecated for the AdminApp command. The support for these options will be removed in a future release.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Determine if there is replacement option for the deprecated option. If so, use the replacement option. If there is no replacement option, you can exclude the deprecated option.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7217I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7217I" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7217I=WASX7217I: Connection to provided datasource was successful.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The AdminControl testConnection command was successfully run. The database adapter code reported no errors or warnings.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX8006I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX8006I" varFormat="Java">
    WASX8006I=WASX8006I: Detailed help for command: {0}

Description: {1}

{2}Target object: {3}

Arguments:
{4}
Steps:
{5}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7247I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINAPP_HELP_DELETEUSERANDGROUPENTRIES" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINAPP_HELP_DELETEUSERANDGROUPENTRIES=WASX7247I: Method: deleteUserAndGroupEntries

	Arguments: application name

	Description: Deletes all the user/group information for all the roles
	and RunAs roles for a given application.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7108E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7108E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7108E=WASX7108E: Invalid data specified for install task: &quot;{0}.&quot;  Errors are: &quot;{1}&quot;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The data is not valid for an AdminApp install command for the specified task.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the errors reported for this task and correct the install command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7184I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINAPP_HELP_USEMETADATAFROMBINARY" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINAPP_HELP_USEMETADATAFROMBINARY=WASX7184I: &quot;useMetaDataFromBinary&quot; option; use this option to specify that the metadata (such as deployment descriptors, bindings, extensions) that are used at runtime come from the earfile; the default is &quot;nouseMetaDataFromBinary,&quot; which means that the metadata used at runtime come from the config repository.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7104I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINAPP_HELP_EDIT" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINAPP_HELP_EDIT=WASX7104I: Method: edit

	Arguments: application name, options

	Description: Modifies the application specified by &quot;application name&quot; 
	using the options specified by &quot;options&quot;. The user is not prompted for
	any information.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7102I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINAPP_HELP_UNINSTALL" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINAPP_HELP_UNINSTALL=WASX7102I: Method: uninstall

	Arguments: application name, options

	Description: Uninstalls application named by &quot;application name&quot; using
	the options supplied by &quot;options&quot;.

	Method: uninstall

	Arguments: application name

	Description: Uninstalls the application specified by 
	&quot;application name&quot; using default options.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7258I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINCONTROL_HELP_STARTSERVER" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINCONTROL_HELP_STARTSERVER=WASX7258I: Method: startServer

	Arguments: server name

	Description: Starts a server by locating it in the configuration
	and asking that node&apos;s NodeAgent to start the server.  This command
	uses the default wait time of 1200 seconds.  Note that this version
	of the command can only be used if the scripting process is attached
	to a Node Agent server.

	Method: startServer

	Arguments: server name, wait time

	Description: Starts a server by locating it in the configuration,
	synchronizing configuration data with the server&apos;s node,
	and asking that node&apos;s NodeAgent to start the server.  The start
	process waits the number of seconds specified by &quot;waittime&quot;
	for the server to start. Note that this version of the command can
	only be used if the scripting process is attached to a Node Agent 
	server.

	Method: startServer

	Arguments: server name, node name

	Description: Starts a server in the specified node by locating it in
	the configuration, synchronizing configuration data with the server&apos;s 
	node and asking that node&apos;s NodeAgent to start the server. This version
	of the command can be used when the scripting process is attached
	either to a Node Agent or Deployment Manager process.

	Method: startServer

	Arguments: server name, node name, wait time

	Description: Starts a server in the specified node by locating it in
	the configuration, synchronizing configuration data with the server&apos;s 
	node and asking that node&apos;s NodeAgent to start the server.  The start
	process waits the number of seconds specified by &quot;waittime&quot;
	for the server to start.  This version of the command can be used when
	the scripting process is attached either to a Node Agent or Deployment
	Manager process.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX8005I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX8005I" varFormat="Java">
    WASX8005I=WASX8005I: Available admin command groups: 

{0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7128I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINCONFIG_HELP_SETSAVEMODE" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINCONFIG_HELP_SETSAVEMODE=WASX7128I: Method: setSaveMode

	Arguments: save mode

	Description: Changes the mode used when &quot;save&quot; is invoked.
	Possible values are:
		&quot;overwriteOnConflict&quot; to save changes even if they conflict
		with other configuration changes; and
		&quot;rollbackOnConflict&quot; to cause a save operation to fail if
		changes conflict with other configuration changes;
		this value is the default.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7453I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINAPP_HELP_FILEPERMISSION" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINAPP_HELP_FILEPERMISSION=WASX7453I: &quot;filepermission&quot; option; Allow user to set appropriate file permissions on application files in the install destination directory.

File permissions specified at the application level must be a subset of the node level file permission which defines the most lenient file permission that can be specified, otherwise node level permission value is used to set file permissions in install destination.

The default is &quot;.*\.dll=755#.*\.so=755#.*\.a=755#.*\.sl=755&quot;
The filename pattern is a regular expression.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7457I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINCONTROL_HELP_GETOBJECTINSTANCE" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINCONTROL_HELP_GETOBJECTINSTANCE=WASX7457I: Method: getObjectInstance

	Arguments: object name 

	Description: Returns the ObjectInstance object that match the input
	object name.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7469E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7469E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7469E=WASX7469E: One or more attributes must be specified for resetAttributes; received: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The attribute will be reset is not specified.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Supply the attribute to be reset.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7107E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7107E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7107E=WASX7107E: Invalid options specified: &quot;{0}&quot;; valid options are:
{1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    One or more options that were specified for an AdminApp or AdminConfig command is not valid.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check the spelling of the options; correct or remove any incorrect options and reissue the command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7048I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINCONTROL_HELP_MAKEOBJECTNAME" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINCONTROL_HELP_MAKEOBJECTNAME=WASX7048I: Method: makeObjectName

	Arguments: object name

	Description: Return an ObjectName object constructed from
	the &quot;object name&quot; string.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7324E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7324E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7324E=WASX7324E: Cannot copy directory &quot;{0}&quot; to directory &quot;{1}&quot;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The wsadmin tool cannot copy an expanded ear directory to a temporary location for AdminApp processing.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the wsadmin.traceout log file to determine the problem.  Verify that there is enough space in the file system and that there are no file permission problems.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX8004I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX8004I" varFormat="Java">
    WASX8004I=WASX8004I: Available admin commands: 

{0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7215E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7215E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7215E=WASX7215E: Cannot complete testConnection function because DataSourceCfgHelper MBean is not running.  Please check to see if the server started correctly.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The wsadmin tool needs the DataSourceCfgHelper MBean to perform the testConnection function.  The MBean should be running in a server.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the wsadmin process is connected to a server and the server is running. CMSG0002.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7125I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINCONFIG_HELP_RESET" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINCONFIG_HELP_RESET=WASX7125I: Method: reset

	Arguments: none

	Description: Discard unsaved configuration changes
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7096I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINAPP_HELP_INSTALL" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINAPP_HELP_INSTALL=WASX7096I: Method: install

	Arguments: filename, options

	Description: Installs the application in the file specified by 
	&quot;filename&quot; using the options specified by &quot;options&quot;. All required 
	information must be supplied in the options string; no prompting is
	performed.

	The AdminApp &quot;options&quot; command may be used to get a list of all 
	possible options for a given ear file.  The AdminApp &quot;help&quot; command
	may be used to get more information about each particular option.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7468E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7468E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7468E=WASX7468E: Connection to provided datasource on node {0} process {1} failed.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The AdminControl testConnection command was failed. See exception message and wsadmin.traceout file to find what is the problem
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Find the problem from the log and try to resolve the problem and reissue the command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7106E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7106E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7106E=WASX7106E: Unable to determine root of WebSphere installation.  Please specify the &quot;{0}&quot; option on the command line.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An AdminApp command is invoked in the local mode, but wsadmin cannot determine the installation root for WebSphere.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    The wsadmin.bat or wsadmin.sh launcher should set the server.root property. If you modified this launcher, correct the changes. CMSG0002.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7342I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINCONFIG_HELP_INSTALLRESOURCEADAPTER" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINCONFIG_HELP_INSTALLRESOURCEADAPTER=WASX7342I: Method: installResourceAdapter

	Arguments: rar file name, node, options

	Description: Installs a J2C resource adapter with the rar file
	specified by &quot;rar file name&quot; using the options specified by &quot;options&quot;
	in the specified &quot;node&quot;.

	The rar file name is the fully qualified file name resided in the
	specified node.

	The valid options are &quot;rar.name&quot;, &quot;rar.desc&quot;, &quot;rar.archivePath&quot;,
	&quot;rar.classpath&quot;, &quot;rar.nativePath&quot;, &quot;rar.threadPoolAlias&quot;,
	&quot;rar.propertiesSet, &quot;isolatedClassLoader&quot;, &quot;enabledHASupport&quot;, and
	&quot;HACapability.  All options are optional.

	The &quot;rar.name&quot; option is the name for the J2CResourceAdapter.
	If it is not specified, then the display name in the rar&apos;s deployment
	descriptor is used.  If that is not specified, then the rar file name
	is used.

	The &quot;rar.desc&quot; option is a description of the J2CResourceAdapter.

	The &quot;rar.archivePath&quot; is the name of the path where the file is
	to be extracted.  If this is not specified, then the archive will be
	extracted to $CONNECTOR_INSTALL_ROOT directory.

	The &quot;rar.classpath&quot; is the additional class path.

	The &quot;rar.threadPoolAlias&quot; is the alias of the thread pool.

	The &quot;rar.propertiesSet&quot; is the property set of the J2CResourceAdapter.

	The &quot;rar.isolatedClassLoader is the option to use isolated classloader.
	If it is specified, it indicated that the J2CResourceAdapter uses the
	isolated classloader. The default value is &quot;false&quot;.

	The &quot;rar.enableHASupport is the option to enable HA support.
	The default value is &quot;false&quot;.

	The &quot;rar.HACapability specifies the type of HA support. The choices are
	the &quot;endpoint&quot;, &quot;instance&quot; and &quot;no&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7323E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7323E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7323E=WASX7323E: Cannot create directory &quot;{0}&quot;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The wsadmin tool cannot create a temporary directory for AdminApp processing.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the wsadmin.traceout log file to determine the problem.  Verify that there is enough space in the file system and that there are no file permission problems.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7359E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7359E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7359E=WASX7359E: Incorrect value specified for reloadInterval option: {0}. reloadInterval option requires an integer value.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The value specified for the -reloadInterval option is not an integer.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify an integer argument for the -reloadInterval option and reissue the AdminApp command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7214E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7214E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7214E=WASX7214E: Cannot resolve confid id {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    This exception is unexpected. The cause is not immediately known.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX8003E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX8003E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX8003E=WASX8003E: Invalid help arguments: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The wsadmin tool cannot run the AdminTask help command.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the number of arguments, command name, or command group name is correct.  Use the AdminTask help command to view a list of valid commands for the help option.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7046I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINCONTROL_HELP_SETATTRIBUTES" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINCONTROL_HELP_SETATTRIBUTES=WASX7046I: Method: setAttributes

	Arguments: object name, attributes

	Description: Sets attributes given in &quot;attributes&quot; for the MBean
	described by &quot;object name.&quot;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7467I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7467I" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7467I=WASX7467I: Connection to provided datasource on node {0} process {1} was successful.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The AdminControl testConnection command was successfully run. The database adapter code reported no errors or warnings.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7105I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7105I" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7105I=WASX7105I: The following install options are valid for any ear file:
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The wsadmin tool displays this informational message in response to an AdminApp options command.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7427I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINAPP_HELP_RELOADINTERVAL" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINAPP_HELP_RELOADINTERVAL=WASX7427I: &quot;reloadInterval&quot; option: this option specifies the time period (in seconds) in which the application&apos;s filesystem will be scanned for updated files; the default setting is 3 seconds.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7271I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HELP_HELP_DESCRIPTION" varFormat="Java">
    HELP_HELP_DESCRIPTION=WASX7271I: Method: description

	Arguments: MBean

	Description: Display the description of the specified MBean.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7430W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7430W" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7430W=WASX7430W: This operation may take longer depending on how many applications installed on your system.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Searching for JNDI references may take longer depending on how many applications installed on your system.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7358E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7358E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7358E=WASX7358E: Invalid option specified: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The wsadmin tool found one or more options that are not valid.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check the spelling of the options. Correct or remove any incorrect options and reissue the command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7010E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_CONNECTION_TYPE" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_CONNECTION_TYPE=WASX7010E: Invalid connection type &quot;{0}.&quot;  Valid types are &quot;SOAP,&quot; &quot;RMI,&quot; &quot;NONE,&quot; and &quot;JMS.&quot;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The connection type was supplied on the command line -conntype option or in the com.ws.scripting.connectionType property in the wsadmin.properties file is not valid.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the connection type on the command line or properties file. Specify &quot;SOAP,&quot; &quot;RMI,&quot; or &quot;NONE.&quot;
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7213I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7213I" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7213I=WASX7213I: This scripting client is not connected to a server process; please refer to the log file {0} for additional information.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The wsadmin tool could not connect to a server using the options supplied on the command line and contained in wsadmin.properties files.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If a connection is not needed, no action is necessary. Specify the &quot;-conntype NONE&quot; option to indicate that no connection is desired.  This option suppresses the WASX7213I message.  If a connection is needed, restart the wsadmin tool with connection information that will allow it to connect to a running server.  Alternatively, verify that the host and port information is correct.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7168I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINAPP_HELP_DEFAULTBINDING.STRATEGY.FILE" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINAPP_HELP_DEFAULTBINDING.STRATEGY.FILE=WASX7168I: &quot;defaultbinding.strategy.file&quot; option; specifies a custom default bindings strategy file
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7368I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINAPP_HELP_UPDATE.IGNORE.NEW" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINAPP_HELP_UPDATE.IGNORE.NEW=WASX7368I: &quot;update.ignore.new&quot; option; this option specifies that when an application is updated, the bindings from the new version are ignored during the reinstall operation.  This option only has meaning if the &quot;update&quot; option is specified; otherwise it is ignored.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7147I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINCONFIG_HELP_GETSAVEMODE" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINCONFIG_HELP_GETSAVEMODE=WASX7147I: Method: getSaveMode

	Arguments: none

	Description: Returns the mode used when &quot;save&quot; is invoked.
	Possible values are:
		&quot;overwriteOnConflict&quot; to save changes even if they conflict
		with other configuration changes; and
		&quot;rollbackOnConflict&quot; to cause a save operation to fail if
		changes conflict with other configuration changes;
		this value is the default.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX8002E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX8002E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX8002E=WASX8002E: Invalid Command name: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The command name is not a valid administrative command.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the command name is correct.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7176I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINAPP_HELP_DEPLOYEJB.VALIDATE" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINAPP_HELP_DEPLOYEJB.VALIDATE=WASX7176I: &quot;deployejb.validate&quot; option; specifies that EJBDeploy should run validation; this is the default setting.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7357I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7357I" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7357I=WASX7357I: By request, this scripting client is not connected to any server process. Certain configuration and application operations will be available in local mode.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The wsadmin tool is not connected to a server process.  A request was made with &quot;-conntype NONE&quot; option from the command line or specified in com.ws.scripting.connectionType property with NONE as the value in wsadmin.properties.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7362I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HELP_HELP_MESSAGE" varFormat="Java">
    HELP_HELP_MESSAGE=WASX7362I: Method: message

	Arguments: Message Id

	Description: Display information for given message id.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX8001I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX8001I" varFormat="Java">
    WASX8001I=WASX8001I: The AdminTask object enables the execution of available admin
	commands.  AdminTask commands operate in two modes:
	the default mode is one which AdminTask communicates with the WebSphere
	server to accomplish its task. A local mode is also available, in which
	no server communication takes place. The local mode of operation is
	invoked by bringing up the scripting client using the command line
	&quot;-conntype NONE&quot; option or setting the
	&quot;com.ibm.ws.scripting.connectiontype=NONE&quot; property in 
	wsadmin.properties file.

The number of admin commands varies and depends on your WebSphere
install. Use the following help commands to obtain a list of supported
commands and their parameters:

help -commands			Lists all the admin commands
help -commands &lt;pattern&gt;	Lists admin commands matching with wildcard
				&quot;pattern&quot;
help -commandGroups		Lists all the admin command groups
help -commandGroups &lt;pattern&gt;	Lists admin command groups matching with
				wildcard &quot;pattern&quot;
help commandName		Displays detailed information for the
				specified command
help commandName stepName	Displays detailed information for the specified
				step belonging to the specified command
help commandGroupName		Displays detailed information for the specified
				command group

There are various flavors to invoke an admin command. They are

commandName			Invokes an admin command that does not require
				any argument.

commandName targetObject	Invokes an admin command with the specified
				target object string, for example, the
				configuration object name of a resource
				adapter. The expected target object varies
				with the admin command invoked. Use help
				command to get information on the target
				object of an admin command.

commandName options		Invokes an admin command with the specified
				option strings. This invocation syntax is
				used to invoke an admin command that does
				not require a target object. It is also
				used to enter interactive mode if
				&quot;-interactive&quot; mode is included in the
				options string.

commandName targetObject options	Invokes an admin command with the
					specified target object and options
					strings.  If &quot;-interactive&quot; is included
					in the options string, then interactive
					mode is entered.  The target object and
					options strings vary depending on the
					admin command invoked. Use help command
					to get information on the target object
					and options.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7465E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7465E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7465E=WASX7465E: stopServer action not supported when server type is &quot;{0}&quot;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Scripting client is connected admin subsystem and try to stop the admiagent server which is not supported.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If you want to stop adminagent server you need to do it from adminagent bin directory or if you are trying to stop admin subsystem you need to connect to adminagent server directly and use AdminAgent mbean to invoke stopProfile operation.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7139E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7139E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7139E=WASX7139E: Operation &quot;{0}&quot; has versions that take one of the following number of parameters: {1}; {2} parameters were supplied: &quot;{3}.&quot;  The &quot;operations&quot; command on the Help object can be used to learn more about the signatures available for &quot;{0}.&quot;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    No operation was defined for the AdminControl invoke command that has been issued for an MBean operation. The MBean accepts the same number of parameters specified in the AdminControl invoke command.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify the correct number of parameters and reissue the invoke command.  Use the &quot;operations&quot; command for the Help object to learn more about the signatures available for this operation.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7400I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SECURITY_USEFIPS_DESCRIPTION" varFormat="Java">
    SECURITY_USEFIPS_DESCRIPTION=WASX7400I: This will enable the use of FIPS (Federal Information Processing Standard) approved cryptographic algorithms.  Note that setting this flag does not automatically change the existing JSSE provider in the Secure Socket Layer configuration.  Also note that FIPS approved JSSE provider only allows TLS protocol.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7320E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7320E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7320E=WASX7320E: Server &quot;{0}&quot; is already running on node &quot;{1}&quot; and cannot be started.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The AdminControl startServer command did not run because the server is already started.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the correct server name is specified.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7356E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7356E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7356E=WASX7356E: Unrecognized argument: {0}. The specified argument is not a valid node name or wait time when connected to {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The argument passed to the startServer command is not valid.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Reissue the command with the correct value for the argument.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7455I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINAPP_HELP_NOALLOWSERVICEREMOTEINCLUDE" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINAPP_HELP_NOALLOWSERVICEREMOTEINCLUDE=WASX7455I: &quot;noallowServiceRemoteInclude&quot; option; Disables an enterprise application to service 
an include request from an enterprise application with -allowDispatchRemoteInclude set to true.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7210W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7210W" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7210W=WASX7210W: Cannot determine type of server; exception information: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The wsadmin tool cannot determine the type of server to which it is connected.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the wsadmin.traceout file for additional information.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7340I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINCONFIG_HELP_EXISTSDOCUMENT" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINCONFIG_HELP_EXISTSDOCUMENT=WASX7340I: Method: existsDocument

	Arguments: documentURI

	Description: Tests to see if a document exists in the configuration 
	repository. The &quot;documentURI&quot; is the document to be tested which is 
	relative to the root of the configuration repository such as 
	&quot;cells/MyCell/myfile.xml&quot;.  Returns a true value if the document 
	exists; false otherwise.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7409I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINAPP_HELP_DELETEUSERANDGROUPENTRIES_ZOS" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINAPP_HELP_DELETEUSERANDGROUPENTRIES_ZOS=WASX7409I: Method: deleteUserAndGroupEntries

	Arguments: application name

	Description: Deletes all the user/group information for all the roles
	and RunAs roles for a given application.

	Method: deleteUserAndGroupEntries

	Arguments: application name

	Description: Deletes all the user/group information for all the roles
	and RunAs roles for a given application.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7038I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINCONTROL_HELP_GETDOMAINNAME" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINCONTROL_HELP_GETDOMAINNAME=WASX7038I: Method: getDomainName

	Arguments: none

	Description: returns &quot;WebSphere&quot;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7355E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7355E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7355E=WASX7355E: The attribute &quot;{0}&quot; is of type &quot;{1}&quot;; an invalid value was supplied.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The value supplied for the attribute is not valid.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the syntax and reissue the command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7153I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINAPP_HELP_CELL" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINAPP_HELP_CELL=WASX7153I: &quot;cell&quot; option; specifies the cell name for AdminApp install functions.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7246E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7246E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7246E=WASX7246E: Cannot establish &quot;{0}&quot; connection to host &quot;{1}&quot; because of an authentication failure. Ensure that user and password are correct on the command line or in a properties file.
Exception message (if any): &quot;{2}&quot;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The wsadmin tool did not connect to a server process because it could not authenticate to the server.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that user and password are correct on the command line or in a properties file.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7094I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINCONFIG_HELP_PARENTS" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINCONFIG_HELP_PARENTS=WASX7094I: Method: parents

	Arguments: type

	Description: Displays the object types that can contain &quot;type.&quot;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7448E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="TRACEFILE_NOT_WRITTABLE" varFormat="Java">
    TRACEFILE_NOT_WRITTABLE=WASX7448E: The trace file cannot be written to location {0}. Please specify a different location with -tracefile option.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The wsadmin launcher did not run because the location that has been specified is not writable.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a different location for the -tracefile option and reissue the wsadmin command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7354E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7354E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7354E=WASX7354E: The attribute &quot;{0}&quot; is an embedded object of type &quot;{1}&quot;; an invalid value was supplied.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Specify attribute values that are embedded objects as a list of name-value pairs.  An example of an embedded object consisting of three attributes is:
{{attr1 val1a} {attr2 val2a}}.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the syntax of the command so that the embedded object is formatted as a list of name-value pairs.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WSCP0142E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WSCP_EXC_UNEXPECTED_CLOSING_BRACE" varFormat="Java">
    WSCP_EXC_UNEXPECTED_CLOSING_BRACE=WSCP0142E: Unexpected &apos;}&apos; found
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    There is a syntax error in a string provided in an attribute list
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the attribute list syntax.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7353E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7353E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7353E=WASX7353E: The value of the attribute &quot;{0}&quot; must be a collection of objects of type &quot;{1}&quot;; an additional set of braces may be required to signify that this is a collection.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Specify attribute values that are collections of objects as a list of name-value pairs.  An example of a collection consisting of two objects is:
{{{attr1 val1a} {attr2 val2a}} {attr1 val1b} {attr2 val2b}}}.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the syntax of the command to note the attribute as a collection.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7389E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7389E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7389E=WASX7389E: Operation not supported - getPropertiesForDataSource command is not supported.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The wsadmin tool does not support this command.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Do not use this command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7235I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINAPP_HELP_DEFAULTBINDING.VIRTUAL.HOST" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINAPP_HELP_DEFAULTBINDING.VIRTUAL.HOST=WASX7235I: &quot;defaultbinding.virtual.host&quot; option; default name for virtual host.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7041I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINCONTROL_HELP_ISINSTANCEOF" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINCONTROL_HELP_ISINSTANCEOF=WASX7041I: Method: isInstanceOf

	Arguments: object name, classname

	Description: Returns true if MBean described by &quot;object name&quot; is of 
	the class given by &quot;classname.&quot;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7488I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINAPP_HELP_RENAME" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINAPP_HELP_RENAME=WASX7488I: Method: rename

	Arguments: application name, new application name

	Description: Renames the application specified by &quot;application name&quot;
	to the name specified by &quot;new application name&quot;. In a WebSphere
	Virtual Enterprise environment, composite names are supported to
	allow specification of application name and edition. A composite
	name has the form, &lt;name&gt;-edition&lt;edition&gt;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7352E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7352E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7352E=WASX7352E: Wrong number of arguments for &quot;{0}&quot; command.  Help information follows:
 {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The number of arguments supplied for the given command is not correct.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Review the help information and reissue the command with the correct number of arguments.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7388E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7388E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7388E=WASX7388E: Connection to provided datasource failed.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An error occured during invoking test connection to the provided data source.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the exception in the trace log and correct the problem accordingly.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7279E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7279E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7279E=WASX7279E: An application with name &quot;{0}&quot; already exists. Select a different name.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The AdminApp install command did not run because the specified application name already exists.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Use the -appname option to specify a different application name.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7144I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINCONFIG_HELP_SHOWALL" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINCONFIG_HELP_SHOWALL=WASX7144I: Method: showall

	Arguments: config id

	Description: Shows all the attributes for the configuration object
	named by &quot;config id.&quot; The showall command recursively displays the
	contents of all the subobjects contained inside each of the attributes.

	Method: showall

	Arguments: config id, attribute list

	Description: Shows the attributes specified by &quot;attribute list&quot; for 
	the configuration object named by &quot;config id.&quot;  The showall command
	recursively displays the contents of each specified attribute.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7134E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7134E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7134E=WASX7134E: &quot;{0}&quot; option must be specified for war file installation.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The -contextroot option must be specified for the AdminApp install command for invoking a war file.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a valid value for the -contextroot option.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7351I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7351I" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7351I=WASX7351I: The parents command cannot be used to find the parents of type &quot;{0}&quot;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The parents command does not support the specified object type.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7387E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7387E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7387E=WASX7387E: Operation not supported - testConnection command in AdminControl scripting object is not supported when connected to a 5.0 server.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Version 5.1 and later supports the testConnection command.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Use the testConnectionToDataSource method in DataSourceCfgHelper MBean to test the connection of a DataSource that resides in a 5.0 server.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7421I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINAPP_HELP_CONTENTS" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINAPP_HELP_CONTENTS=WASX7421I: &quot;contents&quot; option; this option is used in the update or updateInteractive command to specify the file containing the contents to be updated. Depending on the content type, the file can be a module, a partial zip, an application file, or a single file. The path to the file has to be local to the scripting client. This option is required except when delete operation is specified.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7278I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7278I" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7278I=WASX7278I: Generated command line: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The installInteractive or editInteractive AdminApp commands returns the previous string that can be modified and copied into a script for use with the install or edit commands.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If needed, use the command string in a script.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7133E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7133E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7133E=WASX7133E: Application uninstall of {0} failed: see previous messages for details.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An AdminApp uninstall command did not run.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See previous messages for details.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7350E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7350E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7350E=WASX7350E: This field requires container or per connection factory as the value. Please try again.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The value for the resource authorization field was not specified.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Enter &quot;container&quot; or &quot;per connection factory&quot; as the value of resource authorization.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7241I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7241I" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7241I=WASX7241I: There are no unsaved changes in this workspace.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    No changes were made to the configuration by this scripting process since the last &quot;save&quot; or &quot;reset&quot; AdminConfig command.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7285I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINCONTROL_HELP_QUERYNAMES_JMX" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINCONTROL_HELP_QUERYNAMES_JMX=WASX7285I: Method: queryNames_jmx

	Arguments: object name (type ObjectName), query (type QueryExp)

	Description: Returns a Set containing ObjectNames that match the input
	object name and query.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7299E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CLASSPATH_REQUIRES_ARG" varFormat="Java">
    CLASSPATH_REQUIRES_ARG=WASX7299E: &quot;-wsadmin_classpath&quot; option must be followed by a classpath.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The wsadmin launcher has been invoked with the -wsadmin_class path option, but no class path argument was found.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a class path for the -wsadmin_classpath option and reissue the wsadmin command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7132E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7132E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7132E=WASX7132E: Application install for {0} failed: see previous messages for details.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An AdminApp install command did not run.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See previous messages for details.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7240I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7240I" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7240I=WASX7240I: Resetting workspace at the start of a scripting session; workspace reports unsaved changes in the following files:
 {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    If a scripting session begins with unsaved changes in the workspace, the workspace resets and the unsaved changes are lost.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7131E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7131E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7131E=WASX7131E: Runtime exception: &quot;{0}&quot;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The wsadmin tool created a RuntimeMBeanException exception from an MBean.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the exception information and modify the command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7304I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINCONTROL_HELP_GETNODE" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINCONTROL_HELP_GETNODE=WASX7304I: Method: getNode

	Arguments: none

	Description: Returns the node to which the scripting process is
	connected.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7174I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINAPP_HELP_DEPLOYEJB.CLASSPATH" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINAPP_HELP_DEPLOYEJB.CLASSPATH=WASX7174I: &quot;deployejb.classpath&quot; option; specifies extra classpath to be used for EJBDeploy
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7020E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CONN_REQUIRES_HOST" varFormat="Java">
    CONN_REQUIRES_HOST=WASX7020E: The &quot;{0}&quot; connection type requires that a host be specified in a properties file or with &quot;-host&quot; on the command line.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A host must be specified for the connection type.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a valid host with the -host command line option or the com.ibm.ws.scripting.host property in wsadmin.properties.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7130E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7130E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7130E=WASX7130E: The requested operation is not supported.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The wsadmin tool created an UnsupportedOperationException exception from an MBean. This exception might result from an AdminControl invoke command.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check the spelling of the operation.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7396I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINCONFIG_HELP_UNINSTALLRESOURCEADAPTER" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINCONFIG_HELP_UNINSTALLRESOURCEADAPTER=WASX7396I: Method: uninstallResourceAdapter

	Arguments: config id

	Description: Uninstall a J2C resource adapter by the &quot;config id&quot;

	Method: uninstallResourceAdapter

	Arguments: config id, option list

	Description: Uninstall a J2C resource adapter by the &quot;config id&quot; using options in &quot;option list&quot;.
	Option list is optional. The valid option is &quot;force&quot;.
	The &quot;force&quot; option will force the uninstall of resource adapter
	without checking whether the resource adapter is still being
	used by any application.
	If this option is not specified and the specified resource adapter is still in use,
	the resource adapter will not be uninstalled.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7182I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINAPP_HELP_DISTRIBUTEAPP" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINAPP_HELP_DISTRIBUTEAPP=WASX7182I: &quot;distributeApp&quot; option; specifies that the application management component should distribute application binaries.  This is the default setting.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7074I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="RECONNECT_COMPLETE" varFormat="Java">
    RECONNECT_COMPLETE=WASX7074I: Reconnect of {0} connector to host {1} completed.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The AdminControl reconnect command completed successfully.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7016E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ERROR_READING_FILE" varFormat="Java">
    ERROR_READING_FILE=WASX7016E: Exception received while reading file &quot;{0}&quot;; exception information: {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An IO exception occurred while reading a script or profile.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the wsadmin.traceout log file to determine the problem. Verify that there is enough space in the file system, and that there are no file permission problems.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7152I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINAPP_HELP_EXTRACTDDL" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINAPP_HELP_EXTRACTDDL=WASX7152I: This method is deprecated. Use exportDDL instead.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7385I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINAPP_HELP_PUBLISHWSDL" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINAPP_HELP_PUBLISHWSDL=WASX7385I: Method: publishWSDL

	Arguments: application name, filename, soapAddressPrefixes

	Description: Publish WSDL files for the application specified
	to the file specified by &quot;filename&quot; using the soap address prefixes.
	The soapAddressPrefixes is a compound parameter that defines url
	endpoint information for the soap addresses in each module.
	This information is used to customize the SOAP addresses in
	the published WSDL.

	Method: publishWSDL

	Arguments: application name, filename

	Description: Publish WSDL files for the application specified
	to the file specified by &quot;filename&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7042I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINCONTROL_HELP_ISREGISTERED" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINCONTROL_HELP_ISREGISTERED=WASX7042I: Method: isRegistered

	Arguments: object name

	Description: Returns true if supplied object name is registered.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7382I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINAPP_HELP_DEPLOYWS.CLASSPATH" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINAPP_HELP_DEPLOYWS.CLASSPATH=WASX7382I: &quot;deployews.classpath&quot; option; specifies extra classpath to be used to deploy WebServices
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7198W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7198W" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7198W=WASX7198W: The configuration service is not running. Configuration commands will not run.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    No connection was obtained to the configuration service.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Restart the wsadmin tool to obtain a server connection.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7161I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINAPP_HELP_DEFAULTBINDING.DATASOURCE.USERNAME" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINAPP_HELP_DEFAULTBINDING.DATASOURCE.USERNAME=WASX7161I: &quot;defaultbinding.datasource.username&quot; option; specifies the user name for the default datasource
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7451I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINAPP_HELP_ALLOWDISPATCHREMOTEINCLUDE" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINAPP_HELP_ALLOWDISPATCHREMOTEINCLUDE=WASX7451I: &quot;allowDispatchRemoteInclude&quot; option; Enables an enterprise application to dispatch 
includes to resources across web modules in different JVMs in a managed node environment via the standard RequestDispatcher mechanism.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7403I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SECURITY_USEFIPS_BACKUP_DESCRIPTION" varFormat="Java">
    SECURITY_USEFIPS_BACKUP_DESCRIPTION=WASX7403I: This will enable the use of FIPS (Federal Information Processing Standard) approved cryptographic algorithms.  Note that setting this flag does not automatically change the existing JSSE provider in the Secure Socket Layer configuration.  Also note that FIPS approved JSSE provider only allows TLS protocol.  Moreover, the FIPS approved LTPA authentication mechanism is not backward compatible with non-FIPS approved LTPA implementation that is used in all prior version of WebSphere Application Server products.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7032I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINCONTROL_HELP_GETHOST" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINCONTROL_HELP_GETHOST=WASX7032I: Method: getHost

	Arguments: none

	Description: Returns the host to which the scripting process is
	connected.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7197E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7197E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7197E=WASX7197E: Error creating validation output file {0}; exception information: {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The wsadmin tool cannot open an output file for validation results.  The wsadmin tool cannot create this file.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the wsadmin.traceout log file to determine the problem.  Verify that there is enough space in the file system and that there are no file permission problems.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7212I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINCONFIG_HELP_CREATEUSINGTEMPLATE" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINCONFIG_HELP_CREATEUSINGTEMPLATE=WASX7212I: Method: createUsingTemplate

	Arguments: type, parent, attributes, template

	Description: Creates an object of the given type with the given
	parent.  The specified template is used as the basis for this new
	object, and the specified attributes override settings in the template.

	The template parameter is a configuration ID of an existing object -- .
	this object can be either a template object, returned by using the 
	listTemplates command, or any other existing object of the correct type.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7058I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINCONFIG_HELP_MODIFY" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINCONFIG_HELP_MODIFY=WASX7058I: Method: modify

	Arguments: config id, attributes

	Description: Changes the attributes specified by &quot;attributes&quot;  for
	the configuration object named by &quot;config id.&quot;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7088E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7088E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7088E=WASX7088E: Invalid numeric value specified for attribute &quot;{0}&quot;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An attribute specified by an AdminConfig create or modify command requires a numeric data type.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a numeric value for the attribute.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7017E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ERROR_RUNNING_FILE" varFormat="Java">
    ERROR_RUNNING_FILE=WASX7017E: Exception received while running file &quot;{0}&quot;; exception information: {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The script or profile cannot run.  The wsadmin tool created an exception.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the wsadmin.traceout log file to determine the problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7008E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CONN_REQUIRES_INTEGER_PORT" varFormat="Java">
    CONN_REQUIRES_INTEGER_PORT=WASX7008E: {0} connection type requires an integer port; found: &quot;{1}&quot;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The wsadmin launcher has been invoked with the -port option, but the string following -port is not an integer.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify an integer port argument for the -port option and reissue the wsadmin command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7196E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7196E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7196E=WASX7196E: Cannot write to validation output file &quot;{0}&quot;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The wsadmin tool cannot open an output file for validation results.  The file exists on your system, but the wsadmin tool cannot write to it.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the wsadmin.traceout log file to determine the problem. Verify that there is enough space in the file system and that there are no file permission problems.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7439I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINAPP_HELP_ISAPPREADY" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINAPP_HELP_ISAPPREADY=WASX7439I: Method: isAppReady

	Arguments: application name

	Description: Tests to see if the specified application has been
	distributed and is ready to be run.  Returns true if the application
	is ready; false otherwise.

	Arguments: application name, ignoreUnknownState

	Description: Tests to see if the specified application has been
	distributed and is ready to be run.  Valid values for ignoreUnknownState
	argument are true or false. If true is specified as its value, then
	any node or server with unknown state is not included in the final
	ready return. Returns true if the application is ready; false
	otherwise.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7290I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINCONTROL_HELP_SETATTRIBUTE_JMX" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINCONTROL_HELP_SETATTRIBUTE_JMX=WASX7290I: Method: setAttribute_jmx

	Arguments: object name (type ObjectName), attribute (type Attribute)

	Description: Sets the Attribute contained in &quot;attribute&quot; for the MBean
	described by &quot;object name.&quot;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7087E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7087E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7087E=WASX7087E: Invalid value for attribute &quot;{0}&quot; -- valid values are &quot;{1}&quot;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The value specified for an AdminConfig create or modify command attribute of some ENUM type is not a valid value.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify one of the valid values for the ENUM attribute.  See the WASX7087E error message for the possible values.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7485I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINAPP_HELP_NOVALIDATESCHEMA" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINAPP_HELP_NOVALIDATESCHEMA=WASX7485I: &quot;validateSchema&quot; option; Use this option to specify that the schema is not to be validated.  This is the default.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7195I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7195I" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7195I=WASX7195I: Severity {0}; line {1}; target &quot;{2}&quot;;	{3}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The user requested validation. By default, the name of the file is wsadmin.valout, located in the logs directory.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Fix any configuration problems noted by the previous message.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7180I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINAPP_HELP_DEPLOYEJB.PRECOMPILEJSPS" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINAPP_HELP_DEPLOYEJB.PRECOMPILEJSPS=WASX7180I: &quot;deployejb.preCompileJSPs&quot; option; specifies that EJBDeploy should pre-compile JSPs; the default setting is &quot;nodeployejb.preCompileJSPs&quot;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7461I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HELP_HELP_ADMINTASK" varFormat="Java">
    HELP_HELP_ADMINTASK=WASX7461I: Method: AdminTask

	Arguments: none

	Description: Display general help information for the
	AdminTask object provided by wsadmin.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7086E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7086E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7086E=WASX7086E: Unable to determine relationship information for type &quot;{0}&quot;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The wsadmin tool could not run an AdminConfig parents command.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    This exception is unexpected. The cause is not immediately known.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7194I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7194I" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7194I=WASX7194I: Number of messages of severity {0}: {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message provides a summary of messages generated during configuration validation.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7061I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINCONFIG_HELP_ATTRIBUTES" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINCONFIG_HELP_ATTRIBUTES=WASX7061I: Method: attributes

	Arguments: type

	Description: Displays all the possible attributes contained by an 
	object of type &quot;type.&quot;  The attribute types are also displayed; when
	the attribute represents a reference to another object, the type of
	the tattribute has a suffix of &quot;@.&quot;  When the attribute represents a
	collection of objects, the type is listed with a suffix of &quot;*.&quot;  If the
	type represents a base type, possible subtypes are listed after the
	base type in parenthesis.  If the type is an enumeration, it is listed
	as &quot;ENUM,&quot; followed by the possible values in parentheses.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7045I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINCONTROL_HELP_SETATTRIBUTE" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINCONTROL_HELP_SETATTRIBUTE=WASX7045I: Method: setAttribute

	Arguments: object name, attribute name, attribute value

	Description: Sets the attribute with name &quot;attribute name&quot; to the
	value given by &quot;attribute value&quot; for the MBean described by
	&quot;object name.&quot;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7226I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINAPP_HELP_NOVALIDATEAPP" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINAPP_HELP_NOVALIDATEAPP=WASX7226I: &quot;novalidateApp&quot; option; this option is obsolete
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7171I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINAPP_HELP_DEPLOYEJB.DBNAME" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINAPP_HELP_DEPLOYEJB.DBNAME=WASX7171I: &quot;deployejb.dbname&quot; option; specifies the database name for EJBDeploy; default is&quot;was50.&quot;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7047I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINCONTROL_HELP_INVOKE" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINCONTROL_HELP_INVOKE=WASX7047I: Method: invoke

	Arguments: object name, operation

	Description: Invoke the operation named by &quot;operation&quot; on the MBean
	described by &quot;object name.&quot;  No arguments are passed for the operation.

	Method: invoke

	Arguments: object name, operation, arguments

	Description: Invoke the operation named by &quot;operation&quot; on the MBean
	described by &quot;object name&quot; using the parameters described by 
	&quot;arguments.&quot;  If no arguments are required for this operation, the
	&quot;arguments&quot; parameter may be omitted.

	Method: invoke

	Arguments: object name, operation, arguments, signature

	Description: Invoke the operation named by &quot;operation&quot; on the MBean
	described by &quot;object name&quot; using the parameters described by &quot;arguments&quot;
	and the signatures described by &quot;signature.&quot;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7193I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7193I" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7193I=WASX7193I: Validation results are logged in {0}: Total number of messages: {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Validation is complete.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Optional- Examine the messages logged in the specified file to see if corrective action is needed.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7084E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7084E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7084E=WASX7084E: No help available for : &quot;{0}&quot;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    No help is available for the argument that has been specified with the help &lt;argument&gt; command.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the argument is a valid argument for help.  Reissue the &quot;help&quot; command without the argument for a list of valid options.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7378I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINAPP_HELP_RELOADENABLED" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINAPP_HELP_RELOADENABLED=WASX7378I: &quot;reloadEnabled&quot; option; this option specifies to enable class reloading; this is the default setting.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7063E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CONNECTOR_NOT_AVAIL" varFormat="Java">
    CONNECTOR_NOT_AVAIL=WASX7063E: Error creating &quot;{0}&quot; connection to server: server may not be running; connector properties: {1}; exception information: {2}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The connector did not establish a connection to the server.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the accompanying exception information and the information in the wsadmin.traceout file to determine the cause of the error.  The server might not be running.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7083E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7083E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7083E=WASX7083E: Cannot find config object: &quot;{0}&quot;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The wsadmin tool cannot find the configuration object specified by an AdminConfig command.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a valid configuration object.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7244I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINAPP_HELP_RAR.ARCHIVEPATH" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINAPP_HELP_RAR.ARCHIVEPATH=WASX7244I: &quot;rar.archivePath&quot; option; this option is the name of the path where the file is assume to reside.  If this is not specified, then the path is taken to be given by CONNECTOR_INSTALL_ROOT
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7200I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINCONFIG_HELP_SETVALIDATIONLEVEL" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINCONFIG_HELP_SETVALIDATIONLEVEL=WASX7200I: Method: setValidationLevel

	Arguments: level

	Description: Sets the validation level to one of five possibilities:
	none, low, medium, high, or highest.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7018E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="LANGUAGE_NOT_REGISTERED" varFormat="Java">
    LANGUAGE_NOT_REGISTERED=WASX7018E: Language &quot;{0}&quot; is not registered to BSF.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An unsupported scripting language was specified.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a supported scripting language with the -lang option or com.ibm.ws.scripting.defaultLang option.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7028I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HELP_GENERAL_HELP" varFormat="Java">
    HELP_GENERAL_HELP=WASX7028I: The Help object has two purposes: 

	First, provide general help information for the objects
	supplied by wsadmin for scripting: Help, AdminApp, AdminConfig,
	AdminControl and AdminTask.

	Second, provide a means to obtain interface information about
	MBeans running in the system.  For this purpose, a variety of
	commands are available to get information about the operations,
	attributes, and other interface information about particular
	MBeans.

	The following commands are supported by Help; more detailed
	information about each of these commands is available by using the
	&quot;help&quot; command of Help and supplying the name of the command
	as an argument.


attributes		Given an MBean, returns help for attributes
operations		Given an MBean, returns help for operations
constructors		Given an MBean, returns help for constructors
description		Given an MBean, returns help for description
notifications		Given an MBean, returns help for notifications
classname		Given an MBean, returns help for classname
all			Given an MBean, returns help for all the above
help			Returns this help text
AdminControl		Returns general help text for the AdminControl object
AdminConfig		Returns general help text for the AdminConfig object
AdminApp		Returns general help text for the AdminApp object
AdminTask		Returns general help text for the AdminTask object
wsadmin			Returns general help text for the wsadmin script
			launcher
message			Given a message id, returns explanation and user
			action message
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7082E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7082E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7082E=WASX7082E: The creation of a {1} in a {0} object requires that an attribute name be specified, because more than one attribute exists with the same type.  Please specify one of the following attribute names as a fourth parameter to the &quot;create&quot; method: {2}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    When an object is created with AdminConfig, wsadmin determines what attribute name to use for the new object in the parent.  In certain cases, the wsadmin tool cannot determine this information if the parent object contains more than one attribute of the type being created.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Use the AdminConfig create command that uses four parameters.  As a fourth parameter, supply one of the attribute names supplied in this message.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7148I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINCONTROL_HELP_TESTCONNECTION" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINCONTROL_HELP_TESTCONNECTION=WASX7148I: Method: testConnection

	Arguments: config id

	Description: Tests the connection to a DataSource.  The &quot;config id&quot; 
	argument is the configuration ID of a DataSource object. The DataSource 
	object passed in has to be saved in the configuration before 
	attempting to run testConnection.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7190I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7190I" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7190I=WASX7190I: Validation at level {0} with cross-document validation {1}, requested at {2} for action &quot;{3}&quot;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The wsadmin tool writes this informational message to the validation output file each time validation is requested.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7428W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7428W" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7428W=WASX7428W: contextroot option will be ignored if module exists.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Use the contextroot option with the update command, the modulefile content type, and the update or addupdate operation.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    For an update operation with a modulefile content type, the wsadmin tool ignores the contextroot option.  For the addupdate operation with a modulefile the content type, the wsadmin tool ignores the contextroot option if the module exists.  This message is for the informational purposes only.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7006E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DASH_LANG_NEEDS_FOLLOWING_LANGUAGE" varFormat="Java">
    DASH_LANG_NEEDS_FOLLOWING_LANGUAGE=WASX7006E: &quot;-lang&quot; option must be followed by a language identifier.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The wsadmin launcher has been invoked with the -lang option, but no language argument was found.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a supported scripting language for the -lang option and reissue the wsadmin command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7081E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7081E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7081E=WASX7081E: Error obtaining enum information: exception information: &quot;{0}&quot;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The wsadmin tool could not initialize an enum attribute.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    This exception is unexpected. The cause is not immediately known.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX8022E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INCOMPATIBLE_NODE" varFormat="Java">
    INCOMPATIBLE_NODE=WASX8022E: Incompatible node version; exception information: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The wsadmin tool is connecting to an incompatible server or deployment manager node.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that the wsadmin tool connect to the same or higher version of the server or deployment manager node.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7319I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7319I" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7319I=WASX7319I: The {0} attribute is set to false.  A start will be attempted for server &quot;{1}&quot; but the configuration information for node &quot;{2}&quot; may not be current.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The wsadmin tool is using the startServer command to start a server. The configuration used by the starting server may not be the most recent configuration because the configuration has not be synchronized for this node.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the configuration is incorrect, stop the server and invoke a configuration synchronization for this node.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7080E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7080E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7080E=WASX7080E: Invalid attributes specified for type &quot;{0}&quot; -- &quot;{1}&quot;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An attribute name that has been specified for the given type is not valid.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a valid attribute name.  Run the AdminConfig attributes command for a list of valid attribute names.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7277I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HELP_HELP_ADMINCONTROL" varFormat="Java">
    HELP_HELP_ADMINCONTROL=WASX7277I: Method: AdminControl

	Arguments: none

	Description: Display general help information for the
	AdminControl object provided by wsadmin.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7462I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HELP_HELP_WSADMIN" varFormat="Java">
    HELP_HELP_WSADMIN=WASX7462I: Method: wsadmin

	Arguments: none

	Description: Display general help information for the
	wsadmin script launcher.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7386E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="EXTENSION_PARSER_EXCEPTION_MESSAGE" varFormat="Java">
    EXTENSION_PARSER_EXCEPTION_MESSAGE=WASX7386E: {0} in {1} at line {2} column {3}
{4}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A parser exception occured when getting the scripting extension.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the exception in the trace log and correct the problem accordingly.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7055I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINCONFIG_HELP_REMOVE" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINCONFIG_HELP_REMOVE=WASX7055I: Method: remove

	Arguments: config id

	Description: Removes the configuration object named by &quot;config id.&quot;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7209I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7209I" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7209I=WASX7209I: Connected to process &quot;{0}&quot; on node {1} using {2} connector;  The type of process is: {3}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The wsadmin tool has connected to a server during initialization.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7291I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINCONTROL_HELP_SETATTRIBUTES_JMX" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINCONTROL_HELP_SETATTRIBUTES_JMX=WASX7291I: Method: setAttributes_jmx

	Arguments: object name (type ObjectName),
	attributes (type AttributeList)

	Description: Sets attributes in the MBean described by
	&quot;object name.&quot;  The attribute names and values are contained in the 
	&quot;attributes&quot; argument.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7208I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7208I" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7208I=WASX7208I: Validation settings in effect now: Level={0}, Cross-validation={1}, Output file={2}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The wsadmin tool is initialized or validation settings have been changed.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7072E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CONTROL_SERVICE_NOT_AVAILABLE" varFormat="Java">
    CONTROL_SERVICE_NOT_AVAILABLE=WASX7072E: The control service is not available.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The wsadmin tool is initialized but cannot connect to a server.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Reissue the wsadmin command to create a server connection.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7316W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7316W" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7316W=WASX7316W: Error creating Dynamic Scripting object. These objects will not be available -- &quot;{0}&quot;. Please use the generic AdminControl facilities.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The dynamic scripting objects did not initialize.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Use the AdminControl invoke and get/setAttribute(s) commands to interact with MBeans instead of dynamic scripting support.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7156I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINAPP_HELP_LOCAL" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINAPP_HELP_LOCAL=WASX7156I: &quot;local&quot; option; specifies that the AdminApp function will be performed in local mode, without communicating with a server.

This option is deprecated. Use &quot;-conntype NONE&quot; in the command line or &quot;com.ws.scripting.connectionType=NONE&quot; in wsadmin.properties to perfrom AdminApp function in local mode.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7022E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ERROR_RUNNING_COMMAND" varFormat="Java">
    ERROR_RUNNING_COMMAND=WASX7022E: Problem running command &quot;{0}&quot; -- exception information: {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The wsadmin tool created an exception when executing the command.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the exception information provided in the message to determine the appropriate user action.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7233I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINAPP_HELP_VERBOSE" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINAPP_HELP_VERBOSE=WASX7233I: &quot;verbose&quot; option; this option causes additional messages to be displayed during install.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7127I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINCONFIG_HELP_QUERYCHANGES" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINCONFIG_HELP_QUERYCHANGES=WASX7127I: Method: queryChanges

	Arguments: none

	Description: Returns a list of unsaved configuration files
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7315W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7315W" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7315W=WASX7315W: Failed to generated dynamic scripting object: &quot;{0}&quot;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A dynamic scripting object did not initialize.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    This exception is unexpected. The cause is not immediately known.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7154I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINAPP_HELP_NODE" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINAPP_HELP_NODE=WASX7154I: &quot;node&quot; option; specifies the node name for AdminApp install functions.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7206W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7206W" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7206W=WASX7206W: The application management service is not running. Application management commands will not run.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    No connection was obtained to the application management service.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Restart the wsadmin tool to obtain a server connection, or use &quot;-conntype NONE&quot; option to run the local mode.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7159I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINAPP_HELP_NOUSEDEFAULTBINDINGS" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINAPP_HELP_NOUSEDEFAULTBINDINGS=WASX7159I: &quot;nousedefaultbindings&quot; option; specifies that default bindings are not used for install; this is the default setting.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7167I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINAPP_HELP_DEFAULTBINDING.FORCE" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINAPP_HELP_DEFAULTBINDING.FORCE=WASX7167I: &quot;defaultbinding.force&quot; option; specifies that the default bindings should override current bindings.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7158I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINAPP_HELP_USEDEFAULTBINDINGS" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINAPP_HELP_USEDEFAULTBINDINGS=WASX7158I: &quot;usedefaultbindings&quot; option; specifies that default bindings are to used for install.  Default is &quot;nousedefaultbindings&quot;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7463I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINAPP_HELP_DEPLOYEJB.DBACCESSTYPE" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINAPP_HELP_DEPLOYEJB.DBACCESSTYPE=WASX7463I: &quot;deployejb.dbaccesstype&quot; option; specifies the database access type for EJBDeploy
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7459E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7459E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7459E=WASX7459E: The configuration service is not available. Target node&apos;s nodeagent may not be running &quot;{0}.&quot;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The AdminConfig object was specified, but the wsadmin process is not connected to a server with a running configuration service.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the node agent of the target node is not running, start it and reissue the wsadmin command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7073E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="RECONNECT_FAILED" varFormat="Java">
    RECONNECT_FAILED=WASX7073E: Attempt to reconnect to the server failed for the following objects: {0}; server may no longer be running.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The AdminControl reconnect command did not reconnect to the server.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the accompanying exception information and the information in the wsadmin.traceout file to determine the cause of the error.  The server might not be running.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7314I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7314I" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7314I=WASX7314I: Finished generating Dynamic Scripting Objects.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The wsadmin tool initialized the dynamic scripting objects.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7440E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="METHOD_NOT_SUPPORTED" varFormat="Java">
    METHOD_NOT_SUPPORTED=WASX7440E: &quot;{0}&quot; method is not supported when connecting to local mode.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The wsadmin tool is connected to local mode.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the scripting client is connected to a server and that the server is running.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7269I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HELP_HELP_OPERATIONS" varFormat="Java">
    HELP_HELP_OPERATIONS=WASX7269I: Method: operations

	Arguments: MBean

	Description: Display information about the operations of the 
	specified MBean.

	Method: operations

	Arguments: MBean, operation name

	Description: Display information about the specified operation on 
	the specified MBean.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7177I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINAPP_HELP_NODEPLOYEJB.VALIDATE" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINAPP_HELP_NODEPLOYEJB.VALIDATE=WASX7177I: &quot;nodeployejb.validate&quot; option; specifies that EJBDeploy should not run validation; the default setting is &quot;deployejb.validate&quot;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7437I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINAPP_HELP_PROCESSEMBEDDEDCONFIG" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINAPP_HELP_PROCESSEMBEDDEDCONFIG=WASX7437I: &quot;processEmbeddedConfig&quot; option; Use this option to process the embedded configration data that is included in the application. This setting is the default.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7458E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7458E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7458E=WASX7458E: Invalid file permission string &quot;{0}&quot;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The parameter value for file permission is not valid.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a file permission value with a valid string.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7383I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINAPP_HELP_DEPLOYWS.JARDIRS" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINAPP_HELP_DEPLOYWS.JARDIRS=WASX7383I: &quot;deployews.jardirs&quot; option; specifies extra extension directories to be used to deploy WebServices
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7313I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7313I" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7313I=WASX7313I: Generating Dynamic Scripting Objects. Please Wait...
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The wsadmin tool is initializing the dynamic scripting objects.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7349I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7349I" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7349I=WASX7349I: Possible value for resource authorization is container or per connection factory
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7450I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINAPP_HELP_BUILDVERSION" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINAPP_HELP_BUILDVERSION=WASX7450I: &quot;buildVersion&quot; option; specifies the build version of an application ear file.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7329I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINCONFIG_HELP_SHOWATTRIBUTE" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINCONFIG_HELP_SHOWATTRIBUTE=WASX7329I: Method: showAttribute

	Arguments: config id, attribute

	Description: Shows the value of the single attribute specified for
	the configuration object named by &quot;config id.&quot;  The output of this
	command is different from the output of &quot;show&quot; when a single
	attribute is specified:  the showAttribute command does not display a
	list containing the attribute name and value; rather, the attribute 
	value alone is displayed.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7335I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINAPP_HELP_REDEPLOY.IGNORE.NEW" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINAPP_HELP_REDEPLOY.IGNORE.NEW=WASX7335I: This option is deprecated. Use the &quot;update.ignore.new&quot; option instead.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7056I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINCONFIG_HELP_LIST" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINCONFIG_HELP_LIST=WASX7056I: Method: list

	Arguments: type

	Description: Lists all the configuration objects of the type named
	by &quot;type.&quot;

	Method: list

	Arguments: type, scope

	Description: Lists all the configuration objects of the type named
	by &quot;type&quot; within the scope of the configuration object named by &quot;scope.&quot;

	Method: list

	Arguments: type, pattern

	Description: Lists all the configuration objects of the type named
	by &quot;type&quot; matching with the wildcard &quot;pattern&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7433I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINAPP_HELP_CUSTOM" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINAPP_HELP_CUSTOM=WASX7433I: &quot;custom&quot; option; specifies a name-value pair using the format name=value. Use this option to pass option to application deployment extension. Consult application deployment extension documentation for available custom options.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7199I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINCONFIG_HELP_VALIDATE" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINCONFIG_HELP_VALIDATE=WASX7199I: Method: validate

	Arguments: none

	Description: Requests configuration validation results based on the
	files in your workspace, the value of the cross-document validation
	enabled flag, and the validation level setting. 

	Method: validate

	Arguments: config id

	Description: Requests configuration validation results based on the
	files in your workspace, the value of the cross-document validation
	enabled flag, and the validation level setting.  The scope of this 
	request is the object named by &quot;config id.&quot;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7348I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7348I" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7348I=WASX7348I: Each element of the {0} task consists of the following {1} fields: {2}
Of these fields, the following are required and used as keys to locate the rows in the task: {3}
and the following may be assigned new values: {4}

The current contents of the task after running default bindings are:
{5}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The previous information results from an AdminApp taskInfo command and details the task information requested.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7401W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SECURITY_NONFIPS_SSL" varFormat="Java">
    SECURITY_NONFIPS_SSL=WASX7401W: The security policy is set to use only FIPS approved cryptographic algorithms, however at least one SSL configuration may not be using a FIPS approved JSSE provider. FIPS approved cryptographic algorithms may not be used in those cases.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    When security policy is set to use only FIPS approved cryptographic algorithms, no SSL configuration can use FIPS approved JSSE provider.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the exception in the trace log and correct the problem accordingly.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7239E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7239E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7239E=WASX7239E: Unexpected error setting attribute &quot;{0}&quot; of type &quot;{1}&quot; to value &quot;{2}.&quot;  Additional information may be found in the trace log.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The wsadmin tool did not invoke the AdminConfig modify or create command.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the wsadmin.traceout log for more information.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7347E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7347E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7347E=WASX7347E: An argument is required for option &quot;{0}.&quot;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified option requires an accompanying argument.  For example, if you specify the &quot;-node&quot; option, you must follow the &quot;-node&quot; option with the name of a node such as &quot;-node mynode.&quot;
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify an argument for the indicated option, or remove the option from the command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7270I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="HELP_HELP_CONSTRUCTORS" varFormat="Java">
    HELP_HELP_CONSTRUCTORS=WASX7270I: Method: constructors

	Arguments: MBean

	Description: Display information about the constructors of the 
	specified MBean.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7295I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINCONFIG_HELP_CHECKIN" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINCONFIG_HELP_CHECKIN=WASX7295I: Method: checkin

	Arguments: documentURI, filename, digest

	Description: Checks a file named by &quot;filename&quot; into the configuration 
	repository that is described by the &quot;documentURI&quot;. The &quot;documentURI&quot; 
	is relative to the root of the configuration repository such as 
	&quot;cells/MyCell/nodes/MyNode/serverindex.xml&quot; which must exist 
	in the repository, and the &quot;filename&quot; is the name of the source 
	file to check in and it must be a valid local file name such as 
	&quot;c:/myfile&quot;. The &quot;digest&quot; parameter should be the opaque object 
	which is returned by a prior extract command of AdminConfig object.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7446E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="TRACE_FILE_REQUIRES_ARG" varFormat="Java">
    TRACE_FILE_REQUIRES_ARG=WASX7446E: &quot;-tracefile&quot; option must be followed by a file path.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The wsadmin launcher did not run because no logfile argument was found for the -tracefile option.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a file path for the -tracefile option and reissue the wsadmin command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7011E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="FILE_NOT_FOUND" varFormat="Java">
    FILE_NOT_FOUND=WASX7011E: Cannot find file &quot;{0}&quot;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The wsadmin launcher has been invoked with an option that requires the name of a file, but the file cannot be found.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the name of the file specified by the -p, -f, or -profile option, or in a wsadmin.properties file.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7426I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINAPP_HELP_NORELOADENABLED" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINAPP_HELP_NORELOADENABLED=WASX7426I: &quot;noreloadEnabled&quot; option: this option specifies not to enable class reloading; the default is reloadEnabled.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7129E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7129E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7129E=WASX7129E: Cannot create objects of type &quot;{0}&quot; in parents of type &quot;{1}&quot;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The parent that has been specified with the AdminConfig create command is not valid.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a valid parent object for the object to create and reissue the command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7237W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7237W" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7237W=WASX7237W: The attribute &quot;{0}&quot; has a type that is not supported by the String signatures of AdminControl -- the type is &quot;{1}.&quot;  AdminControl will attempt to convert the attribute to and from String type, but this may not give the desired result. Use the native JMX object signatures for actions involving this type.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The AdminControl setAttribute command contains an attribute type that is not supported by the setAttribute command.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Use the setAttribute_jmx command to set this attribute.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7346E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WASX7346E" varFormat="Java">
    WASX7346E=WASX7346E: Cannot locate NodeAgent object for server &quot;{0}&quot; of process type {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The wsadmin tool cannot run the AdminControl stopServer command because the node agent for the specified server is not located in the configuration.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the client is connected to the appropriate process type.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7185I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINAPP_HELP_NOUSEMETADATAFROMBINARY" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINAPP_HELP_NOUSEMETADATAFROMBINARY=WASX7185I: &quot;nouseMetaDataFromBinary&quot; option; use this option to specify that the metadata (such as deployment descriptors, bindings, extensions) that are used at runtime come from the config repository; this is the default setting.  Use &quot;useMetaDataFromBinary,&quot; to indicate that the metadata used at runtime come from the earfile.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7035I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINCONTROL_HELP_ISALIVE" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINCONTROL_HELP_ISALIVE=WASX7035I: Method: isAlive

	Arguments: none

	Description: Is the client session alive?
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7155I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINAPP_HELP_SERVER" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINAPP_HELP_SERVER=WASX7155I: &quot;server&quot; option; specifies the server name for AdminApp install functions.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WSCP0169E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="WSCP_EXC_CLOSING_QUOTE" varFormat="Java">
    WSCP_EXC_CLOSING_QUOTE=WSCP0169E: Expected &quot; not found
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    There is a syntax error in a string provided in an attribute list
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the attribute list syntax.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="WASX7460I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADMINAPP_HELP_GETDEPLOYSTATUS" varFormat="Java">
    ADMINAPP_HELP_GETDEPLOYSTATUS=WASX7460I: Method: getDeployStatus

	Arguments: application name

	Description: Returns a string which represents the deployment status
	of the application.  The status of each node, to which the application is
	deployed, is concatenated by the &quot;+&quot; character.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<!-- END MESSAGES -->
</TMSSource>
