<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/css" href="../../resources/stylesheets/wasmsgxml.css"?>
<TMSSource name="TivoliMessages" tmsVersion="1.0" xml:lang="en">
<!-- CMVC MSG File Name = /com.ibm.ws.eba.obr.provisioner/src/com/ibm/ws/eba/provisioning/exception/nls/resolver.nlsprops -->
<!-- DO NOT EDIT THIS FILE - This file was generated by the XML/Html & Property emitter -->
<!-- BEGIN MESSAGES -->
<Message ID="CWSAJ1003E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="TOO_MANY_CB_SYM_NAMES" varFormat="Java">
    TOO_MANY_CB_SYM_NAMES=CWSAJ1003E: An internal error occurred. A composite bundle manifest must contain exactly one Bundle-SymbolicName entry. The following entry was found: {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The runtime environment attempted to process the metadata for a composite bundle, and could not determine the bundle&apos;s symbolic name.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    CMSG0002
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAJ1006E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_FILTER_STRING" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_FILTER_STRING=CWSAJ1006E: A syntax error occurred attempting to parse the blueprint filter string &apos;&apos;{0}&apos;&apos; for element with id {1}: {2}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An InvalidSyntaxException was thrown whilst attempting to parse the filter string for the element with the specified id.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check the filter string for the specified id is syntactically correct.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAJ1001E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="TOO_MANY_SYM_NAMES" varFormat="Java">
    TOO_MANY_SYM_NAMES=CWSAJ1001E: An internal error occurred. A bundle manifest must contain exactly one Bundle-SymbolicName entry. The following entry was found: {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The runtime attempted to process the metadata for a bundle, and was unable to determine the bundle&apos;s symbolic name.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    CMSG0002
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAJ1005E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="TOO_MANY_FRAG_HOSTS" varFormat="Java">
    TOO_MANY_FRAG_HOSTS=CWSAJ1005E: An internal error occurred. A bundle fragment manifest must define exactly one Fragment-Host entry. The following entry was found: {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The runtime environment attempted to process the metadata for a bundle fragment, and could not determine the fragment&apos;s host bundle.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    CMSG0002
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAJ1004E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INCORRECT_CB_MANDATORY_HEADERS" varFormat="Java">
    INCORRECT_CB_MANDATORY_HEADERS=CWSAJ1004E: An internal error occurred. A composite bundle with symbolic name {0} and manifest version {1} could not be processed.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A composite bundle manifest must contain both a valid Bundle-SymbolicName and CompositeBundle-ManifestVersion entry.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check that all composite bundles contain a valid Bundle-SymbolicName and CompositeBundle-ManifestVersion entry in their manifest files.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAJ1002E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INCORRECT_MANDATORY_HEADERS" varFormat="Java">
    INCORRECT_MANDATORY_HEADERS=CWSAJ1002E: An internal error occurred. A bundle with symbolic name {0} and manifest version {1} could not be processed.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A bundle manifest must contain both a valid Bundle-SymbolicName and Bundle-ManifestVersion entry.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check that all bundles contain a valid Bundle-SymbolicName and Bundle-ManifestVersion entry in their manifest files.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<!-- END MESSAGES -->
</TMSSource>
