<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/css" href="../../resources/stylesheets/wasmsgxml.css"?>
<TMSSource name="TivoliMessages" tmsVersion="1.0" xml:lang="en">
<!-- CMVC MSG File Name = /com.ibm.ws.eba.admin/src/com/ibm/ws/eba/admin/messages/EBAADMINMessages.nlsprops -->
<!-- DO NOT EDIT THIS FILE - This file was generated by the XML/Html & Property emitter -->
<!-- BEGIN MESSAGES -->
<Message ID="CWSAJ0073E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="EBAADMIN0073E" varFormat="Java">
    EBAADMIN0073E=CWSAJ0073E: The symbolicName parameter has not been specified and is required.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The command requires the symbolicName parameter to be specified.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Reissue the command specifying the symbolicName.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAJ0053E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="EBAADMIN0053E" varFormat="Java">
    EBAADMIN0053E=CWSAJ0053E: Unable to find the deployment manifest from the location {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The deployment manifest, DEPLOYMENT.MF, to import does not exist.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check that the path of the deployment manifest is correct.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAJ0069E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="EBAADMIN0069E" varFormat="Java">
    EBAADMIN0069E=CWSAJ0069E: The bundles {0} could not be removed from the internal bundle repository. All other bundles {1} have been successfully removed.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Some bundles could not be deleted from the internal bundle repository.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Stop any applications that might be using the bundles that could not be deleted, then attempt to remove them again.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAJ0033E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="EBAADMIN0033E" varFormat="Java">
    EBAADMIN0033E=CWSAJ0033E: Bundle {0} is already stopped.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    You can not stop the bundle because it is already stopped.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAJ0049E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="EBAADMIN0049E" varFormat="Java">
    EBAADMIN0049E=CWSAJ0049E: Cannot delete the bundle {0} because the following Composite Bundle Archives have a dependency on the bundle: {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A bundle cannot be deleted from the internal bundle repository if a Composite Bundle Archive depends on that bundle.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    To delete the bundle, first delete the Composite Bundle Archives listed, then delete the bundle.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAJ0013E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="EBAADMIN0013E" varFormat="Java">
    EBAADMIN0013E=CWSAJ0013E: Unable to obtain required feature capabilities for features like the JPA2 feature.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    CMSG0001
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    CMSG0002
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAJ0029E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="EBAADMIN0029E" varFormat="Java">
    EBAADMIN0029E=CWSAJ0029E: Unable to find service with service ID {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The service ID that was supplied to the command does not match a service in the registry.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Retry the command with a valid service ID.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAJ0009E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="EBAADMIN0009E" varFormat="Java">
    EBAADMIN0009E=CWSAJ0009E: The bundle {1} with version {2}, defined in the file {0}, already exists in the repository.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The bundle cannot be added to the repository because the bundle already exists in the repository.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check whether the bundle in the repository is the correct one. If the bundle in the repository is not correct, remove that bundle from the repository before you add the correct bundle.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAJ0072E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="EBAADMIN0072E" varFormat="Java">
    EBAADMIN0072E=CWSAJ0072E: The cuName parameter has not been specified and is required.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The command requires the cuName parameter to be specified.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Reissue the command specifying the cuName.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAJ0084W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CBA_WITH_MISSING_SERVICE_IMPORTS" varFormat="Java">
    CBA_WITH_MISSING_SERVICE_IMPORTS=CWSAJ0084W: Service references in the contents of the Composite Bundle Archive (CBA) {0} cannot be resolved. If these services are provided by bundles that are not included in the CBA, then the CBA must import them. The following service dependencies were unresolved: {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    If a bundle in a Composite Bundle Archive (CBA) uses a service that is not contained in the bundle, or exported by another bundle within the CBA, then the CBA must import the service.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the composite manifest, COMPOSITEBUNDLE.MF, so that the CBA imports any services that are used by bundles in the CBA and not otherwise available within the CBA.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAJ0052E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="EBAADMIN0052E" varFormat="Java">
    EBAADMIN0052E=CWSAJ0052E: An internal error has occurred. Unable to find the deployment manifest from the EBA asset {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    CMSG0001
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    CMSG0001
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAJ0068E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="EBAADMIN0068E" varFormat="Java">
    EBAADMIN0068E=CWSAJ0068E: An internal error occurred. Metadata for the bundles {0} could not be removed from the internal bundle repository. Also, the bundles {1} could not be deleted from the repository. The exception was {2}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Some bundles could not be deleted from the internal bundle repository, and others could not have their metadata removed. The system might now be in an inconsistent state.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Discard the changes in the current workspace, and attempt to remove the bundles one at a time.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAJ0032I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="EBAADMIN0032I" varFormat="Java">
    EBAADMIN0032I=CWSAJ0032I: Bundle {0} started successfully.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAJ0048E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="EBAADMIN0048E" varFormat="Java">
    EBAADMIN0048E=CWSAJ0048E: Unable to get package information because you have not connected to a framework.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    You are not currently connected to a framework.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Use the connect command to connect to a framework. For a list of available frameworks, use the list() command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAJ0012E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="EBAADMIN0012E" varFormat="Java">
    EBAADMIN0012E=CWSAJ0012E: An internal error occurred. Cannot find the Launcher service.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    CMSG0001
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    CMSG0002
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAJ0028E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="EBAADMIN0028E" varFormat="Java">
    EBAADMIN0028E=CWSAJ0028E: Unable to find bundle with bundle ID {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The bundle ID that was supplied to the command does not match a bundle in the framework.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Retry the command with a valid bundle ID.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAJ0008E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="EBAADMIN0008E" varFormat="Java">
    EBAADMIN0008E=CWSAJ0008E: The specified file {0} does not contain a valid bundle manifest.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified file is not an OSGi bundle.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check and correct the bundle manifest of the supplied file.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAJ0071E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="EBAADMIN0071E" varFormat="Java">
    EBAADMIN0071E=CWSAJ0071E: An internal error occurred. A runtime service is not available from the OSGi service registry: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    CMSG0001
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    CMSG0002
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAJ0051E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="EBAADMIN0051E" varFormat="Java">
    EBAADMIN0051E=CWSAJ0051E: The asset {0} supplied is not an EBA asset.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The asset supplied is not an enterprise bundle archive (EBA) asset.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Make sure the asset supplied is an EBA asset.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAJ0067E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="EBAADMIN0067E" varFormat="Java">
    EBAADMIN0067E=CWSAJ0067E: An internal error occurred. Metadata for the bundles {0} could not be removed from the internal bundle repository. The exception was {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The bundles could not be removed from the internal bundle repository. The system might now be in an inconsistent state.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Discard the changes in the current workspace, and attempt to remove the bundles one at a time.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAJ0031E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="EBAADMIN0031E" varFormat="Java">
    EBAADMIN0031E=CWSAJ0031E: Bundle {0} is already started.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    You cannot start the bundle because it is already started.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAJ0047E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="EBAADMIN0047E" varFormat="Java">
    EBAADMIN0047E=CWSAJ0047E: Service filter is not valid: {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The service filter supplied is not valid.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check that the service filter is valid and retry the command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAJ0011E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="EBAADMIN0011E" varFormat="Java">
    EBAADMIN0011E=CWSAJ0011E: An internal error occurred. The repository generator service is not available from the OSGi service registry.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    CMSG0001
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    CMSG0002
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAJ0027E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="EBAADMIN0027E" varFormat="Java">
    EBAADMIN0027E=CWSAJ0027E: Unable to get service information because you have not connected to a framework.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    You are not currently connected to a framework.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Use the connect command to connect to a framework. For a list of available frameworks, use the list() command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAJ0070E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="EBAADMIN0070E" varFormat="Java">
    EBAADMIN0070E=CWSAJ0070E: The bundle {0} contained in the composite bundle archive {1} does not contain a valid bundle manifest.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified file is not an OSGi bundle.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check and correct the bundle manifest of the supplied file.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAJ0080E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CBA_WITH_MISSING_PACKAGE_IMPORTS" varFormat="Java">
    CBA_WITH_MISSING_PACKAGE_IMPORTS=CWSAJ0080E: The Composite Bundle Archive (CBA) {0} is not valid. Packages imported by bundles in the CBA are missing from the Import-Package header of the CBA manifest file. The following problems were reported: {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    If a bundle in a Composite Bundle Archive (CBA) uses a package that is not contained in the bundle, or exported by another bundle within the CBA, then the CBA must import the package.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the composite manifest, COMPOSITEBUNDLE.MF, so that the CBA imports any packages that are used by bundles in the CBA and not otherwise available within the CBA.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAJ0050E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="EBAADMIN0050E" varFormat="Java">
    EBAADMIN0050E=CWSAJ0050E: The connection is no longer available. Please check available connections and reconnect if required.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The framework that you were connected to is no longer available. This might be because an application has stopped.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check whether the framework is still available and reconnect if required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAJ0066E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="EBAADMIN0066E" varFormat="Java">
    EBAADMIN0066E=CWSAJ0066E: The string {0} does not match the correct syntax of symbolicname;version.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The string supplied in the list of bundles to remove could not be processed because it did not match the expected syntax.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the syntax of the supplied string.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAJ0030E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="EBAADMIN0030E" varFormat="Java">
    EBAADMIN0030E=CWSAJ0030E: Unable to get header information because you have not connected to a framework.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    You are not currently connected to a framework.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Use the connect command to connect to a framework. For a list of available frameworks, use the list() command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAJ0046E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="EBAADMIN0046E" varFormat="Java">
    EBAADMIN0046E=CWSAJ0046E: Unable to find package with package name {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The package name that was supplied to the command did not match a package in the framework.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check that the package name is valid and retry the command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAJ0010E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="EBAADMIN0010E" varFormat="Java">
    EBAADMIN0010E=CWSAJ0010E: The specified bundle {0} with version {1} does not exist in the local bundle repository.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The bundle cannot be shown or deleted because no bundle with that name exists.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check and correct the version or symbolic name of the bundle.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAJ0026E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="EBAADMIN0026E" varFormat="Java">
    EBAADMIN0026E=CWSAJ0026E: Unable to get bundle information because you have not connected to a framework.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    You are not currently connected to a framework.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Use the connect command to connect to a framework. For a list of available frameworks, use the list() command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAJ0006E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="EBAADMIN0006E" varFormat="Java">
    EBAADMIN0006E=CWSAJ0006E: The bundle repository {0} does not exist.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An attempt was made to modify the bundle repository, but it does not exist.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Create the bundle repository.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAJ0065E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="EBAADMIN0065E" varFormat="Java">
    EBAADMIN0065E=CWSAJ0065E: The specified file {0} cannot be parsed as a manifest file because of exception {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified file does not appear to be a valid manifest file.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check the supplied file is a valid manifest file.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAJ0045E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="EBAADMIN0045E" varFormat="Java">
    EBAADMIN0045E=CWSAJ0045E: Unable to find package with location {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The package location that was supplied to the command did not match a package location in the framework.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check that the package location is valid and retry the command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAJ0025I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="EBAADMIN0025I" varFormat="Java">
    EBAADMIN0025I=CWSAJ0025I:      OSGi application console
 
 Display commands: These commands work only if connected to a framework
 
     ss()                - This command gives the summary information about the installed bundles.
     bundles()           - This command gives comprehensive information about the installed bundles.
     packages()          - This command gives information about the imported/exported packages.
     services()          - This command gives information about the registered Services.
 
     bundle(&lt;bundleID&gt;)  - This command gives information about the specified bundle
     headers(&lt;bundleID&gt;) - This command gives information about the headers associated with the specified bundle
     packages(&lt;bundle ID&gt;) - This command gives information about the exported packages for this bundle.
     packages(&lt;package Name&gt;) - This command gives information about the specified package.
     services(&lt;service ID&gt;) - This command gives information about the specified service.
     services(&lt;OSGI Filter&gt;) - This command gives information about the services matching the filter.
 
     refresh() - This command refreshes the internal OSGi application console cache with the latest information about the state of the framework.
 
 Framework commands:
 
     list() - This command lists the available frameworks that you can connect to.
     connect(&lt;Framework id&gt;) - This command connects to the specified framework.
     connect(&lt;Bundle Name&gt;, &lt;Bundle Version&gt;, &lt;Node Name&gt;, &lt;Server Name&gt;) - This command connects to the specified framework.
 
 Controlling Bundles:
 
     start(&lt;bundleID&gt;) - This command starts the requested bundle.
     stop(&lt;bundleID&gt;   - This command stops the requested bundle.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    None.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    None.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAJ0064E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="EBAADMIN0064E" varFormat="Java">
    EBAADMIN0064E=CWSAJ0064E: The specified file {0} is not a JAR or a Composite Bundle Archive.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The name of the specified file does not end with either a .jar or a .cba file extension.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check and correct the name of the supplied file. The supplied file must be a valid JAR or Composite Bundle Archive (CBA).
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAJ0044E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="EBAADMIN0044E" varFormat="Java">
    EBAADMIN0044E=CWSAJ0044E: Unable to find package with package ID {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The package ID that was supplied to the command did not match a package in the framework.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check that the package ID is valid and retry the command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAJ0024E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="EBAADMIN0024E" varFormat="Java">
    EBAADMIN0024E=CWSAJ0024E: The CompositeBundle-Content header in Composite Bundle Archive {0} must contain only bundles with an exact version. The following entries are not valid: {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A CompositeBundle-Content entry must use a format similar to &apos;bundle.name;version=&quot;[1.0.0,1.0.0]&quot;&apos;.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that entries in the CompositeBundle-Content header in the composite bundle manifest file specify an exact version and use the correct format.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAJ0063E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="EBAADMIN0063E" varFormat="Java">
    EBAADMIN0063E=CWSAJ0063E: Cannot install the Composite Bundle Archive, {0}, because the following export packages differ from those contained by the Composite Bundle Archive: {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A Composite Bundle Archive (CBA) can export only packages that the bundles it contains also export. The attributes and directives must also match.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the composite manifest, COMPOSITEBUNDLE.MF, so that it exports packages that the bundles that the CBA contains also export.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAJ0082W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="EBAADMIN0082W" varFormat="Java">
    EBAADMIN0082W=CWSAJ0082W: The application extension functionality is not available for this composition unit because the composition unit is deployed on the following targets, which do not support application extension: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The targets which the composition unit is deployed against do not all support the application extension functionality.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure the composition unit that you wish to add extensions to is deployed on targets that support the application extension functionality.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAJ0043E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="EBAADMIN0043E" varFormat="Java">
    EBAADMIN0043E=CWSAJ0043E: Bundle {0} cannot stop. It is currently in {1} state.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The bundle cannot be stopped.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Refer to accompanying error messages for more information about why this bundle cannot stop.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAJ0059E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="EBAADMIN0059E" varFormat="Java">
    EBAADMIN0059E=CWSAJ0059E: The {0} parameter has not been specified and is required for the command {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This command requires the specified parameter.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Retry the command and specify the required parameter.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAJ0039I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="EBAADMIN0039I" varFormat="Java">
    EBAADMIN0039I=CWSAJ0039I: Valid frameworks are:
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAJ0023E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="EBAADMIN0023E" varFormat="Java">
    EBAADMIN0023E=CWSAJ0023E: The following bundles that the Composite Bundle Archive, {0}, requires cannot be found in the internal bundle repository: {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A Composite Bundle Archive can be deployed only if all the dependencies can be found in the internal bundle repository.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that the Composite Bundle Archive dependencies listed are either in the Composite Bundle Archive or installed in the internal bundle repository.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAJ0078E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADD_RESOLVE_FAILED" varFormat="Java">
    ADD_RESOLVE_FAILED=CWSAJ0078E: A resolution problem has occurred while adding an extension to composition unit {0}. The exception is: {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The system cannot resolve the selected extension in conjunction with the current deployment of the asset. Bundles might have missing dependencies, be incompatible, or not exist.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Inspect the error. Make any neccessary changes to the asset and to the extension, then reapply the extension.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAJ0003E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="EBAADMIN0003E" varFormat="Java">
    EBAADMIN0003E=CWSAJ0003E: The bundle repository at {0} is already defined as name {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An attempt was made to define a new bundle repository, but another bundle repository already uses the specified URL.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a different URL.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAJ0019E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="EBAADMIN0019E" varFormat="Java">
    EBAADMIN0019E=CWSAJ0019E: An internal error occurred. Attempted to generate an AriesApplicationModel object from a non-file URL {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    CMSG0001
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    CMSG0002
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAJ0062E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="EBAADMIN0062E" varFormat="Java">
    EBAADMIN0062E=CWSAJ0062E: Unable to find the EBA asset {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    You imported a deployment manifest to an asset, but the enterprise bundle archive (EBA) asset does not exist.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check that the EBA asset is installed.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAJ0042I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="EBAADMIN0042I" varFormat="Java">
    EBAADMIN0042I=CWSAJ0042I: Stopping Bundle {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAJ0079E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="REMOVE_RESOLVE_FAILED" varFormat="Java">
    REMOVE_RESOLVE_FAILED=CWSAJ0079E: A resolution problem has occurred while removing an extension from composition unit {0}. The exception is: {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The system cannot resolve the selected extension in conjunction with the current deployment of the asset. Bundles might have missing dependencies, be incompatible, or not exist.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Inspect the error. Make any neccessary changes to the asset then remove, as a set, the extension and any other interdependent extensions.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAJ0058E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="EBAADMIN0058E" varFormat="Java">
    EBAADMIN0058E=CWSAJ0058E: The deployment manifest to import is not valid for the asset {0} because it does not meet the requirements in the application manifest.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The deployment manifest, DEPLOYMENT.MF, is not compatible with the application manifest, APPLICATION.MF, of the asset.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check the new deployment manifest for the following:
   1. The Application-SymbolicName and Application-Version in the DEPLOYMENT.MF file must match the corresponding entries in the APPLICATION.MF file.
   2. The bundles listed in the Deployed-Content header in the DEPLOYMENT.MF file must match the bundles listed in the Application-Content header in the APPLICATION.MF file.
   3. The bundle version in the Deployed-Content header in the DEPLOYMENT.MF file must be within the version range for the corresponding bundle in the APPLICATION.MF file.
   4. The bundles listed in the Deployed-Use-Bundle header in the DEPLOYMENT.MF file must also be listed in the Use-Bundle header in the APPLICATION.MF file.
   5. The bundle version in the Deployed-Use-Bundle header in the DEPLOYMENT.MF file must be within the version range for the corresponding bundle in the Use-Bundle header in the APPLICATION.MF file.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAJ0022E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="EBAADMIN0022E" varFormat="Java">
    EBAADMIN0022E=CWSAJ0022E: Composite Bundle Archive, {0}, has a deployment dependency on another Composite Bundle Archive, {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Nesting of Composite Bundle Archives is not supported.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check that the Composite Bundle Archive depends only on bundles in the CompositeBundle-Content header of the Composite Bundle Archive manifest.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAJ0038E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="EBAADMIN0038E" varFormat="Java">
    EBAADMIN0038E=CWSAJ0038E: Unable to connect to a framework with framework name {0}, node name {1} and server name {2}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A framework with the specified attributes could not be found.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check that the framework attributes are valid and retry the command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAJ0002E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="EBAADMIN0002E" varFormat="Java">
    EBAADMIN0002E=CWSAJ0002E: A bundle repository with the name {0} already exists.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An attempt was made to define a new bundle repository, but the specified name is already in use.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a different name.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAJ0018E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="EBAADMIN0018E" varFormat="Java">
    EBAADMIN0018E=CWSAJ0018E: It is not possible to model the Aries application {0} because some of its required components are still being downloaded.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    One or more bundles that the application requires are being downloaded. The application cannot be modeled until all downloads are complete.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Wait until all the required bundles are downloaded, then try again.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAJ0081E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="EBAADMIN0081E" varFormat="Java">
    EBAADMIN0081E=CWSAJ0081E: Cannot add extension(s) because the composition unit is deployed on the following targets, which do not support application extension: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The targets which the composition unit is deployed against do not all support the application extension functionality.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure the composition unit that you wish to add extensions to is deployed on targets that support the application extension functionality.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAJ0061E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="EBAADMIN0061E" varFormat="Java">
    EBAADMIN0061E=CWSAJ0061E: Unable to create the directory structure {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The directory cannot be created.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check that storage space exists, and that the product has the necessary permissions to create the directory.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAJ0077E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="EBAADMIN0077E" varFormat="Java">
    EBAADMIN0077E=CWSAJ0077E: The symbolic name {0} and version {1} do not match any existing extension.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    There are no extensions on the composition unit that match the specified symbolic name and version.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAJ0041E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="EBAADMIN0041E" varFormat="Java">
    EBAADMIN0041E=CWSAJ0041E: Bundle {0} cannot start. It is currently in {1} state.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The bundle cannot be started.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Refer to accompanying error messages for more information about why this bundle cannot start.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAJ0057E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="EBAADMIN0057E" varFormat="Java">
    EBAADMIN0057E=CWSAJ0057E: The deployment manifest to import cannot be resolved. The unsatisfied requirements are {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The deployment manifest, DEPLOYMENT.MF, to import has a requirement that cannot be satisfied.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check that the new deployment manifest is complete and includes the bundles needed to resolve the enterprise bundle archive (EBA) asset.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAJ0021E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="EBAADMIN0021E" varFormat="Java">
    EBAADMIN0021E=CWSAJ0021E: A problem occurred processing the manifest for the Composite Bundle Archive, {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Either the manifest is not present, or the name or format are not correct.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check that the manifest is present and formatted and named correctly.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAJ0037E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="EBAADMIN0037E" varFormat="Java">
    EBAADMIN0037E=CWSAJ0037E: Unable to connect to a framework with ID {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A framework with the specified ID could not be found.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check that the framework ID is valid and retry the command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAJ0083W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CBA_WITH_EXTRA_SERVICE_EXPORTS" varFormat="Java">
    CBA_WITH_EXTRA_SERVICE_EXPORTS=CWSAJ0083W: The Composite Bundle Archive (CBA) {0} exports services that are not provided by bundles contained in the CBA. These services will not be available for use by bundles outside the CBA. The following problems were reported: {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A CBA cannot export services for which there is no Blueprint declaration or Bundle-ExportService: header on one of bundles in the CBA.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Either add the missing Blueprint service declarations to the CBA contents, or remove the details of the unsatisfied exports from the composite manifest, COMPOSITEBUNDLE.MF.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAJ0001E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="EBAADMIN0001E" varFormat="Java">
    EBAADMIN0001E=CWSAJ0001E: The name parameter has not been specified and is required.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The command requires the name parameter to be specified.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Reissue the command specifying the name.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAJ0017E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="EBAADMIN0017E" varFormat="Java">
    EBAADMIN0017E=CWSAJ0017E: The URL parameter has not been specified and is required.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The URL parameter is required for the addExternalBundleRepository command.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Reissue the command and specify the URL of the external bundle repository.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAJ0060E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="EBAADMIN0060E" varFormat="Java">
    EBAADMIN0060E=CWSAJ0060E: Unable to create the directory structure {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    You attempted to export a deployment manifest to a directory that does not exist, and the directory structure cannot be created.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check that storage space exists, and that the product has the necessary permissions to create the directory.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAJ0076E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="EBAADMIN0076E" varFormat="Java">
    EBAADMIN0076E=CWSAJ0076E: The symbolic name {0} and version {1} do not match any available extension in any available bundle repository.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    There is no composite bundle with the specified symbolic name and version in any repository available to the environment.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Either add the composite bundle to an available repository, or select a different composite bundle to add as an extension.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAJ0040I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="EBAADMIN0040I" varFormat="Java">
    EBAADMIN0040I=CWSAJ0040I: Starting Bundle {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAJ0056E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="EBAADMIN0056E" varFormat="Java">
    EBAADMIN0056E=CWSAJ0056E: An internal error occurred. The resolving process does not generate a list of bundles to be installed.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    CMSG0001
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    CMSG0002
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAJ0036I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="EBAADMIN0036I" varFormat="Java">
    EBAADMIN0036I=CWSAJ0036I: Successfully connected to framework {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAJ0020E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="EBAADMIN0020E" varFormat="Java">
    EBAADMIN0020E=CWSAJ0020E: An internal error occurred extracting bundle {0} from the Composite Bundle Archive, {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    CMSG0001
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    CMSG0002
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAJ0016E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="EBAADMIN0016E" varFormat="Java">
    EBAADMIN0016E=CWSAJ0016E: The name parameter has not been specified and is required.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The name parameter is required for the addExternalBundleRepository command.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Reissue the command and specify the name of the external bundle repository.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAJ0075E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="EBAADMIN0075E" varFormat="Java">
    EBAADMIN0075E=CWSAJ0075E: The extension with symbolic name {0} and version {1} has already been added to the composition unit.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This extension is already included in the composition unit.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAJ0055E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="EBAADMIN0055E" varFormat="Java">
    EBAADMIN0055E=CWSAJ0055E: The deployment manifest content is not correct. The following bundles are redundant: {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The deployment manifest, DEPLOYMENT.MF, to import includes bundles that are not needed to resolve the enterprise bundle archive (EBA) asset.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check that the new deployment manifest does not include the bundles that are listed in the message.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAJ0035I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="EBAADMIN0035I" varFormat="Java">
    EBAADMIN0035I=CWSAJ0035I: Connecting to framework {0} on node {1} and server {2}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    You are currently connecting to the framework.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAJ0015E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="EBAADMIN0015E" varFormat="Java">
    EBAADMIN0015E=CWSAJ0015E: An internal error occurred. Attempted to generate an AriesApplicationModel object from a null deployment manifest.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    CMSG0001
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    CMSG0002
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAJ0074E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="EBAADMIN0074E" varFormat="Java">
    EBAADMIN0074E=CWSAJ0074E: The version parameter has not been specified and is required.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The command requires the version parameter to be specified.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Reissue the command specifying the version.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAJ0054E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="EBAADMIN0054E" varFormat="Java">
    EBAADMIN0054E=CWSAJ0054E: The deployment manifest content is not correct. The following extra bundles are required {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The deployment manifest, DEPLOYMENT.MF, to import does not include all the bundles needed to resolve the enterprise bundle archive (EBA) asset.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check that the new deployment manifest includes all the bundles that are listed in the message.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAJ0034I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="EBAADMIN0034I" varFormat="Java">
    EBAADMIN0034I=CWSAJ0034I: Bundle {0} stopped successfully.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAJ0014E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="EBAADMIN0014E" varFormat="Java">
    EBAADMIN0014E=CWSAJ0014E: An internal error occurred. Attempted to generate an AriesApplicationModel object from a null application manifest.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    CMSG0001
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    CMSG0002
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<!-- END MESSAGES -->
</TMSSource>
