<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/css" href="../../resources/stylesheets/wasmsgxml.css"?>
<TMSSource name="TivoliMessages" tmsVersion="1.0" xml:lang="en">
<!-- CMVC MSG File Name = /com.ibm.ws.cloud.productinsights/resources/com/ibm/ws/cloud/productinsights/common/resources/ProductInsightsMessages.nlsprops -->
<!-- DO NOT EDIT THIS FILE - This file was generated by the XML/Html & Property emitter -->
<!-- BEGIN MESSAGES -->
<Message ID="CWWKR0433W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="USAGE_EXCEPTION_CWWKR0433W" varFormat="Java">
    USAGE_EXCEPTION_CWWKR0433W=CWWKR0433W: The productInsights feature encountered an exception when enabling usage data collection for the {0} product. The following exception occurred: {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The productInsights feature encountered an exception when enabling usage data collection for a product. It&apos;s usage will not be sent.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See the problem determination information for the product identified in the message.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWKR0435W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="REGISTRATION_STACK_PROD_EXCEPTION_CWWKR0435W" varFormat="Java">
    REGISTRATION_STACK_PROD_EXCEPTION_CWWKR0435W=CWWKR0435W: The productInsights feature could not obtain registration information for the {0} product.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The productInsights feature encountered a problem obtaining registration information from a product and this information will be missing from registration.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See the problem determination information for the product identified in the message.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWKR0427I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="FOUND_AVAILABLE_PROCESSORS_CWWKR0427I" varFormat="Java">
    FOUND_AVAILABLE_PROCESSORS_CWWKR0427I=CWWKR0427I: The value that indicates the number of available processors for the productInsights feature was overridden and is now {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The com.ibm.websphere.cloud.productinsights.availableProcessorsOverride property was used to override the value of the available processors metric.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWKR0423E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="KEYSTORE_NOT_FOUND_CWWKR0423E" varFormat="Java">
    KEYSTORE_NOT_FOUND_CWWKR0423E=CWWKR0423E: The keystore file at {0} could not be found.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The productInsights trustStore property in the server configuration referenced a keystore file that does not exist.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Install the keystore file at the target location, or update the productInsights trustStore configuration.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWKR0409W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="USAGE_EXCEPTION_CWWKR0409W" varFormat="Java">
    USAGE_EXCEPTION_CWWKR0409W=CWWKR0409W: The productInsights feature encountered an exception when collecting product usage. The following exception occurred: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The productInsights feature encountered an exception when collecting product usage.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWKR0432W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="USAGE_EXCEPTION_CWWKR0432W" varFormat="Java">
    USAGE_EXCEPTION_CWWKR0432W=CWWKR0432W: The productInsights feature encountered an exception when resetting usage data collection for the {0} product. The following exception occurred: {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The productInsights feature encountered an exception when resetting usage data collection for a product.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See the problem determination information for the product identified in the message.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWKR0408W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PRODUCT_TAGS_CORRUPT_CWWKR0408W" varFormat="Java">
    PRODUCT_TAGS_CORRUPT_CWWKR0408W=CWWKR0408W: The server was unable to process the {0} product information file. The following exception occurred: {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The server encountered an exception when processing one of the product information files.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the product has been installed correctly.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWKR0410I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="METRIC_NOT_SUPPORTED_CWWKR0410I" varFormat="Java">
    METRIC_NOT_SUPPORTED_CWWKR0410I=CWWKR0410I: The productInsights feature does not support the {0} metric for the {1} OS on the {2} software developers kit.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The productInsights feature was unable to collect product usage given the environment.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWKR0420E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="REGISTRATION_ERROR_CWWKR0420E" varFormat="Java">
    REGISTRATION_ERROR_CWWKR0420E=CWWKR0420E: The server cannot be registered with the {0} service. The SSL configuration is missing.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The SSL configuration needed for product insights is missing.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Configure SSL for product insights.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWKR0428W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_METRIC_TYPE_CWWKR0428W" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_METRIC_TYPE_CWWKR0428W=CWWKR0428W: The productInsights feature has ignored the &apos;&apos;{0}&apos;&apos; value for the &apos;&apos;{1}&apos;&apos; metric type reported by the {2} product. The metric type or a definition of the metric type was not provided during product registration.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The productInsights feature requires a metric type with a metric definition for all metric values reported. Metrics values reported without a type or definition will be ignored.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See the problem determination information for the product identified in the message.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWKR0404E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="REGISTRATION_INTERNAL_ERROR_CWWKR0404E" varFormat="Java">
    REGISTRATION_INTERNAL_ERROR_CWWKR0404E=CWWKR0404E:  The server cannot be registered with the {0} service. The following internal error prevented the server from registering: {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Application service returned an error during registration.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support web page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWKR0422E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SSLREF_AND_TRUSTSTORE_CODEFINED_CWWKR0422E" varFormat="Java">
    SSLREF_AND_TRUSTSTORE_CODEFINED_CWWKR0422E=CWWKR0422E: Both a sslRef and a trustStore property were defined in the productInsights configuration.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The SSL configuration for the productInsights feature references a keystore file that is configured in trustStore. The SSL configuration is referenced by sslRef property of productInsights. The SSL configuration for the productInsights feature requires either a definition for the sslRef or trustStore property, but not both.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Remove either the sslRef or trustStore property from the productInsights configuration.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWKR0419W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="GROUP_DUPLICATE_NAME_CWWKR0419W" varFormat="Java">
    GROUP_DUPLICATE_NAME_CWWKR0419W=CWWKR0419W: The {0} group name is not unique, so this server will be registered without any group membership. To add the server to a group, ensure that each group name is unique.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Groups in the productInsights element must have unique names.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    In the server configuration, change the groups specified on the productInsights element so that each group name is unique.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWKR0411W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="METRIC_EXCEPTION_CWWKR0411W" varFormat="Java">
    METRIC_EXCEPTION_CWWKR0411W=CWWKR0411W: The {0} program cannot run on the {1} operating system. The following exception occurred: {2}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The productInsights feature was unable to run the specified program because of the given exception.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWKR0434W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="STACK_PROD_LISTENER_EXCEPTION_CWWKR0434W" varFormat="Java">
    STACK_PROD_LISTENER_EXCEPTION_CWWKR0434W=CWWKR0434W: The productInsights feature could not set a registration listener for the {0} product.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The productInsights feature could not set a registration listener for a product and product changes do not cause a re-registration.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See the problem determination information for the product identified in the message.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWKR0431W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="USAGE_EXCEPTION_CWWKR0431W" varFormat="Java">
    USAGE_EXCEPTION_CWWKR0431W=CWWKR0431W: The productInsights feature encountered an exception when collecting product usage for the {0} product. The following exception occurred: {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The productInsights feature encountered an exception when collecting product usage from a product. Its usage is not sent.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See the problem determination information for the product identified in the message.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWKR0402W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="REGISTRATION_BAD_RESPONSE_CWWKR0402W" varFormat="Java">
    REGISTRATION_BAD_RESPONSE_CWWKR0402W=CWWKR0402W: The server cannot be registered. Server registration with the {0} service will be attempted again within {1} minutes. The following response was received from the {0} service: {2}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An error was returned when registering the server. Server registration will be retried later.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWKR0403E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="REGISTRATION_FATAL_ERROR_CWWKR0403E" varFormat="Java">
    REGISTRATION_FATAL_ERROR_CWWKR0403E=CWWKR0403E: The server cannot be registered with the {0} service. Registration cannot complete until the problem is corrected. The following error occurred: {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An exception occurred when registering the server.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See the previous messages to determine why the server did not register.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWKR0414E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="REGISTRATOR_INVALID_URL_CWWKR0414E" varFormat="Java">
    REGISTRATOR_INVALID_URL_CWWKR0414E=CWWKR0414E: The &lt;productInsights&gt; element {0} is malformed.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The productInsights feature was unable to register with the service because a &lt;productInsights&gt; element is malformed.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Update the server configuration &lt;productInsights&gt; element.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWKR0407E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PRODUCT_TAGS_NOT_FOUND_CWWKR0407E" varFormat="Java">
    PRODUCT_TAGS_NOT_FOUND_CWWKR0407E=CWWKR0407E: The productInsights feature was unable to start because of missing product information. The server does not have an international program license agreement (IPLA) and cannot be registered with the {0} service.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The server installation is missing required files and the productInsights feature did not start.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check that the product has an international program license agreement (IPLA) and has been installed correctly. If the problem persists, see the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWKR0436W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="USAGE_EXCEPTION_CWWKR0436W" varFormat="Java">
    USAGE_EXCEPTION_CWWKR0436W=CWWKR0436W: The productInsights feature was unable to send metrics for the last {0} collection intervals. Metrics for each {1} minute collection interval are aggregated until the {2} service can be reached.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The productInsights feature is unable to communicate with the cloud service.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Determine the root cause of the communication problem, such as an incorrect URL in the Liberty Product Insights feature configuration, lack of internet connection, unavailable cloud service, or proxy tunneling failure.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWKR0401W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="REGISTRATION_EXCEPTION_CWWKR0401W" varFormat="Java">
    REGISTRATION_EXCEPTION_CWWKR0401W=CWWKR0401W: The server cannot be registered. Server registration with the {0} service will be attempted again within {1} minutes. The following exception occurred: {2}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An exception occurred when registering the server. Server registration will be retried later.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWKR0418W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="GROUP_LOOP_DETECTED_CWWKR0418W" varFormat="Java">
    GROUP_LOOP_DETECTED_CWWKR0418W=CWWKR0418W: The {0} group is a parent of itself, so this server will be registered without any group membership. To add the server to a group, specify a valid group name.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Groups in the productInsights element cannot be parents of themselves.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    In the server configuration, change the groups specified on the productInsights element so that no group is a parent of itself.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWKR0429W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_METRIC_VALUE_CWWKR0429W" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_METRIC_VALUE_CWWKR0429W=CWWKR0429W: The productInsights feature has ignored the &apos;&apos;{0}&apos;&apos; value for the &apos;&apos;{1}&apos;&apos; metric type reported by the {2} product. The metric value is not valid.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The metric value is not valid and is ignored.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See the problem determination information for the product identified in the message.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWKR0412E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="REGISTRATION_ERROR_WRONG_API_KEY_CWWKR0412E" varFormat="Java">
    REGISTRATION_ERROR_WRONG_API_KEY_CWWKR0412E=CWWKR0412E: The server cannot be registered with the {0} service. The API Key is incorrect.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The productInsights feature was unable to register with the service because the API Key was incorrect.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Update the server configuration to have the correct API Key for the service.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWKR0405E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MISSING_ATTRIBUTE_CWWKR0405E" varFormat="Java">
    MISSING_ATTRIBUTE_CWWKR0405E=CWWKR0405E: The &lt;productInsights&gt; element is missing the {0} required attribute.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The missing attribute is required in the server.xml file or to one of its referenced configuration files.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Add the attribute to the server.xml file or to one of its referenced configuration files.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWKR0415E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="REGISTRATOR_URL_PROTOCOL_NOT_HTTPS_CWWKR0415E" varFormat="Java">
    REGISTRATOR_URL_PROTOCOL_NOT_HTTPS_CWWKR0415E=CWWKR0415E: The &lt;productInsights&gt; element url is incorrect. The protocol must be https.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Https is the only supported protocol for the &lt;productInsights&gt; element url.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Change the &lt;productInsights&gt; element url to use https for the protocol.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWKR0417W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="GROUP_RESERVED_NAME_CWWKR0417W" varFormat="Java">
    GROUP_RESERVED_NAME_CWWKR0417W=CWWKR0417W: The {0} group name is not valid because it begins with WAS_, which is a reserved term. This server will be registered without any group membership. To add the server to a group, specify a valid group name.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The productInsights group names cannot start with WAS_ because this term is reserved.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    In the server configuration, remove WAS_ from the group names specified on the groups attribute of the productInsights element.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWKR0413E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="REGISTRATION_ERROR_CWWKR0413E" varFormat="Java">
    REGISTRATION_ERROR_CWWKR0413E=CWWKR0413E: The server cannot be registered with the {0} service. The server was unable to communicate with bluemix due to incorrect SSL configuration.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The productInsights feature was unable to register with the service because the SSL configuration is incorrect.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Update the server configuration to have the correct SSL settings.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWKR0416W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="GROUP_INVALID_CHARACTER_CWWKR0416W" varFormat="Java">
    GROUP_INVALID_CHARACTER_CWWKR0416W=CWWKR0416W: The {0} group name contains one or more invalid characters, so this server will be registered without any group membership. To add the server to a group, ensure that the group name contains only valid characters, which include letters, numbers, hyphens, periods, colons, and underscores.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The productInsights group names can contain only letters, numbers, hyphens (-), periods (.), colons (:), and underscores (_).
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    In the server configuration, change the name specified on the groups attribute of the productInsights element so that it only contains valid characters.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWKR0424E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="KEYSTORE_UNREADABLE_CWWKR0424E" varFormat="Java">
    KEYSTORE_UNREADABLE_CWWKR0424E=CWWKR0424E: The application server process has insufficient privileges to read the keystore file at {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The application server process does not have read access privileges for the keystore file that is referenced in the productInsights trustStore configuration.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Update the file access privileges for the keystore file to grant read privileges to the application server process.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWKR0430W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SEND_USAGE_EXCEPTION_CWWKR0430W" varFormat="Java">
    SEND_USAGE_EXCEPTION_CWWKR0430W=CWWKR0430W: The productInsights feature encountered an exception when sending product usage. The following exception occurred: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The productInsights feature encountered an exception when sending product usage.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWKR0421I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="USING_DIGICERT_KEYSTORE_CWWKR0421I" varFormat="Java">
    USING_DIGICERT_KEYSTORE_CWWKR0421I=CWWKR0421I: Neither the productInsights sslRef property nor a trustStore property were defined in the server configuration, so the following keystore was used: {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The SSL configuration for the productInsights feature references a keystore file that is configured in the trustStore property. The SSL configuration is referenced by the sslRef property of productInsights. If both the trustStore and the sslRef properties are not defined, the productInsights feature uses the specified keystore file from IBM Bluemix.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWKR0426W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_AVAILABLE_PROCESSORS_CWWKR0426W" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_AVAILABLE_PROCESSORS_CWWKR0426W=CWWKR0426W: The {0} value of the {1} property is not valid. The value must be a data type of integer or float.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The property value is not valid and is ignored.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Change the value of the property to a data type of integer or float.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWKR0425E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_HTTPS_PROTOCOL_CWWKR0425E" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_HTTPS_PROTOCOL_CWWKR0425E=CWWKR0425E: The value of the httpsProtocol property is not valid: {0} Valid protocols include: {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The productInsights httpsProtocol referenced a protocol that is not valid.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Change the productInsights httpsProtocol to a valid value.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWKR0406E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="BAD_PRODUCT_VERSION_FILES_CWWKR0406E" varFormat="Java">
    BAD_PRODUCT_VERSION_FILES_CWWKR0406E=CWWKR0406E: The product version files are missing or corrupted. The productInsights feature did not start. The following exception occurred: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The server did not process the product version files and the productInsights feature did not start.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check that the product has been installed correctly. If the problem persists, see the problem determination information on the WebSphere Application Server Support Web page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWKR0400I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="REGISTERED_CWWKR0400I" varFormat="Java">
    REGISTERED_CWWKR0400I=CWWKR0400I: The server was registered with the {0} service on the specified URL {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The server has registered itself.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<!-- END MESSAGES -->
</TMSSource>
