<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/css" href="../../resources/stylesheets/wasmsgxml.css"?>
<TMSSource name="TivoliMessages" tmsVersion="1.0" xml:lang="en">
<!-- CMVC MSG File Name = SERV1/ws/code/admin.deploy/src/com/ibm/ws/management/bla/resources/BLAMessages.nlsprops -->
<!-- DO NOT EDIT THIS FILE - This file was generated by the XML/Html & Property emitter -->
<!-- BEGIN MESSAGES -->
<Message ID="CWWMH0186E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0186E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0186E=CWWMH0186E: Unexpected error occurred while reading composition unit configuration data.  Error data: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An unexpected error occurred while reading composition unit configuration data.  The configuration could be corrupted.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0150E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0150E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0150E=CWWMH0150E: Could not save configuration data for business-level application &quot;{0}&quot;.  Your workspace may be in an inconsistent state.  Discard your workspace.  Error data: {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Unexpected error occurred while saving business-level application configuration data to the workspace.  Changes were made to the workspace which cannot be undone.  Do not save the the workspace in this inconsistent state; otherwise, you will corrupt your configuration.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Discard the workspace and reattempt your configuration changes.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0146E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0146E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0146E=CWWMH0146E: Ambiguous business-level application ID &quot;{0}&quot; specified as the &quot;blaID&quot; parameter value. Specify a single business-level application edition by using a fully-qualified business-level application ID, for example, WebSphere:blaname=myBLA,blaedition=1.0.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified business-level application ID matches multiple editions of a business-level application.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Fully qualify the ID to select a specific business-level application edition.  The complete business-level application ID format is WebSphere:blaname=&lt;name&gt;,blaedition=&lt;edition&gt;.  An example of a fully-qualified business-level application ID is WebSphere:blaname=myBLA,blaedition=1.0.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0110E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0110E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0110E=CWWMH0110E: Class &quot;{0}&quot;, specified through the content-depl-providers Eclipse extension point, could not be instantiated.  Error data: {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Business-level application content providers must configure an extension of com.ibm.wsspi.management.bla.framework.ContentHandler.  The specified content handler class could not be instantiated.  The product is pre-configured with content handlers for certain types of assets such as Java EE applications and general Java archives.  Product extensions can also configure content handlers to handle other types of assets.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    This error indicates a problem with a business-level application content provider added as a product extension.  Contact the source of the problem content handler class for support.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0106E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0106E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0106E=CWWMH0106E: Composition unit &quot;{0}&quot;, specified in an asset dependency relationship declaration, already exists.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    When you create a composition unit, you can specify assets which the new composition unit is dependent on.  Each asset dependency is configured as a composition unit, and you can optionally specify the name of the composition unit.  The name cannot conflict with any existing composition units.  A composition unit name was specified as part of an asset dependency declaration, and the name conflicts with an existing composition unit.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a composition unit name that does not conflict with any existing composition units.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0185E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0185E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0185E=CWWMH0185E: Unexpected error occurred while reading business-level application configuration data.  Error data: &quot;{0}&quot;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An unexpected error occurred while reading business-level application configuration data.  The configuration could be corrupted.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0145E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0145E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0145E=CWWMH0145E: No business-level application matches the ID &quot;{0}&quot; specified as the &quot;blaID&quot; parameter value.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Cannot find a business-level application which matches the specified business-level application ID.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the ID you specified is correct and identifies an existing business-level application.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0209E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0209E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0209E=CWWMH0209E: The specified &quot;deplUnit&quot; parameter value of &quot;{0}&quot; includes the deployable unit name &quot;{1}&quot;, but the asset being configured has no deployable unit with that name.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The &quot;deplUnit&quot; parameter value, if specified, must include only the names of deployable units which are part of the asset you are configuring as a composition unit.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Retry the command with a valid &quot;deplUnit&quot; parameter value.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0184E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0184E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0184E=CWWMH0184E: Unexpected error occurred while reading asset configuration data.  Error data: &quot;{0}&quot;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An unexpected error occurred while reading asset configuration data.  The configuration could be corrupted.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0144E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0144E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0144E=CWWMH0144E: Cannot export asset because its storage type is &quot;{0}&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The asset file for an asset with a storage type of METADATA or NONE is not stored in the product configuration repository.  Therefore, the asset cannot be exported.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Export only assets with a storage type of &quot;FULL&quot;.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0104E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0104E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0104E=CWWMH0104E: Asset &quot;{0}&quot; already exists.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The asset being imported already exists.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Because the asset already exists, you may not need to import the asset.  If you want to import the asset, you can specify a different asset name to resolve the name confict.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0183E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0183E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0183E=CWWMH0183E: Configuration file URI &quot;{0}&quot; is not valid.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This exception is unexpected. The cause is not immediately known.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0179E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0179E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0179E=CWWMH0179E: Could not save asset reference data for asset &quot;{0}&quot;.  Your workspace may be in an inconsistent state.  Discard your workspace.  Error data: {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Unexpected error occurred while saving asset reference configuration data to the workspace.  Changes were made to the workspace which cannot be undone.  Do not save the the workspace in this inconsistent state; otherwise, you will corrupt your configuration.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Discard the workspace and reattempt your configuration changes.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0211E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0211E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0211E=CWWMH0211E: Could not save reference data for business-level application &quot;{0}&quot;.  Your workspace may be in an inconsistent state.  Discard your workspace.  Error data: {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Unexpected error occurred while saving business-level application reference configuration data to the workspace.  Changes were made to the workspace which cannot be undone.  Do not save the the workspace in this inconsistent state; otherwise, you will corrupt your configuration.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Discard the workspace and reattempt your configuration changes.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0143E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0143E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0143E=CWWMH0143E: Ambiguous composition unit ID &quot;{0}&quot; specified as the &quot;cuID&quot; parameter value. Specify a single composition unit edition by using a fully-qualified composition unit ID, for example, WebSphere:cuname=myCompUnit,cuedition=1.0.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified composition unit ID matches multiple editions of a composition unit.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Fully qualify the ID to select a specific composition unit edition.  The complete composition unit ID format is WebSphere:cuname=&lt;name&gt;,cuedition=&lt;edition&gt;.  An example of a fully-qualified composition unit ID is WebSphere:cuname=myCompUnit,cuedition=1.0.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0207E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0207E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0207E=CWWMH0207E: Source &quot;{0}&quot; for &quot;addCompUnit&quot; operation is not recognized by any content handler configured in the product.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The source for a composition unit being created must be recognized by some content handler.  The product is pre-configured with content handlers for certain types of assets such as Java EE applications and general Java archives.  Product extensions can also configure content handlers to handle other types of assets.  No content handler recognized the source you are trying to configure as a composition unit.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    The error is possibly caused by a problem with the product extension associated with the source you are trying to configure as a composition unit.  In this case, contact the provider of the product extension associated with the source for support.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0139E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0139E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0139E=CWWMH0139E: Ambiguous asset ID &quot;{0}&quot; specified as the &quot;assetID&quot; parameter value. Specify a single asset version by using a fully-qualified asset ID, for example, WebSphere:assetname=myAsset.jar,assetversion=1.0.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified asset ID matches multiple versions of an asset.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Fully qualify the ID to select a specific asset version.  The complete asset ID format is WebSphere:assetname=&lt;name&gt;,assetversion=&lt;version&gt;.  An example of a fully-qualified asset ID is WebSphere:assetname=myAsset.jar,assetversion=1.0.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0250E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0250E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0250E=CWWMH0250E: Configuration data repository entry &quot;{0}&quot; in scope &quot;{1}&quot; does not exist.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Command step data could not be found in the configuration data repository when attempting to update it after user interaction.  This condition is the result of an internal error.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0182E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0182E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0182E=CWWMH0182E: Could not read configuration data for business-level application ID &quot;{0}&quot;.  Error data: {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An unexpected error occurred while reading configuration data for the specified business-level application.  The configuration could be corrupted.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0178E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0178E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0178E=CWWMH0178E: Could not read asset reference configuration data for asset &quot;{0}&quot;.  Error data: {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An unexpected error occurred while reading asset reference configuration data for the specified asset.  The configuration could be corrupted.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0210E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0210E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0210E=CWWMH0210E: Could not read reference configuration data for business-level application &quot;{0}&quot;.  Error data: {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An unexpected error occurred while reading business-level application reference configuration data for the specified business-level application.  The configuration could be corrupted.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0142E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0142E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0142E=CWWMH0142E: No composition matches the ID &quot;{0}&quot; specified as the &quot;cuID&quot; parameter value.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Cannot find a composition unit which matches the specified composition unit ID.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the ID you specified is correct and identifies an existing composition unit.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0206E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0206E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0206E=CWWMH0206E: Unexpected error occurred while obtaining default Java EE binding data.  Error message received: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    There was some problem analyzing the Java EE application file being imported as an asset.  Default binding options could not be determined due to some unexpected error.  The mesage for the unexpected error is included in this error message for additional information.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Refer to the message associated with the unexpected error for more details about the origin of the problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0138E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0138E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0138E=CWWMH0138E: No asset matches the ID &quot;{0}&quot; specified as the &quot;assetID&quot; parameter value.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Cannot find an asset which matches the specified asset ID.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the ID you specified is correct and identifies an existing asset.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0102E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0102E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0102E=CWWMH0102E: Could not read configuration data for {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An unexpected error occurred while reading configuration data for the specified object.  The configuration could be corrupted.  FFDC log entries might contain additional data about the root cause.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0181E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0181E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0181E=CWWMH0181E: Could not import Java EE asset.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This exception is unexpected. The cause is not immediately known.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0177E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0177E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0177E=CWWMH0177E: The value &quot;{1}&quot; for parameter &quot;{0}&quot; is not valid. Specify a value of either &quot;true&quot; or &quot;false&quot;, or leave the value empty to choose the default value.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified parameter is an optional parameter which requires a value of &quot;true&quot; or &quot;false&quot;.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a value of either &quot;true&quot; or &quot;false&quot;, or leave the value empty to choose the default value.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0141E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0141E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0141E=CWWMH0141E: Asset &quot;{0}&quot; cannot be removed because the following composition units are based on it: {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Asset specified cannot be removed because it has been configured as a composition unit in one or more business-level applications.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Given that business-level applications are using the asset, removal of the asset might not be appropriate. If you decide that removing the asset is appropriate, first remove the composition units based on the asset from their respective business-level applications.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0205E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0205E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0205E=CWWMH0205E: Invalid property &quot;{0}&quot; specified in defaultBindingOptions parameter. The property specified must applicable to the type of asset being configured.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The default binding property specified is not supported by the composition unit&apos;s underlying asset. You can specify only those properties which can be used for that particular type of asset.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Retry the command with the correct value for defaultBindingOptions parameter.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0137E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0137E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0137E=CWWMH0137E: No asset or business-level application matches the ID &quot;{0}&quot; specified as the &quot;cuSourceID&quot; parameter value.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Cannot find an asset or business-level application which matches the specified ID.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the ID you specified is correct and identifies an existing asset or business-level application.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0101E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0101E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0101E=CWWMH0101E: An internal error occurred.  Error data: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This exception is unexpected. The cause is not immediately known.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0180E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0180E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0180E=CWWMH0180E: Internal error. Scheduler is null.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This exception is unexpected. The cause is not immediately known.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0176E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0176E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0176E=CWWMH0176E: The specified starting weight value of &quot;{0}&quot; is not valid. The starting weight must be an integer value between 0 to 2,147,483,647, inclusive.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The starting weight value must be an integer value between 0 and 2,147,483,647, inclusive.  Start order is according to starting weight in ascending order.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a starting weight between 0 and 2,147,483,647.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0140E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0140E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0140E=CWWMH0140E: An asset&apos;&apos;s storage type cannot be changed from &quot;{0}&quot; to &quot;{1}&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Storage type values indicate how much of the asset is stored in the product configuration repository.  Storage type values in decreasing order include &quot;FULL&quot;, &quot;METADATA&quot;, and &quot;NONE&quot;.  Storage types other than &quot;FULL&quot; typically are used by development tools based on the product.  The storage type for an asset can be decreased, such as from &quot;FULL&quot; to &quot;METADATA&quot;, but not the reverse.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    The asset can be imported again with the desired storage type.  If the asset is not deleted from the product&apos;s configuration repository first, it must be imported again with another name in order to avoid a name conflict.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0204E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0204E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0204E=CWWMH0204E: Invalid value &quot;{0}&quot; for &quot;defaultBindingOptions&quot; parameter. The value should be in the form of &lt;prop&gt;=&lt;value&gt;[#&lt;prop&gt;=&lt;value&gt;]..., where &lt;prop&gt; is the property name and &lt;value&gt; is the property value.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The value specified for defaultBindingOptions parameter is incorrect. Make sure that the values are specified in a &lt;prop&gt;=&lt;value&gt; format with each property-value pair separated by a pound sign (#).
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Retry the command with the correct value for defaultBindingOptions parameter.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0136E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0136E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0136E=CWWMH0136E: The value for the &quot;cuSourceID&quot; parameter cannot be empty or null.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The composition unit source ID must be a non-null, non-empty value.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a valid composition unit source ID.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0100E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0100E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0100E=CWWMH0100E: The format of &quot;{0}&quot; is not a valid ID.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified value does not follow the expected ID syntax.  Valid values for an asset ID include: &lt;asset name&gt;, assetname=&lt;asset name&gt;, and WebSphere:assetname=&lt;asset name&gt;; where &lt;asset name&gt; is the name of the asset.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the value was specified as input, specify a syntactically valid ID.  Otherwise, the error may be an internal error.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0283E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0283E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0283E=CWWMH0283E: Authorization failure. Insufficient authority to edit business-level application &quot;{0}&quot;. This operation requires &quot;deployer&quot; or &quot;configurator&quot; role on the cell, or &quot;deployer&quot; role on the  business-level application.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    You are not assigned the roles required to edit the specified business-level application.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    You must obtain the required role assignments before you can complete the requested operation.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0279E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0279E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0279E=CWWMH0279E: Authorization failure. Insufficient authority to access the resource &quot;{0}&quot;. This operation requires &quot;{1}&quot; role on the cell or on the resource.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    You are not assigned the roles required to execute the requested operation on the specified resource.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    You must obtain the required role assignments before you can complete the requested operation.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0243E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0243E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0243E=CWWMH0243E: An &quot;updateAsset&quot; command with the &quot;operation&quot; parameter set to &quot;{0}&quot; is being used to update an asset which was imported with the &quot;loose config&quot; option, and no file exists at the path &quot;{1}&quot;, specified by the &quot;ADTCommandProps&quot; parameter table entry, &quot;contents.loose.config&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    When the &quot;updateAsset&quot; command with an &quot;operation&quot; parameter value of &quot;replace&quot;, &quot;add&quot;, &quot;addupdate&quot;, or &quot;update&quot;, is executed on an asset imported with the &quot;loose config&quot; option, the command &quot;ADTCommandProps&quot; table parameter must be specified and must include a &quot;contents.loose.config&quot; property setting, the value of which is the path of the input content file.  No file was found with the specified path.  This error applies only to development tools interoperating with WebSphere Application Server.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Report the problem to the provider of the development tool you are using.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0175E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0175E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0175E=CWWMH0175E: Client notifier not set.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This exception is unexpected. The cause is not immediately known.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0239E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0239E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0239E=CWWMH0239E: The file, looseconfig.xmi, does not exist at the specified location &quot;{0}&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The file, looseconfig.xmi, does not exist at the specified location.  This error applies only to development tools interoperating with WebSphere Application Server.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Report the problem to the provider of the development tool you are using.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0135E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0135E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0135E=CWWMH0135E: No &quot;filename&quot; parameter value was specified.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified operation requires a non-empty value for the &quot;filename&quot; parameter.  Either no value was specfied or the specified value was empty.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a non-empty &quot;filename&quot; parameter value.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0282E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0282E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0282E=CWWMH0282E: Authorization failure. Insufficient authority to edit asset &quot;{0}&quot;. This operation requires &quot;deployer&quot; or &quot;configurator&quot; role on the cell, or &quot;deployer&quot; role on the asset.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The user is not assigned the roles required to edit the specified asset.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    You must obtain the required role assignments before you can complete the requested operation.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0242E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0242E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0242E=CWWMH0242E: An &quot;updateAsset&quot; command with the &quot;operation&quot; parameter set to &quot;merge&quot; is being used to update an asset which was imported with the &quot;loose config&quot; option, but the &quot;ADTCommandProps&quot; parameter table entry &quot;{0}&quot; is not specified.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    When the &quot;updateAsset&quot; command with an &quot;operation&quot; parameter value of &quot;merge&quot; is executed on an asset imported with the &quot;loose config&quot; option, the command parameter &quot;ADTCommandProps&quot; must also be specified and must include a table which includes lists of added, removed, and/or updated content URIs.  This error applies only to development tools interoperating with WebSphere Application Server.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Report the problem to the provider of the development tool you are using.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0174E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0174E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0174E=CWWMH0174E: A parameter definition (part of a control operation definition) was created with an attribute value of null or empty string..  The specified parameter definition attribute values are: name: &quot;{0}&quot;, description: &quot;{1}&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A control operation definition contains a parameter definition with an attribute value which is not valid.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    This error indicates a problem with the product extension associated with the asset you are trying to configure as a composition unit.  Contact the provider of the product extension associated with the asset for support.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0238E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0238E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0238E=CWWMH0238E: The specified &quot;operation&quot; parameter value of &quot;{0}&quot; is not valid.  Valid values are &quot;merge&quot;, &quot;replace&quot;, &quot;add&quot;, &quot;addupdate&quot;, &quot;update&quot;, and &quot;delete&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The &quot;operation&quot; parameter value specified on an &quot;updateAsset&quot; command invocation is not valid.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify an &quot;operation&quot; parameter value of &quot;merge&quot;, &quot;replace&quot;, &quot;add&quot;, &quot;addupdate&quot;, &quot;update&quot;, or &quot;delete&quot;.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0134E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0134E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0134E=CWWMH0134E: The specified &quot;storageType&quot; parameter value &quot;{0}&quot; is not valid. Specify &quot;FULL&quot;, &quot;METADATA&quot;, or &quot;NONE&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified &quot;storageType&quot; parameter value is not valid. Valid &quot;storageType&quot; parameter values include &quot;FULL&quot;, &quot;METADATA&quot;, and &quot;NONE&quot;.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a valid &quot;storageType&quot; parameter value.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0413E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0413E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0413E=CWWMH0413E: Parameter &quot;{0}&quot; requires a value but no value was provided.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    No value for the  required parameter was specified.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Provide a value for the specified parameter.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0277E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0277E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0277E=CWWMH0277E: Authorization failure. Insufficient authority to start or stop business-level application &quot;{0}&quot;. This operation requires &quot;operator&quot; role on the cell, business-level application, or all composition unit targets for the business-level application.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    You are not assigned the roles required to start or stop the specified business-level application.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    You must obtain the required role assignments before you can complete the requested operation.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0241E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0241E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0241E=CWWMH0241E: The &quot;editAsset&quot; command is not supported for the asset &quot;{0}&quot; because it was imported with the &quot;loose config&quot; option.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The &quot;editAsset&quot; command does not support assets imported with the &quot;loose config&quot; option.  This error applies only to development tools interoperating with WebSphere Application Server.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Report the problem to the provider of the development tool you are using.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0173E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0173E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0173E=CWWMH0173E: A control operation definition was created with an attribute value of null or empty string. The control operation definition attribute values are: name: &quot;{0}&quot;, description: &quot;{1}&quot;, operation handler ID: &quot;{2}&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A control operation definition was created with an attributed value which is not valid.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    This error indicates a problem with the product extension associated with the asset you are trying to configure as a composition unit.  Contact the provider of the product extension associated with the asset for support.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0237E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0237E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0237E=CWWMH0237E: Asset &quot;{0}&quot; cannot be configured as a composition unit because it is a Java EE asset which was imported with a storage type of &quot;NONE&quot; and is not accessible through the destination URI specified when it was imported.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A Java EE asset must be accessible when it is added to a business-level application as a composition unit.  An asset imported with a storage type of &quot;NONE&quot; does not reside in the product&apos;s configuration repository.  The only means of access in this case is through the destination URI, which is specified when the asset is imported.  If such an asset cannot be accessed through its destination URI,  it cannot be configured as anything but a shared library.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    The asset in its present state cannot be configured.  To make the asset configurable, make it accessible through its destination URI when it is configured.  Alternatively, the asset can be imported with a storage type of &quot;FULL&quot; so that it is accessible from the product configuration repository.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0169E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0169E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0169E=CWWMH0169E: The file name extension of &quot;{0}&quot; does not match that of the original asset name &quot;{1}&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The extension in the asset name must match the file name extension of the asset being imported.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify an asset file name with an extension which matches the asset file being imported.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0133E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0133E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0133E=CWWMH0133E: No file exists at the path specified by the &quot;source&quot; parameter value &quot;{0}&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The &quot;source&quot; parameter value must specify the path of an existing file.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Set the &quot;source&quot; parameter to the path of an existing file.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0129E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0129E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0129E=CWWMH0129E: Ambiguous asset ID &quot;{0}&quot; specified as the composition unit source. Specify a single asset version by using a fully-qualified asset ID, for example, WebSphere:assetname=myAsset.jar,assetversion=1.0.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified asset ID matches multiple versions of an asset.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Fully qualify the ID to select a specific asset version.  The complete asset ID format is WebSphere:assetname=&lt;name&gt;,assetversion=&lt;version&gt;.  An example of a fully-qualified asset ID is WebSphere:assetname=myAsset.jar,assetversion=1.0.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0200W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0200W" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0200W=CWWMH0200W: Problems were encountered while attempting to stop business-level application &quot;{0}&quot;.  It is possible that the business-level application is still partially running.  Please refer to FFDC log entries for details on any failures which were encountered.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Not all modules in the specified business-level application could be stopped.  It is possible some modules are still running.  This message can also occur when the server which hosts a module is not running.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Refer to the FFDC log for more details on any failures encountered.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0412E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0412E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0412E=CWWMH0412E: The &quot;targetID&quot; parameter value &quot;{0}&quot; matches multiple targets for composition unit &quot;{1}&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The target was partially specified and matches multiple targets for the selected composition unit..
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Provide complete target specification.  For example, instead of specifying only a server name, specify both the server name and node name.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0276E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0276E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0276E=CWWMH0276E: Authorization failure. Insufficient authority to access asset &quot;{0}&quot;. This operation requires &quot;monitor&quot; role on the cell or on the asset.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    You are not assigned the roles required to execute the requested operation on the specified asset.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    You must obtain the required role assignments before you can complete the requested operation.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0240E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0240E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0240E=CWWMH0240E: The asset &quot;{0}&quot; cannot be imported with the &quot;loose config&quot; option with a storage type other than &quot;NONE&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    In order for an asset to be imported with the &quot;loose config&quot; option, the storage type must be &quot;NONE&quot;.  This error applies only to development tools interoperating with WebSphere Application Server.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Report the problem to the provider of the development tool you are using.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0172E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0172E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0172E=CWWMH0172E: The value &quot;{1}&quot; for option &quot;{0}&quot; is not valid. Specify a value of &quot;ALL&quot; to update all composition units backed by this asset. Specify &quot;NONE&quot; to not update any composition units.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The updateAssociatedCUs specification optionally can be included in the AssetOptions step in the updateAsset command for Java EE assets. The updateAssociatedCUs option requires a value of &quot;NONE&quot; or &quot;ALL&quot;. A value of &quot;ALL&quot; updates all composition units backed by the asset being updated. Depending on the asset updates, you might need to edit updated composition units. A value of &quot;NONE&quot;, or not specifying this option at all, does not update any composition units. If composition units are not updated, they cannot use the updated asset. For a composition unit to use an updated Java EE asset, you must update the asset with this option set to &quot;ALL&quot;.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a value of either &quot;NONE&quot; or &quot;ALL&quot;, or do not specify the option to choose the default behavior.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0236E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0236E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0236E=CWWMH0236E: The target &quot;{0}&quot; failed validation.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Either no target matches the specification or the specification is ambiguous.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0168E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0168E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0168E=CWWMH0168E: The specfied &quot;match target&quot; value is not valid. Specify a value of &quot;true&quot; or &quot;false&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A &quot;match target&quot; value must be &quot;true&quot; or &quot;false&quot;.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a &quot;match target&quot; value of &quot;true&quot; or &quot;false&quot;.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0132E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0132E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0132E=CWWMH0132E: No file exists at the path specified by the &quot;source.loose.config&quot; property value &quot;{0}&quot; within the &quot;ADTCommandProps&quot; parameter value.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    No file exists at the specified location.  This error applies only to development tools interoperating with WebSphere Application Server.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Report the problem to the provider of the development tool you are using.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0128E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0128E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0128E=CWWMH0128E: The specified business-level application ID &quot;{0}&quot; does not conform to the required syntax.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The business-level application ID provided is syntactically incorrect.  Examples of valid business-level application IDs include:  myBLA, blaname=myBLA, and WebSphere:blaname=myBLA.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a business-level application ID which conforms to the required syntax.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0411E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0411E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0411E=CWWMH0411E: The &quot;targetID&quot; parameter value &quot;{0}&quot; does not match any targets for composition unit &quot;{1}&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The selected composition unit does not have the specified target.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the composition unit and target you specified are correct.  View the composition unit configuration for target data.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0275E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0275E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0275E=CWWMH0275E: Authorization failure. Insufficient authority to update asset &quot;{0}&quot;. This operation requires &quot;deployer&quot; or &quot;configurator&quot; role on the cell, or &quot;deployer&quot; role on the asset.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The user is not assigned the roles required to update the specified asset.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    You must obtain the required role assignments before you can complete the requested operation.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0235E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0235E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0235E=CWWMH0235E: The following composition units were specified as dependencies but do not exist: {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Composition units specified in a dependency relationship must exist.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify existing composition units as dependencies.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0167E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0167E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0167E=CWWMH0167E: Composition unit &quot;{0}&quot; already exists.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A composition unit with the specified name already exists.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a composition name that is not already that of an existing composition unit.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0131E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0131E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0131E=CWWMH0131E: Ambiguous ID &quot;{0}&quot; specified as the composition unit source. The source matches both an asset name and a business-level application name.  Use a more specific ID format, such as assetname=myApp or blaname=myApp.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The composition unit source ID specified matches both an asset name and a business-level application name.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Use a more specific ID format, such as assetname=myApp or blaname=myApp.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0127E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0127E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0127E=CWWMH0127E: The specified composition unit ID &quot;{0}&quot; does not conform to the required syntax.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The composition unit ID provided is syntactically incorrect.  Examples of valid composition unit IDs include:  myCompUnit, cuname=myCompUnit, and WebSphere:cuname=myCompUnit.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a composition unit ID which conforms to the required syntax.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0410E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0410E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0410E=CWWMH0410E: Cannot set target autostart for composition unit &quot;{0}&quot; because it is a Java EE type composition unit.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Composition units created as a by-product of enterprise application installation cannot be configured for target autostart.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Configure the enterprise application associated with the composition unit to set the target autostart option.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0274E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0274E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0274E=CWWMH0274E: Authorization failure. Insufficient authority to delete asset &quot;{0}&quot;. This operation requires &quot;deployer&quot; or &quot;configurator&quot; role on the cell, or &quot;deployer&quot; role on the asset.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    You are not assigned the roles required to delete the specified asset.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    You must obtain the required role assignments before you can complete the requested operation.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0170E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0170E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0170E=CWWMH0170E: Composition unit &quot;{0}&quot; requires target nodes of version {1} or higher, but the following target nodes are lower versions: {2}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified composition unit cannot run on nodes lower than the specified version.  The composition is being targeted to a node lower than the minumum supported version.  If the target is a cluster, the specified node or nodes contain members of the cluster.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Choose a target that includes only nodes which are at the required level or higher.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0234E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0234E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0234E=CWWMH0234E: The following assets were specified as dependencies but do not exist: {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Assets specified in a dependency relationship must exist.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify existing assets as dependencies.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0166E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0166E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0166E=CWWMH0166E: The specfied name &quot;{0}&quot; is not a valid composition unit name.  The name must be non-empty, cannot have leading or trailing blanks or a leading dot, and cannot contain any of the following characters: \/,#$@:;&quot;*?&lt;&gt;|=+&amp;%&apos;&apos;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified composition unit name is not valid.  The error message lists restrictions to composition unit names.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a name which does not violate any of the stated restrictions.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0130E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0130E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0130E=CWWMH0130E: Ambiguous business-level application ID &quot;{0}&quot; specified as the composition unit source. Specify a single business-level application edition by using a fully-qualified business-level application ID, for example, WebSphere:blaname=myBLA,blaedition=1.0.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified business-level application ID matches multiple versions of a business-level application.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Fully qualify the ID to select a specific business-level application version.  The complete business-level application ID format is WebSphere:blaname=&lt;name&gt;,blaedition=&lt;edition&gt;.  An example of a fully-qualified business-level application ID is WebSphere:blaname=myBLA,blaedition=1.0.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0126E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0126E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0126E=CWWMH0126E: The specified asset ID &quot;{0}&quot; does not conform to the required syntax.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The asset ID provided is syntactically incorrect.  Examples of valid asset IDs include:  myAsset.jar, assetname=myAsset.jar, and WebSphere:assetname=myAsset.jar.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify an asset ID which conforms to the required syntax.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0273E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0273E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0273E=CWWMH0273E: Authorization failure. Insufficient authority to import an asset. This operation requires &quot;deployer&quot; or &quot;configurator&quot; role on the cell.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    You are not assigned the roles required to import an asset.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    You must obtain the required role assignments before you can complete the requested operation.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0301I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0301I" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0301I=CWWMH0301I: Stopping business-level application &quot;{0}&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Informational message indicating that a stopBLA command on the specified business-level application has been issued.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is necessary.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0233E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0233E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0233E=CWWMH0233E: Composition unit &quot;{0}&quot; cannot be removed because the following composition units declare it as a dependency: {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified composition unit cannot be removed because it is declared as a dependency by other composition units.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Given that dependencies on the composition unit exist, removal of the composition unit might not be appropriate. If you decide that removing the composition unit is appropriate, first remove the dependency relationships from the dependent composition units or specify a &quot;force&quot; parameter value of &quot;true&quot; to force the removal of those dependency relationships.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0165E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0165E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0165E=CWWMH0165E: The specfied name &quot;{0}&quot; is not a valid asset name.  The name must be non-empty, cannot have leading or trailing blanks or a leading dot, and cannot contain any of the following characters: \/,#$@:;&quot;*?&lt;&gt;|=+&amp;%&apos;&apos;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified asset name is not valid.  The error message lists restrictions to asset names.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a name which does not violate any of the stated restrictions.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0125E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0125E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0125E=CWWMH0125E: The specified &quot;type aspect&quot; value &quot;{0}&quot; is not valid.  Type aspects have a format of: WebSphere:spec=&lt;name&gt;[,version=&lt;version&gt;]. The spec property is required and the version property is optional.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified &quot;type aspect&quot; value does not conform to the required syntax.  The syntax is: WebSphere:spec=&lt;name&gt;[,version=&lt;version&gt;].  The spec property is required; the version is optional.  An example of a valid &quot;type aspect&quot; value is: WebSphere:spec=SomeSpecThatAssetImplements,version=1.0.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a &quot;type aspect&quot; value which conforms to the required syntax.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0272E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0272E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0272E=CWWMH0272E: Authorization failure. Insufficient authority to delete business-level application &quot;{0}&quot;. This operation requires &quot;deployer&quot; or &quot;configurator&quot; role on the cell, or &quot;deployer&quot; role on the business-level application.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    You are not assigned the roles required to delete the specified business-level application.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    You must obtain the required role assignments before you can complete the requested operation.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0300I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0300I" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0300I=CWWMH0300I: Starting business-level application &quot;{0}&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Informational message indicating that a startBLA command on the specified business-level application has been issued.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is necessary.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0164E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0164E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0164E=CWWMH0164E: The operation &quot;{0}&quot; failed, leaving the workspace in an inconsistent state. Discard your workspace.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified operation did not complete successfully and changes were made to the workspace which cannot be undone.  Do not save the the workspace in this inconsistent state; otherwise, you will corrupt your configuration.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Discard the workspace. If possible, determine the cause leading to the failed operation, and retry.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0124E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0124E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0124E=CWWMH0124E: Could not save configuration data for asset &quot;{0}&quot;.  Your workspace may be in an inconsistent state.  Discard your workspace.  Error data: {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Unexpected error occurred while saving asset configuration data to the workspace.  Changes were made to the workspace which cannot be undone.  Do not save the the workspace in this inconsistent state; otherwise, you will corrupt your configuration.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Discard the workspace and reattempt your configuration changes.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0271E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0271E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0271E=CWWMH0271E: Authorization failure. Insufficient authority to create a business-level application. This operation requires &quot;deployer&quot; or &quot;configurator&quot; role on the cell.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    You are not assigned the roles required to create a business-level application.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    You must obtain the required role assignments before you can complete the requested operation.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0199I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0199I" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0199I=CWWMH0199I: Business-level application &quot;{0}&quot; was stopped successfully.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Informational message indicating that the specified business-level application was stopped successfully.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is necessary.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0231E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0231E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0231E=CWWMH0231E: A non-empty value for the &quot;contenturi&quot; parameter is required when the value for the operation parameter is &quot;{0}&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    No value for the &quot;contenturi&quot; parameter was specified.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a non-empty value for the &quot;contenturi&quot; parameter.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0163E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0163E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0163E=CWWMH0163E: Asset &quot;{0}&quot; is configured with no type aspects.  Assets must be configured with at least one type aspect.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The content handler which recognizes the specified asset did not configure any type aspects for the asset.  An asset must have at least one type aspect.  The product is pre-configured with content handlers for certain types of assets such as Java EE applications and general Java archives.  Product extensions can also configure content handlers to handle other types of assets.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    This error indicates a problem with the product extension associated with the specified asset.  Contact the provider of the product extension associated with the asset for support.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0227E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0227E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0227E=CWWMH0227E: A non-empty value for the &quot;contents&quot; parameter is required when the value for the operation parameter is &quot;{0}&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    No value for the &quot;contents&quot; parameter was specified.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a non-empty value for the &quot;contents&quot; parameter.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0159E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0159E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0159E=CWWMH0159E: Could not find step &quot;{0}&quot; in config data repository.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This exception is unexpected. The cause is not immediately known.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0123E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0123E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0123E=CWWMH0123E: Could not read configuration data for asset ID &quot;{0}&quot;.  Error data: {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An unexpected error occurred while reading configuration data for the specified asset.  The configuration could be corrupted.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0119E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0119E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0119E=CWWMH0119E: Unable to obtain document from the configuration repository.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An unexpected error occurred while attempting to obtain a document from the configuration repository.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0270E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0270E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0270E=CWWMH0270E: Authorization failure. Insufficient authority to access business-level application &quot;{0}&quot;. This operation requires &quot;monitor&quot; role on the cell or on the business-level application.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    You are not assigned the roles required to execute the requested operation on the specified business-level application.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    You must obtain the required role assignments before you can complete the requested operation.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0198I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0198I" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0198I=CWWMH0198I: Control operation &quot;{0}&quot; not executed on composition unit &quot;{1}&quot; in business-level application &quot;{2}&quot; because the composition unit has no targets.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A composition unit in a business-level application cannot be started or stopped unless it is configured to have a target.  When a business-level application is started or stopped, composition units with no targets are ignored.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is necessary.  In order to make the composition unit runnable, configure it with a target server or cluster.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0230E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0230E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0230E=CWWMH0230E: No file exists at the path specified by the &quot;contents&quot; parameter.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The &quot;contents&quot; parameter value must be the pathname to an existing file. No file was found at that path.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify the pathname to an existing file.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0226E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0226E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0226E=CWWMH0226E: Asset &quot;{0}&quot; cannot be removed because the following assets declare it as a dependency: {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Asset specified cannot be removed because it is declared as a dependency by other assets.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Given that dependencies on the asset exist, removal of the asset might not be appropriate. If you decide that removing the asset is appropriate, first remove the dependency relationships from the dependent assets or specify a &quot;force&quot; parameter value of &quot;true&quot; to force the removal of those dependency relationships.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0158E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0158E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0158E=CWWMH0158E: The specfied name &quot;{0}&quot; is not a valid business-level application name.  The name must be non-empty, cannot have leading or trailing blanks or a leading dot, and cannot contain any of the following characters: \/,#$@:;&quot;*?&lt;&gt;|=+&amp;%&apos;&apos;
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified business-level application name is not valid.  The error message lists restrictions to business-level application names.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a name which does not violate any of the stated restrictions.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0122E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0122E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0122E=CWWMH0122E: Could not save configuration data for composition unit &quot;{0}&quot;.  Your workspace may be in an inconsistent state.  Discard your workspace.  Error data: {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Unexpected error occurred while saving composition unit configuration data to the workspace.  Changes were made to the workspace which cannot be undone.  Do not save the the workspace in this inconsistent state; otherwise, you will corrupt your configuration.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Discard the workspace and reattempt your configuration changes.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0118E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0118E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0118E=CWWMH0118E: Unable to obtain ConfigRepositoryClient reference.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This is an internal error.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0197E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0197E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0197E=CWWMH0197E: Problems were encountered while attempting to start business-level application &quot;{0}&quot;.  It is possible that the business-level application is not running or is only partially running.  Please refer to FFDC log entries for details on any failures which were encountered.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Not all modules in the specified business-level application could be started.  It is possible some modules are not running.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Refer to the FFDC log for more details on any failures encountered.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0225E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0225E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0225E=CWWMH0225E: Cannot define a dependency relationship from asset &quot;{0}&quot; to asset &quot;{1}&quot; because doing so would create a circular dependency.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    You are trying to define a dependency relationship from an asset to a second asset where the second asset already has a dependency relationship defined on the first asset.  Circular dependency relationships are not allowed.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Avoid circular dependency relationships.  Consider combining the two mutually-dependent assets into one single asset.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0157E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0157E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0157E=CWWMH0157E: Control operation &quot;{0}&quot; is already defined on composition unit &quot;{1}&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified control operation already exists for the composition unit being configured.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    This error indicates a problem with the product extension associated with the asset you are trying to configure as a composition unit.  Contact the provider of the product extension associated with the asset for support.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0121E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0121E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0121E=CWWMH0121E: Could not read configuration data for composition unit &quot;{0}&quot;.  Error data: {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An unexpected error occurred while reading configuration data for the specified composition unit.  The configuration could be corrupted.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0196I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0196I" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0196I=CWWMH0196I: Business-level application &quot;{0}&quot; was started successfully.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Informational message indicating that the specified business-level application was started successfully.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is necessary.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0160E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0160E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0160E=CWWMH0160E: Input file &quot;{0}&quot; for &quot;importAsset&quot; operation is not recognized by any content handler configured in the product.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Files imported as assets must be recognized by some content handler.  The product is pre-configured with content handlers for certain types of assets such as Java EE applications and general Java archives.  Product extensions can also configure content handlers to handle other types of assets.  No content handler recognized the file you are trying to import as an asset.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the file you are trying to import is not recognizable by any configured content handler, you cannot import that file.  The error could also indicate a problem with the product extension associated with the file you are trying to import.  In this case, contact the provider of the product extension associated with the file for support.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0224E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0224E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0224E=CWWMH0224E: Session ID cannot be null.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The reported condition could be a product internal error or a problem with a third-party content provider plug-in designed to handle specific asset types.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0156E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0156E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0156E=CWWMH0156E: The activation plan &quot;{0}&quot; does not conform to the required syntax.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An activation plan must be expressed as a series of runtime component IDs separated by a &quot;plus&quot; sign (+).  Valid values for a runtime component ID include: &lt;spec name&gt;, specName=&lt;spec name&gt;, WebSphere:specName=&lt;spec name&gt;, and WebSphere:specName=&lt;spec name&gt;,specVersion=&lt;version&gt;; where &lt;spec name&gt; is the name of the runtime component and &lt;version&gt; is the version of the runtime component.  An example of a valid activation plan value is: WebSphere:specName=SomeRuntimeComponent,version=1.0.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify the relationship which conforms to the described syntax.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0116E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0116E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0116E=CWWMH0116E: The value of the &quot;destination&quot; parameter passed to a DeployableObjectWriter is not valid.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This condition could be caused by an internal error or a problem with some business-level application content provider added as a product extension.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0223E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0223E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0223E=CWWMH0223E: Value &quot;{0}&quot; for restart behavior on update is not valid. Valid values are &quot;ALL&quot;, &quot;NONE&quot;, and &quot;DEFAULT&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A value other than &quot;ALL&quot;, &quot;NONE&quot;, or &quot;DEFAULT&quot; was specified for restart behavior on update.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a valid value for restart behavior on update.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0155E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0155E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0155E=CWWMH0155E: Business-level application &quot;{0}&quot; does not exist.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    No business-level application with the specified name can be found.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the ID you specified is correct and identifies an existing business-level application.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0219E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0219E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0219E=CWWMH0219E: Error occurred while listing business-level applications.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Could not list business-level applications due to some unexpected error.  Check FFDC log directory for additional diagnostic data.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0115E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0115E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0115E=CWWMH0115E: The value of the &quot;save options&quot; parameter passed to a DeployableObjectWriter is not valid.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This condition could be caused by an internal error or a problem with some business-level application content provider added as a product extension.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0194E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0194E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0194E=CWWMH0194E: Class &quot;{0}&quot;, specified through the content-depl-data-change-listeners Eclipse extension point, could not be instantiated.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Business-level application content providers must configure an extension of com.ibm.wsspi.management.bla.cdr.ConfigDataListener.  The specified configuration data listener class could not be instantiated.  The product is pre-configured with configuration data listeners for certain types of assets such as Java EE applications and general Java archives.  Product extensions can also configure configuration data listeners to handle other types of assets.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    This error indicates a problem with a business-level application content provider added as a product extension.  Contact the source of the problem configuration data listener class for support.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0222E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0222E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0222E=CWWMH0222E: Asset ID cannot be empty or null.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An asset ID must be a non-null, non-empty value.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a valid asset ID.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0154E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0154E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0154E=CWWMH0154E: Business-level application &quot;{0}&quot; already exists.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A new business-level application cannot be created with the same name as an existing business-level application.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Choose a name which does not conflict with an existing business-level application.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0218E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0218E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0218E=CWWMH0218E: Error occurred while obtaining business-level application status.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Could not obtain business-level application status due to some unexpected error.  Check FFDC log directory for additional diagnostic data.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0114E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0114E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0114E=CWWMH0114E: Unable to get Eclipse extension registry.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This exception is unexpected. The cause is not immediately known.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH1004W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH1004W" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH1004W=CWWMH1004W: Unable to access configuration file &quot;{0}&quot; during synchronization.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This exception is unexpected. The cause is not immediately known.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0261E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0261E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0261E=CWWMH0261E: Invalid value {0} for expansion key. Fail to save Composition unit.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The value specified is not the correct format. The expansion value has to be an integer.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    CSMG0002
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0193E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0193E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0193E=CWWMH0193E: Class &quot;{0}, specified through the content-depl-data-change-listeners extension point, is not a supported configuration data listener class.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Business-level application content providers can configure an extension of com.ibm.wsspi.management.bla.cdr.ConfigDataListener.  The specified configuration data listener class is not an extension of com.ibm.wsspi.management.bla.cdr.ConfigDataListener.  The product is pre-configured with configuration data listeners for certain types of assets such as Java EE applications and general Java archives.  Product extensions can also configure operation handlers to handle other types of assets.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    This error indicates a problem with a business-level application content provider added as a product extension.  Contact the source of the problem configuration data listener class for support.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0221E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0221E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0221E=CWWMH0221E: Composition unit ID cannot be empty or null.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A composition unit ID must be a non-null, non-empty value.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a valid composition unit ID.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0189E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0189E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0189E=CWWMH0189E: Could not access Eclipse extension registory object for the &quot;{0}&quot; extension point type.  Error data: {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An error occurred attempting to access some extension of the specified extension point type.  The failure, while not fatal, could cause some operations related to business-level applications to not function correctly.  The failure could be caused by an internal error or a problem with some business-level application content provider added as a product extension.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0153E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0153E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0153E=CWWMH0153E: The composition unit relationship &quot;{0}&quot; does not conform to the required syntax.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A composition unit relationship must be expressed as a composition unit ID.  Valid values for a composition unit ID include: &lt;composition unit name&gt;, cuname=&lt;composition unit name&gt;, and WebSphere:cuname=&lt;composition unit name&gt;; where &lt;composition unit name&gt; is the name of the composition unit.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify the relationship as a composition unit ID.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0217E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0217E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0217E=CWWMH0217E: Could not save reference data for composition unit &quot;{0}&quot;.  Your workspace may be in an inconsistent state.  Discard your workspace.  Error data: {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Unexpected error occurred while saving composition unit reference configuration data to the workspace.  Changes were made to the workspace which cannot be undone.  Do not save the the workspace in this inconsistent state; otherwise, you will corrupt your configuration.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Discard the workspace and reattempt your configuration changes.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0149E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0149E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0149E=CWWMH0149E: Cannot delete business-level application &quot;{0}&quot; because it contains composition units. Delete all composition units which belong to the business-level application, and then delete the business-level application.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A business-level application which contains composition units cannot be deleted.  All of its composition units must be deleted before it can be deleted.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Delete the delete business-level application&apos;s composition units, and then delete the delete business-level application.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0113E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0113E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0113E=CWWMH0113E: Unable to get Eclipse extension point using the extension point identifier &quot;{0}&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This exception is unexpected. The cause is not immediately known.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0109E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0109E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0109E=CWWMH0109E: Class &quot;{0}&quot;, specified through the content-depl-providers Eclipse extension point, is not a supported content handler class.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Business-level application content providers must configure an extension of com.ibm.wsspi.management.bla.framework.ContentHandler.  The specified class is not an extension of com.ibm.wsspi.management.bla.framework.ContentHandler.  The product is pre-configured with content handlers for certain types of assets such as Java EE applications and general Java archives.  Product extensions can also configure content handlers to handle other types of assets.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    This error indicates a problem with a business-level application content provider added as a product extension.  Contact the source of the problem content handler class for support.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0260E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0260E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0260E=CWWMH0260E: Cannot add business-level application &quot;{0}&quot; as a composition unit to business-level application &quot;{1}&quot; because doing so would create a cycle in the business-level application hierarchy.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A business-level application can be added as a composition unit to another business-level application.  It is therefore possible to create a hierarchy of business-level applications of two or more levels.  However, the same business-level application cannot occur in more than one level in any path of the hierarchy.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Avoid cyclic business-level application hierarchies.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0220E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0220E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0220E=CWWMH0220E: Business-level application ID cannot be empty or null.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A business-level application ID must be a non-null, non-empty value.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a valid business-level application ID.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0188E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0188E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0188E=CWWMH0188E: Content cannot be saved in the form of a Java EE module.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A Java archive which is a Java EE module is being saved to the configuration repository.  This archive format is not supported.  The failure could be caused by an internal error or a problem with some business-level application content provider added as a product extension.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0152E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0152E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0152E=CWWMH0152E: The specified asset relationship &quot;{0}&quot; does not conform to the required asset ID syntax.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An asset relationship must be expressed as an asset ID.  Valid values for an asset ID include: &lt;asset name&gt;, assetname=&lt;asset name&gt;, and WebSphere:assetname=&lt;asset name&gt;; where &lt;asset name&gt; is the name of the asset.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify the relationship as an asset ID.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0216E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0216E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0216E=CWWMH0216E: Could not read reference configuration data for composition unit &quot;{0}&quot;.  Error data: {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An unexpected error occurred while reading composition unit reference configuration data for the specified composition unit.  The configuration could be corrupted.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0112E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0112E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0112E=CWWMH0112E: Class &quot;{0}&quot;, specified through the operation-depl-providers Eclipse extension point, could not be instantiated.  Error data: {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Business-level application content providers must configure an extension of com.ibm.wsspi.management.bla.framework.OperationHandler.  The specified operation handler class could not be instantiated.  The product is pre-configured with operation handlers for certain types of assets such as Java EE applications and general Java archives.  Product extensions can also configure operation handlers to handle other types of assets.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    This error indicates a problem with a business-level application content provider added as a product extension.  Contact the source of the problem operation handler class for support.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0108E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0108E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0108E=CWWMH0108E: The specified target &quot;{0}&quot; does not conform to the required syntax.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A target must be expressed as a target ID.  Valid values for a target ID include: &lt;server name&gt;; server=&lt;server name&gt;; cluster=&lt;cluster name&gt;; WebSphere:server=&lt;server name&gt;,node=&lt;node name&gt;; and WebSphere:cluster=&lt;cluster name&gt;. If the target is a single server and the server name is not unique within the cell, the node name must be specified.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify the target as a target ID.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0215W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0215W" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0215W=CWWMH0215W: Cleanup processing for this business-level application command failed.  Check FFDC log directory for additional diagnostic data.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Cleanup processing for a business-level application command failed.  Cleanup processing occurs whether the command execution ends successfully or unsuccessfully.  The exact nature of cleanup processing varies with the individual command and data being processed by the command.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine FFDC log entries for additional diagnostic data.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0191E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0191E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0191E=CWWMH0191E: Unexpected error occurred while attempting to access the &quot;{0}&quot; Eclipse extension point.  Error data: {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An error occurred while attempting to read Exclipse extension points.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH1002E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH1002E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH1002E=CWWMH1002E: Unable to invoke NotificationService MBean in {0} process to emit business-level application distribution notifications.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Business-level application distribution status events are emitted through the NotificationService MBean.  Because a reference to the NotificationService MBean cannot be obtained or the MBean invocation failed, some application distribution notifications cannot be sent.  Any listeners for those events will not receive them.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See FFDC for more information.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0187E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0187E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0187E=CWWMH0187E: URI &quot;{0}&quot; length is greater than Windows limit of 259 characters.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Some versions of Windows operating systems limit file pathname lengths to 259 characters.  A file related to a business-level application is exceeding that limit.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Various user-chosen names can influence the overall length of pathnames of files stored in the configuration repository.  Such names include the product installation directory pathname and the cell name.  Also, individual business-level application artifact names, including names for assets, composition units, and Java EE application names, affect the pathname length of respective files.  Try using names which are not excessively long with respect to the 259 character limit.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0151E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0151E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0151E=CWWMH0151E: Business-level application &quot;{0}&quot; cannot be removed because the following composition units are based on it: {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Business-level application specified cannot be removed because it is configured as a composition unit in one or more other business-level applications.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Given that composition units are based on the business-level application, removal of the business-level application might not be appropriate. If you decide that removing the business-level application is appropriate, first remove the composition units based on the business-level application from their respective business-level applications.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0111E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0111E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0111E=CWWMH0111E: Class &quot;{0}, specified through the operation-depl-providers Eclipse extension point, is not a supported operation handler class.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Business-level application content providers can configure an extension of com.ibm.wsspi.management.bla.framework.OperationHandler.  The specified operation handler class is not an extension of com.ibm.wsspi.management.bla.framework.OperationHandler.  The product is pre-configured with operation handlers for certain types of assets such as Java EE applications and general Java archives.  Product extensions can also configure operation handlers to handle other types of assets.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    This error indicates a problem with a business-level application content provider added as a product extension.  Contact the source of the problem operation handler class for support.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH1001W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH1001W" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH1001W=CWWMH1001W: Unexpected error occurred during synchronization of configuration files associated with business-level applications.  Error data: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This exception is unexpected. The cause is not immediately known.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWWMH0107E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWWMH0107E" varFormat="Java">
    CWWMH0107E=CWWMH0107E: Composition unit &quot;{0}&quot; does not exist.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified composition unit cannot be found.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Verify that the ID you specified is correct and identifies an existing composition unit.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<!-- END MESSAGES -->
</TMSSource>
