<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/css" href="../../resources/stylesheets/wasmsgxml.css"?>
<TMSSource name="TivoliMessages" tmsVersion="1.0" xml:lang="en">
<!-- CMVC MSG File Name = ws\code\commsvc.ws\src\com\ibm\ws\commsvc\resources\commsvc.nlsprops -->
<!-- DO NOT EDIT THIS FILE - This file was generated by the XML/Html & Property emitter -->
<!-- BEGIN MESSAGES -->
<Message ID="CWSPA0003W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWSPA0003W" varFormat="Java">
    CWSPA0003W=CWSPA0003W: Invalid value, &quot;{0}&quot;, found for custom property com.ibm.ws.commsvc.maxEventQueueSize.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An exception occurred loading the custom property com.ibm.ws.commsvc.maxEventQueueSize.  Default value, -1, is being used.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    The Administrator should examine the custom property com.ibm.ws.commsvc.maxEventQueueSize and take appropriate action.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSPA0005E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWSPA0005E" varFormat="Java">
    CWSPA0005E=CWSPA0005E: The external web service implementation, &quot;{0}&quot;, is not accessible.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Communication Enabled Applications (CEA) settings indicate that an external web service should be used, but the configured WSDL location is not accessible.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    The Administrator should update the Communication Enabled Applications (CEA) settings for the WSDL location and ensure it is reachable.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSPA0001W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWSPA0001W" varFormat="Java">
    CWSPA0001W=CWSPA0001W: Using default values for Communication Enabled Applications (CEA) Settings.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Communication Enabled Applications (CEA) Settings file, cea-extension.xml, was not found.  Default values are being used.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Configure the Communication Enabled Applications (CEA) Settings or ignore if default values are acceptable.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSPA0006E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWSPA0006E" varFormat="Java">
    CWSPA0006E=CWSPA0006E: Member can not be added to cluster because CEA is enabled within the cluster.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A server which does not support Communication Enabled Applications (CEA) may not be added as a member of a cluster in which CEA is enabled.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    The Administrator should either disable Communication Enabled Applications (CEA) in the cluster, or add to the cluster a server which supports CEA.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSPA0002W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWSPA0002W" varFormat="Java">
    CWSPA0002W=CWSPA0002W: Using default values for Communication Enabled Applications (CEA) Settings due to: {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An exception occurred loading the Communication Enabled Applications (CEA) Settings.  Default values are being used.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    The Administrator should examine the exception for a possible cause and take appropriate action.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSPA0004E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CWSPA0004E" varFormat="Java">
    CWSPA0004E=CWSPA0004E: Communication Enabled Applications (CEA) settings indicate that the super user name should be used, but it is not currently set.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An exception occurred during servlet startup.  The configuration indicates that the super user name should be used, but it is empty.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    The Administrator should examine the Communication Enabled Applications (CEA) settings for determining the user name to use.  If the super user name is required, update the configuration with an appropriate value.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<!-- END MESSAGES -->
</TMSSource>
