<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/css" href="../../resources/stylesheets/wasmsgxml.css"?>
<TMSSource name="TivoliMessages" tmsVersion="1.0" xml:lang="en">
<!-- CMVC MSG File Name = ws/code/placement/src/com/ibm/apc/xd/changes/nls/Messages.nlsprops -->
<!-- DO NOT EDIT THIS FILE - This file was generated by the XML/Html & Property emitter -->
<!-- BEGIN MESSAGES -->
<Message ID="DCPC0404I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="LZ_DCMustBeActive" varFormat="Java">
    LZ_DCMustBeActive=DCPC0404I: Dynamic cluster {0} can no longer be deactivated due to inactivity.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The application lazy start controller is not permitted to deactivate this dynamic cluster in the future.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DCPC0120I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PC_ServerRecomendation" varFormat="Java">
    PC_ServerRecomendation=DCPC0120I: The application placement controller recommends that server {0} be changed to state {1} on node {2}.  Dynamic Cluster {3} operating mode is {4}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The application placement controller has determined that a server instance needs to be stopped or started.  See message DCPC0121I for additional information.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the dynamic cluster operating mode is set to supervised, accept or reject the recommendation on the Task Management panel in the administrative console. If the dynamic cluster operating mode is set to automatic, no user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DCPC0045I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PC_GATE_CONNECT_SUCCESS" varFormat="Java">
    PC_GATE_CONNECT_SUCCESS=DCPC0045I: The application placement controller has successfully connected to a remote controller  {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Another application placement controller is configured and the local controller has connected to the remote controller.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DCPC0322I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PC_ChangePerfAut" varFormat="Java">
    PC_ChangePerfAut=DCPC0322I: The application placement controller detected that the system performance can be improved by a reallocation of dynamic cluster instances. Review the strategy for automatically modifying the placement of dynamic cluster instances in the action plan.  The dynamic cluster operating mode is set to automatic.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The application placement controller detected that the system performance can be improved by a reallocation of dynamic cluster instances. Review the strategy for automatically modifying the placement of dynamic cluster instances in the action plan.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required. Placement changes have been initiated.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DCPC0009I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PC_Config1I" varFormat="Java">
    PC_Config1I=DCPC0009I: application placement controller: minTimeBetweenPlacementChanges has been set to {0} min.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Placement Controller configuration has been changed by a user.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DCPC0305I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PC_ChangeNodeUtilization" varFormat="Java">
    PC_ChangeNodeUtilization=DCPC0305I: The application placement controller detected that the CPU utilization values exceed the specified thresholds on nodes: &quot;{0}&quot;.  Modify the placement of dynamic cluster instances to transfer workload to other nodes. Review the strategy for modifying the placement of dynamic cluster instances  in the action plan.  The dynamic cluster operating mode is supervised.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Maximum CPU utilization is specified in the Autonomic Request Flow Manager configuration.  The application placement controller monitors the CPU utilization per node and requests a placement change when the specified threshold is breached.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Review the action plan provided by the system and approve the proposed placement changes.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DCPC0401I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="LZ_DeactivateDC" varFormat="Java">
    LZ_DeactivateDC=DCPC0401I: The application lazy start controller will allow deactivation of dynamic cluster {0} instances if resources are required by other dynamic clusters.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The application lazy start controller detected that this dynamic cluster has been idle for the specified wait period and will allow all its server instances to be stopped if resources consumed by them are needed by other dynamic clusters.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DCPC0102I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PC_AP_STATUS_COMPLETE_KEY" varFormat="Java">
    PC_AP_STATUS_COMPLETE_KEY=DCPC0102I: Placement has completed.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The approved placement plan was successfully completed.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DCPC0127W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PC_TaskCompleteErr" varFormat="Java">
    PC_TaskCompleteErr=DCPC0127W: The application placement controller has completed a change for task ID {0} with errors.  Outstanding changes remaining:{1}.  Outstanding tasks remaining:{2}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    application placement controller has been notified that a change has completed with errors.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DCPC0121I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PC_RecomendationExpire" varFormat="Java">
    PC_RecomendationExpire=DCPC0121I: The application placement controller has submitted a task to the task management subsystem that will expire at {0}.  The operating mode is {1}.  The task ID is {2}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The application placement controller has submitted a task to the task management subsystem. See message DCPC0120I for additional information.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the dynamic cluster operating mode is set to supervised, accept the recommendation prior to the expiration time on the Task Management panel in the administrative console. If the dynamic cluster operating mode is set to automatic, no user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DCPC0311I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PC_ChangeNodeMemory" varFormat="Java">
    PC_ChangeNodeMemory=DCPC0311I: The application placement controller for detected that memory utilization values exceed thresholds on nodes: &quot;{0}&quot;.  Modify the placement of dynamic cluster instances to balance memory usage among nodes. Review the strategy for modifying the placement of dynamic cluster instances  in the action plan.  The dynamic cluster operating mode is supervised.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The application placement controller senses and monitors total memory utilization and memory capacity on a node.  If the sum of memory consumed by all servers on a node exceeds the capacity of a node, application placement change is requested.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Review the action plan provided by the system and approve the proposed placement changes.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DCPC0015E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="BB_SubscribeFailed" varFormat="Java">
    BB_SubscribeFailed=DCPC0015E: Unable to subscribe to topic: cell = {0}, node = {1}, message = {2}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The application placement controller could not subscribe to the specified bulletin board topic.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If BBSON is enabled, verify that no TCP and UDP port conflicts exist.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DCPC0119I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PC_RealTimeWakeUp" varFormat="Java">
    PC_RealTimeWakeUp=DCPC0119I: The application placement controller has been activated to review a dynamic event.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A dynamic event that requires the application placement controller to review the event and potentially reconfigure the system has occurred.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required. Additional messages will be logged if a change is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DCPC0308I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PC_ChangeCapacityAut" varFormat="Java">
    PC_ChangeCapacityAut=DCPC0308I: The application placement controller detected that additional resources can be  allocated to these service classes: &quot;{0}&quot;. Though none of the service classes are projected to breach service policy goals, the placement of dynamic cluster instances can be modified to improve service level performance.  Review the strategy used to automatically modify the placement of dynamic cluster instances in the action plan.  The dynamic cluster operating mode is automatic.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The application placement controller has determined that there is a more optimal placement of dynamic cluster instances and has requested a placement change.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required. Placement changes have been initiated.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DCPC0306I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PC_ChangeGoalAut" varFormat="Java">
    PC_ChangeGoalAut=DCPC0306I: The application placement controller detected that service policy goals have been or soon will be breached  for these service classes: &quot;{0}&quot;.  Modify the placement of dynamic cluster instances to maintain desired service level performance. Review the strategy used to automatically modify the placement of dynamic cluster instances in the action plan.  The dynamic cluster operating mode is automatic.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The application placement controller has requested placement changes in order to maintain service levels for the specified service classes.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required. Placement changes have been initiated.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DCPC0140W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PC_FailedStartAdd" varFormat="Java">
    PC_FailedStartAdd=DCPC0140W: The application placement controller has added server {0} to the failed start list. A manual start might be required. The original task ID was {1}.  {2}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The application placement controller has attempted to start a server that did not start within the allotted time. The server logs or server node agent logs might contain the reason for the failure.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check the server operation timeout value that is specified on the application placement controller configuration.  This value might need to be increased.  To change the value in the administrative console, click Operational Policies &gt; Autonomic Managers &gt; Application Placement Controller.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DCPC0021I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PC_ELASTICITY_MODE" varFormat="Java">
    PC_ELASTICITY_MODE=DCPC0021I: The application placement controller set elasticity mode to {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DCPC0321I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PC_ChangePerf" varFormat="Java">
    PC_ChangePerf=DCPC0321I: The application placement controller detected that the system performance can be improved by a reallocation of dynamic cluster instances. Review the strategy for modifying the placement of dynamic cluster instances in the action plan.  The dynamic cluster operating mode is set to supervised.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The application placement controller detected that the system performance can be improved by a reallocation of dynamic cluster instances. Review the strategy for modifying the placement of dynamic cluster instances in the action plan.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Review the action plan provided by the system and approve the proposed placement changes.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DCPC0310I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PC_ChangeNodeUtilizationAut" varFormat="Java">
    PC_ChangeNodeUtilizationAut=DCPC0310I: The application placement controller detected that the CPU utilization values exceed the specified thresholds on nodes: &quot;{0}&quot;.  Modify the placement of dynamic cluster instances to transfer workload to other nodes. Review the strategy used to automatically modify the placement of dynamic cluster instances in the action plan.  The dynamic cluster operating mode is automatic.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Maximum CPU utilization is specified in the Autonomic Request Flow Manager configuration.  The application placement controller monitors the CPU utilization per node and requests a placement change when the specified threshold is breached.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required. Placement changes have been initiated.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DCPC0005I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PC_PlacementChange" varFormat="Java">
    PC_PlacementChange=DCPC0005I: A placement change occurred. newPlacement={0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The application placement controller proposed a new placement.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DCPC0003E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PC_EnableErr" varFormat="Java">
    PC_EnableErr=DCPC0003E: The following error occurred during an attempt to enable the application placement controller: {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The application placement controller could not be enabled due to an unexpected error.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Restart the cell.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DCPC0132I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PC_DCChangeCommanCall" varFormat="Java">
    PC_DCChangeCommanCall=DCPC0132I: The application placement controller has issued command {0} for task ID {1} on server {2} that will expire at {3}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The application placement controller is attempting to start or stop a server instance.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DCPC0133I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PC_DCChangeCommanReturn" varFormat="Java">
    PC_DCChangeCommanReturn=DCPC0133I: The application placement controller has received status for command {0} for task ID {1} on server {2}. success={3}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The application placement controller is attempting to start or stop a server instance.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DCPC0502E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="APC_CoreDumpErr" varFormat="Java">
    APC_CoreDumpErr=DCPC0502E: The complete set of states for an unhealthy application placement controller is: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message provides a detailed list of all application placement controller states.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Review the runtime tasks submitted by the application placement controller. In the administrative console, select System administration &gt; Task Management &gt; Runtime Tasks.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DCPC0001I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PC_Enabled" varFormat="Java">
    PC_Enabled=DCPC0001I: The application placement controller is enabled.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DCPC0309I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PC_ChangeMinMaxPolicyAut" varFormat="Java">
    PC_ChangeMinMaxPolicyAut=DCPC0309I: The application placement controller detected that these dynamic clusters &quot;{0}&quot; are not running the required number of dynamic cluster instances as specified in the configuration.  Modify the placement of dynamic cluster instances to ensure that the specified minimum and maximum number of instances is met. Review the strategy used to automatically modify the placement of dynamic cluster instances in the action plan.  The dynamic cluster operating mode is automatic.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The minimum and maximum dynamic cluster instances is specified in the dynamic cluster configuration properties. The application placement controller compares the number of active instances against the configured values and requests placement changes if necessary.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required. Placement changes have been initiated.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DCPC0500I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="APC_UP" varFormat="Java">
    APC_UP=DCPC0500I: The application placement controller is operational.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DCPC0142I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PC_MaintModeStatus" varFormat="Java">
    PC_MaintModeStatus=DCPC0142I: The application placement controller detected a {0} operation with notification sequence {1} for {2} with a change count of {3}. {4}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A maintenance mode operation is in progress.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DCPC0503I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="APC_Predictor" varFormat="Java">
    APC_Predictor=DCPC0503I: The application placement controller predictor is: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message indicates which application placement controller predictor is being used.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DCPC0332E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PC_ActionPlanFailedToCreate" varFormat="Java">
    PC_ActionPlanFailedToCreate=DCPC0332E: The application placement controller is unable to create an action plan.  Resource=&quot;{0}&quot;  Reason=&quot;{1}&quot;.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The application placement controller cannot initiate or complete a recommended change.  The change might be attempted during the next placement cycle.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Use the information in the &quot;Resource&quot; and &quot;Reason&quot; fields and correct the problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DCPC0002I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PC_Disabled" varFormat="Java">
    PC_Disabled=DCPC0002I: The application placement controller is disabled.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DCPC0134I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PC_VMRecomendation" varFormat="Java">
    PC_VMRecomendation=DCPC0134I: The Application Placement Controller recommends the following action: {0} resources.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Application Placement Controller has determined resources needs to be added or removed.  See message DCPC0121I for additional information.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If custom property was set to supervised, use the Admin Console Task Management panel to accept or deny the recommendation. If the custom property was set to automatic, no user action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DCPC0334I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PC_ChangeVMAddRemove" varFormat="Java">
    PC_ChangeVMAddRemove=DCPC0334I: The Application Placement Controller detected the action needs to be completed on cell &quot;{0}&quot; : &quot;{1}&quot; resources. Review the strategy used to automatically modify the placement of virtual machines in the action plan.  The elasticity mode is set to supervised mode.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Application Placement Controller determines if more resources are needed to minimize response time and meet service policy goals or resources can be removed and service policy goals will still be met.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Since the custom property was set to supervised, use the Admin Console Task Management panel to accept or deny the recommendation.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DCPC0106E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PC_TaskSubmit_Err" varFormat="Java">
    PC_TaskSubmit_Err=DCPC0106E: The following error occurred during at attempt to submit a task to the task controller: error={0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The application placement controller was unable to communicate with the deployment manager.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that the deployment manager is started, and that there are no network connectivity issues.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DCPC0501I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="APC_CoreDump" varFormat="Java">
    APC_CoreDump=DCPC0501I: The complete set of states for an operational application placement controller is: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message provides a detailed list of all application placement controller states.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DCPC0320I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PC_ChangeAllocationAut" varFormat="Java">
    PC_ChangeAllocationAut=DCPC0320I: The application placement controller detected that instances of dynamic cluster &quot;{0}&quot; are incorrectly running on a node. Review the strategy for automatically modifying the placement of dynamic cluster instances in the action plan.  The dynamic cluster operating mode is set to automatic.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The application placement controller detected that instances of dynamic cluster are incorrectly running on a node. Review the strategy for automatically modifying the placement of dynamic cluster instances in the action plan.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required. Placement changes have been initiated.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DCPC0050E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PC_MINPOLICYErr" varFormat="Java">
    PC_MINPOLICYErr=DCPC0050E: Unable to meet the minInstances policy for dynamic cluster {0}; minInstances = {1}, allocated {2}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The application placement controller is unable to meet the minInstances policy for a dynamic cluster due to insufficient memory.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Increase the total memory in the node group or specify larger minInstances policy values.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DCPC0326I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PC_ChangeLazyStartAut" varFormat="Java">
    PC_ChangeLazyStartAut=DCPC0326I: The application placement controller detected that the following dynamic cluster configured for lazy activation needs to be acted upon because of recent activity. &quot;{0}&quot;.  The dynamic cluster operating mode is set to automatic.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The application placement controller receives dynamic cluster activity information from the on demand router.  That information has changed such that activation is required.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Since the dynamic cluster operating mode is set to automatic, no action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DCPC0330I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PC_ChangeIdleStopAut" varFormat="Java">
    PC_ChangeIdleStopAut=DCPC0330I: The application placement controller detected that the following dynamic cluster configured for idle stop needs to be acted upon. &quot;{0}&quot;.  The dynamic cluster operating mode is set to automatic.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The application placement controller receives dynamic cluster activity information from the on demand router.  That information has changed such that deactivation is required.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Since the dynamic cluster operating mode is set to automatic, no action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DCPC0303I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PC_ChangeCapacity" varFormat="Java">
    PC_ChangeCapacity=DCPC0303I: The application placement controller detected that additional resources can be allocated to these service classes: &quot;{0}&quot;. Though none of the service classes are projected to breach service policy goals, the placement of dynamic cluster instances can be modified to improve service level performance. Review the strategy for modifying the placement of dynamic cluster instances in the action plan.  The dynamic cluster operating mode is supervised.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The application placement controller has determined that there is a more optimal placement of dynamic cluster instances and has requested a placement change.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Review the action plan provided by the system and approve the proposed placement changes.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DCPC0129I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PC_FindBestVacancy" varFormat="Java">
    PC_FindBestVacancy=DCPC0129I: The application placement controller has been requested to find an alternate location to run server {0} and the available replacement location is {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A request to shut down or set the maintenance mode of a server or node has been submitted.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DCPC0141I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PC_FailedStartRemove" varFormat="Java">
    PC_FailedStartRemove=DCPC0141I: The application placement controller has removed server {0} from the failed start list. The original task ID was {1}.  {2}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The application placement controller has removed a server that originally did not start within the allotted time.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check the server operation timeout value that is specified in the application placement controller configuration. This value might need to be increased.  To change the value in the administrative console, click Operational Policies &gt; Autonomic Managers &gt; Application Placement Controller.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DCPC0302I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PC_ChangeBalance" varFormat="Java">
    PC_ChangeBalance=DCPC0302I: The application placement controller detected an imbalance in service level performance among service classes. Modify the placement of dynamic cluster instances to balance service level performance among the service classes that need additional resources: &quot;{1}&quot;, and those that can spare resources: &quot;{0}&quot;. Review the strategy for modifying the placement of dynamic cluster instances in the action plan.  The dynamic cluster operating mode is supervised.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The application placement controller has determined that there is a more optimal placement of dynamic cluster instances and has requested a placement change.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Review the action plan provided by the system and approve the proposed placement changes.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DCPC0304I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PC_ChangeMinMaxPolicy" varFormat="Java">
    PC_ChangeMinMaxPolicy=DCPC0304I: The application placement controller detected that these dynamic clusters &quot;{0}&quot; are not running the required number of dynamic cluster instances as specified in the configuration.  Modify the placement of dynamic cluster instances to ensure that the specified minimum and maximum number of instances is met. Review the strategy for modifying the placement of dynamic cluster instances in the action plan.  The dynamic cluster operating mode is supervised.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The minimum and maximum dynamic cluster instances is specified in the dynamic cluster configuration properties. The application placement controller compares the number of active instances against the configured values and requests placement changes if necessary.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Review the action plan provided by the system and approve the proposed placement changes.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DCPC0307I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PC_ChangeBalanceAut" varFormat="Java">
    PC_ChangeBalanceAut=DCPC0307I: The application placement controller detected an imbalance in service level performance among service classes. Modify the placement of dynamic cluster instances to balance service level performance among the service classes that need additional resources: &quot;{1}&quot;, and those that can spare resources: &quot;{0}&quot;. Review the strategy used to automatically modify the placement of dynamic cluster instances in the action plan.  The dynamic cluster operating mode is automatic.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The application placement controller has determined that there is a more optimal placement of dynamic cluster instances and has requested a placement change.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required. Placement changes have been initiated.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DCPC0318I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PC_ChangeIsolationAut" varFormat="Java">
    PC_ChangeIsolationAut=DCPC0318I: The application placement controller detected that these dynamic clusters &quot;{0}&quot; are in violation of a configured isolation policy. Review the strategy for automatically modifying the placement of dynamic cluster instances in the action plan.  The dynamic cluster operating mode is set to automatic.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The application placement controller detected that these dynamic clusters are in violation of a configured isolation policy. Review the strategy for automatically modifying the placement of dynamic cluster instances in the action plan.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required. Placement changes have been initiated.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DCPC0122I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PC_TaskDenied" varFormat="Java">
    PC_TaskDenied=DCPC0122I: The application placement controller has submitted a task that was denied.  The task ID is {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The application placement controller has submitted a task to the task management subsystem and the task was denied. If there is a reoccurrence of the conditions that originally caused the task to be generated, a new task will be generated.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DCPC0319I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PC_ChangeAllocation" varFormat="Java">
    PC_ChangeAllocation=DCPC0319I: The application placement controller detected that instances of dynamic cluster &quot;{0}&quot; are incorrectly running on a node. Review the strategy for modifying the placement of dynamic cluster instances in the action plan.  The dynamic cluster operating mode is set to supervised.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The application placement controller detected that instances of dynamic cluster are incorrectly running on a node. Review the strategy for modifying the placement of dynamic cluster instances in the action plan.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Review the action plan provided by the system and approve the proposed placement changes.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DCPC0126I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PC_TaskComplete" varFormat="Java">
    PC_TaskComplete=DCPC0126I: The application placement controller has completed a change for task ID {0}.  Outstanding changes remaining:{1}.  Outstanding tasks remaining:{2}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The application placement controller has been notified that a change has completed.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DCPC0012I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PC_RECOMPUTEI" varFormat="Java">
    PC_RECOMPUTEI=DCPC0012I: Extra placement computation has been initiated.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The application placement controller started an out-of-schedule placement cycle.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DCPC0014E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PC_BBFErr" varFormat="Java">
    PC_BBFErr=DCPC0014E: Unable to find bulletin board factory.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The application placement controller could not find the bulletin board factory.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If BBSON is enabled, verify that no TCP and UDP port conflicts exist.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DCPC0329I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PC_ChangeIdleStop" varFormat="Java">
    PC_ChangeIdleStop=DCPC0329I: The application placement controller detected that the following dynamic cluster configured for idle stop needs to be acted upon. &quot;{0}&quot;.  The dynamic cluster operating mode is set to supervised.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The application placement controller receives dynamic cluster activity information from the on demand router.  That information has changed such that deactivation is required.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Since the dynamic cluster operating mode is set to supervised, accept or reject the recommendation on the Task Management panel in the administrative console.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DCPC0315I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PC_ChangeLazyStartStop" varFormat="Java">
    PC_ChangeLazyStartStop=DCPC0315I: The application placement controller detected that the following dynamic cluster configured for lazy activation / deactivation needs to be acted upon because of recent activity or inactivity: &quot;{0}&quot;.  The dynamic cluster operating mode is set to supervised.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The application placement controller receives dynamic cluster activity information from the On Demand Router.  That information has changed such that activation / deactivation is required.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Review the action plan provided by the system and approve the proposed placement changes.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DCPC0328I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PC_ChangeLazyStopAut" varFormat="Java">
    PC_ChangeLazyStopAut=DCPC0328I: The application placement controller detected that the following dynamic cluster configured for lazy activation needs to be acted upon because of recent resource shortages. &quot;{0}&quot;.  The dynamic cluster operating mode is set to automatic.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The application placement controller receives dynamic cluster activity information from the on demand router.  That information has changed such that deactivation is required.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Since the dynamic cluster operating mode is set to automatic, no action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DCPC0125I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PC_TaskSource" varFormat="Java">
    PC_TaskSource=DCPC0125I: The application placement controller will submit tasks from the active location {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The application placement controller will submit tasks to the task management subsystem from the indicated cell/node/server.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DCPC0104E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PC_StartInstance_Err" varFormat="Java">
    PC_StartInstance_Err=DCPC0104E: Errors occurred during an attempt to start DynamicCluster={0}, Node={1}, Member={2} error={3}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The application placement controller was unable to communicate with the node agent on the specified node.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that the node agent process is started, and that there are no network connectivity issues.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DCPC0344I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DCPC0344" varFormat="Java">
    DCPC0344=DCPC0344I: The Application Placement Controller is suggesting to stop server {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Application Placement Controller determined that a server needs to be stopped.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Use the Admin Console Task Management panel to accept or deny the recommendation.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DCPC0343I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DCPC0343" varFormat="Java">
    DCPC0343=DCPC0343I: The Application Placement Controller is suggesting to start a server for cluster {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Application Placement Controller determined that a server needs to be started to meet requirements.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Use the Admin Console Task Management panel to accept or deny the recommendation.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DCPC0342I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DCPC0342" varFormat="Java">
    DCPC0342=DCPC0342I: The Application Placement Controller is suggesting to stop server {0} because it is on a host ({1}) with insufficient memory.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Application Placement Controller determined that a host does not have sufficient memory to run the specified server.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Use the Admin Console Task Management panel to accept or deny the recommendation.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DCPC0341I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DCPC0341" varFormat="Java">
    DCPC0341=DCPC0341I: Proactive idle stop is configured for a cluster and the Application Placement Controller is suggesting to stop server {0} because it has been inactive beyond the configured threshold for the cluster.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Application Placement Controller determined that a server needs to be stopped because it has been idle longer than the configured threshold.  The server is a member of a cluster with proactive idle stop enabled.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Use the Admin Console Task Management panel to accept or deny the recommendation.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DCPC0340I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DCPC0340" varFormat="Java">
    DCPC0340=DCPC0340I: The Application Placement Controller is suggesting an elasticity REMOVE to decrease the capacity of the topology.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Application Placement Controller detected that fewer resources are needed by the topology.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Use the Admin Console Task Management panel to accept or deny the recommendation.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DCPC0101E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PC_AP_STATUS_TIMEOUT_KEY" varFormat="Java">
    PC_AP_STATUS_TIMEOUT_KEY=DCPC0101E: The placement plan was not approved on time.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The placement plan sent for approval was not approved on time. The approval was ignored.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DCPC0124I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PC_TaskExpired" varFormat="Java">
    PC_TaskExpired=DCPC0124I: The application placement controller has submitted a task that has expired.  The task ID is {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The application placement controller has submitted a task to the task management subsystem and the task has expired.  If there is a reoccurrence of the conditions that originally caused the task to be generated, a new task will be generated.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DCPC0333I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PC_ChangeVMAddRemoveAut" varFormat="Java">
    PC_ChangeVMAddRemoveAut=DCPC0333I: The Application Placement Controller detected an action needs to be completed on cell &quot;{0}&quot; : &quot;{1}&quot; resources. Review the strategy used to automatically modify the placement of virtual machines in the action plan.  The elasticity mode is set to automatic mode.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Application Placement Controller determines if more resources are needed to minimize response time and meet service policy goals or resources can be removed and service policy goals will still be met.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required, placement changes have been initiated.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DCPC0135I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PC_VMChangeCommanCall" varFormat="Java">
    PC_VMChangeCommanCall=DCPC0135I: The Application Placement Controller has issued command {0} for task ID {1} on cell(s) {2} that will expire at {3}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Application Placement Controller is attempting to add or remove resources.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required at this time.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DCPC0107E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PC_TaskStatusSubmit_Err" varFormat="Java">
    PC_TaskStatusSubmit_Err=DCPC0107E: The following error occurred during an attempt to submit task status to the task controller: error={0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The application placement controller was unable to communicate with the deployment manager.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that the deployment manager is started, and that there are no network connectivity issues.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DCPC0046W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PC_GATE_CONNECT_FAIL" varFormat="Java">
    PC_GATE_CONNECT_FAIL=DCPC0046W: The application placement controller has not successfully connected to a remote controller  {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Another application placement controller is configured and the local controller was unable to connect to the remote controller.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Use parameter 0 as shown in the message, along with the FFDC log files, to debug the problem.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DCPC0339I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DCPC0339" varFormat="Java">
    DCPC0339=DCPC0339I: The Application Placement Controller is suggesting to stop server {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Application Placement Controller determined that a server needs to be stopped.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Use the Admin Console Task Management panel to accept or deny the recommendation.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DCPC0338I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DCPC0338" varFormat="Java">
    DCPC0338=DCPC0338I: The Application Placement Controller is suggesting to start a server for cluster {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Application Placement Controller determined that a server needs to be started for performance reasons.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Use the Admin Console Task Management panel to accept or deny the recommendation.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DCPC0337I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DCPC0337" varFormat="Java">
    DCPC0337=DCPC0337I: The Application Placement Controller is suggesting an elasticity ADD to increase the capacity of the topology.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Application Placement Controller detected that more resources are needed by the topology.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Use the Admin Console Task Management panel to accept or deny the recommendation.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DCPC0336I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DCPC0336" varFormat="Java">
    DCPC0336=DCPC0336I: The Application Placement Controller detected a change in demand for the cluster {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Application Placement Controller detected a change in demand for the specified cluster.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No actions are necessary.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DCPC0051E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PC_NOSOLUTIONErr" varFormat="Java">
    PC_NOSOLUTIONErr=DCPC0051E: The memory and CPU speed requirements cannot be met.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The application placement controller is unable to find a placement that satisfies all memory and CPU speed requirements.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Increase the node group capacity.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DCPC0335I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DCPC0335" varFormat="Java">
    DCPC0335=DCPC0335I: The Application Placement Controller is suggesting to start a server for {0} to meet the required number of running instances.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Application Placement Controller determined that a server needs to be started to meet the configured number of minimum instances.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Use the Admin Console Task Management panel to accept or deny the recommendation.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DCPC0402E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="LZ_DCStateNotFound" varFormat="Java">
    LZ_DCStateNotFound=DCPC0402E: The application lazy start controller could not locate and update the state of dynamic cluster {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The application lazy start controller attempted to update the state of the dynamic cluster but had no prior representation of that dynamic cluster.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DCPC0403I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="LZ_DCMinIdleTime" varFormat="Java">
    LZ_DCMinIdleTime=DCPC0403I: Dynamic cluster {0} can be deactivated if idle time exceeds {1} min.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The application lazy start controller will permit deactivation of the dynamic cluster if its idle time exceeds the specified time.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DCPC0399W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PC_NO_EXPLANATION" varFormat="Java">
    PC_NO_EXPLANATION=DCPC0399W: A placement change was caused by an unexplainable condition. Additional data={0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This warning message is generated when an unexplainable condition caused a placement change.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required. A placement change is pending or in progress.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DCPC0324I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PC_ChangeMaxAboveAut" varFormat="Java">
    PC_ChangeMaxAboveAut=DCPC0324I: The application placement controller detected that these dynamic clusters &quot;{0}&quot; are violating restrictions associated with collocation of long running jobs and transactional workloads. Review the strategy for automatically modifying the placement of dynamic cluster instances in the action plan.  The dynamic cluster operating mode is set to automatic.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The application placement controller detected that these dynamic clusters &quot;{0}&quot; are violating restrictions associated with collocation of long running jobs and transactional workloads. Review the strategy for automatically modifying the placement of dynamic cluster instances in the action plan.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required. Placement changes have been initiated.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DCPC0022I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PC_ELASTICITY_TIMEOUT" varFormat="Java">
    PC_ELASTICITY_TIMEOUT=DCPC0022I: The application placement controller set elasticity operation time out to {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DCPC0105E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PC_StopInstance_Err" varFormat="Java">
    PC_StopInstance_Err=DCPC0105E: Errors occurred during an attempt to start DynamicCluster={0}, Node={1}, Member={2} error={3}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The application placement controller was unable to communicate with the node agent on the specified node.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that the node agent process is started, and that there are no network connectivity issues.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DCPC0325I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PC_ChangeLazyStart" varFormat="Java">
    PC_ChangeLazyStart=DCPC0325I: The application placement controller detected that the following dynamic cluster configured for lazy activation needs to be acted upon because of recent activity. &quot;{0}&quot;.  The dynamic cluster operating mode is set to supervised.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The application placement controller receives dynamic cluster activity information from the on demand router.  That information has changed such that activation is required.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Since the dynamic cluster operating mode is set to supervised, accept or reject the recommendation on the Task Management panel in the administrative console.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DCPC0019I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PC_SERVER_NO_START_CONFIRMATION_KEY" varFormat="Java">
    PC_SERVER_NO_START_CONFIRMATION_KEY=DCPC0019I: The application placement controller has not received confirmation for server {0} starting on node {1} within the server operation timeout value specified in the application placement controller configuration.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The server failed to start or timed out while starting. The application placement controller will not attempt to restart the server until confirmation of a successful start is received, but will attempt to start other instances if appropriate.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Investigate and resolve any problems relating to the failed start attempt.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DCPC0143I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PC_MaintModeStatus2" varFormat="Java">
    PC_MaintModeStatus2=DCPC0143I: The application placement controller sent notification sequence {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A maintenance mode operation is in progress.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DCPC0131I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PC_DCConfigChanged" varFormat="Java">
    PC_DCConfigChanged=DCPC0131I: The application placement controller has detected a configuration change for dynamic cluster {0}.  PropertyName={1}  OldValue={2}  NewValue={3}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A request to change the configuration of the dynamic cluster has been submitted.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DCPC0020I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PC_ELASTICITY" varFormat="Java">
    PC_ELASTICITY=DCPC0020I: The application placement controller set elasticity to {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This message is for informational purposes only.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DCPC0323I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PC_ChangeMaxAbove" varFormat="Java">
    PC_ChangeMaxAbove=DCPC0323I: The application placement controller detected that these dynamic clusters &quot;{0}&quot; are violating restrictions associated with collocation of long running jobs and transactional workloads. Review the strategy for modifying the placement of dynamic cluster instances in the action plan.  The dynamic cluster operating mode is set to supervised.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The application placement controller detected that these dynamic clusters &quot;{0}&quot; are violating restrictions associated with collocation of long running jobs and transactional workloads. Review the strategy for modifying the placement of dynamic cluster instances in the action plan.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Review the action plan provided by the system and approve the proposed placement changes.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DCPC0136I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PC_VMChangeCommandReturn" varFormat="Java">
    PC_VMChangeCommandReturn=DCPC0136I: The Application Placement Controller has received status for command {0} for task ID {1} on cell(s) {2}. success={3}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Application Placement Controller is attempting to add or remove resources.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No user action is required at this time
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DCPC0013E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PC_BBFindErr" varFormat="Java">
    PC_BBFindErr=DCPC0013E: The bulletin board for {0} cannot be found. Error message is {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The application placement controller could not find the bulletin board.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If BBSON is enabled, verify that no TCP and UDP port conflicts exist.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DCPC0006E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PC_LoopErr" varFormat="Java">
    PC_LoopErr=DCPC0006E: The following error occurred during an attempt to complete the control loop: {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The application placement controller experiences an error while executing the control loop.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Contact IBM Support.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DCPC0103E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PC_AP_STATUS_ABORTED_KEY" varFormat="Java">
    PC_AP_STATUS_ABORTED_KEY=DCPC0103E: Placement will not be completed.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The approved placement plan cannot be completed.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DCPC0400I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="LZ_ActivateDC" varFormat="Java">
    LZ_ActivateDC=DCPC0400I: The application lazy start controller has detected activity for dynamic cluster {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The application lazy start controller detected incoming requests for the dynamic cluster and will start at least one server instance of this dynamic cluster.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required. Placement changes have been initiated.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DCPC0016E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PC_EXCEPTION" varFormat="Java">
    PC_EXCEPTION=DCPC0016E: Message = {0}. Stack Trace = {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    This error message is generated when an exception or an unexpected parameter value occurs within the application placement controller. It is generated to aid in problem diagnosis.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Contact IBM Support.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DCPC0128W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PC_FindBestNoVacancy" varFormat="Java">
    PC_FindBestNoVacancy=DCPC0128W: The application placement controller has been requested to find an alternate location to run server {0} and a replacement location is not available.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A request to shut down or set the maintenance mode of a server or node has been submitted.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Use the administrative console to modify the placement of the dynamic cluster instances to maintain the desired service level performance.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DCPC0017I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PC_SERVER_MM_KEY" varFormat="Java">
    PC_SERVER_MM_KEY=DCPC0017I: The application placement controller has set server {0} on node {1} into maintenance mode.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The server has been placed into maintenance mode. Typical causes are the server fails to start within the server operation timeout value that is specified in the application placement controller configuration.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Investigate and resolve any problems relating to the server starting, and remove the server from maintenance mode when corrected.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DCPC0316I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PC_ChangeLazyStartStopAut" varFormat="Java">
    PC_ChangeLazyStartStopAut=DCPC0316I: The application placement controller detected that the following dynamic cluster configured for lazy activation / deactivation needs to be acted upon because of recent activity or inactivity: &quot;{0}&quot;.  The dynamic cluster operating mode is set to automatic.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The application placement controller detected that the following dynamic cluster configured for lazy activation / deactivation needs to be acted upon because of recent activity or inactivity: &quot;{0}&quot;.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required. Placement changes have been initiated.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DCPC0312I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PC_ChangeNodeMemoryAut" varFormat="Java">
    PC_ChangeNodeMemoryAut=DCPC0312I: The application placement controller detected that memory utilization values exceed thresholds on nodes: &quot;{0}&quot;.  Modify the placement of dynamic cluster instances to balance memory usage among nodes. Review the strategy used to automatically modify the placement of dynamic cluster instances in the action plan.  The dynamic cluster operating mode is automatic.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The application placement controller senses and monitors total memory utilization and memory capacity on a node.  If the sum of memory consumed by all servers on a node exceeds the capacity of a node, application placement change is requested.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required. Placement changes have been initiated.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DCPC0327I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PC_ChangeLazyStop" varFormat="Java">
    PC_ChangeLazyStop=DCPC0327I: The application placement controller detected that the following dynamic cluster configured for lazy activation needs to be acted upon because of recent resource shortages. &quot;{0}&quot;.  The dynamic cluster operating mode is set to supervised.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The application placement controller receives dynamic cluster activity information from the on demand router.  That information has changed such that deactivation is required.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Since the dynamic cluster operating mode is set to supervised, accept or reject the recommendation on the Task Management panel in the administrative console.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DCPC0331I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PC_PLACEMAP_DUMP" varFormat="Java">
    PC_PLACEMAP_DUMP=DCPC0331I: The application placement controller {0} is {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The application placement controller has run and information about the input and output has been logged.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DCPC0123I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PC_TaskApproved" varFormat="Java">
    PC_TaskApproved=DCPC0123I: The application placement controller has received approval for task ID {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The application placement controller has received user approval for a previously submitted task.  The task will be completed.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DCPC0301I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PC_ChangeGoal" varFormat="Java">
    PC_ChangeGoal=DCPC0301I: The application placement controller detected that service policy goals have been or soon will be breached for these service classes: &quot;{0}&quot;.  Modify the placement of dynamic cluster instances to maintain desired service level performance. Review the strategy for modifying the placement of dynamic cluster instances in the action plan.  The dynamic cluster operating mode is supervised.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The application placement controller has requested placement changes in order to maintain service levels for the specified service classes.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Review the action plan provided by the system and approve the proposed placement changes.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DCPC0150I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PC_StateChange" varFormat="Java">
    PC_StateChange=DCPC0150I: The application placement controller detected a resource state change.  Resource={0}  State={1}  {2}  {3}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A resource has been detected as maintenance, started, stopped, added, or removed.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DCPC0011I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PC_Config3I" varFormat="Java">
    PC_Config3I=DCPC0011I: The approvalTimeout value has been set to {0} min.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A configuration setting for the application placement controller has been changed.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DCPC0130I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PC_FindBestNotNeeded" varFormat="Java">
    PC_FindBestNotNeeded=DCPC0130I: The application placement controller has been requested to find an alternate location to run server {0} and a replacement location is not needed.  The server can be stopped or placed into maintenance mode.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A request to shut down or set the maintenance mode of a server or node has been submitted.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Use the administrative console to modify the placement of the dynamic cluster instances to maintain the desired service level performance.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DCPC0018I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PC_SERVER_UNMM_KEY" varFormat="Java">
    PC_SERVER_UNMM_KEY=DCPC0018I: The application placement controller has taken server {0} on node {1} out of maintenance mode.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The application placement controller has detected that the server was started in maintenance mode after it previously failed to start.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DCPC0317I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PC_ChangeIsolation" varFormat="Java">
    PC_ChangeIsolation=DCPC0317I: The application placement controller detected that these dynamic clusters &quot;{0}&quot; are in violation of a configured isolation policy. Review the strategy for modifying the placement of dynamic cluster instances in the action plan.  The dynamic cluster operating mode is set to supervised.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The application placement controller detected that these dynamic clusters are in violation of a configured isolation policy. Review the strategy for modifying the placement of dynamic cluster instances in the action plan.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Review the action plan provided by the system and approve the proposed placement changes.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="DCPC0010I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PC_Config2I" varFormat="Java">
    PC_Config2I=DCPC0010I: The serverStateChangeTimeout value has been set to {0} min.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A configuration setting for the application placement controller has been changed.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<!-- END MESSAGES -->
</TMSSource>
