<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/css" href="../../resources/stylesheets/wasmsgxml.css"?>
<TMSSource name="TivoliMessages" tmsVersion="1.0" xml:lang="en">
<!-- CMVC MSG File Name = /com.ibm.ws.eba.bla/src/com/ibm/ws/eba/bla/nls/Messages.nlsprops -->
<!-- DO NOT EDIT THIS FILE - This file was generated by the XML/Html & Property emitter -->
<!-- BEGIN MESSAGES -->
<Message ID="CWSAL0063E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SUSPECTED_CIRCULAR_DEPENDENCIES" varFormat="Java">
    SUSPECTED_CIRCULAR_DEPENDENCIES=CWSAL0063E: Resolution of asset {0} indicates invalid dependencies of shared content on application content: {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Application bundles cannot provide packages or services to shared bundles. Furthermore, bundles are not allowed to be deployed both as shared and application bundles. Any deployment that requires shared bundles that depend on application bundles is not valid.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check that all the invalid shared bundles are needed by the application. If so, ensure that they do not depend on application content.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0006E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="EXCEPTION_READING_JAR_RESOURCE" varFormat="Java">
    EXCEPTION_READING_JAR_RESOURCE=CWSAL0006E: Cannot read the bundle manifest for the JAR file {0} in the EBA file {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An IOException occurred when locating the manifest of a JAR file in an enterprise bundle archive (EBA) file. The file might be corrupt or unreadable.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check that the file has the appropriate permissions and that it is in the correct format.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0017E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PROVISIONER_SERVICE_UNAVAILABLE" varFormat="Java">
    PROVISIONER_SERVICE_UNAVAILABLE=CWSAL0017E: An internal error has occurred. The provisioner service {0} is unavailable.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    CMSG0001
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    CMSG0002
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0078E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="APP_START_FAILED" varFormat="Java">
    APP_START_FAILED=CWSAL0078E: The OSGi application deployed in composition unit {0} in business-level application {1} did not start.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An exception occurred during the start operation.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Inspect the server logs prior to this exception for more specific problem diagnostics.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0061E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="FORBIDDEN_ROOT_ENTRY" varFormat="Java">
    FORBIDDEN_ROOT_ENTRY=CWSAL0061E: enterprise bundle archive (EBA) file {1} contains directory {0}, which is not supported.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified EBA file contains a directory called byValue, or byReference. Neither of these directory names are supported in the root directory of an EBA file.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Either remove or rename the relevant directory.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0040E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_ROLE" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_ROLE=CWSAL0040E: The specified role {0} does not exist.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Attempted to map users or groups to a security role that does not exist.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check that the specified security role exists, or create the role in the application.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0067E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DEPLOYMENT_MF_DOES_NOT_MEET_REQS" varFormat="Java">
    DEPLOYMENT_MF_DOES_NOT_MEET_REQS=CWSAL0067E: The deployment manifest to import is not valid for the asset {0} because it does not meet the requirements in the application manifest.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The deployment manifest, DEPLOYMENT.MF, is not compatible with the application manifest, APPLICATION.MF, of the asset.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check the new deployment manifest for the following:
   1. The Application-SymbolicName and Application-Version in the DEPLOYMENT.MF file must match the corresponding entries in the APPLICATION.MF file.
   2. The bundles listed in the Deployed-Content header in the DEPLOYMENT.MF file must match the bundles listed in the Application-Content header in the APPLICATION.MF file.
   3. The bundle version in the Deployed-Content header in the DEPLOYMENT.MF file must be within the version range for the corresponding bundle in the APPLICATION.MF file.
   4. The bundles listed in the Deployed-Use-Bundle header in the DEPLOYMENT.MF file must also be listed in the Use-Bundle header in the APPLICATION.MF file.
   5. The bundle version in the Deployed-Use-Bundle header in the DEPLOYMENT.MF file must be within the version range for the corresponding bundle in the Use-Bundle header in the APPLICATION.MF file.
 Do not manually edit the deployment manifest. If necessary, remove the deployment manifest from the EBA. This will cause a fresh deployment manifest file to be generated when the EBA is imported.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0031E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="UPDATE_RESOLVE_FAILED" varFormat="Java">
    UPDATE_RESOLVE_FAILED=CWSAL0031E: The selected bundle versions cannot be resolved or are not compatible.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The system cannot resolve the selected bundle versions. The bundles might have missing dependencies, be incompatible, or not exist.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Modify the selected set of input bundles and try again. You can use the administrative console to view or preview the status of the asset.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0084E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="USER_NOT_IN_ROLE" varFormat="Java">
    USER_NOT_IN_ROLE=CWSAL0084E: The user {0}, is not a mapped user or a member of a mapped group for role {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Any specified user must either be a mapped user on the security role or be a member of a mapped group on the security role. The specified user did not meet either of these requirements.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Either configure the security role to user/group mappings to permit the specified user to act in the specified role, or specify a different user that already has the required permissions.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0097W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CBA_IN_APP_CONTENT_MIXED_VERSION" varFormat="Java">
    CBA_IN_APP_CONTENT_MIXED_VERSION=CWSAL0097W: The application {0} contains one or more composite bundle archives (CBAs) {1} in its Application-Content. This is not supported on the WebSphere Application Server Version 7 OSGi Applications Feature Pack.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    CBAs are supported in Application-Content for WebSphere Application Server Version 8 and later versions.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required. If the application must run on the WebSphere Application Server Version 7 OSGi Applications Feature Pack, rewrite the application so that there are no CBAs in Application-Content.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0002E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="EXCEPTION_READING_APP_MANIFEST" varFormat="Java">
    EXCEPTION_READING_APP_MANIFEST=CWSAL0002E: An IOException occurred when reading the application manifest file of the enterprise bundle archive (EBA) {0}. The file might be invalid, corrupted or unreadable.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An IOException occurred when reading an enterprise bundle archive (EBA) application manifest file. The file might be invalid, corrupted or unreadable.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check that the application manifest file, APPLICATION.MF, follows the specification for manifest files.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0033E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_PLUGIN_CONFIG_FILE_URI" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_PLUGIN_CONFIG_FILE_URI=CWSAL0033E: An internal error has occurred. Plugin Config File URI is not the expected format {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    CMSG0001
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    CMSG0002
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0016E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PROVISIONING_WRONG_VERSION_EXCEPTION" varFormat="Java">
    PROVISIONING_WRONG_VERSION_EXCEPTION=CWSAL0016E: An internal error has occurred. An incorrect result was returned during provisioning of the enterprise bundle archive (EBA) file {0}, the maximum version {1} was expected to be the same as the minimum version {2}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    CMSG0001
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    CMSG0002
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0095W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="RESOLUTION_FAILURE_V8_MIXED_VERSION" varFormat="Java">
    RESOLUTION_FAILURE_V8_MIXED_VERSION=CWSAL0095W: The application {0} could not be provisioned for all nodes in the cell. The application can only be deployed on Version 7 nodes that are running the OSGi Applications Feature Pack. The resolution error was {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The application being imported was successfully provisioned against the WebSphere Application Server Version 7 OSGi Applications Feature Pack, but could not be provisioned against WebSphere Application Server Version 8.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required. However, this warning indicates that the application might contain an overly strict version requirement. You can use the information in the resolution error to help you modify the application so that it can be deployed against Version 8 nodes.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0101E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADD_CLUSTER_MEMBER_RUN_AS_ROLE_MIXED_VERSION" varFormat="Java">
    ADD_CLUSTER_MEMBER_RUN_AS_ROLE_MIXED_VERSION=CWSAL0101E: A cluster member cannot be created on the node {0} because the OSGi application(s) {1} define Run As Roles.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    All cluster members must be able to run the same applications, but the new cluster member cannot support OSGi applications with Run As Roles defined.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Select a Version 8 node to host the cluster member, or modify the application(s) configuration so that they no longer define Run As Roles.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0082E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="APP_NAME_MATCHES_CONTENT" varFormat="Java">
    APP_NAME_MATCHES_CONTENT=CWSAL0082E: The deployment manifest for the application {0} at version {1} lists content with the same symbolic name and version as the application.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Applications, bundles and composite bundles all share the same namespace, so they must have unique identifiers within the namespace. When validating the application deployment, the runtime environment found a reference to a bundle with the same symbolic name and version as the application.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the symbolic name of the bundle, composite bundle or application so that there is no longer a clash in the namespace.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0048E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_PACKAGE_REQUIREMENT_ATTRIBUTES" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_PACKAGE_REQUIREMENT_ATTRIBUTES=CWSAL0048E: The asset {0} cannot be resolved. The attribute {1} on an import for package {2} cannot be satisfied at deployment.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    For bundles listed in the Application-Content header in APPLICATION.MF, all package imports must have attributes that can be satisfied at deployment.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Change the packaging or configuration of the application so that all bundles that are listed in the Application-Content header have package imports that can be satisfied at deployment.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0056E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="UNABLE_TO_LOCATE_EXPANSION_LOCATION" varFormat="Java">
    UNABLE_TO_LOCATE_EXPANSION_LOCATION=CWSAL0056E: An internal error occurred. Unable to locate the configuration data needed to expand {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    CMSG0001
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    CMSG0002
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0126E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MODELLER_EXCEPTION_DEPLOYING_BUNDLE" varFormat="Java">
    MODELLER_EXCEPTION_DEPLOYING_BUNDLE=CWSAL0126E: An exception occurred while modelling bundle {0}: {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified exception occurred while modelling the specified bundle.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Study the specified exception for details of the problem, and fix the issue.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0034E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="UNABLE_TO_READ_WEB_XML" varFormat="Java">
    UNABLE_TO_READ_WEB_XML=CWSAL0034E: An internal error has occurred. Unable to get the InputStream for web.xml zip Entry in War {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    CMSG0001
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    CMSG0002
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0124W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_MDB_LISTENER_AUTHALIAS_REFERENCE" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_MDB_LISTENER_AUTHALIAS_REFERENCE=CWSAL0124W: No MDB Listener Auth Alias that matches the name {0} could be found on the target {1} for the resource used by bean {2} in bundle {3} at version {4}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified Auth Alias does not exist, or is not visible to this application.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Please configure the required Auth Alias, or ensure it is configured in the correct scope for the application.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0044E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="UNSATISFIED_CIRCULAR_SERVICE_DEPENDENCY" varFormat="Java">
    UNSATISFIED_CIRCULAR_SERVICE_DEPENDENCY=CWSAL0044E: The asset {0} cannot be resolved. It requires the bundle {1}, which is not listed in the Application-Content header in the application manifest, APPLICATION.MF. This bundle consumes the service {2} from bundle {3}, which is listed in the Application-Content header.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The application is not correctly configured. A shared bundle cannot consume a service from an isolated bundle. Bundles that are listed in the Application-Content header are isolated and can export services only to other applications through the Application-ExportService mechanism.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Change the packaging or configuration of the application so that bundles that are listed in the Use-Bundle header, or added by the resolver, do not require services that are provided by bundles that are listed in the Application-Content header.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0037W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="BUNDLE_DOWNLOAD_REQUESTED" varFormat="Java">
    BUNDLE_DOWNLOAD_REQUESTED=CWSAL0037W: The asset {0} requires external downloads before it can be deployed to a composition unit.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The new or updated asset requires one or more bundles to be downloaded from a repository before it can be added to a composition unit or updated in a composition unit.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    To start the bundle download process, save your changes to the master configuration. You can view the bundle download status of the asset from the asset detail panel in the administrative console. After the bundle downloads are complete, try again to add or update the asset in a composition unit.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0010E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="COULD_NOT_CONVERT_WAR" varFormat="Java">
    COULD_NOT_CONVERT_WAR=CWSAL0010E: Conversion of the WAR file {0} in EBA file {1} to a WAB file did not complete successfully.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Web application archive (WAR) files in an enterprise bundle archive (EBA) must be converted to web application bundles (WABs) before they can be deployed. The conversion process did not complete successfully.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check that the WAR file is valid.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0076E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="REPOSITORY_ADMIN_SUPPORT_UNAVAILABLE" varFormat="Java">
    REPOSITORY_ADMIN_SUPPORT_UNAVAILABLE=CWSAL0076E: An internal error occurred. The RepositoryAdminSupport service is not available from the OSGi service registry.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    CMSG0001
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    CMSG0002
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0024E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ALIAS_IN_INVALID_DOMAIN" varFormat="Java">
    ALIAS_IN_INVALID_DOMAIN=CWSAL0024E: Authentication alias {0} does not exist in the security domain {2} of the target {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An authentication alias must exist in the global or target security domain when Blueprint resource references are bound.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Select an authentication alias that exists in the global or target security domain, or create a suitable authentication alias.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0100E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADD_CLUSTER_MEMBER_CBA_FAILURE_MIXED_VERSION" varFormat="Java">
    ADD_CLUSTER_MEMBER_CBA_FAILURE_MIXED_VERSION=CWSAL0100E: A cluster member cannot be created on the node {0} because the OSGi application(s) {1} contain composite bundle archives (CBAs) in Application-Content.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    All cluster members must be able to run the same applications, but the new cluster member cannot support OSGi applications with CBAs in Application-Content.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Select a Version 8 node to host the cluster member, or modify the application(s) so that they no longer contain CBAs in Application-Content.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0091E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="NOT_AN_EBA_CU" varFormat="Java">
    NOT_AN_EBA_CU=CWSAL0091E: The composition unit {0} does not correspond to an OSGi application.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The invoked operation operates on a composition unit for an OSGi application. The selected composition unit does not contain an OSGi application.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check that the selected composition unit is backed by an asset with type aspect &quot;EBA,version=1.0&quot;.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0032E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DEPLOYMENT_MANIFEST_MISSING" varFormat="Java">
    DEPLOYMENT_MANIFEST_MISSING=CWSAL0032E: An internal error occurred. Could not extract the deployment manifest from the asset binary {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    CMSG0001
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    CMSG0002
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0074E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MODELLED_RESOURCE_MANAGER_UNAVAILABLE" varFormat="Java">
    MODELLED_RESOURCE_MANAGER_UNAVAILABLE=CWSAL0074E: An internal error occurred. The ModelledResourceManager service is not available from the OSGi service registry.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    CMSG0001
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    CMSG0002
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0125E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CBA_BUNDLE_ASSET_NOT_SUPPORTED" varFormat="Java">
    CBA_BUNDLE_ASSET_NOT_SUPPORTED=CWSAL0125E: An internal error occurred. The CBA bundle {0} at version {1} cannot be modelled.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    CMSG0001
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    CMSG0002
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0008W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="NO_APPLICATION_XML" varFormat="Java">
    NO_APPLICATION_XML=CWSAL0008W: The Java EE application descriptor file was not found in EBA file {0}. Without this descriptor file, context roots for WAR files are set to default values.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The system processed a web application archive (WAR) without an associated application descriptor file, application.xml, which defines context roots. Context roots for the migrated WAR file will be set to default values.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If an application descriptor file is required, check that it is provided and correctly packaged into the enterprise bundle archive (EBA) file.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0064E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="UNABLE_TO_OPEN_DEPLOYMENT_MANIFEST" varFormat="Java">
    UNABLE_TO_OPEN_DEPLOYMENT_MANIFEST=CWSAL0064E: Unable to process the deployment manifest file that was provided by the application from this location {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An attempt was made to import an EBA that contains a deployment manifest file. The processing of this file did not succeed.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check that the application server has permission to access the file and check the file is not corrupted. Do not manually edit the deployment manifest. If necessary, remove the deployment manifest from the EBA. This causes a fresh deployment manifest file to be generated when the EBA is imported.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0093E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SERVICE_UNAVAILABLE" varFormat="Java">
    SERVICE_UNAVAILABLE=CWSAL0093E: An internal error occurred. The {0} service is not available from the OSGi service registry.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    CMSG0001
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    CMSG0002
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0030E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="AJPS_COULD_NOT_CREATE_DIR" varFormat="Java">
    AJPS_COULD_NOT_CREATE_DIR=CWSAL0030E: Cannot create the directory {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified directory cannot be created.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check that storage space exists, and that the product has the necessary permissions to create the directory.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0115E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_MODULE_TYPE" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_MODULE_TYPE=CWSAL0115E: An internal error occurred. The module {0} was of an unexpected type.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    CMSG0001
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    CMSG0002
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0014E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ERRORS_DURING_TRANSFORMATION" varFormat="Java">
    ERRORS_DURING_TRANSFORMATION=CWSAL0014E: EBA file {0} installed with errors.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The validation and installation of the enterprise bundle archive (EBA) file completed with errors.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See the accompanying error messages in the SystemOut.log file for further information.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0116E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="EJB_DEFAULT_BINDING_IMPOSSIBLE" varFormat="Java">
    EJB_DEFAULT_BINDING_IMPOSSIBLE=CWSAL0116E: No default binding could be created for EJB reference {0} in bundle {1} at version {2} with interface {3} since no matching enterprise beans exist in the application.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Default bindings must be created for unbound EJB references. No enterprise bean could be found to which to bind this reference.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Either bind the reference to a known JNDI location, or correct the application.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0130E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ENV_ENTRY_BAD_VALUE" varFormat="Java">
    ENV_ENTRY_BAD_VALUE=CWSAL0130E: Environment entry {0} for EJB {1} in bundle with name {2} and version {3} has invalid value {4} for type {5}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The value specified for the indicated environment entry is not valid.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a valid value for the indicated environment entry.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0083E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ASSET_IN_NOT_FOUND" varFormat="Java">
    ASSET_IN_NOT_FOUND=CWSAL0083E: An internal error has occurred. Cannot find the config asset object for asset {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    CMSG0001
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    CMSG0002
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0131E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ENV_ENTRY_BAD_EMPTY_STRING_VALUE" varFormat="Java">
    ENV_ENTRY_BAD_EMPTY_STRING_VALUE=CWSAL0131E: Environment entry {0} for EJB {1} in bundle with name {2} and version {3} has invalid empty string value for type {4}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The value specified for the indicated environment entry is not valid.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a valid value for the indicated environment entry.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0114E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="NO_EJB_RESOURCE_REFERENCE" varFormat="Java">
    NO_EJB_RESOURCE_REFERENCE=CWSAL0114E: Cannot find the resource reference with JNDI name {0} and type {1} on the target {2} for the EJB resource reference {3} defined in bundle {4} with version {5}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An enterprise bundle archive (EBA) that includes resource references in an EJB module specifies a JNDI name for a resource reference that does not exist in the JNDI namespace.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the resource reference should be in the JNDI namespace, either bind an object to the name, or correct the resource reference and update the EBA.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0079E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="APP_STOP_FAILED" varFormat="Java">
    APP_STOP_FAILED=CWSAL0079E: The OSGi application deployed in composition unit {0} in business-level application {1} did not stop.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An exception occurred during the stop operation.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Inspect the server logs prior to this exception for more specific problem diagnostics.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0085E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_RUNAS_ROLE" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_RUNAS_ROLE=CWSAL0085E: The role {0}, is not a valid role.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified role has not been configured.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Configure the specified role.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0052E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="UNAUGMENTED_CLUSTER_MEMBER" varFormat="Java">
    UNAUGMENTED_CLUSTER_MEMBER=CWSAL0052E: The cluster member {0} is not augmented with the features, {2}, required by the OSGi application {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    In order for an OSGi application to be installed on a cluster, every member of the cluster needs to have all the required features of the application. When adding a new cluster member, that member also needs to have all the features required by all the OSGi applications that are installed on the cluster.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check that the proposed member of the cluster has all the required features for the OSGi application listed in the error message.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0028E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="BPRRBS_COULD_NOT_CREATE_DIR" varFormat="Java">
    BPRRBS_COULD_NOT_CREATE_DIR=CWSAL0028E: Cannot create the directory {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified directory cannot be created.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check that storage space exists, and that the product has the necessary permissions to create the directory.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0068E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DEPLOYMENT_MF_CONTAINS_REDUNDANCY" varFormat="Java">
    DEPLOYMENT_MF_CONTAINS_REDUNDANCY=CWSAL0068E: The deployment manifest content is not correct. The following bundles are redundant: {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The deployment manifest to import includes bundles that are not needed to resolve the enterprise bundle archive (EBA) asset.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check that the new deployment manifest, DEPLOYMENT.MF, does not include the bundles that are listed in the exception message. Do not manually edit the deployment manifest. If necessary, remove the deployment manifest from the EBA. This will cause a fresh deployment manifest file to be generated when the EBA is imported.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0042E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_GROUP" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_GROUP=CWSAL0042E: The specified group {0} is not valid.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Attempted to map a security role to a group that is not valid.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check that the specified group exists.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0128E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ENV_ENTRY_NO_VALUE_OR_LOOKUP_NAME" varFormat="Java">
    ENV_ENTRY_NO_VALUE_OR_LOOKUP_NAME=CWSAL0128E: Environment entry {0} for EJB {1} in bundle with name {2} and version {3} does not have a value or lookup-name specified.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Either a value or a lookup-name for the indicated environment entry must be specified.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a value or lookup-name for the indicated environment entry.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0088E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="UNABLE_TO_LOOKUP_ADMIN_SERVICE" varFormat="Java">
    UNABLE_TO_LOOKUP_ADMIN_SERVICE=CWSAL0088E: An internal error has occurred. The Admin Service has not been registered.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    CMSG0001
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    CMSG0002
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0089W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CU_BUNDLE_DOWNLOAD_REQUESTED" varFormat="Java">
    CU_BUNDLE_DOWNLOAD_REQUESTED=CWSAL0089W: An extension to the composition unit {0} requires external downloads.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    You created or updated a composite bundle archive (CBA) to use as an extension to a composition unit. This extension requires one or more bundles to download from a repository before you can add the extension to the composition unit.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    To start the download process, save your changes to the master configuration.  You can view the bundle download status from the composition unit detail panel in the administrative console. Wait for the bundle download to complete, then add the extension to the composition unit.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0049E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="NO_SERVERS_AVAIL" varFormat="Java">
    NO_SERVERS_AVAIL=CWSAL0049E: None of the servers or clusters has the required feature {0} deployed for the asset {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The required feature could not be found on any of the servers.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Install the required feature on at least one of the servers.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0026E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MISSING_BUNDLES" varFormat="Java">
    MISSING_BUNDLES=CWSAL0026E: An internal error has occurred. The enterprise bundle archive (EBA) file {0} is missing the following bundles: {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    CMSG0001
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    CMSG0002
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0039E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MULTIPLE_CUS_WITH_THE_SAME_ASSET" varFormat="Java">
    MULTIPLE_CUS_WITH_THE_SAME_ASSET=CWSAL0039E: Cannot add the asset {0} to this business-level application because it is already added to the business level application: {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An enterprise bundle archive (EBA) asset can be in only a single business-level application (BLA).
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Create a new application with the same content but with a different application symbolic name. Import the new application as an EBA asset, then add it to this BLA.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0096W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="RESOLUTION_INCONSISTENT_MIXED_VERSION" varFormat="Java">
    RESOLUTION_INCONSISTENT_MIXED_VERSION=CWSAL0096W: Provisioning the application {0} produced different results for WebSphere Application Server Version 8 and the WebSphere Application Server Version 7 OSGi Applications Feature Pack. The Version 8 result will be used.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The application being imported was successfully provisioned against WebSphere Application Server Version 8 and the WebSphere Application Server Version 7 OSGi Applications Feature Pack. However, different results were obtained for the two provisioning operations. You cannot run the same application with different deployments.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0054I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="NEW_DIRECTORY_MAPPING" varFormat="Java">
    NEW_DIRECTORY_MAPPING=CWSAL0054I: {1} has been assigned to the directory {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An enterprise bundle archive (EBA) asset is being added to a composition unit. To set up the web application contained in the EBA, a directory has been assigned to the web application.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    None
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0004E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="NO_APPLICATION_MANIFEST_DURING_RESOLVE" varFormat="Java">
    NO_APPLICATION_MANIFEST_DURING_RESOLVE=CWSAL0004E: An internal error has occurred. Cannot read the application manifest or deployment manifest for the enterprise bundle archive (EBA) file {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    CMSG0001
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    CMSG0002
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0020E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="STEP_NOT_FOUND" varFormat="Java">
    STEP_NOT_FOUND=CWSAL0020E: An internal error has occurred. The step {0} cannot be found.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    CMSG0001
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    CMSG0002
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0038W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="UNCONVERTIBLE_JAR_FILE" varFormat="Java">
    UNCONVERTIBLE_JAR_FILE=CWSAL0038W: The asset {0} contains a JAR file {1} that is not a bundle and that will not be converted. If other parts of the application depend on this file, the application will fail at run time.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Conversion of utility Java archive (JAR) files and Enterprise JavaBeans (EJB) JAR files is not supported.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check that no bundle or web application bundle (WAB) depends on classes from the JAR file. To avoid the warning message, remove the JAR file from the enterprise bundle archive (EBA).
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0005E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="NO_APPLICATION_MANIFEST_DURING_DETAILS" varFormat="Java">
    NO_APPLICATION_MANIFEST_DURING_DETAILS=CWSAL0005E: An internal error has occurred. Cannot read the application manifest or deployment manifest for the enterprise bundle archive (EBA) file {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    CMSG0001
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    CMSG0002
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0110E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="EJB_MAPPING_NAMESPACE_ERROR" varFormat="Java">
    EJB_MAPPING_NAMESPACE_ERROR=CWSAL0110E: The EJB interface {0} for enterprise bean {1} in Bundle {2} at version {3} cannot be bound to the location {4}. Locally accessible EJB interfaces must be bound into the ejblocal: namespace.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Local, &quot;No Interface&quot; and &quot;Local Home&quot; views of an enterprise bean can be bound only into locally acessible JNDI. This means that their binding names must start with &quot;ejblocal:&quot;.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Adjust the binding names for any locally accessible EJB views so that they use the ejblocal: namespace prefix.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0077E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="NO_APPLICABLE_UPDATES_AVAILABLE" varFormat="Java">
    NO_APPLICABLE_UPDATES_AVAILABLE=CWSAL0077E: The CompUnitStatusStep indicates that the composition unit {0} should be upgraded to the latest deployment version available from asset {1}. However, the composition unit {0} is up-to-date.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Before you can upgrade the asset deployed within a composition unit, an updated version of the asset must be available and all bundles required by the updated asset must have finished downloading.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check that a later version of the asset is available, and that all bundle downloads for the asset have completed.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0055E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="UNABLE_TO_OBTAIN_CU" varFormat="Java">
    UNABLE_TO_OBTAIN_CU=CWSAL0055E: An internal error occurred. Unable to obtain composition unit for asset {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    CMSG0001
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    CMSG0002
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0099E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADD_CLUSTER_MEMBER_EXTENSION_FAILURE_MIXED_VERSION" varFormat="Java">
    ADD_CLUSTER_MEMBER_EXTENSION_FAILURE_MIXED_VERSION=CWSAL0099E: A cluster member cannot be created on the node {0} because the OSGi application(s) {1} have been extended.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    All cluster members must be able to run the same applications, but the new cluster member cannot support OSGi application extensions.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Select a Version 8 node to host the cluster member, or remove the extension(s) from the application(s) so that they can be run using the selected node.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0109E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="UPDATE_EXTENSION_CONFLICT" varFormat="Java">
    UPDATE_EXTENSION_CONFLICT=CWSAL0109E: The bundle {0} in Composition Unit {1} could not be updated as there is a conflicting extension with the same symbolic name.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    It is not possible to update a cba bundle to the requested version as there is already an extension present with the same symbolic name at that version.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Either remove the extension, or modify the bundle version you are attempting to update to.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0129E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ENV_ENTRY_BAD_TYPE" varFormat="Java">
    ENV_ENTRY_BAD_TYPE=CWSAL0129E: Environment entry {0} for EJB {1} in bundle with name {2} and version {3} has invalid type {4}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The type specified for the indicated environment entry is not valid.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a valid type for the indicated environment entry.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0121W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_MDB_ACTSPEC_REFERENCE" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_MDB_ACTSPEC_REFERENCE=CWSAL0121W: No MDB Activation Spec that matches the JNDI name {0} could be found on the target {1} for the resource used by bean {2} in bundle {3} at version {4}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified MDB Listener binding Activation Spec reference JNDI name does not exist.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the reference should be in the JNDI namespace, either bind an object to the name, or correct the reference and update the EBA.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0092E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="UNABLE_TO_LOCATE_TYPE" varFormat="Java">
    UNABLE_TO_LOCATE_TYPE=CWSAL0092E: An internal error occurred. The asset {0} could not be queried for content.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    CMSG0001
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    CMSG0002
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0073E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CBA_IN_APPLICATION_CONTENT" varFormat="Java">
    CBA_IN_APPLICATION_CONTENT=CWSAL0073E: The application {0} includes a composite bundle {1} in its application content. This is not supported.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    You cannot use the Application-Content header to include composite bundle archives directly in an EBA.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Remove the composite bundle from the application content. You can either include the individual bundles in the Application-Content or install the composite bundle into a bundle repository for sharing.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0027E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INCORRECT_BUNDLE_IN_CACHE" varFormat="Java">
    INCORRECT_BUNDLE_IN_CACHE=CWSAL0027E: An internal error has occurred. A file with the correct name exists in the bundle cache, but it does not contain the expected bundle {0}/{1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    CMSG0001
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    CMSG0002
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0113E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="NO_EJB_MSG_DEST_REFERENCE" varFormat="Java">
    NO_EJB_MSG_DEST_REFERENCE=CWSAL0113E: Cannot find the message destination reference or resource environment reference with JNDI name {0} and type {1} on the target {2} for the EJB message destination reference or resource environment reference {3} defined in bundle {4} with version {5}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An enterprise bundle archive (EBA) that includes message destination references or resource environment references in an EJB module specifies a JNDI name for a message destination reference or resource environment reference that does not exist in the JNDI namespace.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the message destination reference or resource environment reference should be in the JNDI namespace, either bind an object to the name, or correct the message destination reference or resource environment reference and update the EBA.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0119E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DOTDOT_ILLEGAL_IN_APP_NAME" varFormat="Java">
    DOTDOT_ILLEGAL_IN_APP_NAME=CWSAL0119E: The OSGi application {0} is not valid because its symbolic name contains two consecutive period characters.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An OSGi application symbolic name cannot contain the string &quot;..&quot;; that is, two consecutive period characters.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Change the symbolic name of the OSGi application.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0007E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="EXCEPTION_READING_ZIP" varFormat="Java">
    EXCEPTION_READING_ZIP=CWSAL0007E: Cannot read the EBA file {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An IOException occurred when reading an enterprise bundle archive (EBA) file. The file might be corrupt or unreadable.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check that the file has the appropriate permissions and that it is in the correct format.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0087E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="UNABLE_TO_LOOKUP_ADMIN_MBEAN" varFormat="Java">
    UNABLE_TO_LOOKUP_ADMIN_MBEAN=CWSAL0087E: An internal error has occurred. The SecurityAdmin MBean has not been registered.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    CMSG0001
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    CMSG0002
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0105W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CBA_WITH_MISSING_SERVICE_IMPORTS" varFormat="Java">
    CBA_WITH_MISSING_SERVICE_IMPORTS=CWSAL0105W: Service references in the contents of the Composite Bundle Archive (CBA) {0} cannot be resolved. If these services are provided by bundles that are not included in the CBA, then the CBA must import them. The following service dependencies were unresolved: {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    If a bundle in a  Composite Bundle Archive (CBA) uses a service that is not contained in the bundle, or exported by another bundle within the CBA, then the CBA must import the service.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the composite manifest, COMPOSITEBUNDLE.MF, so that the CBA imports any services that are used by bundles in the CBA and not otherwise available within the CBA.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0001E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="EXCEPTION_WHILE_WRITING_EBA" varFormat="Java">
    EXCEPTION_WHILE_WRITING_EBA=CWSAL0001E: Cannot write the migrated EBA file {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An IOException occurred when writing a migrated enterprise bundle archive (EBA) file.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check that the product has the necessary permissions to write to the relevant directory, that the target file is not locked, and that storage space is available.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0094W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="RESOLUTION_FAILURE_FEP_MIXED_VERSION" varFormat="Java">
    RESOLUTION_FAILURE_FEP_MIXED_VERSION=CWSAL0094W: The application {0} could not be provisioned for all nodes in the cell. The application can only be deployed on Version 8 nodes. The resolution error was {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The application being imported was successfully provisioned against WebSphere Application Server Version 8, but could not be provisioned against the OSGi Applications Feature Pack in WebSphere Application Server Version 7.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required. However, you can use the information in the resolution error to modify the application so that it can be deployed against the WebSphere Application Server Version 7 OSGi Applications Feature Pack.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0072W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="USING_LOCALHOST_AS_HOST_NAME" varFormat="Java">
    USING_LOCALHOST_AS_HOST_NAME=CWSAL0072W: Using localhost as the host name for the transport for the server {0}.{1}. Request routing will work as long as the web server and application server are on the same node.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The host name of the application server specified on the transport has been resolved as localhost.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the web server and application server are on different nodes, investigate why the host name of the application server has been resolved as localhost.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0053E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SYMBOLIC_NAME_ALREADY_IN_USE" varFormat="Java">
    SYMBOLIC_NAME_ALREADY_IN_USE=CWSAL0053E: The EBA file {0} cannot be installed. The Application-SymbolicName {1} of the EBA is already being used by the asset {2}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    You are attempting to install an EBA file but there is an existing asset that has the same symbolic name.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Either change the symbolic name of the EBA you are installing or uninstall the existing asset.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0098E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ADD_CLUSTER_MEMBER_PROVISIONING_FAILURE_MIXED_VERSION" varFormat="Java">
    ADD_CLUSTER_MEMBER_PROVISIONING_FAILURE_MIXED_VERSION=CWSAL0098E: A cluster member cannot be created on the node {0} because the OSGi application(s) {1} cannot be provisioned against it. The resolution error was {2}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    All cluster members must be able to run the same applications, but the new cluster member cannot run the named OSGi applications.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Select another, compatible, node to host the cluster member, or modify the applications so that they can be run using the selected node.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0047E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="SECURITY_PERMISSIONS_PARSEREXCEPTION" varFormat="Java">
    SECURITY_PERMISSIONS_PARSEREXCEPTION=CWSAL0047E: Cannot parse the file {0} for the enterprise bundle archive (EBA) file {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified file could not be parsed.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check that the file is formatted correctly and not corrupted.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0003E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="NO_APPLICATION_MANIFEST_DURING_UPDATE" varFormat="Java">
    NO_APPLICATION_MANIFEST_DURING_UPDATE=CWSAL0003E: An internal error has occurred. Cannot read the application manifest or deployment manifest for the enterprise bundle archive (EBA) file {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    CMSG0001
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    CMSG0002
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0071E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="UNABLE_TO_CREATE_FILE" varFormat="Java">
    UNABLE_TO_CREATE_FILE=CWSAL0071E: Unable to create file: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    There was a problem creating the required pathname during the export of the asset.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check that the application server has permission to create this pathname.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0107E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="UPDATE_APP_CONTENT_VERSION_STEP_CHANGED" varFormat="Java">
    UPDATE_APP_CONTENT_VERSION_STEP_CHANGED=CWSAL0107E: The UpdateAppContentVersionStep command in WAS V7 has been replaced with the UpdateAppContentVersions command in WAS V8.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The WAS V7 UpdateAppContentVersionStep command has been replaced with the UpdateAppContentVersions command in WAS V8. Please see the InfoCenter for more information.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Change the script so as to use the UpdateAppContentVersions command.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0013E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="EMPTY_DEPLOYMENT_CONTENT" varFormat="Java">
    EMPTY_DEPLOYMENT_CONTENT=CWSAL0013E: An internal error has occurred. The enterprise bundle archive (EBA) file {0}, when resolved, has no content that can be deployed.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    CMSG0001
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    CMSG0002
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0015E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PROVISIONING_EXCEPTION" varFormat="Java">
    PROVISIONING_EXCEPTION=CWSAL0015E: Cannot resolve EBA file. Exception: {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The system cannot resolve the locations of the constituent application bundles, at appropriate versions, of the enterprise bundle archive (EBA) file.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    See the exception for further information.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0018E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="RESOLVER_SERVICE_UNAVAILABLE" varFormat="Java">
    RESOLVER_SERVICE_UNAVAILABLE=CWSAL0018E: An internal error has occurred. Cannot resolve the enterprise bundle archive (EBA) file {0} because the service {1} is unavailable.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    CMSG0001
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    CMSG0002
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0041E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_USER" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_USER=CWSAL0041E: The specified user {0} is not valid.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Attempted to map a security role to a user that is not valid.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check that the specified user exists.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0062E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="NO_BUNDLECACHEMANAGER_FOUND" varFormat="Java">
    NO_BUNDLECACHEMANAGER_FOUND=CWSAL0062E: An internal error occurred. Failed to find an MBean for the BundleCacheManager for profile {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    CMSG0001
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    CMSG0002
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0125W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="JAVAGLOBAL_JAVAAPP_WARNING" varFormat="Java">
    JAVAGLOBAL_JAVAAPP_WARNING=CWSAL0125W: The binding {0} for EJB reference {1} in bundle {2} at version {3} with interface {4} might cause the application to function incorrectly after an update.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The constituent parts of the java:global/application_name/module_name/ejb_name or java:app/module_name/ejb_name lookup references can change after an OSGi application is updated, so that the references must be modified accordingly, which makes this approach impractical.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Use OSGi services to configure EJB dependencies, or declare an EJB reference and map it to the EJB JNDI name.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0057E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="UNABLE_TO_EXPAND_EBA_CANNOT_CREATE_DIRECTORY" varFormat="Java">
    UNABLE_TO_EXPAND_EBA_CANNOT_CREATE_DIRECTORY=CWSAL0057E: Unable to expand enterprise bundle archive (EBA) file {0}, cannot create directory {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    While attempting to expand the specified EBA file, a required directory could not be created.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check that the application server has permission to create the specified directory.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0045E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INCOMPATIBLE_PACKAGE_VERSION_REQUIREMENTS" varFormat="Java">
    INCOMPATIBLE_PACKAGE_VERSION_REQUIREMENTS=CWSAL0045E: The asset {0} cannot be resolved. It has incompatible version requirements on the following packages: {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    For bundles that are listed in the Application-Content header in APPLICATION.MF, all imports for a given package must have compatible version requirements.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Change the packaging or configuration of the application so that all bundles that are listed in the Application-Content header have compatible package version requirements.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0102W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="RUN_AS_ROLE_MIXED_VERSION" varFormat="Java">
    RUN_AS_ROLE_MIXED_VERSION=CWSAL0102W: Run As Roles cannot be configured for nodes prior to WebSphere Application Server Version 8. Any configuration will be ignored.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Run As Roles can only be configured for WebSphere Application Server Version 8 and later versions. They cannot be configured for a composition unit that is deployed to WebSphere Application Server Version 7 OSGi Applications Feature Pack targets.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    No action is required. If Run As Roles need to be configured then remove any target mappings for WebSphere Application Server Version 7 OSGi Applications Feature Pack nodes.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0086E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_USERID_OR_PASSWD" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_USERID_OR_PASSWD=CWSAL0086E: The user ID or password is incorrect.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An incorrect user ID or password has been supplied.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Retry the action using the correct user ID and password.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0080E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="APP_UPDATE_FAILED" varFormat="Java">
    APP_UPDATE_FAILED=CWSAL0080E: The update operation did not succeed for the OSGi application deployed in composition unit {0} in business-level application {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An exception occurred during the update operation.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Inspect the server logs prior to this exception for more specific problem diagnostics.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0019E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="APPLICATION_CONTENT_EMPTY" varFormat="Java">
    APPLICATION_CONTENT_EMPTY=CWSAL0019E: An internal error occurred. The Application-Content entry of the application manifest in the enterprise bundle archive (EBA) file {0} is empty, so no bundle will be installed.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    CMSG0001
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    CMSG0002
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0009E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="EXCEPTION_READING_APPLICATION_XML" varFormat="Java">
    EXCEPTION_READING_APPLICATION_XML=CWSAL0009E: Cannot read the Java EE application descriptor file in EBA file {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An IOException occurred when reading the Java EE application descriptor file in an enterprise bundle archive (EBA) file.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check that the application descriptor file is not corrupted, that it is readable and that it has appropriate permissions set.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0035E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="NO_RESOURCE_REFERENCE" varFormat="Java">
    NO_RESOURCE_REFERENCE=CWSAL0035E: Cannot find the resource reference with JNDI name {0} and type {1} on the target {2} for the web module resource reference {3} defined in bundle {4} with version {5}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An enterprise bundle archive (EBA) that includes resource references in a web application archive (WAR) specifies a JNDI name for a resource reference that does not exist in the JNDI namespace.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the resource reference should be in the JNDI namespace, either bind an object to the name, or correct the resource reference and update the EBA.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0117E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="EJB_DEFAULT_BINDING_AMBIGUOUS" varFormat="Java">
    EJB_DEFAULT_BINDING_AMBIGUOUS=CWSAL0117E: No default binding could be created for EJB reference {0} in bundle {1} at version {2} with interface {3} becuase there are two or more possible bindings. The reference could be bound to any of the following enterprise beans: {4}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Default bindings must be created for unbound EJB references. More than one possible enterprise bean was found to which this reference could be bound.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Either bind the reference to a particular enterprise bean, or correct the application.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0025E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="AUTH_ALIAS_SET_FOR_APPLICATION_AUTHTYPE" varFormat="Java">
    AUTH_ALIAS_SET_FOR_APPLICATION_AUTHTYPE=CWSAL0025E: Authentication alias {0} is configured incorrectly. It is not applicable to bind an alias with an authentication type of Application to references.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Authentication aliases with an authentication type of Application cannot be bound to Blueprint resource references.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Remove the authentication alias from the relevant resource reference.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0021E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_VIRTUAL_HOST" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_VIRTUAL_HOST=CWSAL0021E: The virtual host {0} specified for bundle {1} does not exist.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Attempted to map a web application bundle (WAB) to a virtual host that is not valid.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check that the specified virtual host exists.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0046E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="APP_CONTENT_USE_BUNDLE_DUPLICATE" varFormat="Java">
    APP_CONTENT_USE_BUNDLE_DUPLICATE=CWSAL0046E: The EBA file {0} application manifest lists bundles in the Application-Content header that are also listed in the Use-Bundle header.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Bundle names that are listed in the Application-Content header of APPLICATION.MF cannot also be listed in the Use-Bundle header, regardless of bundle versions.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Change the packaging of the Enterprise Bundle Archive (EBA) so that bundle names are not duplicated in the Application-Content and Use-Bundle headers.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0127E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ENV_ENTRY_NO_TYPE" varFormat="Java">
    ENV_ENTRY_NO_TYPE=CWSAL0127E: Environment entry {0} for EJB {1} in bundle with name {2} and version {3} does not have a type.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The indicated environment entry does not specify a type. A type is required when no injection targets are specified.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a type or injection targets for the indicated environment entry.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0103E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CBA_WITH_MISSING_PACKAGE_IMPORTS" varFormat="Java">
    CBA_WITH_MISSING_PACKAGE_IMPORTS=CWSAL0103E: The Composite Bundle Archive (CBA) {0} is not valid. Packages imported by bundles in the CBA are missing from the Import-Package header of the CBA manifest file. The following problems were reported: {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    If a bundle in a  Composite Bundle Archive (CBA) uses a package that is not contained in the bundle, or exported by another bundle within the CBA, then the CBA must import the package.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the composite manifest, COMPOSITEBUNDLE.MF, so that the CBA imports any packages that are used by bundles in the CBA and not otherwise available within the CBA.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0111E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="EJB_DUPLICATE_MAPPING_ERROR" varFormat="Java">
    EJB_DUPLICATE_MAPPING_ERROR=CWSAL0111E: The enterprise bean {0} in bundle {1} at version {2} has multiple mappings for the interface {3} in its bindings file. The mappings were {4} and {5}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The EJB bindings file included in the bundle contains ambiguous mapping configuration information for an EJB interface
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the bindings file so that there is only one configured mapping for each EJB interface.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0090E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="NO_SUCH_CU" varFormat="Java">
    NO_SUCH_CU=CWSAL0090E: No composition unit with name {0} can be found in the current cell.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The given name does not match any existing composition unit name.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check the composition unit name.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0050W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="EXTENSION_LIST_NOT_SUPPORTED" varFormat="Java">
    EXTENSION_LIST_NOT_SUPPORTED=CWSAL0050W: The EBA file {0} contains a MANIFEST.MF with the Extension-List header. Conversion of this header is not supported.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    You attempted to convert an enterprise archive (EAR) file to an enterprise bundle archive (EBA) file when the EAR contains a MANIFEST.MF with an Extension-List header, but conversion of this header is not supported. An EAR file uses the Extension-List header to identify external JARs that the application requires at run time.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Ensure that the external JARs that are listed in the Extension-List header are available as bundles in the bundle repository.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0043E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="UNSATISFIED_CIRCULAR_PACKAGE_DEPENDENCY" varFormat="Java">
    UNSATISFIED_CIRCULAR_PACKAGE_DEPENDENCY=CWSAL0043E: The asset {0} cannot be resolved. It requires the bundle {1}, which is not listed in the Application-Content header in the application manifest, APPLICATION.MF. This bundle imports the package {2} from bundle {3}, which is listed in the Application-Content header.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The application is not correctly configured. A shared bundle cannot import a package from an isolated bundle. Bundles that are listed in the Application-Content header are isolated and can provide packages only to other bundles listed in that header.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Change the packaging or configuration of the application so that bundles that are listed in the Use-Bundle header, or added by the resolver, do not require packages from bundles that are listed in the Application-Content header.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0118E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="EJB_REF_STEP_NO_MAPPINGS" varFormat="Java">
    EJB_REF_STEP_NO_MAPPINGS=CWSAL0118E: EJBRefStep.validateTable(): EJBMappingsStep has not run, and should have done.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    CMSG0001
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    CMSG0002
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0036E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="MORE_THAN_ONE_SECURITY_DOMAIN" varFormat="Java">
    MORE_THAN_ONE_SECURITY_DOMAIN=CWSAL0036E: The asset {0} cannot be deployed to both target {1} in security domain {2} and target{3} in security domain {4}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    To deploy an asset onto more than one target, all targets must be in the same security domain.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Change the deployment targets to choose a set that are in a single security domain.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0104W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CBA_WITH_EXTRA_SERVICE_EXPORTS" varFormat="Java">
    CBA_WITH_EXTRA_SERVICE_EXPORTS=CWSAL0104W: The composite manifest of Composite Bundle Archive (CBA) {0} contains a CompositeBundle-ExportService header but no services defined in the CBA match this filter.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The Composite bundle manifest defines a CompositeBundle-ExportService header but no blueprint service declarations match this filter.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Either add the missing Blueprint service declarations to the CBA contents, or correct the CompositeBundle-ExportService header from the composite manifest, COMPOSITEBUNDLE.MF.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0112E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="EJB_SIMPLE_NAME_AND_MAPPING_ERROR" varFormat="Java">
    EJB_SIMPLE_NAME_AND_MAPPING_ERROR=CWSAL0112E: The enterprise bean {0} in bundle {1} at version {2} has a simple mapping name defined, but also has specific mappings in its bindings file.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The EJB bindings file included in the bundle contains invalid mapping configuration for an enterprise bean.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the bindings file so that there is either a simple mapping name, or specific mapping configuration information, but not both.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0059E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="UNABLE_TO_EXPAND_EBA_CANNOT_DELETE_LAST_DIRECTORY" varFormat="Java">
    UNABLE_TO_EXPAND_EBA_CANNOT_DELETE_LAST_DIRECTORY=CWSAL0059E: An internal error occurred. Unable to delete leaf directory of {0} so that a directory rename can proceed.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    CMSG0001
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    CMSG0002
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0058E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="UNABLE_TO_EXPAND_EBA_NO_EXPANSION_DIRECTORY" varFormat="Java">
    UNABLE_TO_EXPAND_EBA_NO_EXPANSION_DIRECTORY=CWSAL0058E: An internal error occurred. Unable to expand enterprise bundle archive (EBA), no expansion directory specified in the configuration for {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    CMSG0001
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    CMSG0002
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0051E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="UPDATE_ASSET_NOT_SUPPORTED" varFormat="Java">
    UPDATE_ASSET_NOT_SUPPORTED=CWSAL0051E: An attempt has been made to update an OSGi application asset. This is not supported. Update of OSGi application assets can be performed using the &quot;Update bundle versions in this application&quot; panel from the OSGi application asset configuration page.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The update of an OSGi application asset with a new binary is not supported.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If you need to do more than update the bundle versions within the existing asset, you must uninstall the asset before importing its replacement. Alternatively, you can add new bundles to an existing application by packaging them in a composite bundle archive (CBA) and adding the CBA as an extension to the composition unit.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0120W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="NO_MDB_ACTSPEC_REFERENCE" varFormat="Java">
    NO_MDB_ACTSPEC_REFERENCE=CWSAL0120W: No MDB Activation Spec JNDI name has been configured for bean {0} in bundle {1} at version {2}, on target {3}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The MDB Listener binding ActivationSpec JNDI name has not been configured.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    You must configure an Activation Spec JNDI reference for the MDB.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0060E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="UNABLE_TO_RENAME" varFormat="Java">
    UNABLE_TO_RENAME=CWSAL0060E: Unable to rename the file {0} to {1} as part of the expansion of enterprise bundle archive (EBA) file {2}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    To complete the expansion of the specified EBA file, a file needs to be renamed. This rename did not succeed.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check that the application server has permission to rename the file.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0106E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="CBA_WITH_IMPOSSIBLE_PACKAGE_EXPORTS" varFormat="Java">
    CBA_WITH_IMPOSSIBLE_PACKAGE_EXPORTS=CWSAL0106E: The Composite Bundle Archive (CBA), {0} is not valid. The following exported packages listed in the composite manifest are not exported by bundles in the CBA: {1}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    A CBA can only export packages that are exported by the bundles in the CBA.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Either add the missing export packages to the bundles in the CBA, or remove the details of the unsatisfied exports from the composite manifest, COMPOSITEBUNDLE.MF.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0022E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="BUNDLE_DEPENDENCIES_UNAVAILABLE" varFormat="Java">
    BUNDLE_DEPENDENCIES_UNAVAILABLE=CWSAL0022E: Cannot add asset {0} because bundles that it requires are not downloaded. To start the bundle download, save changes to the master configuration after importing the asset.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    You attempted to add an asset that requires one or more bundles to be downloaded from a repository. Either the download has not started, or it is not yet complete.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If you did not saved changes after you imported the asset, save the changes now. Wait for the bundle download to complete, then try again to add the asset to the business-level application (BLA). You can view the bundle download status of the asset from the asset detail panel in the administrative console.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0066E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DEPLOYMENT_MF_INCORRECT" varFormat="Java">
    DEPLOYMENT_MF_INCORRECT=CWSAL0066E: The deployment manifest content is not correct. The following extra bundles are required {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The deployment manifest to import does not include all the bundles needed to resolve the enterprise bundle archive (EBA) asset.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check that the new deployment manifest, DEPLOYMENT.MF, includes all the bundles that are listed in the exception message. Do not manually edit the deployment manifest. If necessary, remove the deployment manifest from the EBA. This causes a fresh deployment manifest file to be generated when the EBA is imported.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0029E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ECES_COULD_NOT_CREATE_DIR" varFormat="Java">
    ECES_COULD_NOT_CREATE_DIR=CWSAL0029E: Cannot create the directory {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified directory cannot be created.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check that storage space exists, and that the product has the necessary permissions to create the directory.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0069E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="ASSET_BUNDLES_UNAVAILABLE" varFormat="Java">
    ASSET_BUNDLES_UNAVAILABLE=CWSAL0069E: Cannot export asset {0} because bundle {1} that it requires is not fully downloaded.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    You attempted to export an asset that requires one or more bundles to be downloaded from a repository. Either the download has not started, or it is not yet complete.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If you did not save changes after you imported the asset, save the changes now. Wait for the bundle download to complete, then try again to export the asset.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0075E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DEPLOYMENT_MANIFEST_MANAGER_UNAVAILABLE" varFormat="Java">
    DEPLOYMENT_MANIFEST_MANAGER_UNAVAILABLE=CWSAL0075E: An internal error occurred. The DeploymentManifestManager service is not available from the OSGi service registry.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    CMSG0001
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    CMSG0002
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0081E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="PROVISIONING_EXCEPTION_WITH_DEP_MF" varFormat="Java">
    PROVISIONING_EXCEPTION_WITH_DEP_MF=CWSAL0081E: Cannot resolve EBA file. The included deployment manifest is not valid on this system. Exception: {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The deployment manifest lists specific versions of required bundles. The system cannot resolve these bundle versions. When a deployment manifest is included in an EBA file, the resolver uses only the bundle versions that are specified in the manifest. Other valid bundle versions might be available on the system, but they are not used because they are not specified in the deployment manifest.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If your application needs to use a deployment manifest, for example to ensure that exactly the same bundle configuration is running in several different environments, use the information given in the exception to identify which bundle versions are required, then  make them available to the system. If your application does not need this extra level of control, remove the deployment manifest. Do not manually edit the deployment manifest.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0108E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INCOMPATIBLE_APP_MF_VERSION" varFormat="Java">
    INCOMPATIBLE_APP_MF_VERSION=CWSAL0108E: The value specified for the application manifest version {0} is not supported. The supported version is {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The value specified for the Application-ManifestVersion header in APPLICATION.MF is incorrect.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the value of Application-ManifestVersion in APPLICATION.MF.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0065E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="DEPLOYMENT_MF_INCOMPATIBLE" varFormat="Java">
    DEPLOYMENT_MF_INCOMPATIBLE=CWSAL0065E: The requirements specified by the deployment manifest within the EBA cannot be satisfied. The exception generated is {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An attempt was made to import an EBA that contains a deployment manifest file. The requirements specified by this file could not be satisfied.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check the contents of the deployment manifest file and verify that the system that this EBA is being deployed on is compatible. Check that any required internal or external bundle repositories are configured. Do not manually edit the deployment manifest. If necessary, remove the deployment manifest from the EBA. This causes a fresh deployment manifest file to be generated when the EBA is imported.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0012E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="EMPTY_APPLICATION_CONTENT" varFormat="Java">
    EMPTY_APPLICATION_CONTENT=CWSAL0012E: The EBA file {0} specifies Application-Content in its application manifest, but the entry is empty.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An enterprise bundle archive (EBA) file contains an empty Application-Content header in its application manifest, application.mf. If provided, this entry must list at least one valid bundle.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Modify the Application-Content header in the application.mf file.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0123W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="INVALID_MDB_DESTINATION_REFERENCE" varFormat="Java">
    INVALID_MDB_DESTINATION_REFERENCE=CWSAL0123W: No MDB Destination that matches the JNDI name {0} could be found on the target {1} for the resource used by bean {2} in bundle {3} at version {4}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The specified MDB listener binding destination reference JNDI name does not exist.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the reference should be in the JNDI namespace, either bind an object to the name, or correct the reference and update the EBA.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0011E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="NO_APPLICATION_CONTENT" varFormat="Java">
    NO_APPLICATION_CONTENT=CWSAL0011E: The EBA file {0} does not specify Application-Content, and contains no valid bundles.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An enterprise bundle archive (EBA) file must contain at least one valid OSGi bundle or web application archive (WAR) file, or list at least one OSGi bundle in the Application-Content header of its application manifest file.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Modify the EBA file to contain at least one valid bundle or WAR (included by value) or list at least one bundle in the in the Application-Content header of its application manifest file, application.mf (included by reference).
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="CWSAL0070E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="UNABLE_TO_CREATE_PATH" varFormat="Java">
    UNABLE_TO_CREATE_PATH=CWSAL0070E: Unable to create directory: {0}
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    There was a problem creating the required pathname during the export of the asset.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Check that the application server has permission to create this pathname.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<!-- END MESSAGES -->
</TMSSource>
