<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/css" href="../../resources/stylesheets/wasmsgxml.css"?>
<TMSSource name="TivoliMessages" tmsVersion="1.0" xml:lang="en">
<!-- CMVC MSG File Name = SERV1/ws/code/utils/src/com/ibm/ws/utils/resources/nls/UtilsMessages.nlsprops -->
<!-- DO NOT EDIT THIS FILE - This file was generated by the XML/Html & Property emitter -->
<!-- BEGIN MESSAGES -->
<Message ID="UTLS0010I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="UTLS0010" varFormat="Java">
    UTLS0010=UTLS0010I: Hung thread detection threshold is now {0} milliseconds for all alarm thread pools.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Indicates that a non-default hung alarm thread threshold is being used.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    none
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="UTLS0009W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="UTLS0009" varFormat="Java">
    UTLS0009=UTLS0009W: Alarm Thread &quot;{0}&quot; ({1}) previously reported to be delayed has now completed.  It was active for approximately {2} milliseconds.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An alarm thread that was previously reported as being excessively active. This situation probably indicates that the work that was being processed on that thread has been completed.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="UTLS0008W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="UTLS0008" varFormat="Java">
    UTLS0008=UTLS0008W: The return of alarm thread &quot;{0}&quot; ({1}) to the alarm thread pool has been delayed for {2} milliseconds. This may be preventing normal alarm function within the application server. The alarm listener stack trace is as follows: {3}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    An alarm thread has been active for an extended period.  This may indicate that the thread is hung, including deadlock, I/O blocked or long running work situations. The stack trace should be examined for insight as to the cause.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    If the problem persists, additional information might be available if you search for the message ID on the following Web sites: WebSphere Application Server Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/was/support/ WebSphere Application Server for z/OS Support page: http://www.ibm.com/software/webservers/appserv/zos_os390/support/ .
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="UTLS0007W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="UTLS0007" varFormat="Java">
    UTLS0007=UTLS0007W: The MANIFEST attributes for the {0} module are ambiguous. Multiple optional packages satisfy the specified version information in the {1} extension-list attributes within the MANIFEST.MF file of the module.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Multiple shared libraries match the specified version criteria. The Library Manager will arbitrarily select one of the libraries that match the attributes of the MANIFEST.MF of the specified module.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Examine the attributes in the MANIFEST.MF files of the module and all optional package libraries. Ensure all attributes are specified and that they allow for a unique match between the MANIFEST.MF file of the identified module and the MANIFEST.MF of the desired optional package library.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="UTLS0006I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="UTLS0006" varFormat="Java">
    UTLS0006=UTLS0006I: Using the default SecureRandom for Id generation.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Session Manager is using the default SecureRandom implementation for session Id generation.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    None.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="UTLS0005W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="UTLS0005" varFormat="Java">
    UTLS0005=UTLS0005W: The MANIFEST attributes for an Installed Optional Package in shared library {1} conflict with and will override those within the MANIFEST attributes of shared library {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The name and specification version attributes that identify an installed optional package in the MANIFEST.MF file of the shared library are not unique.  The name and specification version attributes in the first shared library shown in the message will take precedence over the second shared library. The shared libraries shown in the message might be the same, meaning that the conflicting MANIFEST attributes appear in the same shared library.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Modify the MANIFEST.MF file and specify the name and specification version attributes for the installed optional package to uniquely identify it in any shared library. This allows the system to uniquely resolve any references to the installed optional package.  If you cannot modify the MANIFEST.MF file, ensure that the overriding installed optional package is the version required by your application or applications.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="UTLS0004E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="UTLS0004" varFormat="Java">
    UTLS0004=UTLS0004E: The required attribute {0} was not specifed in the MANIFEST.MF file from the application module {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The syntax of the extension list or specification version attributes might not be valid.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the syntax of the file.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="UTLS0003E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="UTLS0003" varFormat="Java">
    UTLS0003=UTLS0003E: Unable to parse the MANIFEST.MF file from jar file corresponding the library {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The syntax of the extension list or specification version attributes might not be valid.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the syntax of the file.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="UTLS0002E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="UTLS0002" varFormat="Java">
    UTLS0002=UTLS0002E: The shared library {0} contains a classpath entry which does not resolve to a valid jar file, the library jar file is expected to be found at {1}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The class path entry in the library class path field might not be valid.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the class path entry in the library class path field.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="UTLS0001E" severity="E" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="UTLS0001" varFormat="Java">
    UTLS0001=UTLS0001E: Unable to parse the MANIFEST.MF file from application module {0}.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The syntax of the extension list or specification version attributes might not be valid.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Correct the syntax of the file.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="UTLS0014I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="UTLS0014" varFormat="Java">
    UTLS0014=UTLS0014I: Hung thread detection check interval is now {0} milliseconds for all alarm thread pools.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Indicates that a non-default hung alarm thread check interval is being used.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    none
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="UTLS0013W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="UTLS0013" varFormat="Java">
    UTLS0013=UTLS0013W: An invalid value was specified for the hung alarm thread check interval.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The value specified must be a valid number from 0 to 600000.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a correct value or remove the custom property.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="UTLS0012W" severity="W" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="UTLS0012" varFormat="Java">
    UTLS0012=UTLS0012W: An invalid value was specified for the hung alarm thread threshold.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    The value specified must be a valid number from 0 to 600000.
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    Specify a correct value or remove the custom property.
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<Message ID="UTLS0011I" severity="I" prefix="yes">
  <MsgText pgmKey="UTLS0011" varFormat="Java">
    UTLS0011=UTLS0011I: Hung alarm thread detection is disabled.
  </MsgText>
  <Explanation>
    Indicates that hung alarm thread detection has been explicitly disabled by specifying a threshold of zero (0).
  </Explanation>
  <UserResponse>
    none
  </UserResponse>
</Message>
<!-- END MESSAGES -->
</TMSSource>
