<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?> 
<cheatsheet title="Using the Local OS user registry">
	<intro 
		href="localos_intro.htm">
        <description>
Before configuring WebSphere to use the local operating systems user registry, you need to know the user name (ID) and password that will be used by the application server as its own identity when setting up authorization policy and 
when authenticating to other application servers (for example, in a WebSphere Application Server Network Deployment environment). 
&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;  
When using the Local OS user registry with WebSphere for z/OS,  user name and password are not specified through WebSphere administrative facilities.  Rather, the user name associated with the server is configured through the 
administrative facilities of the platform security product.  Read InfoCenter article &lt;a target="help" href="http://publib.boulder.ibm.com/infocenter/ws60help/index.jsp?topic=/com.ibm.websphere.zseries.doc/info/zseries/ae/csec_localos.html"&gt;Local operating system user registries
&lt;/a&gt; for information on configuring server identities on z/OS.
&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;
This user can be any valid user in the user registry. This user will be referred to as either a product security server ID, 
a server ID or a server user ID in the documentation. See &lt;a target="help" href="http://publib.boulder.ibm.com/infocenter/ws60help/index.jsp?topic=/com.ibm.websphere.base.doc/info/aes/ae/tsec_localos.html"&gt;Configuring local operating system user registries&lt;/a&gt;
in the Information Center for more information.
        </description>
	</intro>
	<item
        href="com.ibm.ws.console.security/guidedactivity/cheatsheets/nl/lang/localos_serverid.htm"
		title="Enter user name and password">
		<action
			class="com.ibm.ws.console.security.forwardCmd.do?forwardName=LocalOSUserRegistry.config.view&amp;sfname=userRegistries&amp;resourceUri=security.xml&amp;parentRefId=Security_1&amp;perspective=tab.configuration"/>
		<description>
To enter the server user ID and password: 
            &lt;ol&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt; Click to perform&lt;/strong&gt; loads the Local OS user registry configuration page.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;Enter the server user ID and password&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;Press &lt;strong&gt; Ok&lt;/strong&gt; to submit the changes.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ol&gt;
</description>
	</item>

</cheatsheet>