<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><!DOCTYPE cheatsheet []>

<cheatsheet title="Configuring the on demand router">

	<intro href="intro_configure_odr.htm">
        <description>
            Use this guided activity to configure the on demand router (ODR). The ODR is a 
		surrogate for the content servers in the enterprise, and can enhance the overall experience by providing 
		services such as workload management, cross-cell routing and other off-load services. Before starting this 
activity, install and configure your base WebSphere Network Deployment environment. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
This activity describes how to configure a base configuration and an advanced configuration for your ODR. View 
&lt;a target="help" href="http://publib.boulder.ibm.com/infocenter/wxdinfo/v6r1/index.jsp?searchWord=odr&amp;tab=search"&gt;Creating and configuring the ODR&lt;/a&gt; for more information on performing this task. 
For assistance during these tasks, click the Help icon.

&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;

Before you begin verify that you have a WebSphere Extended Deployment node available and that you have its name and location.&lt;br/&gt;        </description>
	</intro>


	<item href="" title="Create an ODR">
		<action class="navigatorCmd.do?forwardName=ODR.content.main"/>
		<description> Use this section to create an ODR using a WebSphere Extended Deployment cell.  After completing this 
		section, your ODR can route work to available Extended Deployment servers in the cell. 
&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;

&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;

To create a new ODR:
            &lt;ol&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;Click &lt;strong&gt; Click to perform&lt;/strong&gt; to load the On demand router panel.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;Click &lt;strong&gt;New&lt;/strong&gt; and the panel for the creation of a new ODR is 
displayed.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;Complete the panel, and select a WebSphere Extended Deployment node from the available 
nodes. If you select a non-WebSphere Extended Deployment node, the ODR does not function. &lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;Click &lt;strong&gt;Next&lt;/strong&gt; after you complete the panel.&lt;/li&gt;
	   &lt;li&gt;Click &lt;strong&gt;Finish&lt;/strong&gt; to create the new ODR.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;

		</description>
	</item>

	<item href="" title="Configure the ODR setting">
<action class="navigatorCmd.do?forwardName=ODR.content.main"/>
		<description>Use this section to apply a more advanced configuration to your basic ODR 
setup. Use ODR settings to refine the behavior of the ODR. In particular, 
you can configure the connections and requests to the application server, specify requests that 
must be rejected, define how error responses are handled and specify the ODR log location.
&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
You do not have to define ODR settings for your ODR to work. 
&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
To define the ODR settings:
           &lt;ol&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;Click &lt;strong&gt; Click to perform&lt;/strong&gt; to load the On demand router panel.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;Click the name of the ODR that you created in the previous section.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;Scroll to the ODR Properties section and click &lt;strong&gt; ODR Settings&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;Complete the resulting panel. &lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;li&gt;Click &lt;strong&gt;Apply&lt;/strong&gt; or &lt;strong&gt;OK&lt;/strong&gt; after
you complete the panel.&lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;

		</description>
	</item>
	

</cheatsheet>